<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 20:03:14 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Savings Account Receives Another Rate Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-card-savings-account-apr-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-savings-account-receives-another-rate-increase.2415503/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 19:07:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-card-savings-account-apr-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today increased the Apple Card savings account's APY to 4.35%, according to a notification sent to cardholders, including <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-card-savings-account-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892213" /><br/>
This is the second increase to the savings account's APY in as many months, after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/apple-savings-4-25-interest-rate/">raised it from 4.15% to 4.25% in December</a>. Apple's rate now matches that offered by popular high-yield savings accounts from American Express and Discover, but there are still some other options that offer even higher APYs up into the 4.5% to low 5% range in the U.S., such as Marcus by Goldman Sachs and Wealthfront.<br/>
<br/>
Apple launched the high-yield savings account <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/apple-card-savings-account-launching-today/">in April 2023</a>, in partnership with Goldman Sachs. The account can be opened and managed in the Wallet app on the iPhone, and it has no fees, no minimum deposits, and no minimum balance requirements. You must have an Apple Card, be a U.S. resident, and be at least 18 years old to open an account.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/4.35-Apple-Card-Savings.jpg" alt="" width="1179" height="320" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928919" /><br/>
The account allows Apple Card holders to earn interest on their Daily Cash cashback balance, and on personal funds deposited via a linked bank account, or from their Apple Cash balance. The maximum balance allowed is &#36;250,000, and balances are fully insured by the U.S. government's Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation.<br/>
<br/>
The rate increase comes after <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> in November reported that Goldman Sachs is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">looking to terminate its Apple Card partnership</a>, as part of its broader exit from the consumer lending business. The partnership is expected to end within the next year or so, but it's unclear how this might affect the Apple Card in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-card-savings-account-apr-increase/">Apple Card Savings Account Receives Another Rate Increase</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-savings-account-receives-another-rate-increase.2415503/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Miss Physical Keyboards? New &#039;Clicks&#039; Accessory Adds Keys to Your iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/clicks-iphone-keyboard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/miss-physical-keyboards-new-clicks-accessory-adds-keys-to-your-iphone.2415489/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 14:45:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/clicks-iphone-keyboard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[BlackBerry fans that miss having a physical keyboard on their smartphones may want to <a href="https://www.clicks.tech">check out Clicks</a>, a company that has developed a keyboard case that's designed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clicks-keyboard-for-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928870" /><br/>
Clicks is showing off its keyboard accessories ahead of CES, and the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro version of its keyboard will be ready to ship out in February. The keyboard is priced at &#36;139, with an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; version coming in mid-March and a &#36;159 &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max version set to release in the spring.<br/>
<br/>
The Clicks Creator Keyboard is available in "BumbleBee" yellow and "London Sky" gray, and it adds a small physical keyboard to the bottom of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. Clicks says that the case design is meant to "feel like a natural extension" of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the keys have been designed for ideal click resistance and feedback for fast and accurate typing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clicks-keyboard-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928871" /><br/>
The standard QWERTY keyboard features keys for activating dictation, accessing emoji, and activating shortcuts like returning to the Home screen and scrolling. At night, a built-in backlight can be turned on.<br/>
<br/>
An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; connects to the keyboard via Lightning (&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro) or USB-C (&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;), and passthrough charging is supported. The case also supports wireless charging capabilities, though it does not have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; version of the Clicks keyboard measures in at 188.45mm, so it is 41.85mm longer than the 146.6mm &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. That is equivalent to 1.65 inches, so expect an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; equipped with this keyboard to be over an inch and a half longer. It's a little over 3mm wider than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and 2.50mm thicker. The case weighs in at 62 grams, a little under half of the 187 gram weight of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/clicks-keyboard-gray-color.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928872" /><br/>
Dimensions are similar for the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max models, so the keyboards do add some considerable bulk to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Clicks says that the keyboard is easy to put on and remove, and while in use, it does serve as a hardware-based keyboard, so you won't see the software keyboard on the display.<br/>
<br/>
Clicks for &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; <a href="https://www.clicks.tech">can be pre-ordered from the Clicks website</a>, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max version can be reserved for &#36;30.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/clicks-iphone-keyboard/">Miss Physical Keyboards? New &#039;Clicks&#039; Accessory Adds Keys to Your iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/miss-physical-keyboards-new-clicks-accessory-adds-keys-to-your-iphone.2415489/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max Will Look Like</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pro-design/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-the-iphone-16-pro-and-iphone-16-pro-max-will-look-like.2415480/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 13:05:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pro-design/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>MacRumors</em> recently received new information on Apple's 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup, including a look at prototypes of the Pro devices. We've created a series of mockups based on Apple's internal designs, and while the prototypes are not quite finalized, our images represent the clearest look yet of what we can expect from the next-generation iPhones at this point in time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Perspective-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928694" /><br/>
<br/>
Building on the curved edges and titanium frame that Apple introduced with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are set to feature increased display sizes and a new capacitive Capture button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928695" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">As reported by multiple sources</a>, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; (codename Diablo) and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max (codename Lightning) will have larger displays, measuring in at 6.3 inches and 6.9 inches, up from 6.1 inches and 6.7 inches. One possible explanation for this change has to do with the 5x tetraprism Telephoto camera, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/tetraprism-lens-iphone-16-pro/">which is expected to be available on both Pro iPhone models this year</a>. With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup, only the larger &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max includes the 5x Telephoto lens, while the smaller &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; does not. The increased size of this year's devices will give Apple the space to add the tetraprism Telephoto camera to both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and 16 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
While the overall form factor and general design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max have remained consistent through Apple's development phase, the company has experimented with different design details for the devices. There were four total button configurations that were tested, and Apple appears to have settled on a button design similar to the one on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, though with an added button on the right side of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Left-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928696" /><br/>
As with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, both Pro models in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> range will be equipped with a multi-purpose Action button. The button can be configured to perform a range of functions, depending on the user's preference. While Apple has experimented with larger sizes and different designs for the Action button, current design documentation suggests that the Action button will be the same size as the one found on the current &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">An earlier Action button design</a>, developed under the codename Atlas, was envisioned as a larger capacitive button with a force sensor. Given that the most recent designs for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max do not feature this bigger Action button, the future of the Atlas project remains unclear, and it is possible that Apple canceled the Atlas project in favor of a standard mechanical Action button.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/iphone-16-extra-button-rumor/">Weibo leaker "Instant Digital" claimed</a> in October that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; would feature an Action button that lies flush with the frame of the device. Although internal documentation seen by <em>MacRumors</em> corroborates this claim, it was a feature of the earlier "Proto1" development stage. With the current "Proto2" design that we've seen, the Action button is no longer flush with the frame, and is no longer as large.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Right-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928697" /><br/>
On the right side, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models feature an all-new Capture button, which we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/early-iphone-16-prototypes/">showed off in our December renders</a> of the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. The Capture button, developed under the codename Nova, is expected to be a capacitive-type button with force-sensor functionality, and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> recently confirmed that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/iphone-16-capture-button-video/">used for taking video</a>. It is located below the power button, which means that on U.S. models, Apple is relocating the mmWave antenna from the right side of the device to the left side. The Capture button will be flush with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s frame and it will not protrude like the power and volume buttons.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of materials, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will continue to use the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/iphone-15-pro-grade-5-titanium/">Grade 5 Titanium (Ti-6Al-4V) used for the iPhone 15 Pro</a>, with no significant changes to the overall finish. As far as colors are concerned, Apple's prototypes use a "Silver" color, which is marketed by Apple as "White Titanium." Documentation suggests that Apple has so far used the existing colors from the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max for testing purposes, with plans to add another color option. Unfortunately, there are no details on the new color option at this time.<br/>
<br/>
While the mockups we've created accurately portray the current design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max, changes are always possible as the devices are still in an early stage of development and Apple may make further design tweaks. <br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect from the 2024 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup, check out our dedicated rumor roundup pages for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pro-design/">Here&#039;s What the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max Will Look Like</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-the-iphone-16-pro-and-iphone-16-pro-max-will-look-like.2415480/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some Apple Music Subscribers Experiencing Library Syncing Issue Across the iPhone and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-music-library-syncing-issue-18004/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-music-subscribers-experiencing-library-syncing-issue-across-the-iphone-and-mac.2415466/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:44:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-music-library-syncing-issue-18004/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past few months, some users have been unable to sync their Apple Music library between their iPhone and Mac, seemingly due to a bug.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/iOS-17-Apple-Music-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-907547" /><br/>
Affected users receive the following error message in the Music app on the Mac:<blockquote>Genius results can't be updated right now. An unknown error occurred (18004).</blockquote>There are complaints about the issue across the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255233822?sortBy=best">Apple Support Community</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-library-no-longer-works.2415038/">MacRumors Forums</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleMusic/comments/18yacfb/apple_music_library_is_completely_broken/">Reddit</a>, and elsewhere on the internet.<br/>
<br/>
The underlying cause of the issue is unclear, and it's not entirely clear if a fix will require software updates, or if Apple can implement a server-side fix. We've reached out to Apple for comment, and we'll update this story if we receive a response.<br/>
<br/>
This issue comes after another Apple Music bug related to playlists <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-music-playlist-bug-fixed/">was fixed</a> last month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-music-library-syncing-issue-18004/">Some Apple Music Subscribers Experiencing Library Syncing Issue Across the iPhone and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-apple-music-subscribers-experiencing-library-syncing-issue-across-the-iphone-and-mac.2415466/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2415463/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:30:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The second public beta comes three weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-1/">the first public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 includes support for collaborative playlists in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, allowing &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscribers to build playlists with others. When creating a new playlist or selecting an existing playlist, there's a person-shaped icon that can be tapped to turn on collaboration.<br/>
<br/>
Enabling collaboration provides a link that can be shared with others, and anyone with the link is able to contribute to the playlist and listen to the songs. The person who started the playlist can choose to approve those who want to join or open it up to everyone. Anyone with the link to a playlist can add music, though the owner can turn off collaboration at any time or remove people.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 is expected to see a launch at some point in January 2024. Apple has also released public betas of watchOS 10.3 and new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.3 software. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2415463/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.2, Downgrading No Longer Possible</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-2-downgrading-no-longer-possible.2415462/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:29:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last night stopped signing the iOS 17.2 update, preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS going forward. iOS 17.2 is no longer being signed following the December 19 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/apple-releases-ios-17-2-1/">release of iOS 17.2.1</a>, an update that brought bug fixes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918854" /><br/>
It is not unusual that iOS 17.2 is no longer being signed. Apple routinely stops signing older versions of iOS after new releases in order to encourage customers to keep their operating systems up to date and to prevent users from downgrading to older, less secure versions of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; operating system.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 17.2 update brought the Journal app, spatial video recording on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, updates to Messages and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and more. Apple did not ever provide details on the bug fixes included in iOS 17.2.1.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-beta-features/">already testing iOS 17.3</a>, an update that is expected to come out later in January.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-2/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.2, Downgrading No Longer Possible</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-2-downgrading-no-longer-possible.2415462/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung to Unveil New Galaxy S24 Smartphones With Enhanced AI on January 17</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/samsung-galaxy-s24-event-january-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-unveil-new-galaxy-s24-smartphones-with-enhanced-ai-on-january-17.2415459/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 09:52:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/samsung-galaxy-s24-event-january-17/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung this week announced its 2024 Unpacked event, which is set to be held on January 17 in San Jose, California. Samsung is expected to introduce its S24 line of Galaxy smartphones, which will directly compete with Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="[Invitation] Galaxy Unpacked 2024: Opening a New Era of Mobile AI" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wRAwejsqW6A" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Samsung's event announcement teases a "new era of mobile AI," so it's safe to say that Samsung's new smartphones will have enhanced AI capabilities on par with ChatGPT and other AI products. In fact, Samsung says that the new Galaxy S series will feature the "most intelligent mobile experience yet."<br/>
<br/>
Galaxy S24 rumors have suggested that the high-end Ultra model will include a 200-megapixel <a href="https://twitter.com/universeice/status/1736910942318084347">AI-enhanced camera</a> that is able to identify 12 kinds of objects and optimize them for improved image quality. The AI could also be used to translate messages to more than a dozen languages in real time.<br/>
<br/>
The S24 Ultra is also expected to <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/1/23984653/samsung-galaxy-s24-ultra-plus-leaks-rumors-snapdragon-ai">feature a flatter screen design</a> with a more square shape, and it appears that Samsung is going to transition to a titanium frame, mimicking an Apple design decision for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;. Samsung is expected to offer the S24 Ultra in black, gray, violet, and yellow titanium shades.<br/>
<br/>
Other Ultra rumors include a 50-megapixel 5x telephoto lens, which is a downgrade from the prior 10x telephoto lens, and Wi-Fi 7 support. The S24 and S24 Plus are expected to be largely similar to the S23 models, though there will be new color options and lager 6.7 and 6.2-inch displays.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's event will take place on January 17 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time, and customers who plan to pre-order <a href="https://howl.me/cllVxphW5r6">can reserve a device</a> and receive a &#36;50 Samsung credit. The reservation system does not charge automatically, requiring only a name and an email address to reserve devices. Credits will be able to be redeemed when pre-ordering after the devices debut.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/samsung-galaxy-s24-event-january-17/">Samsung to Unveil New Galaxy S24 Smartphones With Enhanced AI on January 17</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-to-unveil-new-galaxy-s24-smartphones-with-enhanced-ai-on-january-17.2415459/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pad &amp; Quill Founder Returns With New Apple Accessory Company Burton Goods</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/pad-quill-founder-burton-goods/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pad-quill-founder-returns-with-new-apple-accessory-company-burton-goods.2415453/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 08:32:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/pad-quill-founder-burton-goods/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been a few months since Apple accessory maker Pad & Quill <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/pad-quill-shutting-down/">announced</a> the closure of its business, ending a 13 year run as a creator of leather accessories for Apple products. This week, former Pad & Quill president Brian Holmes has announced his new venture, <a href="https://burtongoods.com?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">Burton Goods</a>, and it has a 20 percent off grand opening discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/burton-goods-1.jpg" alt="" width="1196" height="666" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928820" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Holmes detailed everything that happened from the closure of Pad & Quill to the founding of Burton Goods <a href="https://burtongoods.com/blogs/news/what-happened-to-pq">in a blog post</a>. Burton Goods will follow in Pad & Quill's footsteps in many ways, focusing on high-quality leather accessories for iPhone and iPad, leather bags for tech enthusiasts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://burtongoods.com?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>Burton Goods Grand Opening Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the grand opening sale, Burton Goods is offering a 20 percent discount sitewide for the entire month of January. This sale will be applied in your cart and does not require a coupon code. It's also specifically a pre-order discount, as Burton Goods' first wave of products doesn't launch until the first week of February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/burton-goods-2.jpg" alt="" width="1198" height="794" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928819" /><br/>
Some featured accessories include the <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/heritage-leather-strap?variant=47424328499512&sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">Heritage Leather Strap for Apple Watch</a> (&#36;63.96), <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/luxury-leather-case-for-macbook-pro-14?sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">Luxury Leather Slim Case for MacBook Pro</a> (&#36;119.96), <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/modern-pocket-book-wallet-case-for-iphone-15-pro?variant=47425040449848&sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">Modern Pocket Book Wallet Case for iPhone 15 Pro</a> (&#36;79.96), and the <a href="https://burtongoods.com/products/magnetic-ipad-case?variant=47540480770360&sca_ref=5180275.Ywgd2BL872">Magnetic Leather iPad Case</a> (&#36;143.96).<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/pad-quill-founder-burton-goods/">Pad &amp; Quill Founder Returns With New Apple Accessory Company Burton Goods</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pad-quill-founder-returns-with-new-apple-accessory-company-burton-goods.2415453/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Adding These Two New Games in February</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-arcade-new-games-february-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-adding-these-two-new-games-in-february.2415447/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 07:46:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-arcade-new-games-february-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Arcade will be getting two new games on February 1, including action game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/beast-bio-exo-arena-suit-team/id1633451852">BEAST: Bio Exo Arena Suit Team</a> and puzzle game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/words-in-progress/id1021231678">Words in Progress</a>. All games available on Apple Arcade are ad-free and do not offer in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Words-in-Progress-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928811" /><br/>
Apple revealed the new titles in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/tamagotchi-adventure-kingdom-and-cornsweeper-launch-on-apple-arcade/">press release</a>:<blockquote>On February 1, players can blast off on a cosmic adventure in BEAST: Bio Exo Arena Suit Team, a unique 3v3 online action game featuring animal heroes piloting powerful mechanized armors, and master Words in Progress, an intriguing new puzzle game.</blockquote>Apple Arcade also added three new games this month, including <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/tamagotchi-adventure-kingdom/id1614952689">Tamagotchi Adventure Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/cornsweeper/id1600387153">Cornsweeper</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/blackjack-by-mobilityware/id6469052640">Blackjack by MobilityWare+</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Launched in November 2019, Apple Arcade is accessible through the App Store. The service provides subscribers with access to around 300 games on the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple TV, with new titles added periodically.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Arcade <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">received its first price increase</a> in many countries last year. In the U.S., for example, pricing went from &#36;4.99 per month to &#36;6.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-arcade-new-games-february-2024/">Apple Arcade Adding These Two New Games in February</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-adding-these-two-new-games-in-february.2415447/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fitness+ Adding Content to Kickstart Your New Year&#039;s Resolution</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-fitness-plus-2024-new-year-content/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fitness-adding-content-to-kickstart-your-new-years-resolution.2415438/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 06:38:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-fitness-plus-2024-new-year-content/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Fitness Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the most common New Year's resolutions is to exercise more, and Apple Fitness+ will be adding more content next week to help out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Fitness-Plus-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928774" /><br/>
Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-fitness-plus-offers-more-ways-to-stay-active-and-mindful-in-the-new-year/">announced</a> that Fitness+ will be gaining a variety of new workouts, meditations, and "Time to Walk" audio episodes starting January 8.<br/>
<br/>
The following new workouts will be available:<ul><li>Starting January 8, 10 new workouts with music by Rihanna will be available.</li><br/>
<li>Starting January 15, new workouts with music by Britney Spears will be available.</li><br/>
<li>Starting January 22, new workouts with music by U2 will be available.</li><br/>
<li>Starting February 5, Artist Spotlight workouts will feature music by Usher, who will be headlining this year's Apple Music Halftime Show at Super Bowl LVIII.</li></ul>Seven new "Sound" meditations coming to Fitness+ will allow you to relax with a variety of "soothing tones and rhythms." Apple is also adding a new workout program called "Strength, Core, and Yoga for Golfers," which it says is designed to improve strength, balance, flexibility, and mobility for golfers of all skill levels.<br/>
<br/>
Similar to podcasts, "Time to Walk" episodes feature influential people sharing stories and music that users can listen to while walking. Upcoming episodes will feature new guests, including Al Roker, Trixie Mattel, Lilly Singh, Common, and Colman Domingo. For the first time ever, select episodes will be available on Apple Podcasts for free in the 21 countries where Fitness+ is available, even without a subscription.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch users can earn a new limited-edition award <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/apple-watch-new-year-2024-challenge/">called "Ring in the New Year"</a> when they close all three Activity rings for seven days in a row any time in January.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Watch-New-Year-Award-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928775" /><br/>
"From sound meditations to help you relax, to building strength for an improved golf swing, or turning up the volume on your workouts, Fitness+ has something for everyone to help them stay active and support their wellbeing in the new year," said Jay Blahnik, Apple's Vice President of Fitness Technologies, in a press release.<br/>
<br/>
Fitness+ is available in the U.S., U.K., Australia, Austria, Brazil, Canada, Colombia, France, Germany, Indonesia, Ireland, Italy, Malaysia, Mexico, New Zealand, Portugal, Russia, Saudi Arabia, Spain, Switzerland, and the United Arab Emirates. In the U.S., the service costs &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;79.99 per year, with free trial options available.<br/>
<br/>
Fitness+ subscribers can read <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-fitness-plus-offers-more-ways-to-stay-active-and-mindful-in-the-new-year/">Apple's press release</a> for more information.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-fitness-plus/">Apple Fitness Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-fitness-plus-2024-new-year-content/">Apple Fitness+ Adding Content to Kickstart Your New Year&#039;s Resolution</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fitness-adding-content-to-kickstart-your-new-years-resolution.2415438/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Version of Siri With Generative AI Again Rumored for WWDC</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/new-version-of-siri-with-generative-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-version-of-siri-with-generative-ai-again-rumored-for-wwdc.2415432/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 05:34:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/new-version-of-siri-with-generative-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>Naver</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing to preview a new version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> with generative AI and a range of new capabilities at WWDC, according to a post on the Korean social media site Naver from a user with a track record for posting Apple rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/siri-symbol-iphone-feature.jpg" alt="" width="850" height="481" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-927705" /><br/>
According to developer sources speaking to the operator of tech news <a href="https://m.blog.naver.com/PostList.naver?blogId=yeux1122&tab=1">aggregator account "yeux1122"</a> on Naver, Apple has recently made progress with integrating generative AI into &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; using its Ajax-based model that <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/apple-experimenting-with-chatgpt-tool/">first mentioned</a> in July. The new version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; apparently touts natural conversation capabilities, as well as increased user personalization.<br/>
<br/>
The new features are believed to be available across devices, suggesting that the new version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will retain conversation information from one device to another. It is also said to feature a new "Apple-specific creational service," which might relate to the previously reported Siri-based <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">Shortcuts capabilities</a> rumored for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is purportedly working on linkages for the new version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to connect to various external services, likely via an API. Finally, the report suggests that some of Apple's new AI features may differ based on subscription service status, but it is unclear what shape this could take.<br/>
<br/>
A recent forecast from Deepwater Asset Management <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year/">similarly claimed</a> that Apple will bring generative AI to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; this year. The Naver blog account has a mixed track record for forecasting Apple's plans, but some of its claims have proven to be significant. For example, in March 2022 it accurately revealed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/08/iphone-se-rumor-magsafe-battery-life/">some details</a> about the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> ahead of Apple launching the model. In October of the same year it also accurately predicted that Apple would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/30/14-16-macbook-pro-next-year/">delay the release</a> of new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models until early 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/naver/">Naver</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/new-version-of-siri-with-generative-ai/">New Version of Siri With Generative AI Again Rumored for WWDC</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-version-of-siri-with-generative-ai-again-rumored-for-wwdc.2415432/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s Ultra Wide Camera Rumored to Receive Major Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pros-ultra-wide-camera-major-upgrade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-ultra-wide-camera-rumored-to-receive-major-upgrade.2415420/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 03:39:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pros-ultra-wide-camera-major-upgrade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models will be the first to feature more than one 48-megapixel sensor, leaving the Telephoto as the only rear-facing camera with a 12-megapixel resolution, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> reports. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/iphone-11-pro-ultra-wide.jpg" alt="" width="2264" height="1186" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-722975" /><br/>
Writing on <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/玉晶光為高階鏡頭升級週期再起的關鍵贏家-iphone-17前相機升級-iphone-16-pro潛望鏡與超廣角-vision-pro-與華為p70超廣角-genius-is-a-key-7f125f60d783">Medium</a>, Kuo explained that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s Ultra Wide camera will feature a 48-megapixel sensor. The upgrade should allow the camera to capture more light, resulting in enhanced photos when shooting in 0.5× mode, especially in low-light environments.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models already have a 48-megapixel Main camera that uses "pixel binning" to merge data from four pixels on the sensor into one "super pixel" for improved low-light capture. With the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, this technology is expected to expand to the Ultra Wide lens, which is currently a 12-megapixel lens.<br/>
<br/>
This also means that &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models should be able to shoot <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-14-pro-take-48-megapixel-proraw-photos/">48-megapixel ProRAW photos</a> in Ultra Wide mode. These photos retain more detail in the image file for more editing flexibility, and can be printed at large sizes.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, International Securities analyst Jeff Pu <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">claimed</a> that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will feature a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera. Just a few months later, further details about Apple's plan for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/iphone-16-pro-rumored-to-feature-48mp-ultra-wide/">new Ultra Wide camera</a> emerged on Chinese social media site Weibo. With Kuo now throwing his weight behind the rumor, the upgrade seems highly likely.<br/>
<br/>
In 2025, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 Pro is expected to complete the rear camera array's transition to 48-megapixel sensors, bringing the technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto-lens-rumor/">to the Telephoto lens</a>. Kuo added that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is on-track to feature the tetraprism Telephoto camera introduced on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. He also said that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 lineup will feature an upgraded front-camera camera unit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/">with a 24-megapixel sensor</a> and a six-element lens.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/iphone-16-pros-ultra-wide-camera-major-upgrade/">iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s Ultra Wide Camera Rumored to Receive Major Upgrade</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-ultra-wide-camera-rumored-to-receive-major-upgrade.2415420/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Could Acquire Peloton This Year, Fund Manager Forecast Suggests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year-fund-manager-forecast-suggests.2415419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 03:34:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Peloton</category>
		<category>Apple Fitness Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will likely acquire the fitness company Peloton this year, a new hedge fund manager forecast claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/peloton-tv-workout-cardio.jpeg" alt="" width="1000" height="562" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-776133" /><br/>
Deepwater Asset Management's <a href="https://deepwatermgmt.com/deepwaters-2024-predictions/">annual forecast</a> for 2024 (via <em><a href="https://connectthewatts.com/2024/01/03/deepwater-predicts-apple-acquisition-of-peloton/">Connect the Watts</a></em>) says that Apple is likely to acquire Peloton sometime this year. The move would help Apple bolster its Fitness+ subscription service, adding workout equipment to compliment the Apple Watch and its existing activity tracking software. Absorbing Peloton's subscriber base of three-million users would ostensibly add about &#36;1.7 billion to Apple's subscription revenue and line up with its continued investment in health and wellness, the company claims.<br/>
<br/>
In 2022, Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/21/apple-floated-as-potential-buyer-of-peloton/">repeatedly floated</a> as a potential buyer of Peloton amid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/07/peloton-now-in-trouble-thanks-to-apple-fitness/">financial difficulties and threats to its business model</a>, but the company's prospects have since improved somewhat and Deepwater Asset Management's new forecast is the first serious mention of the possibility in some time. Major questions remain about why Apple would want to take responsibility for Peloton's fragile business model and not simply focus on growing Fitness+, but anything is possible.<br/>
<br/>
Deepwater Asset Management also believes that Apple will bring generative AI to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> this year, introducing the revamped assistant at WWDC. The hedge fund manager is also not expecting Apple to announce any additional Vision Pro products this year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/peloton/">Peloton</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-fitness-plus/">Apple Fitness Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year/">Apple Could Acquire Peloton This Year, Fund Manager Forecast Suggests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-could-acquire-peloton-this-year-fund-manager-forecast-suggests.2415419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 17 to Feature 24MP Front-Facing Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera.2415409/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 02:20:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 lineup will feature a 24-megapixel front-facing camera, according to Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/dynamic-island.jpeg" alt="" width="1244" height="706" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-889703" /><br/>
The information was shared in a new <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/玉晶光為高階鏡頭升級週期再起的關鍵贏家-iphone-17前相機升級-iphone-16-pro潛望鏡與超廣角-vision-pro-與華為p70超廣角-genius-is-a-key-7f125f60d783">post on Medium</a>. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and 15 feature a 12-megapixel front-facing camera with five plastic lens elements. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is expected to feature the same hardware. With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17, Apple will apparently bolster the hardware to a 24-megapixel camera with a six-element lens. Kuo says that the upgrade will significantly improve the image quality of the front-facing camera.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 6S</strong>: 5-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture and 4P lens</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 7, iPhone X, and iPhone XS</strong>: 7-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture and 4P lens</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 11, iPhone 12, and iPhone 13</strong>: 12-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture and 5P lens</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 14, iPhone 15, and iPhone 16</strong>: 12-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/1.9 aperture, autofocus, and 5P lens</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 17</strong>: 24-megapixel front-facing camera with autofocus and 6P lens</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The upgraded resolution to 24 megapixels is noteworthy because it would allow for greater detail and clarity in images. With a higher resolution, photos can maintain their quality even when cropped or zoomed in, providing more flexibility in post-processing. Additionally, the larger number of pixels can capture finer details, making the images sharper and more vibrant.<br/>
<br/>
The upgrade to a six-element lens would also slightly enhance image quality. Each element can be designed to correct for various aberrations and distortions, leading to clearer, more accurate photos. The additional elements can also improve the efficiency of light transmission to the sensor, enhancing low-light performance.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">expected</a> to be the first ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ to feature under-panel <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> technology, which could reduce the size of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, but a circular cutout for the front-facing camera is expected to remain. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 Pro will probably be Apple's last premium model to include a circular cutout for the front-facing camera. Apple is then <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/">expected</a> adopt under-display cameras in 2027's "Pro" ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ models for a true "all-screen" appearance.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/">Kuo: iPhone 17 to Feature 24MP Front-Facing Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera.2415409/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>T-Mobile Offers Free Ad-Supported Hulu to Subscribers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/t-mobile-free-hulu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-offers-free-ad-supported-hulu-to-subscribers.2415373/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 15:33:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/t-mobile-free-hulu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Hulu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/news/offers/t-mobile-adds-hulu-to-its-streaming-suite">today announced</a> that people who subscribe to the Go5G Next plan will have free access to ad-supported Hulu content starting on January 24.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/07/hulu-logo-2019.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-701546" /><br/>
Hulu is a perk that joins the existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> and Netflix subscriptions that T-Mobile Go5G Next users have access to.<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile says that free Netflix, Hulu, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, and MLB.TV add up to more than &#36;35 per month or &#36;400 per year in benefits.<br/>
<br/>
The Hulu plan that T-Mobile customers are able to access is valued at &#36;7.99 per month, and it does include ads during shows and movies. Hulu says that ads typically play at the beginning of the stream and throughout the video, similar to a traditional TV broadcast.<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile's Go5G Next plan is the company's highest-tier plan that includes a smartphone upgrade with trade-in on an annual basis. It is priced at &#36;100 per month for a single line.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/hulu/">Hulu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/t-mobile-free-hulu/">T-Mobile Offers Free Ad-Supported Hulu to Subscribers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-offers-free-ad-supported-hulu-to-subscribers.2415373/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pulls iOS 17.3 Beta 2 Due to Boot Loop Issue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-pulls-ios-17-3-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-ios-17-3-beta-2-due-to-boot-loop-issue.2415355/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 13:16:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-pulls-ios-17-3-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Three hours after releasing the second betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3, Apple has pulled the updates from the Developer Center and over the air, meaning they are no longer available to download and install.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.3-Buggy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928685" /><br/>
Apple has removed the iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas after a number of people reported that the software is bricking devices. According to reports on <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-beta-2-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2415339/">the <em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/BrandonButch/status/1742628347002204350">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://mastodon.social/@_inside/111693591558795389">Mastodon</a>, some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners who updated found their devices stuck in a boot loop.<br/>
<br/>
The only fix to the issue appears to be restoring a stuck device, which is why Apple has pulled the update. Once the bug is addressed, Apple will re-release the beta.<br/>
<br/>
There are reports that suggest the iOS 17.3 boot loop bug <a href="https://mastodon.social/@_inside/111693804775894724">could be related</a> to the Back Tap setting. A log shared by developer Guilherme Rambo indicates that a Back Tap setting caused his device to crash, and there have been several other affected users who have Back Tap enabled in some capacity.<br/>
<br/>
Some others who had Back Tap enabled were able to install the update, and others who did not have the feature on had the booting issue, so it is not entirely clear how Back Tap is involved.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-pulls-ios-17-3-beta-2/">Apple Pulls iOS 17.3 Beta 2 Due to Boot Loop Issue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-ios-17-3-beta-2-due-to-boot-loop-issue.2415355/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Bug Related to &#039;Add Playlist Songs&#039; Setting is Now Fixed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-music-playlist-bug-fixed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-bug-related-to-add-playlist-songs-setting-is-now-fixed.2415354/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 13:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-music-playlist-bug-fixed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last month, many Apple Music subscribers reported that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/04/apple-music-add-playlist-songs-to-library-bug/">"Add Playlist Songs" setting was broken</a> on the iPhone, iPad, and sometimes the Mac. After a user toggled off the setting, the bug could cause it to turn back on, resulting in any songs that a user added to a playlist being added to their music library in an unwanted manner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17-Apple-Music-Favorites-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916141" /><br/>
Fortunately, it appears that Apple quickly addressed the bug with a server-side fix, and users are no longer impacted by this issue. Given it was a server-side fix, users do not need to update their devices to a newer software version for it to apply.<br/>
<br/>
Apple never publicly acknowledged the bug, so the underlying cause is unclear.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-music-playlist-bug-fixed/">Apple Music Bug Related to &#039;Add Playlist Songs&#039; Setting is Now Fixed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-bug-related-to-add-playlist-songs-setting-is-now-fixed.2415354/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning: iOS 17.3 Beta 2 Bricking Some iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/ios-17-3-beta-2-bricking-some-iphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-ios-17-3-beta-2-bricking-some-iphones.2415350/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:39:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/ios-17-3-beta-2-bricking-some-iphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The second beta of iOS 17.3 that Apple released today is causing major issues for some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners, so users that have not yet installed the new software may want to hold off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/bricked-iphone-vittici.jpg" alt="" width="1662" height="934" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928675" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Image from <a href="https://mastodon.social/@_inside/111693591558795389">MacStories' Federico Vittici</a></div></em><br/>
As noted by reports on <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-beta-2-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2415339/">the <em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/BrandonButch/status/1742628347002204350">Twitter</a>, and <a href="https://mastodon.social/@_inside/111693591558795389">Mastodon</a>, some &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owners who have attempted to update to iOS 17.3 beta 2 have found their devices stuck in a boot loop with a blank black screen that has a frozen spinning wheel.<br/>
<br/>
Restoring to the prior version of iOS 17.3 or the iOS 17.2.1 release software appears to address the problem, but users who do not have a backup may have issues with the restore process.<br/>
<br/>
Not all &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users appear to be affected, as some iPhones updated to iOS 17.3 beta 2 have come through fine.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet commented on the bug, but it is likely the second iOS 17.3 beta will be pulled in the near future until the issue can be addressed.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/ios-17-3-beta-2-bricking-some-iphones/">Warning: iOS 17.3 Beta 2 Bricking Some iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-ios-17-3-beta-2-bricking-some-iphones.2415350/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch New Year Deals Include &#36;50 Off Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-watch-new-year-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-new-year-deals-include-50-off-series-9-se-and-ultra-2.2415345/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 11:11:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-watch-new-year-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is discounting an array of Apple Watches today, including the Apple Watch Series 9, Apple Watch SE, and Apple Watch Ultra 2. Although none are at all-time low prices, these are the best discounts we've tracked since the Black Friday shopping season.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9-and-Ultra-2-Deals-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913210" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9</h2><br/>
Starting with the Apple Watch Series 9, Amazon has the 41mm GPS device for &#36;349.00 in three Aluminum colors, down from &#36;399.00. The 45mm GPS device is on sale for &#36;379.00 in every Aluminum color, down from &#36;429.00.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Series 9 is Apple's newest mainline wearable device. It shares the same look as the previous generation model, but includes a faster S9 chip, brighter display, and new features like Double Tap.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
Amazon has the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for &#36;199.00, down from &#36;249.00, and the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE for &#36;229.00, down from &#36;279.00. Both models are available in three Aluminum colors: Midnight, Silver, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch SE is Apple's low-cost option in the Apple Watch lineup, and it'll get the job done for most people who want a simple fitness tracker. It lacks the Series 9's health sensors like ECG, blood oxygen, and temperature sensing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;229.00</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2</h2><br/>
Finally, the Apple Watch Ultra 2 has dropped to &#36;749.00 on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00. This one is available in a large collection of colors and band styles, and it's just about &#36;10 away from the all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra 2 is Apple's most rugged wearable, and compared to the previous generation it has an improved GPS, more durable display, extra long battery life, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7C4CL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-watch-new-year-deals/">Apple Watch New Year Deals Include &#36;50 Off Series 9, SE, and Ultra 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-new-year-deals-include-50-off-series-9-se-and-ultra-2.2415345/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-to-developers.2415337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2024 10:14:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the updates available three weeks after the release of the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2/">iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 introduces a Stolen Device Protection feature that limits access to your private information in case someone obtains both your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and your passcode. When activated, it requires <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> identity verification to do things like accessing passwords in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, turning off Lost Mode, making purchases through Safari with saved payment credentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
There are also features that require verification <em>and</em> have a one-hour delay to access, such as changing an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; passcode, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode, turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, and turning off &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;. More details can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">found in our article on Stolen Device Protection</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">collaborative Apple Music playlists</a>, a feature that lets <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers share playlists with others to build shared song lists. Collaborative playlists are simple to use, can be shared with a link, and support emoji reactions.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release iOS 17.3 later in January.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-to-developers.2415337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
