<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 09:03:21 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes Up to &#36;70 Off New M4 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;949</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/new-m4-macbook-air-from-949/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-70-off-new-m4-macbook-air-available-from-949.2455201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 07:23:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/new-m4-macbook-air-from-949/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">all-time low prices on the new M4 MacBook Air</a>, with up to &#36;70 off the 13-inch version of the computer. Right now these discounts are only available on Amazon, and most of them have estimated delivery windows of mid April.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/M4-MacBook-Air-13-and-15-inch-Feature-Pink-and-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994261" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon and Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This time around, there are two 13-inch configurations on sale, reaching up to &#36;70 off the original price. You can get the 256GB 13-inch M4 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;949.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00, and the 24GB RAM/512GB 13-inch M4 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,329.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,399.00. Both of these deals are available in two colors on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDCPMGK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/new-m4-macbook-air-from-949/">Amazon Takes Up to &#36;70 Off New M4 MacBook Air, Available From &#36;949</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-up-to-70-off-new-m4-macbook-air-available-from-949.2455201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 19 and iPhone 17 Pro Rumors, Siri Revamp Turmoil, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/top-stories-ios-19-iphone-17-pro-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-19-and-iphone-17-pro-rumors-siri-revamp-turmoil-and-more.2455192/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/top-stories-ios-19-iphone-17-pro-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It was a big week for leaks and rumors in the Apple world, with fresh claims about iOS 19, the iPhone 17 Pro, and even the 20th anniversary iPhone coming a couple of years from now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/top-stories-2025-04-12.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998426" /><br/>
Sources also spilled the tea on the inner turmoil at Apple around the Apple Intelligence-driven Siri revamp that has seen significant delays, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 19 Leak Reveals Alleged New Design With Rounder App Icons, Floating Tab Bar, and More</h2><br/>
YouTuber Jon Prosser is back with some more claims on his Front Page Tech channel regarding <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">design updates coming in iOS 19</a>, and according to information he's seen, we could be in for some major changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iOS-19-Front-Page-Tech-Thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997916" /><br/>
Sources within Apple have shown Prosser a more glass-like interface inspired by visionOS, including rounder icons, a new floating pill-shaped tab bar at the bottom of many built-in apps, and some additional design tweaks.<br/>
<br/>
For an overview of everything we've heard so far about potential design changes for iOS 19 with just about two months ago until its official unveiling at WWDC, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/ios-19-design-rumors/">check out our recap article</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro's New Rear Camera Bar 'Same Color as Rest of Device'</h2><br/>
Leaks have shown the upcoming iPhone 17 Pro models will have a much larger rear camera bump spanning the entire top of the device, and a new claim from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/iphone-17-pro-no-two-tone-rear-design/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman says the bump will be the same color as the rest of the device</a> rather than being a distinct black color seen on some renderings.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-3_4ths-Perspective-Aluminum-Camera-Module-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997826" /><br/>
On the feature front, Jon Prosser has said the iPhone 17 Pro models will include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/iphone-17-pro-dual-video-recording-rumor/">native support for simultaneous video recording from both front and rear cameras</a>, something that so far has only been available through select third-party apps.<br/>
<br/>
We've also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/5-biggest-changes-iphone-17-pro/">recapped a number of other significant changes</a> rumored to be coming to the iPhone 17 Pro later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Planning 'Bold' New 20th Anniversary Design for 2027 iPhone Pro</h2><br/>
We're still a couple of years away from the 20th anniversary of the iPhone's debut, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman says Apple is planning something special for the milestone: a "major shake-up" that will include not only the much-rumored foldable iPhone but also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/apple-new-20th-anniversary-design-iphone-pro/">a "bold" new look for the Pro-level iPhone models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iphone-x-front-back-feature.jpg" alt="" width="868" height="488" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997831" /><em>iPhone X released in 2017 for 10th anniversary</em></div><br/>
Gurman says the 2027 iPhone Pro models will make more extensive use of glass in their construction, but little else is known about what Apple has in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Report Reveals Internal Chaos Behind Apple's Siri Failure</h2><br/>
The Apple Intelligence-powered revamp of Siri has hit a number of stumbling blocks, leading to Apple uncharacteristically announcing a delay in some of the upcoming features. An extensive new report from <em>The Information</em> this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chaos-behind-siri-revealed/">reveals details of the turmoil that has gone on behind the scenes at Apple</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
According to the report, indecision and repeated changes in direction from Apple leadership about how to deploy Apple Intelligence frustrated engineers working on the project, with Siri in particular being a "hot potato" that bounced between teams without significant progress being made.<br/>
<br/>
Sources indicate that some of the most impressive Siri features demoed in Apple's Intelligence's unveiling at WWDC 2024 were effectively fictitious, with the functionality not even working on test devices at that point. The demo even apparently came as a surprise to members of the Siri team.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Waiting for the Perfect MacBook Pro? 2026 Might Be the Year</h2><br/>
We're expecting an update to the MacBook Pro later this year with a new M5 chip and some other upgrades, but for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/2026-perfect-macbook-pro-rumors/">much more substantial revamp, you might want to wait until 2026</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/M6-MacBook-Pro-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984552" /><br/>
Rumors indicate the 2026 MacBook Pro could see a design overhaul with OLED displays, a smaller pinhole camera cutout replacing the current notch, and perhaps even a thinner and lighter design and 5G connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the MacBook Pro overhaul, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-larger-foldable-mass-production-2026/">2026 may also see the launch of Apple's rumored large foldable device</a>, which reportedly features an 18.8-inch display when unfolded.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18.4.1 Update Coming Soon for iPhones</h2><br/>
iOS 18.5 remains in early beta testing, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/ios-18-4-1-coming-soon/">Apple appears to have an interim iOS 18.4.1 update on the way</a>, and it should be arriving within the next week or two.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iOS-18.4.1-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998133" /><br/>
It's unclear what fixes will be included in the update, but these updates typically focus on security issues. It's possible it could also address a few problems that popped up in the iOS 18.4 update such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/ios-18-4-carplay-bugs-multiple-vehicle-brands/">CarPlay connectivity issues some users have been experiencing</a>, though that's merely speculation at this point.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/apr-10-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/top-stories-ios-19-iphone-17-pro-rumors/">Top Stories: iOS 19 and iPhone 17 Pro Rumors, Siri Revamp Turmoil, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-19-and-iphone-17-pro-rumors-siri-revamp-turmoil-and-more.2455192/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 Products Still Coming From Apple in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/10-apple-products-2025-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-products-still-coming-from-apple-in-2025.2455172/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:14:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/10-apple-products-2025-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple may have updated several iPads and Macs late last year and early this year, but there are still multiple new devices that we're looking forward to seeing in 2025. Most will come in September or October, but there could be a few surprises before then.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-2025-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983757" /><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up a list of everything that we're still waiting to see from Apple in 2025.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/"><strong>iPhone 17, 17 Air, and 17 Pro</strong></a> - We get new iPhones every September so it's not a surprise that updated models are coming, but this year should be exciting because the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">rumored iPhone 17 Air</a> will have an all-new ultra-thin form factor, plus the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max</a> are getting a new rear camera design.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 11</a></strong> - There's an updated Apple Watch coming, and it could get blood pressure monitoring and other health features, though that's not a guarantee yet. An update for watchOS has also been rumored, so it could get a new look.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Ultra 3</a></strong> - Apple didn't update the Apple Watch Ultra last year, but we're supposedly getting a new model this year.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a></strong> - We also didn't get an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> in 2024, so Apple's low-cost Apple Watch is due for an update. There were some rumors about a new plastic casing, but that might be scrapped.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-pro-3/"><strong>AirPods Pro 3</strong></a> - It's finally time for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> to get an update, and it sounds like it'll be a big one. The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; will have a new design, and the case could get an update too. We're expecting better audio quality, Active Noise Cancellation improvements, a faster chip, and possibly health features like temperature and heart rate monitoring.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></strong> - The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> is Apple's last Mac that doesn't have an M4 chip inside, and it's going to be refreshed before the end of the year.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a></strong> - The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> was last updated in October 2024, but when October 2025 rolls around, it'll be due for another refresh. No major design changes are planned, but it will get a spec boost in the form of the faster M5 chip.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-apple-tv/">Apple TV 4K</a></strong> - It's been quite some time since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> was refreshed, and a new model is in the works. It'll have a faster processor, perhaps even one that can support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and console-quality games. No design changes are expected.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></strong> - The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> could get its first update with a faster S-series chip, an Apple-designed Wi-Fi and Bluetooth chip for improved performance, and new color options.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags-2/">AirTag 2</a></strong> - There's a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> in the works, and it's slated for launch sometime in 2025. There are no signs of a design update, but it will get a new Ultra Wideband chip for improved range, plus there could be other improvements like a new, louder speaker.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<h2>Bonus: New Software</h2><br/>
In two months, Apple is going to show off new software at its June Worldwide Developers Conference. We'll see the new features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a>, iPadOS 19, macOS 16, tvOS 19, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3.<br/>
<br/>
New software is fun because if you've got a modern Apple device, you don't even need to buy anything new to get the new functionality that Apple will be showing off. While we'll get a June preview, the software updates are slated for September.<br/>
<h2>Read More</h2><br/>
We keep track of all of the products that Apple has coming both in the near future and in the more distant future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/upcoming-apple-products/"><strong>in our upcoming products guide</strong></a>. It's updated regularly, so it's worth keeping an eye if you're interested in what Apple has in the works.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/10-apple-products-2025-launch/">10 Products Still Coming From Apple in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-products-still-coming-from-apple-in-2025.2455172/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Check Out ColorWare&#039;s Custom Apple Pencil Pro With a Crayon Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-pencil-pro-crayons-colorware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-colorwares-custom-apple-pencil-pro-with-a-crayon-design.2455161/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:17:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-pencil-pro-crayons-colorware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ColorWare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[ColorWare today introduced a clever new range of <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/colorware-apple-crayon-pros">custom Apple Pencils</a> that have been designed to look like crayons. ColorWare is known for its custom-painted Apple accessories and products like AirPods, and the company sometimes does unique limited edition designs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/colorware-crayon-pro-1.jpg" alt="" width="1776" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998443" /><br/>
The ColorWare Apple Crayon Pro is available in seven colors, including black, mint, pink, purple, red, white, and yellow. Each one has a custom colored tip and a matching wrapper, all of which is painted on a standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro. ColorWare previously did a custom &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; designed to look like a <a href="https://www.colorware.com/products/colorware-apple-number-2-pencil-pro">number 2 pencil</a>, but the custom crayons in multiple colors are even more fun. With the attention to design, the Apple Crayon Pro does indeed look quite a bit like an actual crayon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/colorware-crayon-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="1776" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998444" /><br/>
ColorWare has been customizing Apple devices for more than a decade, and it has perfected the process for a lasting finish. ColorWare uses a multi-step coating system, including a primer, a proprietary color formula, and a liquid plastic coating to protect the color. All products are warrantied for 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/colorware-crayon-pro-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998445" /><br/>
Because ColorWare is using a standard &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro, all of the functionality of the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; remains intact. The &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro works with the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> and M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, and the A17 Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>.<br/>
<br/>
ColorWare is selling the Apple Crayon Pro for &#36;215, and all colors are <a href="https://www.colorware.com/collections/colorware-apple-crayon-pros">available from the ColorWare website</a> as of today. Orders ship out in about two weeks.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/colorware/">ColorWare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-pencil-pro-crayons-colorware/">Check Out ColorWare&#039;s Custom Apple Pencil Pro With a Crayon Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-colorwares-custom-apple-pencil-pro-with-a-crayon-design.2455161/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Raises Prices on Amazon Due to Tariffs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/anker-amazon-tariff-price-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-raises-prices-on-amazon-due-to-tariffs.2455154/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 11:28:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/anker-amazon-tariff-price-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Anker</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fs%3Fk%3Danker%26amp%3Bcrid%3D1MYIAAZBF52H3%26amp%3Bsprefix%3Danke%252Caps%252C114%26amp%3Bref%3Dnb_sb_noss_2">Chinese company Anker</a> is one of many companies that will be raising prices due to the tariffs put in place by U.S. President Donald Trump, and prices are already starting to go up on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-Accessories-Deals-2024-Anker-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981378" /><br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/chinese-electronics-company-anker-starts-raising-prices-amazon-2025-04-11/">Reuters</a></em>, Anker has increased pricing on about a fifth of its products since Thursday of last week. Prices are up approximately 18 percent, and there is a possibility for further increases. A power bank that was &#36;88 <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Multi-Device-Charging-Retractable%2Fdp%2FB0DCBB2YTR%2Fref%3Dsr_1_9">is now &#36;110</a>, for example, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Real-Time-Interface-Ethernet%2Fdp%2FB0CW9249DK">a charging station</a> that was &#36;250 is now &#36;270.<br/>
<br/>
The tariffs on China are at 145 percent as of yesterday, which means items imported into the United States are significantly more expensive. U.S. customers and companies buying from China need to pay a 145 percent tax on the declared value of an item that is brought into the country. China has also put a 125 percent reciprocal tariff in place on U.S. goods coming to China.<br/>
<br/>
China does not plan to raise its tariffs beyond 125 percent, <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/china/china-increase-tariffs-us-goods-125-up-84-finance-ministry-says-2025-04-11/">and in a statement</a>, China's Finance Ministry said that if U.S. tariffs go higher, it no longer makes sense to increase to match. "Even if the U.S. continues to impose even higher tariffs, it would no longer have any economic significance and would go down as a joke in the history of world economics," reads the Finance Ministry's statement.<br/>
<br/>
China also said that the tariffs are an act of bullying, with the country planning to fight "to the end." From the Ministry's statement:<br/>
<blockquote>The U.S. side's imposition of excessively high tariffs on China seriously violates international economic and trade rules, runs counter to basic economic principles and common sense, and is simply an act of unilateral bullying and coercion.</blockquote><br/>
Earlier this week, Anker told investors that it was able to raise prices because many of its rivals are Chinese and are facing similar tariff pressure. The company also said that it plans to explore non-U.S. markets like Europe and Southeast Asia.<br/>
<br/>
Anker's prices fluctuate regularly due to the numerous sales that the company offers, but e-commerce site SmartScout says that there has been a "concerted effort" to raise prices since last week. Anker is still offering some discounts, and it has a site-wide sale right now for <em>MacRumors</em> readers. Any product <a href="https://www.anker.com/">on the Anker website</a> is discounted by 20 percent with the promo code Ankermacrumors2025.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anker/">Anker</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/anker-amazon-tariff-price-increase/">Anker Raises Prices on Amazon Due to Tariffs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-raises-prices-on-amazon-due-to-tariffs.2455154/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M4 iPad Pro vs. M3 iPad Air: Which One is Best For You</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/m4-ipad-pro-vs-m3-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-ipad-pro-vs-m3-ipad-air-which-one-is-best-for-you.2455147/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 09:14:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/m4-ipad-pro-vs-m3-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> have had fairly recent updates, and there are quite a few similarities between them that might leave you wondering which one is the best to meet your needs. In our latest video, we go over the similarities and differences, and the use cases that might make you choose one over another.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="M3 iPad Air vs M4 iPad Pro: Don't Make This Mistake!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MiqFipjJAvo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The M3 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;599, while the M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is &#36;999, so there's a notable difference in terms of cost. There are 11-inch and 13-inch size options for both models, and performance is not too far off between them.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, you essentially get an improved display, a faster chip, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> support, better audio, ProRes video recording, and the option to use the higher-end keyboard case. There are few things you can do on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> that stress the M3 chip, and most people won't notice the difference in performance from M3 to M4 for day to day tasks.<br/>
<br/>
Where you might see a small difference is apps that are system intensive, like Final Cut Pro or Photoshop, but both handle those tasks just fine. It's actually the display that's the biggest differentiating factor. The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; has an OLED display that's much brighter, supports HDR, offers ProMotion, and has deeper blacks and more vivid colors. If you're doing something where color is a factor, or if display quality is important, that's where you would want to consider the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch our full video where we go into much more depth about the differences, and show off the two tablets side-by-side.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/m4-ipad-pro-vs-m3-ipad-air/">M4 iPad Pro vs. M3 iPad Air: Which One is Best For You</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m4-ipad-pro-vs-m3-ipad-air-which-one-is-best-for-you.2455147/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Apple Watch SE Hits Best Price of the Year So Far, Plus Save on the New iPad and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-11-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-apple-watch-se-hits-best-price-of-the-year-so-far-plus-save-on-the-new-ipad-and-more.2455141/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:52:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-11-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best Apple deals include discounts on AirPods Max, iPad, and Apple Watch SE. We're also tracking a big sitewide sale at OWC, including savings on docks and hubs for your Mac, plus external drives and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/hero-new-blue-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961852" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/airpods-max-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998407" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;49 off AirPods Max</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/usb-c-airpods-max-499/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon discounted the AirPods Max (USB-C) to &#36;499.99 in every color this week. This is the first time in a few weeks that we've tracked a deal on every color of the AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>OWC</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/owc-dock-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998408" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Mac docks, hubs, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fshop%2Fspecials">OWC</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/owcs-spring-savings-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fshop%2Fspecials"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>OWC Spring Savings Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
OWC's "Spring Savings Celebration" kicked off this week, offering big discounts on docks, hubs, memory cards, external drives, and more. Many of these deals won't be applied until you add the items to your cart, at which time an automatic coupon will be applied to your order.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/new-apple-watch-se-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998411" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;79 off Apple Watch SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/amazon-79-off-apple-watch-se/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.97</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHRBF1J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get &#36;79 off the Apple Watch SE this week on Amazon, starting at just &#36;169.97 for the 40mm GPS model. Overall, these are both the best prices we've seen so far in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/new-ipad-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998412" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;49 off the new iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75TN5F%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;319.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76LW4J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;419.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ77SG5C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few new discounts on Apple's 11th generation iPad this week, including &#36;49 off the 512GB Wi-Fi model of the tablet. Prices start at &#36;327.00 for the 128GB Wi-Fi iPad, down from &#36;349.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-4-11-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Apple Watch SE Hits Best Price of the Year So Far, Plus Save on the New iPad and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-apple-watch-se-hits-best-price-of-the-year-so-far-plus-save-on-the-new-ipad-and-more.2455141/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Select Faster on iPhone With This Two-Finger Trick</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/select-faster-on-iphone-two-finger-trick/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/select-faster-on-iphone-with-this-two-finger-trick.2455136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:16:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/select-faster-on-iphone-two-finger-trick&#038;post_date=1744391807/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Your iPhone has multiple touch and gesture capabilities that can enhance how you interact with apps. Some, like pinch and zoom, are well known enough to be considered second nature, but others are less obvious, like the one we're about to explain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/multiple-select-gesture.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956201" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Two-Finger Drag to Select Items</h2><br/>
If you have apps where you habitually tap on each individual item in a list to select them – emails in your Mail inbox, for example – it's time to dial in some efficiency and embrace this faster method.<br/>
<br/>
This gestural feature allows you to easily select (or deselect) multiple items in apps like Contacts, Mail, Messages, Voice Memos, Notes, and indeed any Apple app that lists multiple items. Here's how it works. <br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open an app where multiple item selection is supported.</li><br/>
  <li>Touch and hold the screen with two fingers at the same time.</li><br/>
  <li>While keeping both fingers on the screen, drag them down (or up) to select multiple items. As you drag, items will be highlighted to indicate they are selected.</li><br/>
  <li>Once the desired items are selected, you can perform actions such as moving, deleting, or organizing them.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/two-finger-select-gesture.jpg" alt="" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956202" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. This simple yet powerful feature streamlines your workflow, saving you time and effort when handling multiple items. Looking to speed up your iPhone text editing skills? Check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/speed-up-text-navigation-iphone-hidden-trackpad/">favorite hidden trick</a> by following the link.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/select-faster-on-iphone-two-finger-trick/">Select Faster on iPhone With This Two-Finger Trick</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/select-faster-on-iphone-with-this-two-finger-trick.2455136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: New iOS 19, iPhone 17, and Apple Watch Ultra 3 Leaks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-19-iphone-17-leaks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-19-iphone-17-and-apple-watch-ultra-3-leaks.2455135/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 07:13:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-19-iphone-17-leaks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/new-ios-19-iphone-17-and-apple-watch-ultra-3-leaks/id1602394741?i=1000703158336">The MacRumors Show</a>, we catch up on the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and watchOS 12 rumors, upcoming devices, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/mO9kzY0EWmY?si=oj0LYQdAVssMDU0z" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Detailed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">new renders</a> from leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jon-prosser/">Jon Prosser</a> claim to provide the best look yet at the complete redesign rumored to arrive in &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;, showing more rounded elements, lighting effects, translucency, and an all-new pill-shaped tab bar with an elongated search bar. This visonOS-style redesign is also now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/apple-watch-visionos-design/">rumored to come to the Apple Watch</a>, and a sketchy report claims that the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will tout <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/apple-watch-visionos-design/">exclusive AI features</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration with activity information and sleep tracking, health monitoring, and more.<br/>
<br/>
We look at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/09/leaked-iphone-17-pro-cases-huge-cutout-camera-bump/">first iPhone 17 Pro cases</a>, which emphasize just how large the new full-width camera bump is set to be, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/iphone-17-pro-dual-video-recording-rumor/">exclusive camera features</a> rumored for the device. We also discuss the report about the second-generation Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/vision-pro-2-now-in-production/">now being in mass production</a>, the delay of Apple's smart home hub product <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/apple-might-delay-smart-home-hub/">to 2026</a>, and Sir Jony Ive's work on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/jony-ive-ai-phone-without-a-screen/">smartphone without a screen</a> for OpenAI. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> also has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/04/the-macrumors-show-wwdc25-announced-and-ios-18-4/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our in-depth discussion about the announcement of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a>, key iOS 18.4 features, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-19-iphone-17-leaks/">The MacRumors Show: New iOS 19, iPhone 17, and Apple Watch Ultra 3 Leaks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-19-iphone-17-and-apple-watch-ultra-3-leaks.2455135/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Plans to Release Delayed Apple Intelligence ‌Siri‌ Features This Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-to-release-delayed-apple-intelligence-‌siri‌-features-this-fall.2455125/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:53:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release its delayed Apple Intelligence Siri features in the fall, according to a new report by <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/11/technology/apple-issues-trump-tariffs.html">The New York Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
In early March, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">said</a> that it was going to take longer than expected to roll out the more personalized ‌Siri‌ experience, and that these features would be rolled out "in the coming year." Subsequently, <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-says-some-ai-improvements-siri-delayed-2026-2025-03-07/">Reuters</a></em> reported that the ‌Apple Intelligence‌ ‌Siri‌ features have been delayed until 2026. <br/>
<br/>
However, <em>NYT</em> reports today that its sources within Apple are still confident of a fall release. From the report:<br/>
<blockquote>Apple hasn't canceled its revamped Siri. The company plans to release a virtual assistant in the fall capable of doing things like editing and sending a photo to a friend on request, three people with knowledge of its plans said.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The ‌Siri‌ features in question were demonstrated at WWDC when introducing ‌iOS 18‌, and they were expected to come out in an update to ‌iOS 18‌. The functionality includes personal context, onscreen awareness, and improved app integration. Here's a quick summary:<br/>
<h3>Personal Context</h3><br/>
Siri will be able to track emails, messages, files, photos, and more – learning from your interactions to help you stay organized and complete tasks.<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Show me the files Sam sent me last week.</li><br/>
  <li>Find the email where Sam mentioned ice hockey.</li><br/>
  <li>Find the books Sam recommended to me.</li><br/>
  <li>Where's the recipe Sam sent me?</li><br/>
  <li>What's my passport number?</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Onscreen Awareness</h3><br/>
Siri will understand what's on your screen and act on it. For example, if someone texts you an address, you can ask Siri to add it to their contact card. Or, if you're viewing a photo, you can ask Siri to send it.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Deeper App Integration</h3><br/>
Siri will handle more complex tasks across apps – things it currently can't do. Apple shared a few examples of what to expect:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Move files between apps.</li><br/>
  <li>Edit a photo and send it.</li><br/>
  <li>Get directions home and share the ETA with Sam.</li><br/>
  <li>Send the draft email to Sam.</li><br/>
</ul>Already, Siri has gained Type to Siri, a refreshed interface, ChatGPT integration, and improved natural language understanding.<br/>
<br/>
Apple demonstrated many of the above missing Siri features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">WWDC previews</a>, and went on to advertise them on its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/apple-website-siri-features-fine-print/">website</a>. It also promoted them in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/apple-pulls-iphone-16-ad-more-personal-siri/">since-pulled TV ad</a> for iPhone 16 starring actor Bella Ramsey, as well as elsewhere. Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/">sued at least three times</a> over the delayed Siri features in California.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/">Apple Plans to Release Delayed Apple Intelligence ‌Siri‌ Features This Fall</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-plans-to-release-delayed-apple-intelligence-‌siri‌-features-this-fall.2455125/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>NYT: Apple&#039;s AI Struggles Began with 2023 Chip Budget Dispute</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-ai-struggles-2023-chip-budget-dispute/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nyt-apples-ai-struggles-began-with-2023-chip-budget-dispute.2455123/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 04:33:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-ai-struggles-2023-chip-budget-dispute/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>New York Times</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's current struggles with Apple Intelligence and Siri began in early 2023 when AI head John Giannandrea sought approval from CEO Tim Cook to purchase more AI chips for development, according to a new report from <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/11/technology/apple-issues-trump-tariffs.html">The New York Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
Cook initially approved doubling the team's chip budget, but CFO Luca Maestri reportedly reduced the increase to less than half that amount, and instead encouraged the team to make existing chips more efficient.<br/>
<br/>
The lack of adequate GPU resources meant Apple's AI team had to negotiate for computing power from providers like Google and Amazon. <br/>
<br/>
At the time, Apple's data centers had about 50,000 GPUs that were more than five years old – far fewer than the hundreds of thousands of chips being purchased by competitors like Microsoft, Google, and Meta.<br/>
<br/>
The <em>NYT</em> report goes on to cover the leadership conflicts within the company, describing a power struggle between Robby Walker, who oversaw Siri, and Sebastien Marineau-Mes, a senior executive with the software team. The two reportedly battled over who would spearhead Siri's new capabilities, with both ultimately receiving pieces of the project.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence faced significant delays after internal testing revealed Siri was inaccurate on nearly a third of requests. Apple subsequently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">admitted</a> that it would take longer than expected to roll out the more personalized ‌Siri‌ experience, and that these features will be rolled out "in the coming year."<br/>
<br/>
However, according to the report, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/">still plans to release its enhanced Siri experience this fall</a>. The functionality includes personal context, onscreen awareness, and improved app integration. Some Apple executives reportedly aren't concerned about the delay, and believe competitors haven't perfected AI either, giving Apple time to get it right.<br/>
<br/>
Following the delay, software chief Craig Federighi reorganized executives, removing responsibility for the new Siri from Giannandrea and reassigning it to Mike Rockwell, who leads the Vision Pro division. The details of Apple's Siri team changes and the delayed Siri revamp were previously reported by <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/14/apple-siri-team-reassurance/">Bloomberg</a></em> and <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chaos-behind-siri-revealed/">The Information</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on Apple's internal issues, including political infighting, budget constraints, and talent drain, see <em>The New York Times</em>' <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/04/11/technology/apple-issues-trump-tariffs.html">full report</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nytimes-com/">New York Times</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-ai-struggles-2023-chip-budget-dispute/">NYT: Apple&#039;s AI Struggles Began with 2023 Chip Budget Dispute</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nyt-apples-ai-struggles-began-with-2023-chip-budget-dispute.2455123/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Adjust Mac Volume and Brightness More Precisely</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/adjust-mac-volume-brightness-more-precisely/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-adjust-mac-volume-and-brightness-more-precisely.2455117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 03:13:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/adjust-mac-volume-brightness-more-precisely&#038;post_date=1744377233/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On a Mac that has a top row of function keys, Apple includes volume and brightness controls that can be used to make adjustments in stepwise increments. However, there may be times when you want to make more fine grained adjustments to these settings than the default increments allow – in which case, read on.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/new-mac-keyboard-mute.jpeg" alt="" width="1500" height="949" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-993727" /><br/>
Whenever you tap the volume or brightness controls on your keyboard, you'll see an indicator appear on your Mac's screen with 16 fixed increments separated by lines. With the help of a keyboard modifier, it's actually possible to make more nuanced quarter-step changes to sound volume and screen brightness using a total of 64 increments. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/volume-symbol.jpg" alt="Mac" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998354" /><br/>
Before you press the volume or brightness controls, hold down the Option and Shift keys together on your keyboard. Now go ahead and make your adjustments, and you should see the onscreen indicator move forwards and backwards in smaller increments (four over each segment).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/volume-incremental.jpg" alt="Mac" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998357" /><br/>
It's a simple tip, but it's really useful for when just tapping the control on its own feels like too much of a jump, and you'd prefer more accurate control over, let's say, how quiet or loud your headphone audio output is, for example.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/adjust-mac-volume-brightness-more-precisely/">How to Adjust Mac Volume and Brightness More Precisely</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-adjust-mac-volume-and-brightness-more-precisely.2455117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bluesky Gains Twitter-Like Message Reactions and New Search Page</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/bluesky-message-reactions-new-search-page/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bluesky-gains-twitter-like-message-reactions-and-new-search-page.2455116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 02:42:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/bluesky-message-reactions-new-search-page/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Bluesky is <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/bsky.app/post/3lmi3hlglc224">rolling out</a> a new update introducing features that might ease the transition for social media users coming over from X (Twitter). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/bluesky.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935373" /><br/>
First up, version 1.100 adds emoji reactions to Bluesky's direct messaging system. Users can now respond to messages with quick emoji reactions by holding down on a message and selecting from common options like hearts, thumbs up, and laughing faces. For those wanting more expression, the three-dot menu provides access to a full emoji keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
The app's search page has also been completely revamped and renamed "Explore." This new discovery hub prominently displays trending topics labeled with tags like "Hot" or "New," along with timestamps showing when topics started gaining traction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/bluesky-emoji-reactions.jpg.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="523" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998346" /><br/>
Beyond trends, the Explore page now recommends accounts to follow across various interest categories such as Art, Sports, Music, and Politics. Users can also personalize their experience by selecting specific interests that inform what appears on their Explore page.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/bluesky-explore.jpg.jpg" alt="" width="804" height="754" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998347" /><br/>
Meanwhile, for newcomers, Bluesky has added curated "Starter Packs," or pre-made lists of accounts focused on specific topics that users can follow with a single tap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/bluesky-explore-page-2.jpg.jpg" alt="" width="804" height="886" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998348" /><br/>
The features are designed to make the transition easier for users migrating from other platforms while improving content discovery within Bluesky.<br/>
<br/>
Bluesky has over 34 million active users, according to the company. That's still a lot less than Meta's Threads in total users, but the platform continues to gain popularity as an alternative to X. The update is available now on the App Store [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/bluesky-social/id6444370199">Direct Link</a>] for iPhone users running iOS 15.1 or later.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/bluesky-message-reactions-new-search-page/">Bluesky Gains Twitter-Like Message Reactions and New Search Page</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bluesky-gains-twitter-like-message-reactions-and-new-search-page.2455116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Razer Launches PC Remote Play for Streaming Games to iPhones and iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/razer-pc-remote-play/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/razer-launches-pc-remote-play-for-streaming-games-to-iphones-and-ipads.2455099/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:12:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/razer-pc-remote-play/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Razer</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Razer today announced <a href="https://press.razer.com/product-news/razer-pc-remote-play-officially-launches/">the official launch</a> of <a href="https://www.razer.com/gaming-software/razer-pc-remote-play">Razer PC Remote Play</a>, which is designed to allow Razer PC users to stream their games directly to mobile devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/razer-pc-remote-play.jpg" alt="" width="1684" height="946" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998339" /><br/>
According to Razer, the platform provides ultra-smooth, high-fidelity gameplay on smartphones and tablets, with support for all iOS-compatible gaming controllers for a PC gaming experience on the go. On the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, there's also support for keyboards, mice, and trackpads.<br/>
<br/>
PC users can browse through, configure, and launch PC games from an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, as well as customize controls, record and share gameplay, and more. Razer PC Remote Play is able to automatically optimize games to match the maximum resolution and refresh rate of a mobile device without having a fixed aspect ratio.<br/>
<br/>
On an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, users will need to install Razer Nexus and Razer PC Remote Play, and on a PC running Windows 11 or later, Remote Play needs to be enabled in Razer Cortex. More information is <a href="https://www.razer.com/gaming-software/razer-pc-remote-play">available on Razer's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/razer/">Razer</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/razer-pc-remote-play/">Razer Launches PC Remote Play for Streaming Games to iPhones and iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/razer-launches-pc-remote-play-for-streaming-games-to-iphones-and-ipads.2455099/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Gets Better at Remembering Info About You With Memory Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chatgpt-memory-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gets-better-at-remembering-info-about-you-with-memory-improvements.2455091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:12:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chatgpt-memory-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI today <a href="https://x.com/sama/status/1910380643772665873">updated ChatGPT</a> with an improved memory feature that allows the chatbot to remember more about your conversations. OpenAI CEO Sam Altman says that ChatGPT can "reference all your past conversations," allowing for a more personalized experience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/chatgpt-logo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998332" /><br/>
ChatGPT will remember context from previous conversations, such as preferences and interests, using that information to tailor the responses that it provides. You can add something directly to ChatGPT's memory by telling it to "remember" a fact.<br/>
<br/>
The option to reference saved memories is opt-in, and can be toggled off in the ChatGPT settings under Personalization. There is an option to manage all of the memories that ChatGPT has stored, including deleting them all or deleting just one or two. ChatGPT will save memories indefinitely, but they can be removed at any time.<br/>
<br/>
The updated memory features are rolling out to all Plus and Pro tier users, but the functionality is not available in the EU, UK, Switzerland, Norway, Iceland, and Liechtenstein.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chatgpt-memory-improvements/">ChatGPT Gets Better at Remembering Info About You With Memory Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gets-better-at-remembering-info-about-you-with-memory-improvements.2455091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Continues Rolling Out Support for Carrier Satellite Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-carrier-satellite-services-expansion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-rolling-out-support-for-carrier-satellite-services.2455076/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:55:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-carrier-satellite-services-expansion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to add support for carrier-based satellite services, with au customers in Japan and One NZ customers in New Zealand now able to use the satellite connectivity offered by those carriers on compatible <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/starlink-au.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998326" /><br/>
Both <a href="https://newsroom.kddi.com/english/news/detail/kddi_nr-533_3818.html">au</a> and <a href="https://one.nz/why-choose-us/satellite/">One NZ</a> have partnered with SpaceX to provide their customers with Starlink Direct satellite service, joining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/28/ios-18-3-starlink-t-mobile-support/">T-Mobile in the U.S.</a> in offering Starlink connectivity as an alternative to the satellite messaging features built into Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 and later models. Japan and New Zealand both have large swathes of land where traditional cellular coverage is unavailable due to terrain limitations.<br/>
<br/>
For au customers, Starlink Direct covers all of Japan, providing connectivity in remote areas where cellular towers are not available. au does not charge for the service, which allows users to send and receive text messages, get emergency earthquake alerts, and share their location with friends and family.<br/>
<br/>
In New Zealand, One NZ customers can use Starlink Direct to send and receive texts anywhere in the country, with the functionality included in eligible mobile plans.<br/>
<br/>
Starlink Direct is available when cellular signal is not, as long as there is a clear line of sight to the sky. While an open space not obstructed by buildings helps with connectivity, users do not need to hold their smartphone up to the sky to connect, which is a requirement for Apple's built-in satellite service offered through its partnership with Globalstar.<br/>
<br/>
Carrier-based satellite services are supported on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 models and later, and customers who have access to carrier satellite options can use those in addition to the satellite connectivity that is included in Apple's modern iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://x.com/dhinakg">Dhinak</a>!)</em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-carrier-satellite-services-expansion/">Apple Continues Rolling Out Support for Carrier Satellite Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-rolling-out-support-for-carrier-satellite-services.2455076/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hit With More Class Action Lawsuits Over Delayed Siri Features in U.S. and Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hit-with-more-class-action-lawsuits-over-delayed-siri-features-in-u-s-and-canada.2455072/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 08:09:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been hit with at least two more proposed class action lawsuits over its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">delayed personalized Siri features</a> for iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-More-Personal-Siri-Ad.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994006" /><br/>
In the U.S., a <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/848452424/Martin-et-al-v-Apple-Inc">complaint</a> filed in a California federal court this week alleges that Apple violated false advertising and unfair competition laws by marketing Apple Intelligence upgrades for Siri that are still not available. The two named plaintiffs said they never would have purchased or been willing to pay as much for an iPhone 16 had they known that Apple's marketing surrounding the features was false and misleading.<br/>
<br/>
Apple advertised the Siri features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">in product presentations</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/apple-website-siri-features-fine-print/">on its website</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/apple-pulls-iphone-16-ad-more-personal-siri/">in a TV commercial starring actor Bella Ramsey</a>, and elsewhere.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/apple-intelligence-siri-lawsuit/">already sued over the delayed Siri features</a> in California last month, and the class action lawsuits could eventually be merged if they proceed.<br/>
<br/>
A similar complaint was filed against Apple last week <a href="https://vancouversun.com/news/class-action-lawsuit-alleges-apple-false-ai-promises-iphone-16">in the Canadian province of British Columbia</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed the personalized Siri features during its WWDC 2024 keynote last June, as part of a wide range of Apple Intelligence features that it said would be rolling out over the course of the following year. That gave Apple until WWDC 2025 this June to roll out the Siri features, but last month the company announced that it needed more time and anticipated rolling out the features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">at some point "in the coming year"</a> from then.<br/>
<br/>
The features were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">initially expected to launch in iOS 18.4</a> last week, but they are now expected to arrive at some point during the iOS 19 cycle. Many well-connected Apple reporters and observers believe the features will not be available until 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Whenever they launch, the Siri upgrades will include understanding of a user's personal context, on-screen awareness, and deeper per-app controls. For example, during its WWDC 2024 keynote, Apple showed an iPhone user asking Siri about their mother's flight and lunch reservation plans based on info from the Mail and Messages apps.<br/>
<br/>
The class action lawsuits in the U.S. and Canada are both seeking damages from Apple, in an amount to be proven at trial, so class members who purchased an iPhone 16 in order to use the personalized Siri features could eventually receive a payout from Apple, if the judges presiding over each case find that the company broke the law.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's lawyers have yet to respond to any of the lawsuits.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/apple-hit-with-more-siri-delay-lawsuits/">Apple Hit With More Class Action Lawsuits Over Delayed Siri Features in U.S. and Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hit-with-more-class-action-lawsuits-over-delayed-siri-features-in-u-s-and-canada.2455072/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report Reveals Internal Chaos Behind Apple&#039;s Siri Failure</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chaos-behind-siri-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-reveals-internal-chaos-behind-apples-siri-failure.2455066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 07:15:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chaos-behind-siri-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Craig Federighi</category>
		<category>John Giannandrea</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new report from <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-fumbled-siris-ai-makeover"><em>The Information</em></a> today reveals much of the internal turmoil behind <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>'s revamped version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-18-Siri-Personal-Context.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-994536" /><br/>
Apple apparently weighed up multiple options for the backend of &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;. One initial idea was to build both small and large language models, dubbed "Mini Mouse" and "Mighty Mouse," to run locally on iPhones and in the cloud, respectively. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s leadership then decided to go in a different direction and build a single large language model to handle all requests via the cloud, before a series of further technical pivots. The indecision and repeated changes in direction reportedly frustrated engineers and prompted some members of staff to leave Apple.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to Apple's deeply ingrained stance on privacy, conflicting personalities within Apple contributed to the problems. More than half a dozen former employees who worked in Apple's AI and machine-learning group told <em>The Information</em> that poor leadership is to blame for its problems with execution, citing an overly relaxed culture, as well as a lack of ambition and appetite for taking risks when designing future versions of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's AI/ML group has been dubbed "AIMLess" internally, while employees are said to refer to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; as a "hot potato" that is continually passed between different teams with no significant improvements. There were also conflicts about higher pay, faster promotions, longer vacations, and shorter days for colleagues in the AI group.<br/>
<br/>
Apple AI chief John Giannandrea was apparently confident he could fix &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; with the right training data and better web-scraping for answers to general knowledge questions. Senior leaders didn't respond with a sense of urgency to the debut of ChatGPT in 2022; Giannandrea told employees that he didn't believe chatbots like ChatGPT added much value for users.<br/>
<br/>
In 2023, Apple managers told engineers that they were forbidden from including models from other companies in final Apple products and could only use them to benchmark against their own models, but Apple's own models "didn't perform nearly as well as OpenAI's technology."<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; leader Robby Walker focused on "small wins" such as reducing wait times for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; responses. One of Walker's pet projects was removing the "hey" from the "hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;" voice command used to invoke the assistant, which took over two years to achieve. He also shot down an effort from a team of engineers to use LLMs to give &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; more emotional sensitivity so it could detect and give appropriate responses to users in distress.<br/>
<br/>
Apple started a project codenamed "Link" to develop voice commands to control apps and complete tasks for the Vision Pro, with plans to allow users to navigate the web and resize windows with voice alone, as well as support commands from multiple people in a shared virtual space to collaborate. Most of these features were dropped because of the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; team's inability to achieve them.<br/>
<br/>
The report claims that the demo of &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;'s most impressive features at WWDC 2024, such as where &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; accesses a user's emails to find real-time flight data and provides a reminder about lunch plans using messages and plots a route in maps, was effectively fictitious. The demo apparently came as a surprise to members of the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; team, who had never seen working versions of the capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
The only feature from the WWDC demonstration that was activated on test devices was &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;'s pulsing, colorful ribbon around the edge of the display. The decision to showcase an artificial demonstration was a major departure from Apple's past behavior, where it would only show features and products at its events that were already working on test devices and that its marketing team had approved to ensure they could be released on schedule.<br/>
<br/>
Some Apple employees are said to be optimistic that Craig Federighi and Mike Rockwell can turn &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; around. Federighi has apparently instructed &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; engineers to do "whatever it takes to build the best AI features," even if that means using open-source models from other companies in its software products as opposed to Apple's own models.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on Apple's &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; debacle, see <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-fumbled-siris-ai-makeover"><em>The Information</em></a>'s full report.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/craig-federighi/">Craig Federighi</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/john-giannandrea/">John Giannandrea</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/chaos-behind-siri-revealed/">Report Reveals Internal Chaos Behind Apple&#039;s Siri Failure</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-reveals-internal-chaos-behind-apples-siri-failure.2455066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s USB-C AirPods Max Drop to &#36;499.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/usb-c-airpods-max-499/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-usb-c-airpods-max-drop-to-499-99-on-amazon.2455065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 06:58:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/usb-c-airpods-max-499/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the USB-C AirPods Max on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> in every color, down from &#36;549.00. While not an all-time low price, this is the first time in a few weeks that every color of the USB-C AirPods Max has been on sale on Amazon, and it's still a solid markdown for anyone who's been waiting for a sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Max-Discount-Feature-Blue-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895391" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Colors available on sale include Blue, Midnight, Orange, Starlight, and Purple. All colors are available to be delivered by mid April, with most providing a delivery estimate around April 15 for free shipping options. Prime members in certain cities should be able to see same-day delivery options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/usb-c-airpods-max-499/">Apple&#039;s USB-C AirPods Max Drop to &#36;499.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-usb-c-airpods-max-drop-to-499-99-on-amazon.2455065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Gets Updates to Group Chats, Events, Calls, Channels, More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/whatsapp-new-features-roundup/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-gets-updates-to-group-chats-events-calls-channels-more.2455057/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 04:52:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/whatsapp-new-features-roundup/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp has <a href="https://blog.whatsapp.com/new-feature-roundup-updates-to-group-chats-events-calls-channels-and-more">announced</a> a laundry list of new features aimed at enhancing the user experience across chats, calls, and channels, with some of the features available now or currently rolling out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/whatsapp-feature-roundup.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998271" /><br/>
Among the most notable additions is a new "Online" indicator for group chats, which shows how many people are currently active in a conversation without revealing specific names. The feature makes it easier to see whether members are available or if you're messaging into a quiet group.<br/>
<br/>
For users overwhelmed by group notifications, WhatsApp has introduced customizable alert settings. The new "Notify for" option allows users to choose between receiving all notifications or only "Highlights" – which includes @mentions, replies, and messages from saved contacts.<br/>
<br/>
The encrypted chat platform has also expanded its Events functionality, which was previously limited to groups. Users can now create events in one-on-one conversations, add RSVP options including "maybe," invite plus-ones, and pin events directly in chats.<br/>
<br/>
Elsewhere, communication has been made more interactive with tappable reactions. When someone reacts to a message, users can simply tap on that reaction to add their own or to "+1" the existing emoji, similar to platforms like Slack.<br/>
<br/>
Video calling has received several improvements, including a more reliable connection system designed to reduce freezing and dropped calls. WhatsApp says it has optimized its routing system to find the best connection path and improved bandwidth detection to upgrade video quality to HD faster when internet speed allows.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, iPhone users are set to gain some platform-specific features, including the ability to pinch-to-zoom during video calls, and document scanning directly from the attachment menu. As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/27/whatsapp-ios-default-calling-messaging-app/">previously reported</a>, users can also now set WhatsApp as their default call and messaging app on iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, for Channels, WhatsApp is rolling out tools for admins to record and share short video clips up to 60 seconds long, generate unique QR codes for easy channel sharing, and provide transcripts of voice messages for followers who can't listen to audio updates.<br/>
<br/>
Most of these features are now available in the latest stable build of WhatsApp for both iPhone and Android, although some users may need to wait a few weeks as the rollout completes.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/10/whatsapp-new-features-roundup/">WhatsApp Gets Updates to Group Chats, Events, Calls, Channels, More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-gets-updates-to-group-chats-events-calls-channels-more.2455057/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
