<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:00:52 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Blames Apple for Loss of iPhone Volume Button Control of Connected Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-blames-apple-for-loss-of-iphone-volume-button-control-of-connected-devices.2434749/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:58:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify says users on iPhone will no longer be able to control the volume of connected devices using their physical volume buttons after Apple "<a href="https://support.spotify.com/us/article/spotify-connect/?ref=related">discontinued</a>" the technology that enables the functionality. The change impacts Spotify Connect, a feature that allows users to control Spotify playback on various devices like speakers, game consoles, and smart TVs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-vs-Spotify-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801789" /><br/>
The streaming giant claims that the previous method had become unstable, leading to issues such as volume spikes during playback. As a result, iPhone users will now have to resort to an in-app slider to adjust volume, a change that Spotify is calling a "workaround," reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/29/24231516/spotify-apple-physical-iphone-volume-controls">The Verge</a></em>.  <br/>
<br/>
To use the new volume control, iPhone owners will need to tap a notification that appears when they press the physical volume buttons. This notification will prompt them to use the in-app slider. Spotify claims that the new solution will provide "persistent, high-quality" volume control, despite the extra steps involved for users. The change is set to take effect on September 3, but some users are <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/alexa/comments/1d7whh9/no_more_volume_control_via_iphone_buttons_when/">reportedly already seeing it</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Spotify claims that Apple is refusing to grant access to the same technology that allows Apple Music to play on third-party devices. In a continuation of long-held tensions between the two companies, the streaming service has gone as far as suggesting that this could violate the EU's Digital Markets Act, which requires major platforms to open up to third-party services.<br/>
<br/>
"We've made requests to Apple to introduce a similar solution to what they offer users on HomePod and Apple TV for app developers who control non-Apple media devices," Spotify said in its update. "Apple has told us that they require apps to integrate into HomePod in order to access the technology that controls volume on iPhones."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/spotify_connected_devices_volume.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1093" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963142" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Spotify's volume control workaround for Spotify Connect</em></div><br/>
Apple actually offers an API for third-party music services to stream directly to HomePods, but for whatever reason Spotify has chosen not to implement it. Fortunately, iPhone users running iOS 17 can still start an AirPlay session on HomePod using a Siri command (e.g. "Siri, play Fleetwood Mac on Spotify"). It's worth noting that this change only affects Spotify Connect on iOS. Spotify users controlling volume via Bluetooth or AirPlay will not be impacted.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/">Spotify Blames Apple for Loss of iPhone Volume Button Control of Connected Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-blames-apple-for-loss-of-iphone-volume-button-control-of-connected-devices.2434749/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Are Apple&#039;s Oldest Products Still Sold Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-apples-oldest-products-still-sold-today.2434708/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:49:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For over two decades, the <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/">MacRumors Buyer's Guide</a> has served as a valuable resource for keeping track of when Apple products were last updated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/AirPods-Max-1360-Days-Old-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963047" /><br/>
Below, we have highlighted five current-generation Apple products that have not received hardware upgrades in several years. We also provide some purchasing recommendations based on both rumors and our own opinions.<br/>
<br/>
This list excludes previous-generation Apple products still sold, such as the iPhone 13, along with various accessories and cables.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pro Display XDR</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/05/Pro-Display-XDR-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-740290" /><br/>
Apple released the Pro Display XDR <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/12/07/apple-releasing-mac-pro-december-10/">in December 2019</a>, so it will be five years old later this year. The high-end monitor starts at &#36;4,999 and features a 32-inch screen size with 6K resolution, but it lacks a built-in camera and speakers.<br/>
<br/>
In December 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/18/updated-pro-display-xdr-gurman/">working on multiple new external monitors</a>, including an updated version of the Pro Display XDR that will be equipped with an Apple silicon chip, just like the Studio Display with the A13 chip. However, it's unclear when the new Pro Display XDR will be released or what other new features it will have.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 4 years and 8 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Given how expensive the Pro Display XDR is, it is worth waiting for the next model at this point. Also consider the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Studio Display</a>, which is over two years newer, more affordable, and has a built-in camera and speakers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/homepod-mini-thumb-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-770560" /><br/>
Released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/apple-announces-homepod-mini/">in November 2020</a>, the HomePod mini is also nearly four years old. The smaller Siri-enabled smart speaker has not received any hardware updates since launching, although it did get Blue, Orange, and Yellow color options in November 2021, and Space Gray was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/">replaced with a virtually-identical Midnight finish</a> a few months ago.<br/>
<br/>
In February 2023, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said mass shipments of a second-generation HomePod mini would begin <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/03/homepod-mini-2-shipping-next-year/">in the second half of 2024</a>, but it is unclear if that info is still accurate, as there have not been any recent HomePod mini rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 3 years and 9 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Given there was a rumor that a new HomePod mini might be released later this year, it might be best to hold off for three to four more months to see if that happens. However, given the HomePod mini is a modest &#36;99, there is not too much harm in purchasing one now if you don't want to wait.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Black-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877635" /><br/>
Released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/airpods-max/">in December 2020</a>, the AirPods Max will turn four years old later this year. Apple's over-ear headphones have not received any hardware updates since, and remain priced at &#36;549 on Apple's online store, with five color options available. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 3 years and 8 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> We recommend waiting for the AirPods Max with a USB-C port to launch later this year, but the headphones will still more or less be four years old beyond that change, so you may wish to consider newer competing options, such as the Sony XM5, Bose QuietComfort Ultra, and Sonos Ace. Amazon does have the AirPods Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/airpods-max-hit-399/">on sale for &#36;399</a> if you are interested in purchasing them now at a discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iPad-mini-6-orange-BG.jpg" alt="" width="1881" height="1058" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816576" /><br/>
Apple released the current iPad mini in September 2021, with new features at the time including a larger 8.3-inch display, a USB-C port, a Touch ID power button, the A15 Bionic chip, 5G support on cellular models, a 12-megapixel rear camera with Center Stage support, compatibility with the second-generation Apple Pencil, and more.<br/>
<br/>
In November 2023, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">said</a> mass production of the next iPad mini would begin in the second half of 2024. More recently, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said inventory of the current iPad mini‌ was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/ipad-mini-stock-dwindling/">starting to dwindle at Apple Stores</a>, which could be a sign that the device will be updated in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/">Rumored features</a> for the next iPad mini include a newer chip, upgraded cameras, Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support, new color options, and a fix for the so-called "jelly scrolling" effect on the current model's display. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 2 years and 11 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> At this point, we suggest waiting for the new iPad mini that is rumored to launch later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 3</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airpods-3-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953897" /><br/>
Released in October 2021, the third-generation AirPods are nearly three years old.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">Two new fourth-generation AirPods models</a> are expected to be unveiled at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">Apple's special event on September 9</a>, with both options rumored to feature a tweaked design with better fit in the ear, improved sound quality, and an updated charging case with a USB-C port. The higher-end AirPods 4 are also said to feature active noise cancellation, and a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for Find My location tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 2 years and 10 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Do not buy! Apple is expected to announce the fourth-generation AirPods in less than two weeks.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/">These Are Apple&#039;s Oldest Products Still Sold Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-apples-oldest-products-still-sold-today.2434708/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly in Talks to Invest in ChatGPT Maker OpenAI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-chatgpt-maker-openai.2434707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:52:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		<category>The Wall Street Journal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in talks to invest in artificial intelligence company OpenAI, according to sources cited by <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/openai-apple-funding-chatgpt-50754cd6"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-ChatGPT.jpg" alt="" width="1825" height="1027" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960667" /><br/>
The report did not indicate how much money Apple would be investing in OpenAI, or provide any additional details about the discussions, but it said this latest fundraising round would value the ChatGPT maker above &#36;100 billion. <br/>
<br/>
Apple previously announced that ChatGPT integration is coming to Siri on iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/">before the end of the year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
With user permission, Siri will be able to show ChatGPT answers directly in response to questions and other prompts. ChatGPT will also be an option for Apple's system-wide Writing Tools feature, allowing users to generate text and images. Apple said ChatGPT will be powered by OpenAI's latest GPT-4o model on its platforms.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone, iPad, and Mac users will be able to use ChatGPT for free, without creating an account, and ChatGPT Plus subscribers will be able to connect their accounts to access paid features on these devices. Apple said OpenAI will not store ChatGPT requests made from its devices, and it said users' IP addresses will be obscured.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features started rolling out to developers for testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">in the iOS 18.1 beta last month</a>, but ChatGPT integration is not available yet.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features require an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, or a Mac or iPad equipped with an M1 chip or newer. The device's language must be set to U.S. English, with support for additional languages to roll out over the next year.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft is also planning to further invest in OpenAI, the report said.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-wall-street-journal/">The Wall Street Journal</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/">Apple Reportedly in Talks to Invest in ChatGPT Maker OpenAI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-chatgpt-maker-openai.2434707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Labor Day Sales Include Year&#039;s Best Prices on iPads, MacBooks, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-labor-day-sales-include-years-best-prices-on-ipads-macbooks-and-more.2434700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:47:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we head into the long weekend ending with Labor Day on Monday, a number of retailers have introduced deals that should be advantageous for anyone shopping around for Apple products and related accessories. In this article we've rounded up some of the best Labor Day deals for Apple devices, also including discounts on charging accessories, headphones, speakers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/Labor-Day-Deals-Feature0011.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-860632" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/airpods-max-blue-image.png" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-857001" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods Max for &#36;399.00 in every color this week, down from &#36;549.00. This is nearly a match of the all-time low price on the headphones, just &#36;5 higher than that Prime Day deal we saw in July.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/ipad-blue-image.png" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-857000" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon recently introduced a new all-time low price on Apple's 9th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, available for just &#36;199.00, down from &#36;329.00. This sale beats the previous low price by about &#36;30, and it's available in both colors right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888416" /><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;379.99 this week on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This is a match for the record low price on the tablet, and right now we're only tracking it on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/macbook-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905733" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want a cheaper MacBook model, Best Buy has Apple's 2022 M2 MacBook Air starting at just &#36;799.00 this week. This is a match for the all-time low price on the notebook, and you'll find <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matching deals at Amazon</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmYZCN2uvXB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmYZD1hiHc0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
<br/>
For newer models, Amazon has every 15-inch M3 MacBook Air on sale right now, available from &#36;1,049.00 and reaching &#36;250 off.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><h2>Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/studio-display-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963033" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.00, which is a match of the all-time low price on the monitor. This is the standard glass version of the Studio Display with the tilt adjustable stand, and Amazon also has a few other models on sale as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><h2>iMac</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/imac-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883127" /><br/>
<br/>
Record low prices hit Apple's newest iMacs this week, starting at &#36;1,099.99 for the 8-core/256GB model, down from &#36;1,299.00. You'll also find the 10-core/256GB and 10-core/512GB model on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5BFRND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;199 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-core/256GB) for &#36;1,099.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/256GB) for &#36;1,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KBG3M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;199 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/512GB) for &#36;1,499.99</div></a></div><h2>Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a> - Get up to 20% off select devices</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-15268034?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.sony.com%2Fc%2F1%3Fquery%3D%253Arelevance%253AsnaAllCategories%253A1%253AoffersAndSales%253AOn%2BSale%253AoffersAndSales%253AFree%2Bwith%2BPurchase%26currentPage%3D1">Sony</a> - Save on headphones and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1724942100511">Eufy Security SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1592498&u=63177&m=100061">Casely</a> - BOGO everything sitewide with code BOGO-WEEKEND</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=592602.5&type=3&subid=0">Hyper</a> - Get 20% off select chargers with code POWERUP20</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11803854">OWC</a> - Save on computer accessories sitewide</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=&afftrack=">Satechi</a> - Get 25% off sitewide with code SUMMER25</li></ul> Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/">Best Apple Labor Day Sales Include Year&#039;s Best Prices on iPads, MacBooks, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-labor-day-sales-include-years-best-prices-on-ipads-macbooks-and-more.2434700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sports App to Offer Live Scores and Play-by-Play for More Leagues on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-to-offer-live-scores-and-play-by-play-for-more-leagues-on-iphones-lock-screen.2434699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:28:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-sports-is-ready-for-football-season/">announced</a> several new features and changes coming to its Sports app on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Apple-Sports-to-Offer-Live-Activities-for-All-Leagues-Available-Within-App-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2322" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963060" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 18 and watchOS 11, the Apple Sports app will offer Live Activities for all teams and leagues available in the app, according to Apple. Live Activities provides live scores and play-by-play information at a glance on the iPhone's Lock Screen and in the Dynamic Island on newer models, and on the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added that Live Activities will no longer be available in the Apple TV app with iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the Sports app has also been optimized for the latest NFL and college football seasons. The app now offers "quick access to scoring drives presented alongside the view of every game play," along with a new dynamic drive tracker that "lets fans visualize where the ball is on the field at any time," the press release said. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, Apple said the app will be updated later this year with a new drop-down navigation and enhanced search functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports provides scores and more for the following leagues:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>NFL</li><br/>
<li>NCAAF</li><br/>
<li>MLS</li><br/>
<li>MLB</li><br/>
<li>NBA</li><br/>
<li>WNBA</li><br/>
<li>NCAA basketball (men's and women's)</li><br/>
<li>NHL</li><br/>
<li>NWSL</li><br/>
<li>Premier League</li><br/>
<li>Bundesliga</li><br/>
<li>LaLiga</li><br/>
<li>Liga MX</li><br/>
<li>Ligue 1</li><br/>
<li>Serie A</li></ul>Apple said additional leagues will become available in the app over time, including Champions League and Europa League.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is a free app <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">available in the App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/">Apple Sports App to Offer Live Scores and Play-by-Play for More Leagues on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-to-offer-live-scores-and-play-by-play-for-more-leagues-on-iphones-lock-screen.2434699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will a New Apple TV Still Launch This Year?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-a-new-apple-tv-still-launch-this-year.2434693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 07:41:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been nearly two years since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> last received a hardware upgrade, so you may be wondering when a new model will be released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about the next-generation Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
In January 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reported that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">new Apple TV was on track for release in the first half of 2024</a>:<blockquote>Beyond the future smart displays and new speaker, Apple is working on revamping its TV box. A new version with the current design is in the works for the first half of next year with a faster processor, the people said.</blockquote>The first half of 2024 passed by without a new Apple TV, so that rumor has expired, and there have been no credible rumors about the device since. As such, it is currently unclear when the next Apple TV will be released.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently announced that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">holding a special event on September 9</a>, but the only products firmly rumored to be unveiled then include new iPhones, Apple Watches, and AirPods, with no expectation of a new Apple TV so far.<br/>
<br/>
Here is when the previous five Apple TV models were announced:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>Second-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> April 2021</li><br/>
<li><strong>First-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> September 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple TV HD:</strong> September 2015</li><br/>
<li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV:</strong> March 2012</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Whenever it comes out, the next Apple TV is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">faster processor</a> than the current A15 Bionic chip, and even lower pricing. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo suggested that the next Apple TV <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">could have a sub-&#36;100 starting price</a>. The current Apple TV starts at &#36;129 in the U.S. with 64GB of storage, and a 128GB model is available for &#36;149.<br/>
<br/>
Both the second-generation (2010) and third-generation (2012) models of the Apple TV were priced at &#36;99 in the U.S. at launch, and Apple eventually lowered the price of the third-generation model to &#36;69, so there is precedent for a sub-&#36;100 Apple TV that would better compete with low-priced streaming devices sold by the likes of Amazon and Roku.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes have been rumored for the next Apple TV specifically, but Gurman said Apple has considered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">adding a built-in camera</a> to a future model. tvOS 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-iphone-facetime-camera-apple-tv/">added a FaceTime app to the Apple TV</a>, allowing for users to have video calls by using the rear camera on a connected iPhone or iPad. If the Apple TV gained a built-in camera, users would no longer need to rely on an external device for video calls on the TV.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/">Will a New Apple TV Still Launch This Year?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-a-new-apple-tv-still-launch-this-year.2434693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Not Device Region Locked to US in Latest Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-device-region-locked-to-us-in-latest-betas.2434676/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:20:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/">iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia 15.1 betas</a> no longer requires users to set their device region to the United States, so now it's just the US English language requirement that remains.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-intelligence-symbol.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962975" /><br/>
In previous betas, users not only had to change Siri's language to the US to access Apple Intelligence, but they also had to change both their device region and language to the US as well.<br/>
<br/>
However, as per the latest release notes and spotted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-no-longer-requires-setting-the-device-region-to-the-us/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the requirement to change device region to US appears to have been dropped, which means things like measurement system, temperature, and calendar formatting can remain unchanged with Apple Intelligence enabled.<br/>
<br/>
In other words, users running the third betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia 15.1 only have to ensure that English is their preferred language in Settings ➝ General ➝ Language & Region, and that English (United States) is the set Siri language in Settings ➝ Apple Intelligence & Siri.<br/>
<br/>
With those two settings in place, users outside of the US can opt to join the Apple Intelligence waitlist, which in most cases gets accepted in just a few minutes. Note that Apple Intelligence remains unavailable in China, while users in the EU must still have a device signed in with a US App Store ID.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence encompasses a range of capabilities, including composing text and emails, automating actions across various apps, generating images, summarizing documents and texts, and more. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/">How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You're Outside the US</a></li></ul><br/>
These features require a lot of on-device computing power, so before you do anything, it's worth checking if your device is compatible. iPhone users need either an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max to run Apple Intelligence, while only iPads and Macs powered by M1 or later Apple silicon processors are compatible.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/">Apple Intelligence Not Device Region Locked to US in Latest Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-device-region-locked-to-us-in-latest-betas.2434676/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Next Year&#039;s Upgrade to 12GB RAM Will Be Limited to iPhone 17 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-next-years-upgrade-to-12gb-ram-will-be-limited-to-iphone-17-pro-max.2434654/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 19:51:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a day after a noted leaker on Chinese microblogging site Weibo suggested the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup in 2025 could see an upgrade to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-17-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb/">12GB of RAM across the board</a>, analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has claimed that the upgrade <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1828959136421425493/">will be limited to the iPhone 17 Pro Max</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-17-Pro-Max-Smaller-Dynamic-Island-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949323" /><br/>
If Kuo is correct, it means the smaller &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro, the base &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">all-new iPhone 17 "Slim"</a> will stick with the 8GB figure rumored for the entire <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup this year. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/when-to-expect-iphone-se-4/">fourth-generation iPhone SE</a> expected in early 2025 will reportedly also carry 8GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
The amount of RAM in Apple's devices is currently of increased importance, as Apple has judged that 8GB is the minimum required for the Apple Intelligence features coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, which means only the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and Pro Max of Apple's current phones will support them. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 15 Plus carry only 6GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
While a move to 8GB across the board starting with next month's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup will enable all new iPhones to support Apple Intelligence going forward, a further bump to 12GB would likely allow for even more powerful AI capabilities, but it now appears that may be limited to Apple's highest-end model in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from the increased 12GB of RAM, Kuo says the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro Max will also have an exclusive cooling system combining vapor chamber technology with graphite sheets. The other new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models launching in 2025 will rely solely on graphite sheets for cooling.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/">Kuo: Next Year&#039;s Upgrade to 12GB RAM Will Be Limited to iPhone 17 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-next-years-upgrade-to-12gb-ram-will-be-limited-to-iphone-17-pro-max.2434654/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac OS X Snow Leopard Launched 15 Years Ago Today With &#039;0 New Features&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-launched-15-years-ago-today-with-0-new-features.2434641/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the 15th anniversary of Apple releasing Mac OS X Snow Leopard, which became available to purchase for &#36;29 <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2009/08/24Apple-to-Ship-Mac-OS-X-Snow-Leopard-on-August-28/">on August 28, 2009</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Mac-OS-X-Snow-Leopard-Web-Banner-Large.jpeg" alt="" width="895" height="503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962904" /><br/>
After advertising Mac OS X Leopard as having "over 300 new features" in 2007, Apple previewed Snow Leopard at WWDC 2008. Notably, during that year's "State of the Union" session, Apple showed a presentation slide that said the update had "0 new features," as Apple opted to focus on under-the-hood performance and stability improvements.<br/>
<br/>
"We've built on the success of Leopard and created an even better experience for our users from installation to shutdown," said Apple's former software engineering chief Bertrand Serlet. "Apple engineers have made hundreds of improvements so with Snow Leopard your system is going to feel faster, more responsive and even more reliable than before."<br/>
<br/>
With Snow Leopard, Apple said it refined 90% of the foundational "projects" that were built into Mac OS X. Apple pitched the update as offering a more responsive Finder app, an improved Mail app that loads emails up to twice as fast as before, up to 80% faster Time Machine backups, and a 64-bit version of Safari that was up to 50% faster than the previous version. Snow Leopard also took up around half as much disk space as Leopard.<br/>
<br/>
You can watch Serlet speak more about Snow Leopard at WWDC 2009 below.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FTfChHwGFf0?si=W8T4DNbdZse49D_N" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/">Mac OS X Snow Leopard Launched 15 Years Ago Today With &#039;0 New Features&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-launched-15-years-ago-today-with-0-new-features.2434641/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 202 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2434638/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 14:41:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser that was <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to allow users to test features that are planned for future release versions of the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Safari-Technology-Preview-Updated-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960117" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 202 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, CSS, Editing, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, SVG, Web Animations, Web API, Web Assembly, and WebDriver. <br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta. Set to launch this fall, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; is the newest version of macOS that Apple is working on.  <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a> from Apple's website. Complete release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while it is designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download and use. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 202 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2434638/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats and Verdy Debut Collectible Bear Figure That Holds Your Beats Pill</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/verdy-beats-pill-vear/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-and-verdy-debut-collectible-bear-figure-that-holds-your-beats-pill.2434630/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 13:37:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/verdy-beats-pill-vear/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Beats brand is partnering with Japanese graphic artist Verdy for a <a href="https://shop.complex.com/products/vear-speaker-bundle/">limited edition collectible art figure</a> that doubles as a holder for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">new Beats Pill speaker</a>. The &#36;500 hyper-limited drop includes a matte black Beats Pill and a cream-colored bear named Vear that holds the speaker between its paws.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/beats-pill-vear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962892" /><br/>
Beats has a tradition of fun characters associated with the Beats Pill, including ad campaigns and speaker stands for previous models centered around the Beats Pill Characters or "Dudes" in various colors. Apple <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=icoxLqNQyLo">revived the Dudes</a> for the launch of the updated Beats Pill this year, so the new Vear character fits right into that theme even though it won't be seeing a wide release.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7KGB_wE4Cfg?si=-OsGcrCRrDhO-D5S" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Beats and Verdy also have a history of collaborations, most recently in 2023 for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/29/beats-flex-verdy-heart-charm/">Beats Flex earphones themed around Verdy's Girls Don't Cry brand</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Vear and Beats Pill bundle will be available to order this Friday, August 30, <a href="https://shop.complex.com/products/vear-speaker-bundle/">exclusively through Complex</a>, with shipping following in two to three weeks.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/verdy-beats-pill-vear/">Beats and Verdy Debut Collectible Bear Figure That Holds Your Beats Pill</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-and-verdy-debut-collectible-bear-figure-that-holds-your-beats-pill.2434630/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>See the Apple Intelligence Photos App &#039;Clean Up&#039; Tool in Action</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-clean-up-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/see-the-apple-intelligence-photos-app-clean-up-tool-in-action.2434628/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 13:01:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-clean-up-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the third beta of iOS 18.1, and it adds Clean Up, a new Apple Intelligence tool created for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app. With Clean Up, you can remove unwanted objects from your photos, but its performance is hit or miss right now.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rQZjAPxDLTs" title="Clean Up Your Photos With NEW Apple Intelligence Feature in iOS 18.1 Beta 3" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
When you tap into any of your photos and then tap on the edit button, you'll see a new "Clean Up" tool that has an eraser icon. Tap on that, and if there's something obvious that can be removed from the image, it'll be automatically highlighted.<br/>
<br/>
You can tap on the highlighted object to remove it, and it works like magic. If there isn't something automatically highlighted, don't worry, you can circle or scribble on any object in the photo to use Clean Up on it.<br/>
<br/>
With the automatically highlighted objects, Clean Up works well. Apple has already done all the work in the background to find depth information and to calculate the fill the object should be replaced with. When you're selecting your own objects, it can be a little more difficult to get a clean look.<br/>
<br/>
Clean Up works best when there's a clear, uncluttered background behind the object that you want to remove, and the smaller the object the better. Trying to remove a whole person from the foreground of image (such as in a group shot) with a lot going on in the background doesn't work super well, but it's really more designed for small, unwanted objects in the background of images anyway.<br/>
<br/>
You can go through multiple iterations of Clean Up to try to get it to look better, and to remove small areas, just zoom in and then circle.<br/>
<br/>
Clean Up can't be used on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-photos/">Live Photos</a>, and when you use Clean Up, it turns off &zwnj;Live Photos&zwnj;. You can turn &zwnj;Live Photos&zwnj; back on, but then you lose the Clean Up edit. You also can't use Clean Up on videos, but it does work on all other kinds of images, including screenshots, old photos, and photos you didn't take with your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
For quick edits on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Clean Up works well. It's not on par with some other desktop tools at this time, but Apple will undoubtedly make improvements going forward. Also, when you use Clean Up, a note is added to the metadata that lets you know that an AI edit has been made, so people will be able to see that it's been modified.<br/>
<br/>
All Clean Up edits are reversible, so if you want to get back to your original image, you can revert at any time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Other New Features in iOS 18.1 Beta 3</h2><br/>
Along with Cleanup, iOS 18.1 beta 3 adds a couple of other features. The notification summary feature that was previously working for Mail and Messages now works for all of your apps, so you can see summaries of both multiple incoming messages and single notifications, giving you more information at a glance.<br/>
<br/>
Also, in the Messages app, you can now use third-party stickers in-line like emoji. This was a feature in prior betas, but it only worked with stickers from Apple apps and stickers you created from photos.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-clean-up-hands-on/">See the Apple Intelligence Photos App &#039;Clean Up&#039; Tool in Action</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/see-the-apple-intelligence-photos-app-clean-up-tool-in-action.2434628/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 vs. iOS 18.1: Here&#039;s How the Two Updates Compare</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1-heres-how-the-two-updates-compare.2433249/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 12:59:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As a result of the first Apple Intelligence features being delayed, iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 are currently in beta testing simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Below, we explain the differences between the two upcoming software updates, including new features and estimated release timing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<h3>iOS 18.0</h3><br/>
iOS 18 introduces new customization options for the Home Screen and Control Center, a redesigned Photos app, numerous enhancements to the Messages app, an option to lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Home-Screen.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954462" /><br/>
The highlight of iOS 18 is Apple Intelligence, but the rollout of these artificial intelligence features was pushed back to iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
Read our in-depth <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> to learn more about the update.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iOS 18.1</h3><br/>
The first iOS 18.1 developer beta added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">some Apple Intelligence features</a> for testing, including new writing tools for generating and summarizing text, suggested replies in the Messages app, email summarization, phone call recording and transcribing, and a few others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
The third iOS 18.1 developer beta added a few more Apple Intelligence features, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-beta-3-clean-up/">"Clean Up" tool in the Photos app</a> that "can identify and remove distracting objects in the background of a photo," and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-notification-summaries/">notification summaries for additional apps</a> beyond Mail and Messages.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features that are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">still not available</a> to try include Image Playground for custom-generated images, Genmoji for custom-generated emoji, and several enhancements to Siri, including ChatGPT integration, richer language understanding, deeper per-app controls, on-screen awareness, and personalized context.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Release Timing</h2><br/>
<h3>iOS 18.0</h3><br/>
iOS 18 will likely be released in mid-September, based on the timing of previous major releases:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iOS 17: September 18, 2023</li><br/>
<li>iOS 16: September 12, 2022</li><br/>
<li>iOS 15: September 20, 2021</li><br/>
<li>iOS 14: September 16, 2020</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>iOS 18.1</h3><br/>
iOS 18.1 will likely be released in late October, based on the timing of previous similar updates:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iOS 17.1: October 25, 2023</li><br/>
<li>iOS 16.1: October 24, 2022</li><br/>
<li>iOS 15.1: October 25, 2021</li><br/>
<li>iOS 14.1: October 20, 2020</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Latest Versions</h2><br/>
As of August 28 at 12:55 p.m. Pacific Time, the latest iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 betas are as follows:<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-8-to-developers/">iOS 18 Developer Beta 8</a></li><br/>
<li>iOS 18 Public Beta 5</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/">iOS 18.1 Developer Beta 3</a></li><br/>
<li>iOS 18.1 Public Beta not currently available</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Install Betas</h2><br/>
<h3>Developer Betas</h3><br/>
iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 are both available as developer betas.<br/>
<br/>
To enroll in Apple's developer beta program, visit <a href="https://developer.apple.com/">developer.apple.com</a>, sign in to your Apple ID, and accept the terms and conditions of the Apple Developer Agreement.<br/>
<br/>
Since 2023, installing iOS developer betas no longer requires being enrolled in the Apple Developer Program for &#36;99/year. Anyone with an Apple ID can accept the Apple Developer Agreement and access the betas for free.<br/>
<br/>
After accepting the agreement, open the Settings app on your iPhone and tap General → Software Update → Beta Updates. This is where the iOS 18 and iOS 18.1 developer betas are listed, and you can tap on one to begin the installation process. Note that the iPhone must be signed in to the same Apple ID set up as a developer account.<br/>
<br/>
Due to software bugs and other potential issues, we recommend installing the iOS 18 or iOS 18.1 betas on a secondary iPhone, rather than the device that you use daily. We also highly recommend <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iph3ecf67d29/ios">backing up your iPhone to your Mac</a> before installing beta software on the device, to prevent data loss in the event something goes wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Step-by-step guide:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-18-developer-beta-iphone/">How to Get the iOS 18 Developer Beta on Your iPhone</a><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Public Betas</h3><br/>
iOS 18 is available as a public beta, but iOS 18.1 is not currently.<br/>
<br/>
To enroll in Apple's free public beta program, visit <a href="https://beta.apple.com/">beta.apple.com</a>, sign in to your Apple ID, and accept the terms and conditions. <br/>
<br/>
After signing up, open the Settings app on your iPhone and tap General → Software Update → Beta Updates. This is where the iOS 18 public beta is listed, and you can tap on it to begin the installation process. Note that the iPhone must be signed in to the same Apple ID enrolled in the public beta program.<br/>
<br/>
Due to software bugs and other potential issues, we recommend installing the iOS 18 public beta on a secondary iPhone, rather than the device that you use daily. We also highly recommend <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iph3ecf67d29/ios">backing up your iPhone to your Mac</a> before installing beta software on the device, to prevent data loss in the event something goes wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Step-by-step guide:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-the-ios-18-public-beta/">How to Install the iOS 18 Public Beta</a><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatible iPhones</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17 is:<ul><div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max </li><br/>
</div></ul><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><ul><li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR </li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation or later) </li></ul></div><div style="clear:both;"></div>While the iOS 18.1 beta is currently limited to the iPhone 15 Pro models, the update should be released for all of the iPhones listed above eventually. However, Apple Intelligence features will remain exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro models and newer.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1/">iOS 18 vs. iOS 18.1: Here&#039;s How the Two Updates Compare</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-vs-ios-18-1-heres-how-the-two-updates-compare.2433249/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.1 Beta Now Offers Notification Summaries for All Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-notification-summaries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-beta-now-offers-notification-summaries-for-all-apps.2434619/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:45:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-notification-summaries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the third beta of iOS 18.1, Apple has introduced new Apple Intelligence features for notifications. The notification summarization option that was previously available for the Mail and Messages apps now works with all of your apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/summarize-notification-previews.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962909" /><br/>
After updating to the latest beta, there is an Apple Intelligence setup flow that walks through some of the new features and includes settings for the Summarize Notification Previews section.<br/>
<br/>
During setup, you can opt to summarize all of your notification previews or choose which apps should use the summarization feature. After setup, these preferences can be tweaked in the Summarize Previews of the Settings app under the Notifications heading.<br/>
<br/>
Notification summarization allows Apple Intelligence to glean key details from groups of notifications from an app, making them more succinct so you can see what's important at a glance. From the Settings app:<br/>
<blockquote>Summarize content in direct messages and groups of notifications making them more succinct and easier to read. Summary accuracy may vary based on content.</blockquote><br/>
There are individual toggles to enable or disable summarization on a per-app basis, and it can also be entirely disabled for those who do not want to use the feature.<br/>
<br/>
You will see notification summaries on the Lock Screen, and it is a feature that pairs well with the new Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode.<br/>
<br/>
As with other Apple Intelligence features, notification summarization requires a device that can run Apple Intelligence, aka the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> or Mac with an M-series chip. The functionality is limited to developers who have installed the third beta of iOS 18.1 at the current time, but Apple Intelligence will see a public release later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Today's beta also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-beta-3-clean-up/">adds the Clean Up object removal tool</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-notification-summaries/">iOS 18.1 Beta Now Offers Notification Summaries for All Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-beta-now-offers-notification-summaries-for-all-apps.2434619/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iOS 18.1 Beta Adds &#039;Clean Up&#039; Apple Intelligence Photos Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-beta-3-clean-up/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-18-1-beta-adds-clean-up-apple-intelligence-photos-feature.2434618/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:22:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-beta-3-clean-up/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The third beta of iOS 18.1 that Apple provided to developers today includes a new Apple Intelligence feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app. Clean Up can be used to remove distracting objects from the background of a photo while leaving the subject of the image intact. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Photos-Feature-Chromatic.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961382" /><br/>
The Clean Up tool in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app is able to automatically detect objects in an image that might not be wanted, but users can also tap, circle, or brush over an unwanted object to remove it. <br/>
<br/>
Zooming in on an image can help with using a finger as a brush to remove smaller blemishes and issues with an image, and it is intelligent enough not to remove part of a person even if a person or main subject is selected. <br/>
<br/>
Clean Up works on all images in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; library, including older images and images captured by other devices like a point and shoot camera or a DSLR.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that Clean Up works using multiple machine learning models to detect distractions, determine the where the edges of an object are, and then fill in the area seamlessly to replace the unwanted object, even filling in the object's shadow or reflection.<br/>
<br/>
The update also includes notification summaries for additional apps beyond Messages and Mail.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/ios-18-1-beta-3-clean-up/">New iOS 18.1 Beta Adds &#039;Clean Up&#039; Apple Intelligence Photos Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-18-1-beta-adds-clean-up-apple-intelligence-photos-feature.2434618/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Developer Betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1 and macOS Sequoia 15.1 With Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-developer-betas-of-ios-18-1-ipados-18-1-and-macos-sequoia-15-1-with-apple-intelligence.2434613/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:06:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the third betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 to continue testing Apple Intelligence features. The third betas come two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-2-to-developers/">seeded the second</a> iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960229" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-Intelligence-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
A device capable of supporting Apple Intelligence is required to download the updates, which includes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and Pro Max, Apple silicon iPads, and Apple silicon Macs. The updates can be downloaded from the Settings app on a compatible device, with developers able to choose between the standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>/<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>/&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15 betas or the .1 betas with Apple Intelligence functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools that are available wherever text can be selected and edited, and it can be used for spell checking, fixing grammar, rewriting with a new tone, and summarizing text.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> has a new design with a subtle glow around the display, and there is a Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; feature so you don't have to speak to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can follow along if you stumble over your words, and can maintain context between requests. Safari can summarize articles, and there's a new Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode.<br/>
<br/>
Smart replies are available in Messages and Mail, plus the Mail app surfaces time sensitive messages and puts them at the top of your inbox. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> has a Memory Movie feature for creating slideshows based on text descriptions, and you can record, transcribe, and summarize phone calls. Transcription and summarization are also available for any audio recording.<br/>
<br/>
More on all of the features that are available in the betas right now can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">found in our Apple Intelligence guide</a>. Image Playground, Genmoji, and other new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">have not yet been implemented</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has split Apple Intelligence into a separate set of betas because these features will not be available in the initial launch versions of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;. Apple Intelligence will be available to the public later in the fall after a developer testing period.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Developer Betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1 and macOS Sequoia 15.1 With Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-developer-betas-of-ios-18-1-ipados-18-1-and-macos-sequoia-15-1-with-apple-intelligence.2434613/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Eighth Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-8-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434611/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:05:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-8-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the eighth betas of upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-7-to-developers/">release of the seventh betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;/&zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;‌ Developer Beta setting. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta. The &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; beta track is now separate from the iOS 18.1 and iPadOS 18.1 beta track, with the .1 betas adding support for Apple Intelligence on devices that are able to run the features. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, a set of AI features that are built deeply into the operating system. Apple Intelligence won't be coming until later in the beta testing process, but it includes features for refining and editing writing, generating images and emoji, and most notably, improving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and search. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is gaining a better understanding of natural language, improved contextual awareness, and the personal assistant will integrate with ChatGPT to answer more complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features are limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads with an M-series chip, but there are a number of other features that are coming. Apple is allowing users to rearrange Home screen apps to have open spaces, plus there's a dark mode for app icons and tinting options.<br/>
<br/>
The Control Center is customizable and third-party developers can add controls for their apps, with the Lock Screen Flashlight and Camera icons able to be replaced or removed. Messages is gaining Rich Communication Services support to improve conversations with Android users, the option to schedule texts to be sent later, new text effects, messages over satellite when there's no cellular, and the option to use any emoji for Tapback responses.<br/>
<br/>
There's a dedicated Passwords app for logins, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, and verification codes, and there's now an option to lock and hide apps, which means they can't be opened without secondary <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication even when your phone is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
Safari has a highlights feature that summarizes articles and surfaces key information on websites, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app interface has been overhauled, and there's a new Tap to Cash feature for privately and securely transferring money using Apple Cash. Other features include equation solving and voice memo transcription in Notes, a game mode for improving game performance, and an option to respond to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on AirPods with head gestures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will release &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; to the public this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-8-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Eighth Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434611/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Eighth Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers  [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-8/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-8/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the eighth beta of upcoming an upcoming macOS 15 Sequoia update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-7/">release of the seventh beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which allows you to control your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. You can open and use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, interact with notifications, and drag and drop files between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
There are new options for window tiling, and dragging a window to the edge of the display will suggest a tiled location to make it easier to use multiple apps at once. Apple is adding a Passwords app for managing passwords, Safari can summarize websites, surface key information, and Notes has support for live audio transcription and math equations.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Intelligence features coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will also be available in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, but Apple does not plan to add these until later in the beta testing process. Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools for editing, proofreading, and summarizing text in apps, and an Image Playground allows for AI images to be created from prompts.<br/>
<br/>
Custom emoji or "Genmoji" can be created for any situation and used just like emoji, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting much smarter. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in apps and will better understand requests, especially those made in regard to on-screen content.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-8/">Apple Seeds Eighth Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers  [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Eighth visionOS 2 Beta to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-visionos-2-beta-8/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-visionos-2-beta-to-developers.2434617/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 10:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-visionos-2-beta-8/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the eighth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> update to developers, with the beta coming a week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-seventh-visionos-2-beta-to-developers/">after the seventh beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app on their device, going to the Software Update Section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; is able to take the depth information from 2D photos and turn them into 3D photos using advanced machine learning. Apple says that the feature is meant to add depth to photos to make memories more immersive.<br/>
<br/>
There are new hand gestures for activating the Home View and Control Center, and the Home View is also now customizable with apps able to be rearranged. Travel Mode now includes support for trains, and Guest User profiles are now saved for 30 days so guests don't have to do the setup process every time they try out the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Later in the year, Mac Virtual Display will support higher resolution and larger sized virtual displays, which Apple says will be equivalent to two 4K monitors side by side. With an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> update, the Vision Pro can serve as an &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; receiver, so content from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac can be shared to the headset.<br/>
<br/>
The Mindfulness app can track and respond to breathing patterns using the camera for an improved meditation experience, and the Vision Pro supports Bluetooth mice with &zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-visionos-2-beta-8/">Apple Seeds Eighth visionOS 2 Beta to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-visionos-2-beta-to-developers.2434617/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Eighth Beta of tvOS 18 to Developers  [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-8/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-beta-of-tvos-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434616/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 09:58:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-8/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the eighth beta of the upcoming tvOS 18 refresh to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-7/">the seventh beta came out</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-4k-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953895" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 18 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 adds an InSight feature to the TV app, and it is able to provide real-time information about actors, music, and more in &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ shows and music. Enhanced Dialogue has been refined with machine learning and computational audio so it is better able to boost vocal clarity over background noise and music, plus it is now available on built-in TV speakers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices.<br/>
<br/>
Subtitles will now show up automatically when relevant, such as when the TV's volume is muted, a show or movie is rewound, or when the language of a show doesn't match the device language.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include 21:9 aspect ratio support for projectors, new screen savers and improved controls for swapping screen savers, and support for Live Captions during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls through an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-8/">Apple Seeds Eighth Beta of tvOS 18 to Developers  [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-eighth-beta-of-tvos-18-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2434616/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
