<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 03:03:55 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Gets New Co-Heads in Latest Leadership Shuffle</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-music-gets-new-heads-leadership-shuffle/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-gets-new-co-heads-in-latest-leadership-shuffle.2456223/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 02:41:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-music-gets-new-heads-leadership-shuffle/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making another round of leadership changes across two key divisions ahead of its earnings report on Thursday, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-04-30/apple-aapl-reshuffles-government-affairs-and-music-units-in-latest-changes">Bloomberg</a></em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/apple-park-at-night-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-844497" /><br/>
The company's Apple Music division will now be co-managed by longtime Apple executive Rachel Newman and former TikTok music veteran Ole Obermann. Both will report to Oliver Schusser, who has taken on additional responsibilities over the past year including Apple TV+ and sports initiatives.<br/>
<br/>
The restructuring appears designed to ease Schusser's workload as he continues to oversee the Beats brand and international services while reporting to Eddy Cue, Apple's senior vice president of online services.<br/>
<br/>
On the global affairs front, Apple is adjusting how it manages government relations teams worldwide. The heads of Europe and Asia will now report directly to Lisa Jackson, a former Obama administration official who reports to CEO Tim Cook. Previously, these teams reported to Nick Ammann, vice president of global policy.<br/>
<br/>
Ammann, who still reports to Jackson, will now oversee the India and China government affairs teams. He'll also remain Apple's main liaison with the Trump administration, a role he held during Trump's first presidency.<br/>
<br/>
The reshuffling follows other recent leadership adjustments at Apple, including changes to its retail division, and reorganizations of its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/siri-management-team-overhaul/">Siri</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/apple-robotics-team-leadership-change/">robotics</a> teams.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/apple-music-gets-new-heads-leadership-shuffle/">Apple Music Gets New Co-Heads in Latest Leadership Shuffle</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-gets-new-co-heads-in-latest-leadership-shuffle.2456223/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPlay Security Flaws Impact Third-Party Devices and Unpatched Apple Products</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/airplay-vulnerabilities-third-party-devices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airplay-security-flaws-impact-third-party-devices-and-unpatched-apple-products.2456204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:53:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/airplay-vulnerabilities-third-party-devices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Researchers at cybersecurity firm Oligo today outlined a series of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> vulnerabilities that impact millions of Apple devices (<em>via <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/airborne-airplay-flaws/">Wired</a></em>) and accessories that connect to Apple devices. While Apple has addressed the flaws in security updates that have come out over the last several months, some third-party devices that support &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; remain vulnerable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/AirPlay-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000014" /><br/>
Dubbed "Airborne," the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; vulnerabilities allowed attackers to take control of devices that support &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; to spread malware to other devices on any local device that the infected device connects to. An attacker would need to be on the same Wi-Fi network as the intended victim, putting public Wi-Fi spots, businesses, and other high-traffic areas at more risk.<br/>
<br/>
Oligo researchers said that the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; flaws could lead to "sophisticated attacks related to espionage, ransomware, supply-chain attacks, and more." The vulnerabilities could be used independently or chained together for a "variety of possible attack vectors," such as Remote Code Execution, user interaction bypass, Denial of Service attacks, Man-in-the-Middle attacks, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple worked with Oligo to identify and fix the vulnerabilities. Oligo found 23 separate security flaws, and Apple issued 17 CVEs to address them. Information on each vulnerability is <a href="https://www.oligo.security/blog/airborne">outlined on Oligo's website</a>. Apple also deployed fixes for its &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; SDK for third-party manufacturers.<br/>
<br/>
The same Airborne vulnerabilities also impact <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, which could allow hackers to hijack the automotive computer in a car. This attack vector would require the attacker to be directly in the car and connected to either the car's Bluetooth or an in-car USB port, which makes it unlikely.<br/>
<br/>
Oligo recommends that users upgrade to the latest versions of iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, and visionOS, to protect themselves from these vulnerabilities. Other devices that support &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; may still be vulnerable, so users should take steps like disabling the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; Receiver feature on Macs and restricting &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; to the current user instead of all users.<br/>
<br/>
Oligo CTO Gal Elbaz told <em><a href="https://www.wired.com/story/airborne-airplay-flaws/">Wired</a></em> that there could be tens of millions of third-party &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; devices that are still vulnerable to attack. Because &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; is supported in such a wide variety of devices, there are a lot that will take years to patch--or they will never be patched," he said.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/airplay-vulnerabilities-third-party-devices/">AirPlay Security Flaws Impact Third-Party Devices and Unpatched Apple Products</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airplay-security-flaws-impact-third-party-devices-and-unpatched-apple-products.2456204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta Launches New AI App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/meta-launches-new-ai-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-launches-new-ai-app.2456201/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 15:52:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/meta-launches-new-ai-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Facebook</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Facebook parent company Meta <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2025/04/introducing-meta-ai-app-new-way-access-ai-assistant/">today announced</a> the launch of Meta AI, its first standalone AI app. Meta AI has already been integrated into Instagram, WhatsApp, Messenger, and Facebook, but now it is also available in a dedicated app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/meta-ai-app.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000007" /><br/>
The Meta AI app is built with Llama 4, and Meta says the app is its first step toward building a more personal AI that's designed around voice conversations. After downloading the Meta AI app, Meta AI will ask you personal questions so that it can get to know you, which Meta claims will provide "more helpful" answers. Meta AI is "easy to talk to," and has been created to be "natural to interact with."<br/>
<br/>
The Meta AI voice features can be used in the background while multitasking, so you can use other apps while continuing to speak to the AI. Voice conversations will feel personal, relevant, and conversational in tone. The voice conversation feature is available in the United States, Canada, Australia, and New Zealand as of now.<br/>
<br/>
The app integrates image generation and editing too, both of which can be done through a voice or text conversation with the AI assistant. Llama 4 is able to search the web for finding product recommendations and delving into topics for research, with Meta providing "conversation starters" to inspire searches.<br/>
<br/>
Meta says that it is using its decades of work on personalizing experiences on social media to make Meta AI more personal. It is able to remember facts about you, and it can pick up details based on context. It is also able to draw on information you've already shared on Meta platforms, like your profile and content that you like to engage with to provide more personalized responses.<br/>
<br/>
The new Meta AI app can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/meta-ai/id1558240027">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facebook/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/meta-launches-new-ai-app/">Meta Launches New AI App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-launches-new-ai-app.2456201/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Bird Buddy Debuts New &#039;Wonder Blocks&#039; and &#039;Petal&#039; Products for Getting Up Close to Pollinators</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/bird-buddy-wonder-pollinator-system/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bird-buddy-debuts-new-wonder-blocks-and-petal-products-for-getting-up-close-to-pollinators.2456194/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:05:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/bird-buddy-wonder-pollinator-system/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Bird Buddy, known for its line of camera-equipped bird feeders and accessories, today launched new nature tech products, <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mybirdbuddy/experience-wonder">Wonder Blocks and Petal</a>. The devices are designed to let users attract and view all manner of insects, from butterflies to bees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/wonder-kickstarter.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1246" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000018" /><br/>
Wonder Blocks is a modular system that create an ecosystem for pollinators, and there are several different components that are part of the setup. The system includes smart planters, a hummingbird feeder, a butterfly feeder, a butterfly shelter, a bee habitat, a bee observatory, a stream for providing insects with water, an observation pole, and a frame for holding all of the components. Petal is an AI camera that attaches to the Wonder Blocks setup so that users can watch the pollinators that visit their homes.<br/>
<br/>
The camera, which is equipped with a solar panel, is able to recognize more than 2,000 species of butterflies, bees, birds, and plants in real time, and it can be equipped with either wide or macro lens options. As with the Bird Buddy, camera footage is turned into more viewable snapshots that are viewable in the associated app.<br/>
<br/>
For the Petal camera, footage is turned into "beautifully narrated nature clips." The camera is able to identify creatures, but it can also detect behavior patterns and environmental changes to alert users about nesting or plant stress. It also visualizes biodiversity activity and provides an impact score on the contribution the user is making to their local ecosystem. While the Petal camera can be mounted to the Wonder Blocks setup, it is also possible to mount the cameras anywhere in an existing garden.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/petal-kickstarter.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000019" /><br/>
There are three different versions of the Wonder Blocks available to order. The Wonder Planter is a self-watering planter that has an integrated Bee Habitat that can integrate with a full Wonder Blocks system or work on a standalone basis. The Wonder Blocks are the main modular habitat with an observation pole, feeding stations, and more, while the Wonder Blocks Hero is the full-featured setup with The Frame and multiple cameras.<br/>
<br/>
The Wonder Blocks and Petal have already raised more than &#36;1.2 million on Kickstarter, <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mybirdbuddy/experience-wonder">where the project has launched</a>. The first products are set to launch in June 2026, so only pre-orders <a href="https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mybirdbuddy/experience-wonder">are available right now</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Petal camera alone is &#36;129, while the Petal Duo bundle with wide and macro lenses is &#36;249. The Habitat with no camera is &#36;149, and the Wonder Blocks set with Petal camera is &#36;299. A Hero set with two cameras and extra accessories is also available &#36;499.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/bird-buddy-wonder-pollinator-system/">Bird Buddy Debuts New &#039;Wonder Blocks&#039; and &#039;Petal&#039; Products for Getting Up Close to Pollinators</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/bird-buddy-debuts-new-wonder-blocks-and-petal-products-for-getting-up-close-to-pollinators.2456194/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE 3 Could Get New Display Sizes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-watch-se-3-could-get-new-display-sizes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-3-could-get-new-display-sizes.2456190/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:18:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-watch-se-3-could-get-new-display-sizes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on an updated version of the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, and the displays for the new model have entered production, according to <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/">display analyst Ross Young</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/new-apple-watch-se-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998411" /><br/>
Young says that the new &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; 3 will be available with 1.6-inch and 1.8-inch display sizes, which suggests little in the way of an upgrade over the current &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; models. The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; 2 comes in 40mm and 44mm size options, and Apple could stick with those sizes for the next-generation models.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; has historically been based on an existing Apple Watch model, and the current version is based on the Apple Watch Series 6. Apple could continue with another model based on the Series 6 design, but there are other options. The display sizes could be off somewhat due to rounding issues and Apple could be planning for a larger Series 7 design with 41mm and 45mm sizes, or the new &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; could get an entirely new design.<br/>
<br/>
There were rumors that Apple was working on an &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; with a hard plastic casing in a variety of fun colors, though it's not clear if Apple followed through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/23/plastic-apple-watch-se-in-jeopardy/">with that design plan</a>. If Apple did opt for an SE design that does not follow existing Apple Watch models, it's possible that the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; could have 1.6 and 1.8-inch displays in a smaller, slimmed down chassis that's closer to 38mm and 42mm size options. In this scenario, the next &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; would be smaller than the current &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, but with a larger display area and slimmer bezels for a more modern look.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been marketing the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; as a low-cost option for children, so a smaller &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; 3 seems plausible as it would better fit smaller wrists.<br/>
<br/>
We'll learn more about the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; as its launch approaches. We're expecting the new device to come out in September alongside upgraded Apple Watch Series 11 and Apple Watch Ultra 3 models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-watch-se-3-could-get-new-display-sizes/">Apple Watch SE 3 Could Get New Display Sizes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-3-could-get-new-display-sizes.2456190/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Firefox Browser Gets Tab Groups</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/firefox-browser-gets-tab-groups/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/firefox-browser-gets-tab-groups.2456187/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:01:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/firefox-browser-gets-tab-groups/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Firefox</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mozilla recently updated the Firefox browser to <a href="https://blog.mozilla.org/en/firefox/tab-groups-community/">add support for tab groups</a>, a feature that Firefox users have been wanting for years. According to Mozilla, tab groups have been the most requested idea on the Mozilla Connect community platform, and it was actually the first request that Mozilla received when launching Connect in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/mozilla-firefox-banner-fixed.jpg" alt="" width="1599" height="838" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-811266" /><br/>
With the Firefox tab group implementation, users are able to drag and drop tabs into organized groups and label them by name or color, with groups listed in the right side of the Firefox browser's top menu. Tab groups are available starting with Firefox version 137, and all users will see the feature by May 6.<br/>
<br/>
Safari already supports tab groups, with the option to save a number of open browser tabs into a tab group that can be revisited later. It's helpful for vacation planning, comparison shopping, project research, and other tasks where it's helpful to have multiple tabs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/firefox-tab-groups.png" alt="" width="1137" height="640" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000004" /><br/>
Mozilla is experimenting with smart tab groups, an AI option that suggests names and groups based on the tabs that are open, and that could launch in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Mozilla has instructions on creating and managing tab groups in Firefox <a href="https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/tab-groups">on its website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/firefox/">Firefox</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/firefox-browser-gets-tab-groups/">Firefox Browser Gets Tab Groups</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/firefox-browser-gets-tab-groups.2456187/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches New &#039;Snapshot&#039; Web Page: &#039;Your Favorites, At a Glance&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-snapshot-page/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-snapshot-web-page-your-favorites-at-a-glance.2456184/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:38:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-snapshot-page/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today launched a new page that highlights content from popular music artists, actors, and athletes across three of its biggest services.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/Apple-Snapshot-Page.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000001" /><br/>
The new <a href="https://snapshot.apple.com/">"Snapshot on Apple" page</a> has a scrolling carousel of celebrities, including Billie Eilish, Taylor Swift, Sabrina Carpenter, Kendrick Lamar, Ariana Grande, Brad Pitt, Jennifer Aniston, Brie Larson, Shohei Ohtani, Lionel Messi, Stephen Curry, Serena Williams, and many others. There are also pages for the bands Coldplay and BTS.<br/>
<br/>
Each page includes some basic details about the person or band, and showcases their related content across the Apple Music, Apple TV, and Apple Podcasts apps. For example, Billie Eilish's page highlights her songs in Apple Music, her Apple TV+ documentary from 2021, and her appearances on a variety of podcasts.<br/>
<br/>
"Your favorites, at a glance," the page says. "Discover more about the artists, actors, and athletes you love across Apple."<br/>
<br/>
A tipster alerted us to the page's existence today, and we can confirm that snapshot.apple.com is a new address. Unfortunately, the page currently has a very basic design, with no search functionality. Apple has yet to officially announce the page, and it is unclear how or where the company plans to promote it.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-snapshot-page/">Apple Launches New &#039;Snapshot&#039; Web Page: &#039;Your Favorites, At a Glance&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-snapshot-web-page-your-favorites-at-a-glance.2456184/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Pro Display XDR 2: Rumors, Features, and What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/pro-display-xdr-2-rumors-and-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-pro-display-xdr-2-rumors-features-and-what-to-expect.2456179/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 09:05:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/pro-display-xdr-2-rumors-and-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Pro Display XDR has now been on the market for over five years, and while persistent rumors hint at a second-generation model, surprisingly little definitive information has emerged about Apple's plans for its premier external monitor. Here's everything we know so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Pro-Display-XDR-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-978197" /><br/>
In December 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reported that Apple was developing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/18/updated-pro-display-xdr-gurman/">updated iteration of the Pro Display XDR</a>, this time incorporating an Apple silicon chip, presumably to enable additional functionality. The Studio Display contains an A13 Bionic chip to power its built-in webcam, spatial audio, and always-on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Since the original Pro Display XDR lacks any of these smart capabilities, it stands to reason that its successor could gain a built-in camera, microphone array, high-fidelity speakers, and perhaps even support for new software features like Center Stage video framing, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> for Mac, or automatic color calibration based on ambient lighting conditions.<br/>
<br/>
Hardware improvements are also expected. A second-generation Pro Display XDR could feature a higher refresh rate, Thunderbolt 5 connectivity for faster data throughput, and even a shift to OLED or hybrid OLED/QD-OLED panels. OLED technology would offer significantly better contrast ratios, deeper blacks, and lower power consumption, making it even better at professional color work. <br/>
<br/>
In July 2023, Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/next-pro-display-xdr-rumor-recap/">reaffirmed</a> that Apple was continuing development on several next-generation external monitors, but cautioned that releases were unlikely before late 2024 at the earliest.<br/>
<br/>
In November 2024, a report from Display Supply Chain Consultants analyst Ross Young said that the next Pro Display XDR may adopt the same quantum-dot display technology now seen in the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> models. According to Young, these newer quantum-dot films offer an equal or better color gamut and superior motion performance compared to the older KSF phosphor film used in the current Pro Display XDR and previous &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; models. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/14/m4-macbook-pro-quantum-dot/">Young's report</a> suggested that the Pro Display XDR 2 could boast even more precise color accuracy, faster response times, and better consistency.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/16/pro-display-xdr-2-and-larger-imac-rumors/">Gurman noted</a> that a new Pro Display XDR was currently "less of a priority" for Apple, given its niche market and premium price tag. Nonetheless, he revealed in March that Apple is actively <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/16/apple-working-on-mystery-new-display/">developing a new display</a> codenamed J527, intended to launch alongside a second-generation Studio Display. This mystery monitor could turn out to be the long-awaited Pro Display XDR successor.<br/>
<br/>
Since then, no further leaks about the device have surfaced. While the launch timeline remains uncertain, it is plausible that Apple could unveil the second-generation Pro Display XDR alongside refreshed high-end Macs—particularly a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> model. The current Pro Display XDR was released alongside the 2019 &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj;. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/pro-display-xdr-2-rumors-and-features/">Apple&#039;s Pro Display XDR 2: Rumors, Features, and What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-pro-display-xdr-2-rumors-features-and-what-to-expect.2456179/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get AirPods Pro 2 for Lowest Price of the Year so Far at &#36;169 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/get-airpods-pro-2-169-amazon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-airpods-pro-2-for-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-on-amazon.2456175/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:23:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/get-airpods-pro-2-169-amazon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon kicked off a ton of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/airpods-4-99-99-on-amazon/">steep discounts on Apple products</a> earlier this week, and they include the AirPods Pro 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. Free delivery options provide an estimated delivery date of around May 4, while Prime members should get the headphones sooner in most cases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895407" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to past sales, this is a match of the best price we've tracked so far in 2025 and it's an overall solid second-best price on the AirPods Pro 2. Amazon also has the AirPods 4 available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.99</strong></a> during this sale, an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0D1XD1ZV3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Other Amazon discounts include record low prices on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/11-gen-ipad-50-discounts/">11th generation iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/apple-watch-series-10-299-amazon/">Apple Watch Series 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/amazon-150-off-m4-macbook-air/">M4 MacBook Air</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/">M3 iPad Air</a>. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/get-airpods-pro-2-169-amazon/">Get AirPods Pro 2 for Lowest Price of the Year so Far at &#36;169 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-airpods-pro-2-for-lowest-price-of-the-year-so-far-at-169-on-amazon.2456175/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 18 to Use High Performance Six-Channel Memory, Claims Leaker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/iphone-18-six-channel-memory-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-to-use-high-performance-six-channel-memory-claims-leaker.2456171/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 07:00:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/iphone-18-six-channel-memory-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone 18 lineup will introduce a major leap in memory performance, according to new information shared today by Weibo-based leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PpvMic2B5">Digital Chat Station</a>. Apple is reportedly planning to equip the 2026 models with a high-capacity six-channel LPDDR5X memory configuration, significantly upping the memory bandwidth for future AI features and multitasking.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-ghost-hand.jpg" alt="" width="1785" height="1004" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966100" /><br/>
Expanding the memory bandwidth should enable faster app switching, smoother multitasking, and significantly improved AI capabilities – all areas Apple would likely to heavily invest in as part of its broader Apple Intelligence strategy. Paired with the A20 Pro chip, which will reportedly be built using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/20/iphone-18-a20-chip-2nm-rumor/">TSMC's third-generation 3nm process</a>, the iPhone 18 Pro models would stand to benefit the most.<br/>
<br/>
The Weibo account Digital Chat Station has a decent track record with Apple product rumors, and they have previously shared accurate information about unreleased hardware from the broader semiconductor supply chain. Still, Apple's precise hardware plans could still evolve ahead of the iPhone 18's launch late next year.<br/>
<br/>
Before then, if supply chain shortages can be overcome, the iPhone 17 series is expected to see a move to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">12GB of RAM as standard across all models</a>. That transition is likely to set the stage for the more aggressive hardware upgrades rumored for 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/iphone-18-six-channel-memory-rumor/">iPhone 18 to Use High Performance Six-Channel Memory, Claims Leaker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-to-use-high-performance-six-channel-memory-claims-leaker.2456171/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Gains New Shopping Features With Visual Search and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/chatgpt-gains-new-shopping-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gains-new-shopping-features-with-visual-search-and-more.2456166/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:35:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/chatgpt-gains-new-shopping-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI has <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1916947241086095434">announced</a> several updates to ChatGPT, including a suite of shopping-focused tools that turn the chatbot into a full-featured product discovery and comparison engine. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/chatgpt-logo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998332" /><br/>
The update brings visual search results, personalized recommendations, and improved product filtering to the existing ChatGPT interface. Users can browse and compare products from across the web by simply describing what they're looking for. <br/>
<br/>
Queries like "best 4K monitor under &#36;500" now return cleaner, scrollable product cards complete with images, star ratings, pricing, and summaries pulled from user reviews. Tapping on a product brings up more details, along with a direct link to the retailer's website for purchase.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI says the results are organic and free from advertising or affiliate influence, wherease traditional search engines and shopping aggregators typically prioritize sponsored listings. Product suggestions are tailored based on user preferences, such as budget, style, and category interests, although OpenAI notes that certain personalization features may be restricted in countries with stricter privacy rules, like the UK and EU.<br/>
<br/>
The update also includes a new "Ask about this" button that lets users dig deeper into specific products directly from search results.<br/>
<br/>
The new features are available for all ChatGPT users, including those on the free tier, with no account required to try them. OpenAI says the rollout is global and should be visible across platforms, including web and mobile apps.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Shopping<br><br>We're experimenting with making shopping simpler and faster to find, compare, and buy products in ChatGPT.<br><br>✅ Improved product results<br>✅ Visual product details, pricing, and reviews<br>✅ Direct links to buy<br><br>Product results are chosen independently and are not ads.… <a href="https://t.co/PkZwsTxJUj">pic.twitter.com/PkZwsTxJUj</a></p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1916947243044856255?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 28, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
In addition to the shopping search features, ChatGPT can now include multiple citations for a given response, allowing users to learn more or verify information across more sources. OpenAI says users can also now search faster with trending searches and autocomplete suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, WhatsApp users can now send a message to 1-800-ChatGPT (+1-800-242-8478) to get up-to-date answers and live sports scores.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/chatgpt-gains-new-shopping-features/">ChatGPT Gains New Shopping Features With Visual Search and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gains-new-shopping-features-with-visual-search-and-more.2456166/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Supplier Forecasts Product Shortages in US Amid Tariff Chaos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-supplier-product-shortages-tariff-chaos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-forecasts-product-shortages-in-us-amid-tariff-chaos.2456164/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 05:13:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-supplier-product-shortages-tariff-chaos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supplier Pegatron has warned that U.S. stores could face "empty shelves" within two months due to ongoing uncertainty around tariffs imposed by the Trump administration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series-store.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913490" /><br/>
Pegatron chairman T.H. Tung told <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/americas/trump-tariffs-risk-us-electronics-shortages-taiwans-pegatron-says-2025-04-28/">Reuters</a></em> that the on-again, off-again nature of the levies has created confusion for U.S. retailers and disrupted supply chain decisions.<br/>
<br/>
"Within two months, shelves in the United States might resemble those in third-world countries, where people visit department stores and markets only to find empty shelves, all because everyone is waiting and seeing," Tung said.<br/>
<br/>
The Taiwan-based manufacturer, which assembles MacBooks, iPads, and Apple Watches, explained that U.S. importers are hesitant to ramp up shipments during the current tariff pause because they're uncertain whether the 10% levy might eventually be repealed.<br/>
<br/>
This comes after the Trump administration recently paused some tariffs targeting countries where Pegatron has manufacturing bases, including Vietnam, Indonesia, and India. However, a 10% levy on nearly all goods imported into the U.S. remains in effect.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the challenges, Tung said that Pegatron won't alter its long-term manufacturing plans based on short-term tariff fluctuations.<br/>
<br/>
"Just because Trump raises tariffs doesn't mean the rest of the world will do the same. Taiwanese contract manufacturers are sticking to their overseas plans," he said. "We won't immediately adjust our long-term plans just because of two or three months of tariff changes."<br/>
<br/>
Last week, Apple CEO Tim Cook <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/17/tim-cook-trump-apple-tariff-exemption/">reportedly</a> had a phone call with Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick to explain how tariffs would cause iPhone prices to increase. Cook's efforts appeared to pay off when the Trump administration <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/12/apple-tariff-exemptions/">exempted</a> iPhones, Macs, Apple Watches, iPads, and other electronics from the bulk of tariffs on Chinese goods.<br/>
<br/>
However, the exemption may only be temporary. The day after the announcement, Trump stated that there was "no tariff exception" and that no one would be "getting off the hook," suggesting that Apple and other tech companies will be "moving to a different tariff bucket."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been diversifying its manufacturing locations away from China since Trump's first term, and has recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/25/apple-source-us-bound-iphones-india-2026/">ramped up plans</a> to build out its iPhone manufacturing base in India and manufacture U.S.-bound devices in the country by the end of 2026.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/apple-supplier-product-shortages-tariff-chaos/">Apple Supplier Forecasts Product Shortages in US Amid Tariff Chaos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-supplier-forecasts-product-shortages-in-us-amid-tariff-chaos.2456164/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All iPhone 17 Models Again Rumored to Feature 12GB of RAM</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/all-iphone-17-models-feature-12gb-of-ram/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-17-models-again-rumored-to-feature-12gb-of-ram.2456153/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 03:36:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/all-iphone-17-models-feature-12gb-of-ram/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All upcoming iPhone 17 models will come equipped with 12GB of RAM to support Apple Intelligence, according to the Weibo-based leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PpvMic2B5">Digital Chat Station</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-on-Desk-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998158" /><br/>
The claim from the Chinese leaker, who has sources within Apple's supply chain, comes a few days after industry analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said that the iPhone 17 Air, iPhone 17 Pro, and iPhone 17 Pro Max will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">all be equipped with 12GB of RAM</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo also said even the base-model iPhone 17 could be equipped with 12GB of RAM, but it will depend on whether supply chain shortages can be overcome. He said that Apple will make a final decision on the amount of RAM it will offer in the regular iPhone 17 model by May. Even if the base-model iPhone 17 sticks with 8GB of RAM, Kuo said he expects all models in next year's iPhone 18 lineup to have 12GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/all-iphone-16-models-have-8gb-ram/">all iPhone 16 models come with 8GB of RAM</a>, so going to 12GB would be a major increase. More RAM enables larger and more capable AI models to run locally, improving the speed, responsiveness, and complexity of tasks without relying heavily on cloud services. A fifty percent increase in allocable RAM would also allow for smoother multitasking, with AI processes operating in the background without slowing down active apps. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release the iPhone 17 lineup around its usual September timeframe. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/29/all-iphone-17-models-feature-12gb-of-ram/">All iPhone 17 Models Again Rumored to Feature 12GB of RAM</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-17-models-again-rumored-to-feature-12gb-of-ram.2456153/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>It&#039;s Been 22 Years Since Apple Launched the iTunes Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/itunes-store-22-year-anniversary/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/its-been-22-years-since-apple-launched-the-itunes-store.2456135/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 15:53:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/itunes-store-22-year-anniversary/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iTunes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On April 28, 2003, Apple introduced the iTunes Store, its iconic digital marketplace for downloading music. 22 years later, most of us don't purchase songs and albums individually anymore, and the iTunes Store doesn't exist as it once did, but played a major role in Apple history.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iTunes-22nd-Anniversary-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999938" /><br/>
<h2>Early Years</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2003/04/28/new-ipods-new-apple-music-service-itunes-4/">When it launched</a>, the iTunes Store was only for the Mac, but it expanded to Windows PCs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2003/10/16/apple-releases-itunes-windows-and-more/">before the end of 2003</a>. It was a one-stop shop for music that could be loaded onto an iPod, and Apple CEO Steve Jobs inked deals with a number of different record labels to get it up and running.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2003/05/01/itunes-music-store-a-success/">the first 18 hours</a> following the launch of the iTunes Store, Apple sold ~275,000 tracks, with songs priced at &#36;0.99 at the time. Less than a week after launch, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2003/05/05/one-million-tunes-sold/">sold 1 million songs</a>, and at the two week mark, Apple was at 2 million songs sold.<br/>
<br/>
By 2008, five years after the iTunes Store launched, Apple's iTunes Store was the biggest music vendor in the United States. In 2010, it was the largest music seller in the world, bringing in over a billion dollars.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pricing</h2><br/>
The iTunes Store sold songs for &#36;0.99 in the United States, though some were more expensive at &#36;1.29. Albums were priced at &#36;9.99 by default, but distributors were able to set higher prices. Apple regularly offered iTunes promotions, including weekly free songs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beyond Music</h2><br/>
Before the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> launched in 2008, the iTunes Store also housed apps, plus it was home to digital books before the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ibooks/">iBooks</a> Store. Apple also used the iTunes Store for distributing podcasts, TV shows, and movies.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Rise of Streaming Music</h2><br/>
In the 2010s, interest in streaming music started to pick up, cutting into music purchases. Streaming services like Rhapsody, Yahoo Music, and Pandora launched earlier in the decade, but more people became interested in streaming music when Spotify launched in the United States in 2011.<br/>
<br/>
Beats Music launched in 2014, and was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/05/28/apple-buys-beats/">quickly purchased by Apple</a> when Apple acquired the Beats brand. Apple ended up turning Beats Music <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/06/08/apple-announces-apple-music-streaming-music-service/">into Apple Music</a>, a Spotify competitor that launched on June 30, 2015. By 2016, just 24 percent of the music industry's revenue came from digital music sales, with streaming services bringing in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/03/30/us-music-industry-revenue-growth-streaming-music/">over 50 percent</a> of total revenue.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The iTunes Store Today</h2><br/>
You'll still find the iTunes Store app on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but it's a little harder to find on the Mac. It's available as a dedicated section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app for those who still purchase music.<br/>
<br/>
TV shows and movies were split out into the TV app, while podcasts were split into the Podcasts app as part of changes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/05/apple-itunes-changes-macos-catalina/">made in macOS Catalina</a> back in 2019. The Windows version of the iTunes Store stuck around longer, but in 2024, Apple launched dedicated &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and Apple Devices apps for Windows users to replace iTunes.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itunes/">iTunes</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-apps.2">Mac Apps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/itunes-store-22-year-anniversary/">It&#039;s Been 22 Years Since Apple Launched the iTunes Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/its-been-22-years-since-apple-launched-the-itunes-store.2456135/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17&#039;s Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display Coating Canceled</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/iphone-17-anti-reflective-coating-canceled/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17s-scratch-resistant-anti-reflective-display-coating-canceled.2456125/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:48:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/iphone-17-anti-reflective-coating-canceled/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple may have canceled the super scratch resistant anti-reflective display coating that it planned to use for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> models, according to a source with reliable information that spoke to <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-display.jpg" alt="" width="1780" height="1001" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965160" /><br/>
Last spring, Weibo leaker Instant Digital suggested Apple was working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">new anti-reflective display layer</a> that was more scratch resistant than the Ceramic Shield. We haven't heard anything else about an upgraded display coating since then, and it's sounding like that's because it didn't work out.<br/>
<br/>
Apple planned to use the anti-reflective coating for the higher-end &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max models, which would have made them the first iPhones with an anti-reflective display. Apple ran into problems scaling up the display coating process, and it is currently no longer a planned feature for the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
The process for adding the anti-reflective coating to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> display was too slow when taking into account the millions of devices that Apple produces, so even though it was only planned for the Pro models, it still seems that it wasn't feasible this year.<br/>
<br/>
Current &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models have a fingerprint-resistant oleophobic coating, but Apple hasn't focused heavily on anti-reflective technology. For the Mac and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, Apple offers a nano-texture display that cuts down on glare, but that's not something that has been expanded to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. It's possible Apple pivoted to nano-texture or a simpler coating, but it's also possible it's just been scrapped entirely for now.<br/>
<br/>
With the Galaxy S24 Ultra, Samsung debuted a Gorilla Glass Armor display panel, which cuts down on reflections by up to 75 percent. The technology improves contrast in bright lighting conditions and makes colors seem more true to life even in the sun or in rooms with bright lights.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-15-galaxy-s24-ultra-corning-glass.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941959" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Anti-reflection properties of Galaxy S24 Ultra (bottom) vs. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> (Image: <a href="https://x.com/UniverseIce/status/1749261102310199416?s=20">IceUniverse</a>)</em></div><br/>
If the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> models don't end up with the planned anti-reflective display properties, Apple could introduce the display improvement in a future &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as the manufacturing process improves.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/iphone-17-anti-reflective-coating-canceled/">iPhone 17&#039;s Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display Coating Canceled</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17s-scratch-resistant-anti-reflective-display-coating-canceled.2456125/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Record Low Prices Arrive for M3 iPad Air on Amazon at &#36;100 Off Nearly Every Model</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-record-low-prices-arrive-for-m3-ipad-air-on-amazon-at-100-off-nearly-every-model.2456123/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 12:18:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is kicking off the week with discounts across the entire M3 iPad Air lineup, offering &#36;100 off these tablets. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M3 iPad Air, down from &#36;599.00. Across the board, these are all new all-time low prices on the M3 iPad Air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/m3-ipad-air-spring-sale.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996418" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Every deal has been automatically applied and does not require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final sale price. We've rounded up every discount available on Amazon in the lists below, and they include both 11-inch and 13-inch models. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>11-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our list below focuses on Wi-Fi models, but you'll also find many cellular models on sale at &#36;100 off right now. The 128GB cellular 11-inch iPad Air is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ73LCP8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;649.00</strong></a> and the 128GB cellular 13-inch iPad Air is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ754K11%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a>, both &#36;100 discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74YQ1V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ76RM7P%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ7466KC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74CF3K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>13-inch M3 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ749BQ2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">128GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;699.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ75R957%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;799.00, down from &#36;899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZ74RTQD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
Amazon is offering similarly major discounts on other Apple devices this week, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/airpods-4-99-99-on-amazon/">AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/11-gen-ipad-50-discounts/">11th generation iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/27/apple-watch-series-10-299-amazon/">Apple Watch Series 10</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/amazon-150-off-m4-macbook-air/">M4 MacBook Air</a>. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/m3-ipad-air-at-100-off/">New Record Low Prices Arrive for M3 iPad Air on Amazon at &#36;100 Off Nearly Every Model</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-record-low-prices-arrive-for-m3-ipad-air-on-amazon-at-100-off-nearly-every-model.2456123/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of visionOS 2.5, tvOS 18.5, and watchOS 11.5</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-watchos-11-5-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-visionos-2-5-tvos-18-5-and-watchos-11-5.2456107/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:10:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-watchos-11-5-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the fourth betas of upcoming visionOS 2.5, tvOS 18.5, and watchOS 11.5 updates for testing purposes. The software is available a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/21/third-betas-visionos-2-5-tvos-18-5-watchos-11-5/">seeded the third betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/General-visionOS-watchOS-and-tvOS-Betas-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999927" /><br/>
The betas are available to registered developers, and can be downloaded from the Settings app on each device.<br/>
<br/>
No notable new features have been found in any of the software updates so far, suggesting Apple is focusing on under-the-hood performance improvements and bug fixes.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-watchos-11-5-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of visionOS 2.5, tvOS 18.5, and watchOS 11.5</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-visionos-2-5-tvos-18-5-and-watchos-11-5.2456107/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sequoia 15.5 [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-5-update-public-beta-available.2456106/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:06:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.5 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/21/macos-sequoia-15-5-beta-3-developers/">released the third</a> &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961501" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macOS-Sequoia-Night-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.5 appears to be a minor update so far, and no notable new features were found in the first three betas.<br/>
<br/>
Work on new features for &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; is winding down, as Apple will soon transition to macOS 16. The next-generation version of macOS is set to be unveiled at WWDC in June.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-5/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sequoia 15.5 [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-5-update-public-beta-available.2456106/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of iOS 18.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-5-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-ios-18-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2456104/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 10:04:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-5-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth betas of upcoming iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple released the third betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-997322" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iOS-18.5-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5 can be downloaded from the Settings app on a compatible device by going to General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
So far, iOS 18.5 and iPadOS 18.5 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-5-beta-features/">are relatively minor updates</a>, introducing just a few new design changes. There are more options for reverting the Mail app back to the prior design, including removing contact photos, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a> info is easier to find. The update also likely has bug fixes and performance improvements that are less obvious.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is transitioning to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> and iPadOS 19, which are set to be previewed in June at the Worldwide Developers Conference.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-5-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of iOS 18.5 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-ios-18-5-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2456104/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Creative With Sound by Layering Tracks in Voice Memos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/layer-tracks-voice-memos-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-creative-with-sound-by-layering-tracks-in-voice-memos.2456100/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 09:01:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/layer-tracks-voice-memos-iphone&#038;post_date=1745866877/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max, the Voice Memos app includes a recording feature that lets you record a second audio layer – like vocals, narration, or an extra instrument – over an existing memo, all without needing headphones. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/voice-memos-multitrack.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965867" /><br/>
Thanks to the A18 Pro chip's advanced audio processing, iPhone 16 Pro models can play an original Voice Memo recording through the speakers while simultaneously isolating and capturing new audio cleanly. Whether you're capturing a quick harmony, adding context to a saved memo, or simply experimenting with sound, layering recordings like this offers a seamless way to capture richer ideas.<br/>
<br/>
Once finished, layered recordings can be edited, separated, and fine-tuned directly on the iPhone or easily transferred to apps like Logic Pro for more advanced mixing. For musicians, podcasters, or anyone who regularly records voice notes, it's a bit like having a mini studio setup right in your pocket. Here's how to make your first layered recording.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Add a Second Layer to a Recording</h2><br/>
<ol><li>Open the Voice Memos app (in the Utilities folder) on your iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the recording you want to add a vocal layer to, then tap the <strong>waveform icon</strong> to view the waveform.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the plus (<strong>+</strong>) button.</li><br/>
<li>When you're ready to record the second layer, tap the red <strong>record button</strong>.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/add-second-layer-voice-memos.jpg" alt="voice memos" width="4170" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999918" /><br/>
<br/>
The recording will appear in Voice Memos' list of recordings with a layered symbol (two overlapping tiles) next to it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mix the Layers</h2><br/>
While viewing the waveform, you can easily mix the layers by tapping the settings button in the top-left corner and dragging the <strong>Layer Mix</strong> slider. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/mix-layers-voice-memos.jpg" alt="voice-memos" width="2760" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999920" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Separate the Layers</h2><br/>
You can also separate the two layers to edit or play them separately: Simply tap the <strong>More</strong> button (three encircled dots) in the top-right corner, then tap <strong>Separate Layers</strong>. If you then tap <strong>Done</strong>, you'll see the two layers appear as separate recordings in the list. From there, you can select them, edit them, and play them separately. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/separate-layers-voice-memos.jpg" alt="voice memos" width="3030" height="1172" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999921" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Things to Know</h2><br/>
While creating layered recordings is exclusive to the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max, playback is more widely supported. Any device running iOS 18.2, iPadOS 18.2, macOS Sequoia 15.2, or later can play layered recordings without issue.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ios-18-2-layered-voice-memos.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981727" /><br/>
It's worth noting that layered recordings are saved in the QuickTime Audio (QTA) format. Devices on earlier software versions, such as iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, or macOS Sequoia 15.1, won't display layered memos. However, if you separate the layers, each track is converted into an individual .m4a file, making them accessible across older devices. Also, keep in mind that only the original layer can be transcribed or recorded in stereo – additional layers are captured in mono.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/layer-tracks-voice-memos-iphone/">Get Creative With Sound by Layering Tracks in Voice Memos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-creative-with-sound-by-layering-tracks-in-voice-memos.2456100/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
