<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 09:03:52 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Father&#039;s Day Sale Introduces Big Discounts on Arc Ultra Soundbar and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/sonos-fathers-day-sale-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-fathers-day-sale-introduces-big-discounts-on-arc-ultra-soundbar-and-more.2457976/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 07:26:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/sonos-fathers-day-sale-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos has kicked off its <a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/JKo9Pa">Father's Day sale</a>, offering discounts on home audio equipment through the middle of June. This includes discounts on the Sonos Arc Ultra soundbar, Ace headphones, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/sonos-fathers-day-blue.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954109" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale includes Sonos product bundles that should help elevate your home theater setup with various soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers. There are also a few products available outside of a bundle, including the <a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/XmogBa">Sonos Arc Ultra for &#36;899</a> (&#36;100 off), <a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/BneNLL">Sonos Ace headphones for &#36;329</a> (&#36;120 off), and <a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/7aLEvy">Era 100 Smart Speaker for &#36;179</a> (&#36;20 off). <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/JKo9Pa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;250 OFF</div>Sonos Father's Day Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sonos very rarely offers discounts this steep on its website, so it'll likely be quite a long time before these deals return after this sale ends later in June. We've accumulated a few of the devices in the sale below, but be sure to <a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/JKo9Pa">browse this landing page</a> on the Sonos website for everything being discounted.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos Sale</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/XmogBa">Arc Ultra Soundbar</a> - &#36;899, down from &#36;999</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/BneNLL">Ace Headphones</a> - &#36;329, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/4GRz9Z">Move 2 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;336, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/N9o5MK">Beam (Gen 2)</a> - &#36;369, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/MAoPMK">Sub 4</a> - &#36;679, down from &#36;799</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/7aLEvy">Era 100 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;179, down from &#36;199</li><br/>
</ul> <br/>
<h2>Bundles</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/mOrLPX">2x Era 100 Smart Speakers</a> - &#36;358, down from &#36;498</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/LKojMZ">Ray Soundbar + 2x Era 100 Smart Speakers</a> - &#36;557, down from &#36;777</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/xLXeg5">Sonos Ace Headphones + Beam (Gen 2) Soundbar</a> - &#36;698, down from &#36;948</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://sonos.sjv.io/QjzaMA">Sub Mini + 2x Era 100 Smart Speakers</a> - &#36;785, down from &#36;827</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/sonos-fathers-day-sale-2025/">Sonos Father&#039;s Day Sale Introduces Big Discounts on Arc Ultra Soundbar and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-fathers-day-sale-introduces-big-discounts-on-arc-ultra-soundbar-and-more.2457976/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 26 Incoming?, iPhone 17 Pro Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/top-stories-ios-26-incoming/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-26-incoming-iphone-17-pro-rumors-and-more.2457974/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/top-stories-ios-26-incoming/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There was blockbuster news this week regarding Apple's naming conventions, while WhatsApp finally made the jump to iPad after 15 years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/top-stories-2025-05-31.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003524" /><br/>
Other news this week included a report on Apple's now-scaled-back aspirations for providing satellite-based internet service, tidbits on Apple's plans for smart home hubs including one with a robotic arm, and more, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>No iOS 19: Apple Going Straight to iOS 26</h2><br/>
Here's a shocking rumor less than two weeks ahead of WWDC: Apple is reportedly going to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/apple-ios-26/">overhaul the numbering convention it uses for its various operating systems</a>, unifying them all under a "26" branding to represent the upcoming year, much like how car manufacturers typically release their new model years late in the previous year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VL_UcDYm5Gk?si=XPqTL3A8AO9NsQyS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
So say goodbye to what we thought were going to be iOS 19, iPadOS 19, macOS 16, tvOS 19, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3, because it looks like they're all just going to be numbered "26."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro Launching Later This Year With These 12 New Features</h2><br/>
Apple's Pro iPhone models are usually the highlight of the September release cycle, and while they'll have some competition this year from the new ultra-thin "iPhone 17 Air," we're still expecting some very notable changes for Apple's most expensive iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/iPhone-17-Pro-Blue-Feature-Tighter-Crop.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-999328" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-17-pro-rumors-list/">Check out our overview of a dozen significant changes</a> we're expecting in the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max, including some visual changes that will make it immediately obvious if you have Apple's latest iPhone model.<br/>
<br/>
Looking further ahead, a source claims Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/iphone-200-megapixel-camera-rumor/">testing a 200-megapixel camera sensor for the iPhone</a>. That would likely first appear as the Main camera in Pro iPhone models, but it's probably a year or two away.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>WhatsApp for iPad Now Available</h2><br/>
Incredibly, one of the biggest news stories of the week was the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/whatsapp-for-ipad-now-available/">launch of an iPad-optimized version of WhatsApp</a>, more than 15 years after the messaging service debuted. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/whatsapp-teases-ipad-app/">WhatsApp teased the launch</a> early this week, and released the app just a day later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
With WhatsApp now available for iPad, attention is now on Meta's other major app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/08/instagram-ipad-app/">still lacking a native iPad app, Instagram</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pulls Some Features From Rumored Smart Home Robot</h2><br/>
Apple's rumored smart home tabletop robot has been the subject of some intriguing rumors over the past few years, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman says Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/apple-smart-home-hub-setback/">pulling some of the "bolder features" planned for it in order to bring it to market faster</a>. The unspecified features could appear in later models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Apple-Robot-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961758" /><br/>
The tabletop robot will reportedly feature an iPad-like display on a robotic arm that can adjust to remain in view of a person moving about the room, and it would be able to respond to voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
The robot is rumored to follow a simpler smart home hub that Gurman says could launch "by the end of this year at the earliest."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Report: Apple Planned to Offer Starlink-Like Home Internet Service</h2><br/>
A decade ago, Apple reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-planned-home-internet-service/">explored working with Boeing to launch a Starlink-like satellite internet service</a> for Phones and homes, according to <em>The Information</em>. The companies would have launched thousands of satellites into orbit around the Earth to beam internet services down to the surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/Emergency-SOS-via-Satellite-iPhone-YT.jpg" alt="" width="3564" height="1996" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-873000" /><br/>
The project was ultimately nixed over concerns related to cost and Apple's relationship with carriers, and the company ultimately partnered with Globalstar on the much more modest satellite services Apple currently offers on recent iPhone models. Just this week, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/messages-via-satellite-mexico/">expanded Messages and Find My via satellite to Mexico</a>, joining existing coverage in the U.S. and Canada even as the company is reportedly weighing whether it's worth continuing to offer the features as carriers have started to introduce their own satellite services.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 Leak Reveals Apple Tested MacBook Pros With M3 Ultra Chip</h2><br/>
While Apple's highest-end M3 Ultra chip is currently limited to the Mac Studio, it appears that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/23/ios-18-leak-macbook-pro-m3-ultra-chip/">Apple tested the chip in the MacBook Pro as well</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-MacBook-Pro-M4-hero.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-974025" /><br/>
A user on Chinese social media platform BiliBili claims to have found code references to unreleased 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with the M3 Ultra chip in an internal build of iOS 18 running on an iPhone 16 engineering prototype. Apple of course ultimately did not release an M3 Ultra MacBook Pro, potentially over thermal and/or power concerns, but it's interesting to see that Apple apparently tested the chip in that form factor.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sony's New WH-1000XM6 Headphones vs. AirPods Max</h2><br/>
Sony recently came out with a new set of high-end over-ear noise canceling headphones, so we thought we'd compare them to the AirPods Max to see how Sony's 2025 headphones measure up to Apple's headphones that haven't seen a notable update since their 2020 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/sony-xm6-airpods-max.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003520" /><br/>
In one of our latest YouTube videos, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/23/sony-xm6-vs-airpods-max/">Dan takes a look at the two sets of headphones</a>, finding that while the AirPods Max offer some key benefits for the Apple ecosystem, Sony's latest headphones deliver a more comfortable fit and a better overall package.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/may-29-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/31/top-stories-ios-26-incoming/">Top Stories: iOS 26 Incoming?, iPhone 17 Pro Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-26-incoming-iphone-17-pro-rumors-and-more.2457974/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>6 visionOS-Inspired Design Elements Coming to iOS 26</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/ios-26-visionos-inspired-design-elements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-visionos-inspired-design-elements-coming-to-ios-26.2457951/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 15:26:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/ios-26-visionos-inspired-design-elements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-26/">macOS 26</a>, tvOS 26, and watchOS 26, Apple is planning to debut a new design that's been described as taking inspiration from visionOS, the newest operating system. With WWDC coming up soon, we thought we'd take a closer look at visionOS and some of the design details that Apple might adopt based on current rumors and leaked information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/iOS-19-visionOS-UI-Elements.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994345" /><br/>
<h2>1. Translucency</h2><br/>
Inside Apple, the &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; redesign project <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/30/apple-codename-for-ios-19-design/">is known as</a> "Solarium," which gives us some insight into Apple's focus. A solarium is basically an all-glass room that's designed to let in a lot of light.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-files-app-translucency.jpg" alt="" width="1178" height="666" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003681" /><br/>
Since launch, visionOS has had menus and interface elements that are translucent because in an AR/VR environment, people need to be able to see their surroundings as much as possible to feel immersed.<br/>
<br/>
The translucent design elements in visionOS better blend into the background for an unobtrusive look, letting color and light from the real world blend through. It's not hard to picture how this sort of translucent design would work well in apps like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, which we've already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/ios-19-visionos-like-design-rumors/">seen a mockup of</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2. Floating Navigation Bars and Menus</h2><br/>
Floating menus and navigation bars go right along with translucency. In visionOS, everything is essentially floating in the open space around you, whether you're looking at your surroundings through the passthrough camera, or a virtual reality background.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-design.jpeg" alt="" width="1800" height="1012" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935810" /><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, Apple could replicate this effect with shading and shadowing that makes interface elements look slightly raised over the content in the background, for a soft, blurred depth effect.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/spatial-photo-visionos-2.jpg" alt="" width="3825" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-987518" /><br/>
visionOS has a lot of top-aligned toolbars rather than bottom bars, so it's possible we'll see iOS shifting that way too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Rounded Buttons and Interface Elements</h2><br/>
iOS already has rounded squares and rounded rectangles for icons, notifications, menus within apps, search bars, and all of the card-style interfaces that we're used to, but visionOS is even rounder. The floating navigation bars in iOS could be pill-shaped with more starkly rounded edges.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-app-icons.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003684" /><br/>
visionOS also has more dramatic rounding at the corners, and the app icons are fully round. &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; could be rounder in general, more closely matching some of the shapes in visionOS. Leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jon-prosser/">Jon Prosser</a> has claimed that there will be an option <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/07/ios-19-rounder-app-icons-video/">for round app icons</a>, but it's not clear if Apple would want to go in that direction for iOS because Android has long used round app icons. The iconic squircle has been one of many design features distinguishing iOS from Android.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-keynote-app.jpg" alt="" width="1178" height="666" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003683" /><br/>
<h2>4. Glassy Look</h2><br/>
With its translucency, the visionOS interface can look almost like frosted glass. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a> design features a frosted glass rainbow with shifting pastel colors, which is perhaps a hint at plans to adopt a frosted, sea-glass-style look that's not too far off from what we've already got in visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003677" /><br/>
visionOS actually uses a system-designed material that Apple calls glass for app windows. It lets light, virtual content, and objects in the surroundings show through menus and windows. Glass adapts to background color and provides contrast for app content while also taking into account people's physical surroundings. Apple could use a similar material design in &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-glassy-look.jpg" alt="" width="1800" height="1100" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003679" /><br/>
<h2>5. Subtle Lighting Changes</h2><br/>
In visionOS, the translucent interface elements can interact with lighting conditions of the room the user is in. That doesn't translate to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but iOS is apparently going to have some subtle light effects that will emphasize the translucency and glass-like design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/visionos-app-preview.jpg" alt="" width="1470" height="827" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929750" /><br/>
In visionOS, the windows also cast shadows that are responsive to head movements. That's not something that translates to iOS, but lighting and shadow effects that shift when you move your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is a possibility. In fact, Prosser claims there's a glint on the Lock Screen's Flashlight and Camera (or customized) buttons when moving the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-glass.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003682" /><br/>
Apple could use dynamic shadowing in apps and for widgets, and adaptive color could further the effect by allowing interface elements to blend with wallpaper and shift with ambient light.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6. Simplicity</h2><br/>
For the most part, visionOS has a simplified design in Apple apps, with an airier feel due to the spacing that's needed to ensure people have enough room to look at a button to interact with it. &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; could adopt streamlined navigation and menu elements for a less cluttered look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-2-photos-app-design.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1103" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003678" /><br/>
visionOS uses cleaner fonts, bolder text, and increased line height, which may or may not translate to iOS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/visionos-safari.jpg" alt="" width="1178" height="666" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003680" /><br/>
Apple is likely taking a good look at navigation, menu options, and layout, because one of the main aspects of the redesign is more cross-platform cohesion, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/apple-believes-users-love-major-ios-19-redesign/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. He says that &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; will be "simpler to use, faster to navigate, and easier to learn."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Design Consistency</h2><br/>
It's not just &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; that's being overhauled. The visual changes and tweaks to menus, buttons, and navigation will also extend to &zwnj;macOS 26&zwnj;, and of course, iPadOS 26. watchOS 26 and tvOS 26 will see design refreshes, too.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will undoubtedly provide developers with new design guidelines and resources to extend the updated look to third-party apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>WWDC Debut</h2><br/>
The new design that we've been hearing so much about is set to be unveiled at the WWDC keynote event on Monday, June 9. It starts at 10:00 a.m. and while Apple will livestream it, if you can't watch, you can follow along here on MacRumors.com or on our <a href="https://x.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive X account</a>. Apple will provide developers with the new operating system updates complete with redesign after the keynote event, and a public beta will follow in July. &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; and its sister updates will launch to the public in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/ios-26-visionos-inspired-design-elements/">6 visionOS-Inspired Design Elements Coming to iOS 26</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-visionos-inspired-design-elements-coming-to-ios-26.2457951/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 With a Smaller Dynamic Island? Here&#039;s What Rumors Say</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-metalens-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-with-a-smaller-dynamic-island-heres-what-rumors-say.2457944/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:51:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-metalens-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Dynamic Island</category>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[All four iPhone 17 models will adopt metalens technology for Face ID, according to Jeff Pu, an Apple analyst at equity research firm GF Securities. He revealed this information in an investor research note earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-14-Pro-Dynamic-Island.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003664" /><br/>
Earlier this year, a leaker known as Digital Chat Station also claimed that the iPhone 17 Pro Max would adopt a metalens for Face ID that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/13/iphone-17-pro-max-smaller-dynamic-island/">integrates the transmitter and receiver components</a>. They said that this change would reduce the size of some of the Face ID components, resulting in a smaller Dynamic Island on the device.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, Pu also said that the iPhone 17 Pro Max would have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-rumor/">much narrower Dynamic Island</a>, as a result of the metalens. However, he now believes that all of the iPhone 17 models will adopt a metalens, meaning that the change would extend to the base model iPhone 17, the ultra-thin iPhone 17 Air, and the smaller iPhone 17 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
In January, however, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said that he expects the Dynamic Island‌'s size to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/24/iphone-17-no-dynamic-island-change/">remain "largely unchanged"</a> across the ‌iPhone 17‌ series.<br/>
<br/>
All three sources have proven track records of sharing details about future Apple products, so it remains to be seen if the Dynamic Island will change in size.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, next year's iPhone 18 Pro models are rumored to feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/03/iphone-18-pro-under-screen-face-id-rumor/">under-screen Face ID with only a small front camera hole</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-metalens-rumor/">iPhone 17 With a Smaller Dynamic Island? Here&#039;s What Rumors Say</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-with-a-smaller-dynamic-island-heres-what-rumors-say.2457944/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Base Model Now Said to Feature A18 Chip and 8GB of RAM</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-rumored-a18-chip-8gb-ram/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-base-model-now-said-to-feature-a18-chip-and-8gb-of-ram.2457941/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:07:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-rumored-a18-chip-8gb-ram/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The latest rumored specs for the iPhone 17 base model are underwhelming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964610" /><br/>
In a research note with equity research firm GF Securities this month, Apple analyst Jeff Pu said that the lowest-end iPhone 17 model will be equipped with the same A18 chip that is used in the iPhone 16 base model. The chip will continue to be manufactured with TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, known as N3E, he said.<br/>
<br/>
The ultra-thin iPhone 17 Air is expected to have an A19 chip, while the iPhone 17 Pro models are expected to have an A19 Pro chip. Both of those chips are expected to be manufactured with TSMC's third-generation 3nm process, known as N3P.<br/>
<br/>
Pu also expects the iPhone 17 to be equipped with 8GB of RAM, matching the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said the iPhone 17 Air and both iPhone 17 Pro models will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/24/iphone-17-air-12gb-ram-rumor/">all be equipped with an increased 12GB of RAM</a>. He said that Apple was still deciding on 8GB or 12GB of RAM for the iPhone 17 base model at that time, and if Pu's information is accurate, the company has settled on 8GB for the device.<br/>
<br/>
Overall, the base iPhone 17 is shaping up to be a minor upgrade over the equivalent iPhone 16, with both devices <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/video-shows-iphone-17-mockups-internal-documents/">expected to have the same overall design</a>. Key new features that are rumored for the iPhone 17 include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/30/iphone-17-120hz-promotion-display/">120Hz display</a> and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/17/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-more/">24-megapixel front camera</a>, compared to 60Hz and a 12-megapixel front camera on the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
The base iPhone 17 will also feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/iphone-17-display-sizes/">slightly larger 6.3-inch display</a> compared to the 6.1-inch iPhone 16, according to display industry expert Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil the entire iPhone 17 series in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/iphone-17-rumored-a18-chip-8gb-ram/">iPhone 17 Base Model Now Said to Feature A18 Chip and 8GB of RAM</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-base-model-now-said-to-feature-a18-chip-and-8gb-of-ram.2457941/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 16 Pro From Digiarty VideoProc</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/macrumors-giveaway-videoproc-iphone-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-16-pro-from-digiarty-videoproc.2457937/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 10:11:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/macrumors-giveaway-videoproc-iphone-16-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://www.videoproc.com/">Digiarty VideoProc</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and a lifetime license of <a href="https://www.videoproc.com/video-converting-software/">VideoProc Converter AI</a> to go along with it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/videoproc-giveaway.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="637" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003611" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.videoproc.com/campaign/gift-offer-mac.htm">VideoProc Converter AI</a> is an easy-to-use AI-powered tool for working with videos, images, audio, and DVDs. It has a range of different tools for converting file types, fixing files, compressing files, editing, making GIFs, and more. If you want to do something to a video, there's a good chance this software is capable of the task you want to accomplish.<br/>
<br/>
For videos, there is an option to enhance blurry, noisy, grainy or compressed videos to get a better quality result, with the software able to upscale videos by up to 4x and provide better clarity and detail. A stabilization tool can reduce shake in videos, a noise remover cleans up noise in videos, and there are color correction tools for fixing color issues. If you have footage captured by a fisheye lens, there's an option to fix the distortion.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/ai-superresolution-video.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="969" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003612" /><br/>
To fix low frame rates, there's an AI frame interpolation feature that adds in additional frames to make videos smoother, and it can boost videos up to 480 fps for 20x slow motion. For converting video, VideoProc Converter AI uses GPU acceleration for faster video encoding and decoding. Video transcoding and processing can be sped up significantly without impacting the quality of the output.<br/>
<br/>
The app supports 320 video codecs and formats, including popular formats like MP4, HEVC, AVI, MOV, and MKV. Video can be imported from DJI cameras, GoPros, and other digital cameras, plus the app supports log videos from pro cameras, 3D video, and VR video. There are tools for changing video format, resolution, and frames per second, with no loss of quality.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/frame-interpolation-videoproc.jpg" alt="" width="2154" height="1425" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003613" /><br/>
To cut down on file size, there is a Compress tool that supports entering a target file size or using a compression ratio slider. There are seven video compression methods so you can find what works best.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/image-super-resolution-videoproc.jpg" alt="" width="1517" height="914" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003615" /><br/>
VideoProc Converter AI supports video editing, with tools for cutting, trimming, and splitting video. Clips can be merged, cropped, and adjusted with one-click stylized cinematic effects. Audio volume and sync can be adjusted, and you can create slow or fast motion videos with controls to change speed. Watermarks are also an option so you can prevent your content from being stolen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/videoproc-ai-colorize-images.jpg" alt="" width="1644" height="968" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003614" /><br/>
There is a built-in feature for downloading videos from popular social networks like YouTube, TikTok, Facebook, Instagram, and Twitch, in addition to thousands of other websites. You can even record video directly with the app using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or a webcam. When recording, the app supports picture-in-picture, iOS screen recording, and green screen mode, which is useful for filming gameplay videos or tutorials. You can also digitize and back up DVDs.<br/>
<br/>
AI image editing is supported too, so you can also tweak your photos. There are options for upscaling and denoising images, repairing, retouching, and enhancing faces, and adding color to black and white images. With batch processing, over 3,000 photos can be edited at once.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/face-restoration-videoproc.jpg" alt="" width="2152" height="1429" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003616" /><br/>
VideoProc Converter AI works on all Apple silicon Macs. The app is free to try, but unlocking the complete suite of features requires the full version, which is priced at &#36;25.95 for a one-year license or &#36;45.95 for a lifetime license. Digiarty is offering <em>MacRumors</em> readers a <a href="https://www.videoproc.com/campaign/gift-offer-mac.htm">discount on a lifetime license</a>, dropping the price to &#36;30. The license includes access to a 7-in-1 media toolkit, including AI Super Resolution for video upscaling, AI Frame interpolation for slow-motion playback, Image AI for upscaling, restoring, and colorizing, DVD backup, Mac and iOS device screen recording, and audio/image processing.<br/>
<br/>
We have a lifetime license and an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; to give away to one lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/z48Up/videoproc-giveaway" rel="nofollow"><br/>
  VideoProc Giveaway<br/>
</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (May 30) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on June 6. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after June 6 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/macrumors-giveaway-videoproc-iphone-16-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 16 Pro From Digiarty VideoProc</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-16-pro-from-digiarty-videoproc.2457937/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares 2024 App Store Data: Rejections, Removals, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/app-store-2024-transparency-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-2024-app-store-data-rejections-removals-and-more.2457936/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 09:39:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/app-store-2024-transparency-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple published its third annual <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> Transparency Report today [<a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/more-resources/docs/2024-App-Store-Transparency-Report.pdf">PDF</a>], sharing insights into the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; over the course of 2024. The report includes data on the number of apps rejected during the year, the number of customer and developer accounts deactivated, info on how many apps were removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and so on.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Desaturated.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833991" /><br/>
There were 1,961,596 total apps on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; at the end of 2024, up nearly 100,000 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/2023-app-store-transparency-report/">from last year</a>. The &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; sees 839,266,915 average weekly app downloads, and 813,110,348 average weekly visitors to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, with both metrics up compared to 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Apple reviewed 7.77 million app submissions, and rejected 1.93 million of those. Performance, legal, design, business, and safety were the top reasons for rejection, in that order.<br/>
<br/>
Of the 1.93 million submissions that were rejected, 295,109 were approved after developers addressed the issue. Apple removed 82,509 apps from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; during the year, primarily in the Utilities and Games categories. Apps that were removed are broken down by the reason behind the action, with design issues and fraud at the top of the list.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 4.0 -- Design: 42,252</li><br/>
 	<li>DPLA 3.2(f) -- Fraud: 38,315</li><br/>
 	<li>DPLA 6.3 -- Intellectual Property Infringement: 425</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 4.3.0 -- Spam: 294</li><br/>
 	<li>DPLA 4.8 -- Export Control: 285</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 4.1.0 -- Copycats: 128</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 5.6.0 -- Developer Code of Conduct: 99</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 5.0.0 -- General: 89</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 5.2.1 -- Intellectual Property -- General: 77</li><br/>
 	<li>Guideline 3.1.2 -- Subscriptions: 69</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Apple also pulled some apps due to government takedown demands. The majority of government takedown requests came from China, and Apple removed 1,307 apps at China's request. There were 171 apps removed at Russia's request, 79 from South Korea, 55 from Ukraine, and 50 from Jordan.<br/>
<br/>
Apple received 26,224 appeals of app removals, with 6,978 from China and 3,571 from the United States. Only 78 apps in China and 71 apps in the United States were restored after going through Apple's appeal process.<br/>
<br/>
There were 128,961,839 customer accounts terminated, and Apple says it prevented over &#36;2 billion in fraud. Apple also terminated 146,747 developer accounts due to fraud and export control.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has shared &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Transparency Reports since 2023, because it agreed to do so as part of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/26/app-store-changes-developer-lawsuit-settlement/">2021 class action lawsuit settlement</a> with developers. Apple promised to deliver meaningful statistics about the app review process, listing everything from number of apps rejected to info on search queries. More info is <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/more-resources/docs/2024-App-Store-Transparency-Report.pdf">available in the full report</a>, and even more data can be found in the supplemental file <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/more-resources/">available from Apple's legal site</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/app-store-2024-transparency-report/">Apple Shares 2024 App Store Data: Rejections, Removals, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-2024-app-store-data-rejections-removals-and-more.2457936/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Last-Minute WWDC Rumors – &#039;iOS 26&#039; and Games App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/the-macrumors-show-last-minute-wwdc-rumors-ios-26/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-last-minute-wwdc-rumors-–-ios-26-and-games-app.2457931/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:46:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/the-macrumors-show-last-minute-wwdc-rumors-ios-26/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/last-minute-wwdc-rumors-ios-26-and-games-app/id1602394741?i=1000710566315">The MacRumors Show</a>, we talk through Apple's plan to introduce a complete overhaul of the design and naming system for its operating systems at its Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/WUZLnt-D5xo?si=RFlT06wera0Fj1Yd" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Despite the ongoing focus in the industry on generative artificial intelligence, Apple is reportedly planning to debut a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/10/ios-19-macos-16-major-design-update/">complete visual redesign</a> of its platforms as "the highlight of the show" at WWDC. The updated design language includes translucent interface elements and menus that echo the visual style of visionOS. While the new design was rumored for iOS 19, iPadOS 19, and macOS 16, it is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/26/tvos-19-watchos-12-design-changes-rumor/">now expected</a> to extend to tvOS 19 and watchOS 12 too. The changes mark the most comprehensive cross-platform visual update since the introduction of iOS 7 in 2013.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also apparently shifting its software versioning system from sequential numbers to a year-based format, similar to how car manufacturers label vehicle model years. Instead of releasing iOS 19 and macOS 16, Apple will debut <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-26/">macOS 26</a>, along with iPadOS 26, tvOS 26, watchOS 26, and visionOS 26. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/apple-ios-26/">reports</a> that this change is intended to reduce confusion for users and developers by aligning version numbers across platforms and matching them to the upcoming calendar year.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to these design and branding changes, Apple is said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/27/apple-ios-19-gaming-app/">developing a new standalone gaming app</a> that will be introduced at WWDC. The app is intended to replace Game Center and will offer a unified platform for launching games, tracking achievements, social features, viewing leaderboards, and accessing editorial content. The app is purportedly designed to support both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> titles and third-party games currently distributed through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. On macOS, the app will also be able to detect and organize games installed outside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The gaming app represents Apple's most overt emphasis on gaming infrastructure since the launch of &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; in 2019. While Apple has historically treated Game Center as a background service rather than a user-facing platform, this new app appears to be aimed at making game discovery and engagement more prominent across devices. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/23/the-macrumors-show-google-and-openai-step-up-ai/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up to hear our discussion about all of the major announcements from Google's AI-focused I/O conference this week and the mysterious device former Apple design chief Jony Ive is designing at OpenAI.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/18/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-apple-intelligence/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/21/the-macrumors-show-apple-intelligence-mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/the-macrumors-show-last-minute-wwdc-rumors-ios-26/">The MacRumors Show: Last-Minute WWDC Rumors – &#039;iOS 26&#039; and Games App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-last-minute-wwdc-rumors-–-ios-26-and-games-app.2457931/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Show More (or Fewer) Recent Apps in Your Mac&#039;s Dock</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/show-more-recent-apps-macos-dock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/show-more-or-fewer-recent-apps-in-your-macs-dock.2457930/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:42:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/show-more-recent-apps-macos-dock&#038;post_date=1748630542/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In macOS, a handy option called "Show suggested and recent applications in Dock" (found in <strong>System Settings ➝ Desktop & Dock</strong>) adds a divider to the right-hand side of your Mac's Dock, and after it displays any apps you recently used – or any that macOS thinks may be useful to your workflow – that aren't permanently docked. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/show-recent-apps-dock.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003600" /><br/>
Assuming that you have no undocked apps that are currently open, the right side of the divider shows three of the most recently used apps that have since been closed. However, there is a way to make it show more, which can be useful if your workflow involves using a lot of undocked apps consecutively.<br/>
<br/>
If you're comfortable pasting commands into Terminal, it's perfectly possible to increase or decrease the number of recently opened apps that show in your Dock. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/10-recently-opened-apps.jpg" alt="recently opened" width="1190" height="284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-880663" /><br/>
Open a Terminal window (the app can be found in /Applications/Utilities/) and paste the following at the command prompt, then press <strong>Enter</strong>:<br/>
<br/>
<strong>defaults write com.apple.dock show-recents -bool true;<br/>
defaults write com.apple.dock show-recent-count -int 10;<br/>
killall Dock</strong><br/>
<br/>
Note that the <strong>-int</strong> argument defines the number of recently opened apps that you want to display in the Dock after the divider (10 in this example). You can change the number to suit, and you can revert back to showing three apps anytime by using <strong>-int 3</strong> in the second command.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/show-more-recent-apps-macos-dock/">Show More (or Fewer) Recent Apps in Your Mac&#039;s Dock</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/show-more-or-fewer-recent-apps-in-your-macs-dock.2457930/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s What Automakers Told Us About CarPlay Ultra (Not Very Much)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/carplay-ultra-automaker-comments/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-automakers-told-us-about-carplay-ultra-not-very-much.2457929/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:15:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/carplay-ultra-automaker-comments/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">announced the launch of CarPlay Ultra</a>, the long-awaited next-generation version of its in-vehicle software system. CarPlay Ultra is currently limited to luxury Aston Martin vehicles in the U.S. and Canada, but Apple said that many other automakers around the world are working to offer it within the next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/CarPlay-Ultra-Aston-Martin.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001809" /><br/>
We asked more than a dozen automakers about their CarPlay Ultra plans, and we have rounded up their responses below. Unfortunately, but perhaps unsurprisingly, most of the companies had little to nothing to say about their future plans, and they may not want to risk upsetting Apple by divulging information prematurely.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's announcement did reveal that Hyundai, along with its Kia and Genesis brands, are among the automakers that are committed to offering CarPlay Ultra. A spokesperson for Hyundai confirmed that the automaker intends to offer CarPlay Ultra, and it plans to share additional information when possible in the future.<br/>
<br/>
A spokesperson for Volvo said that it was one of the committed automakers included in Apple's list when it first announced next-generation CarPlay <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/apple-announces-multi-display-carplay/">in June 2022</a>. However, the company did not confirm if it still plans to offer CarPlay Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
That original list from 2022 was as follows:<ul><li>Acura</li><br/>
<li>Audi</li><br/>
<li>Ford</li><br/>
<li>Honda</li><br/>
<li>Infiniti</li><br/>
<li>Jaguar</li><br/>
<li>Land Rover</li><br/>
<li>Lincoln</li><br/>
<li>Mercedes-Benz</li><br/>
<li>Nissan</li><br/>
<li>Polestar</li><br/>
<li>Porsche</li><br/>
<li>Renault</li><br/>
<li>Volvo</li></ul>Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed its next-generation CarPlay instrument cluster design</a> in late 2023, but the automaker has not provided an update since then.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
Mercedes-Benz has <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/4/29/24144356/mercedes-benz-ceo-apple-carplay-next-gen-decoder">since expressed a lack of willingness</a> to let Apple essentially take over its software experience, so it may not offer CarPlay Ultra after all.<br/>
<br/>
Porsche and Mercedes-Benz have yet to respond to our inquiries.<br/>
<br/>
Subaru will be assessing CarPlay Ultra for future vehicle models in its lineup, according to a company spokesperson. Mazda offered a vaguer response, with a representative there confirming that the company is always evaluating new technologies to offer the best customer experience, without mentioning CarPlay Ultra specifically.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/gm-further-explains-phasing-out-carplay/">GM ditched CarPlay</a> in its new EVs, so it is hard to see the automaker adopting CarPlay Ultra across its brands like Chevrolet, Buick, GMC, and Cadillac.<br/>
<br/>
A spokesperson for Ford declined to comment, while other automakers like BMW, GM, and Toyota have yet to respond to our inquiries.<br/>
<br/>
A spokesperson for Honda said the automaker was among the first to offer regular CarPlay, as it values the technology and the customer's in-car user experience. However, it had nothing to announce about CarPlay Ultra at this time.<br/>
<br/>
As the title of this article made clear, these responses do not amount to very much. Most automakers offered non-answers, or sideways answers at best, which aligns with Apple's culture of secrecy. But, we wanted to share what we heard.<br/>
<br/>
CarPlay Ultra features deep integration with a vehicle's instrument cluster and systems, built-in Radio and Climate apps, customizable widgets, and more. The interface is tailored to each vehicle model and automaker's identity, and drivers can also adjust the color scheme. To learn more, read <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/15/apples-carplay-ultra-now-available/">our coverage of Apple's announcement</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/carplay-ultra-automaker-comments/">Here&#039;s What Automakers Told Us About CarPlay Ultra (Not Very Much)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-what-automakers-told-us-about-carplay-ultra-not-very-much.2457929/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Max and MacBook Air Get Big Discounts Alongside Our Exclusive Anker Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-30-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-max-and-macbook-air-get-big-discounts-alongside-our-exclusive-anker-sale.2457928/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:04:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-30-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals focused on big discounts at Anker, Woot, and Peacock, along with an ongoing &#36;69 markdown on the AirPods Max and up to &#36;235 off M4 MacBook Air at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Best-Apple-Deals-Feature-Shelf-Purple-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-992236" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/airpods-max-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002695" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;69 off AirPods Max</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJJDFPR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/usb-c-airpods-max-to-479/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJJDFPR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple's USB-C AirPods Max hit &#36;479.99 in multiple colors this week on Amazon, and these deals are still available today.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/m4-macbook-air-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003569" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;235 for M4 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC3WW5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/amazon-m4-macbook-air-low-prices/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDC3WW5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;869.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDB9JTT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;173 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,025.38</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBHQPQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;185 OFF</div>13-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,213.57</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDB168B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;175 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,203.86</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBS1YD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;162 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,236.59</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DZDBQD4K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;235 OFF</div>15-inch M4 MacBook Air (24GB/512GB) for &#36;1,363.44</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has up to &#36;235 off the M4 MacBook Air this week, with both 13-inch and 15-inch models on sale. These prices have been fluctuating a lot over the past few days, so be sure to browse them soon if you're interested.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/anker-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001959" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 20% off sitewide with our exclusive sale</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/anker-macrumors-readers-20-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker is still offering our readers an exclusive 20 percent off this month, and the code works on nearly every accessory sitewide. In order to get this deal, <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">head to Anker's website</a> and add an accessory to your cart, then enter the code <strong>Ankermacrumors2025</strong> at checkout to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/new-braided-loop.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001961" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy one Solo/Braided Loop on sale, get up to two free</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-band-discovery-box-buy-1-get-some-free"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY ONE GET 2 FREE</div>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot's BOGO sale on Apple Watch Solo Loop and Braided Solo Loop bands is still happening this week, but it is poised to finally end later tonight. If enough stock still remains, Woot could extend the sale again, but now is your best chance to buy one Solo/Braided Loop at a huge discount and get up to two bands for free.<br/>
<br/>
For more information on how this sale works, be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/22/woots-new-apple-watch-band-sale/">visit our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Peacock</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/peacock-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002690" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 68% off your first year of Peacock</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.peacocktv.com/">Peacock</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/19/first-year-of-peacock-24-99/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.peacocktv.com/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">68% OFF</div>Peacock for &#36;24.99/Year</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Peacock recently introduced one of its best offers so far in 2025, allowing new subscribers a chance to get a full year of the premium plan for &#36;24.99, down from &#36;79.99. You can read more about how to claim this offer in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/19/first-year-of-peacock-24-99/">our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-30-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: AirPods Max and MacBook Air Get Big Discounts Alongside Our Exclusive Anker Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-airpods-max-and-macbook-air-get-big-discounts-alongside-our-exclusive-anker-sale.2457928/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Filmmakers Used 20 iPhones at Once to Shoot &#039;28 Years Later&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/filmmakers-used-20-iphones-to-shoot-28-years-later/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/filmmakers-used-20-iphones-at-once-to-shoot-28-years-later.2457927/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 07:27:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/filmmakers-used-20-iphones-to-shoot-28-years-later/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Shot on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sony today provided a closer look at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> rigs used to shoot the upcoming post-apocalyptic British horror movie "28 Years Later" (via <em><a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/28-years-later-danny-boyle-goes-big-with-horror-sequel-widescreen-the-infected">IGN</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/28-years-later-iphone-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1003517" /><br/>
With a budget of &#36;75 million, Danny Boyle's 28 Years Later will become the first major blockbuster movie to be shot on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. 28 Years Later is the sequel to "28 Days Later" (2002) and "28 Weeks Later" (2007), which depict the aftermath of a zombie-style pandemic in the United Kingdom. <br/>
<br/>
The film was shot last summer using the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>‌ Pro Max as the principal camera, along with additional equipment such as custom rigs, aluminum cages, and lens attachments. The filmmakers behind 28 Years Later apparently received technical assistance directly from Apple. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/28-years-later-iphone-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1003518" /><br/>
<br/>
Speaking to <em>IGN</em>, Boyle said that even though the film is largely shot on iPhones, the movie is ambitiously still in full 2.76:1 widescreen–which is typically reserved for IMAX or Ultra Panavision 70mm. Some sequences used up to 20 iPhones at a time, similar to "bullet time." Boyle explained:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Wherever, it gives you 180 degrees of vision of an action, and in the editing you can select any choice from it, either a conventional one-camera perspective or make your way instantly around reality, time-slicing the subject, jumping forward or backward for emphasis. As it's a horror movie, we use it for the violent scenes to emphasise their impact.<br/>
<br/>
I also like it for the same reason I love jumping the line. For a moment the audience is inside the scene, the action, rather than classically observing a picture. You feel like you're in the room with Jodie Comer and her son, venting her rage at Aaron Taylor Johnson, like you’re in the abandoned train with the naked alpha and the unzipped spine and head.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The original 28 Days Later movie was largely shot in 480p standard definition with a Canon XL-1 – a consumer-grade camcorder that wrote data to MiniDV tapes. This was partly due to the need to film complex scenes depicting an abandoned central London under very limited time constraints, where bulky traditional film cameras would have taken too long to set up.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/28-years-later-iphone-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1003519" /><br/>
The unique shot-on-digital aesthetic subsequently became an iconic part of the movie, so the use of iPhones to shoot the latest addition to the series pays homage to the original film's use of camcorders. The Oscar-winning cinematographer of the original movie, Anthony Dod Mantle, returns alongside Boyle.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>I never say this, but there is an incredible shot in the second half [of the film] where we use the 20-rig camera, and you'll know it when you see it. … It's quite graphic but it's a wonderful shot that uses that technique, and in a startling way that kind of kicks you into a new world rather than thinking you've seen it before.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Several smaller-scale movies have already been shot with iPhones, such as Sean Baker's "Tangerine" (2015) and Steven Soderbergh's "Unsane" (2018), but these films were limited-release, low-budget titles compared to the upcoming Boyle movie. 28 Years Later is expected to be the first of a new trilogy of films scripted by Alex Garland. The breakout star of the original movie, Cillian Murphy, is also expected to return. 28 Years Later is set for release on June 20, 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shot-on-iphone/">Shot on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/filmmakers-used-20-iphones-to-shoot-28-years-later/">Filmmakers Used 20 iPhones at Once to Shoot &#039;28 Years Later&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/filmmakers-used-20-iphones-at-once-to-shoot-28-years-later.2457927/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working on Haptic Buttons for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/apple-haptic-buttons-iphone-ipad-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-haptic-buttons-for-iphone-ipad-apple-watch.2457922/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 04:51:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/apple-haptic-buttons-iphone-ipad-apple-watch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is actively exploring stolid-state buttons with haptic feedback, not just for the iPhone, but also for future iPad and Apple Watch models, claims a rumor out of China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPhone-15-Pro-Multi-Purpose-button-Mute-Switch-Feature-Green-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890432" /><br/>
Back in 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/kuo-iphone-15-pro-models-solid-state-buttons/">several reports</a> suggested that Apple intended to bring solid-state buttons to the iPhone 15 Pro in 2023 as part of "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">Project Bongo</a>." Solid-state haptic buttons reduce mechanical wear, while enabling users to differentiate between a light press and a firm press to trigger different functions. However, the plan was reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/11/kuo-iphone-15-pro-no-solid-state-buttons-after-all/">canceled</a> at a late stage. They were then <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/12/iphone-16-pro-solid-state-buttons/">rumored</a> to come to the iPhone 16 Pro, before being shelved indefinitely. <br/>
<br/>
Or that's what was believed at the time. It appears that Apple never fully dropped the idea, if Weibo-based leaker Instant Digital is correct. Last month, the leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/apple-hasnt-given-up-on-haptic-buttons/">claimed</a> Apple was still investigating haptic buttons for a future iPhone. And today the account has <a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/Pue4V9WoS">doubled down on the claim</a>, saying the project is not just active for the iPhone, but for Apple's "entire product line," including iPad and Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Instant Digital says it isn't the production cost that has held the project back, but rather the issue of "mistouches," since an accurate response from the buttons isn't always guaranteed. The current button design is said to be integrated directly into the frame, with no rebound when clicked, but the company is apparently seeking to more closely replicate the experience of a traditional mechanical button.<br/>
<br/>
The project was believed to be on hold while Apple prioritized display and battery technology advancements for upcoming models. While the feature is still not expected to arrive in the iPhone 17 lineup, Project Bongo has indeed "restarted" at the company, according to Instant Digital.  <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/30/apple-haptic-buttons-iphone-ipad-apple-watch/">Apple Working on Haptic Buttons for iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-on-haptic-buttons-for-iphone-ipad-apple-watch.2457922/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Executives Won&#039;t Be Appearing at This Year&#039;s WWDC Episode of The Talk Show Live</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/no-apple-executives-talk-show-live/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-executives-wont-be-appearing-at-this-years-wwdc-episode-of-the-talk-show-live.2457908/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:33:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/no-apple-executives-talk-show-live/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Since 2015, <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber has hosted a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024/">special live episode of his The Talk Show podcast from WWDC</a> each year, with senior executives from Apple routinely participating as guests for the episodes. While the executives typically do not break major news during these appearances, the lively conversations have offered some interesting insights and perspectives on various topics surrounding Apple's WWDC announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/The-Talk-Show-Live-From-WWDC-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955455" /><br/>
In <a href="https://daringfireball.net/linked/2025/05/29/the-talk-show-live-tickets-2025">announcing ticket sales for this year's live episode going live</a> today, Gruber has revealed that Apple declined his invitation for executives to appear on this year's episode, for the first time in the decade of this tradition.<br/>
<br/>
Gruber did not share a reason for Apple declining this year's invitation, and Apple likely did not provide one to him, but it's easy to surmise that it was probably due to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/12/gruber-says-something-is-rotten-at-apple/">Gruber's recent comments sharing his belief that "Something Is Rotten in the State of Cupertino"</a> in the wake of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> delays.<br/>
<br/>
In his March blog post, Gruber faulted himself for not seeing the "red flags" that were appearing as early as last year's WWDC, with Apple apparently showing off planned &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features that were not actually functional at the time and some of which may not even yet be functional.<br/>
<br/>
He faulted Apple for showing off what amounted to vaporware at last year's WWDC, a significant departure from Apple's history over the past several decades of almost always shipping features close to their suggested timelines even when they have been pre-announced before they are fully ready.<br/>
<br/>
Gruber's comments were notable given his status as one of the most well-known Apple pundits, not to mention the fact that Apple had chosen him to be the one to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">share the news days earlier</a> that the Apple Intelligence-powered &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; revamp had been delayed.<br/>
<br/>
It's hard not to view Apple's move as a form of retribution for Gruber's criticism, and also potentially an acknowledgement that Gruber would be liable to ask Apple executives some difficult questions about what occurred to force the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; delay and where things go from here.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/no-apple-executives-talk-show-live/">Apple Executives Won&#039;t Be Appearing at This Year&#039;s WWDC Episode of The Talk Show Live</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-executives-wont-be-appearing-at-this-years-wwdc-episode-of-the-talk-show-live.2457908/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Perplexity Gains Labs for Creating Reports, Spreadsheets, Web Apps and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/perplexity-labs-ai-tool/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/perplexity-gains-labs-for-creating-reports-spreadsheets-web-apps-and-more.2457900/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:53:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/perplexity-labs-ai-tool/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Perplexity</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AI-powered search tool Perplexity <a href="https://www.perplexity.ai/hub/blog/introducing-perplexity-labs">today gained</a> Perplexity Labs, a feature that provides subscribers with a way to create reports, spreadsheets, web apps, and dashboards that are backed by "extensive research and analysis."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/perplexity-ai-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972421" /><br/>
The company says that if Perplexity Search is a 24/7 answer machine, Perplexity Labs is akin to having an entire team available for help.<br/>
<br/>
Perplexity Labs can work on its own for 10 minutes or more, using tools for deep web browsing, code execution, chart creation, and image generation. It is able to complete what would have "taken days of work" in a 10 minute period, developing marketing plans, analyzing finances, creating meal plans, and more. Perplexity has examples of what Perplexity Labs is able to do in its <a href="https://perplexity.ai/labs">Projects Gallery</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Perplexity Pro subscribers have access to Labs as of today, and it can be selected from the mode selector interface on the web or in the iOS app. Mac app support is coming soon. Perplexity Pro is priced at &#36;20 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/perplexity/">Perplexity</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/perplexity-labs-ai-tool/">Perplexity Gains Labs for Creating Reports, Spreadsheets, Web Apps and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/perplexity-gains-labs-for-creating-reports-spreadsheets-web-apps-and-more.2457900/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>With iOS 18 Jumping to iOS 26, Will Apple Renumber iPhones Too?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/will-apple-rename-iphones-ios-26/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/with-ios-18-jumping-to-ios-26-will-apple-renumber-iphones-too.2457896/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:59:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/will-apple-rename-iphones-ios-26/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the next-generation version of iOS and other 2025 software updates, Apple is planning to change its numbering scheme. Rather than iOS 19, which would logically follow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple is instead going to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/28/apple-ios-26/">call the update iOS 26</a>. Apple plans to use 26 across all of its platforms (the number representing the upcoming year), which will presumably be less confusing than having iOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, and visionOS 3. But what does the change mean for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iOS-26-Mock-Rainbow-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003293" /><br/>
If Apple is looking to streamline naming, it could make sense for future &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models to follow the same year-based numbering. An &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 26 or &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 26 Pro that launches with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 26</a> would be more logical than an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> that runs &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;, at least until that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 26 needs to be updated to iOS 27 or iOS 28.<br/>
<br/>
Year-based numbering for iPhones would make it clear to consumers when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; came out. The average &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user that doesn't upgrade on the regular probably can't tell you the year that their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; launched, because there's no obvious link between the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 and 2022, or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may already have a naming conundrum in the works where some kind of transition will make sense. This year, we're on track to get the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;. In 2026, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-18/">iPhone 18</a>, and in 2027, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 19. But 2027 is the 20th anniversary of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, so will Apple want its 20th anniversary device to be the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 19? Apple didn't make that choice in 2017 at the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s 10th anniversary, and we never ended up with a &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 9 because we got the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X instead.<br/>
<br/>
Apple uses year-based numbering for its Macs, though not overtly. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> is just the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, but when you're looking for tech specs or comparison info on Apple's site, you'll find that the latest model <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/122209">is in fact</a> the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (M4, 2025). iPhones could also just be "&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;" and appended in the same way.<br/>
<br/>
There is a disconnect in Mac naming and the way Apple is doing software update naming going forward, though. Macs are named for the year they're released, but iOS and its sister updates are going to be named for the coming year on launch. &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; in September 2025, iOS 27 in September 2026, iOS 28 in September 2027, and so on. Mac-like numbering for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; would be the sensible choice instead of the year-ahead numbering, but it's doubtful that Apple will want to launch an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; (2025) running &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could also go with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> numbering for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the future. iPads aren't named like iPhones, and have historically used generations. The low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, for example, was the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; (5th generation) and then (6th generation) and (7th generation) and so on. More recently, Apple is using chips to differentiate between different generations of the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. So there's the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, and the M3 &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, along with the A16 &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; (11th generation) and the A17 Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>. Chip-based naming probably won't work for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; like it does for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and some Macs because there are multiple iPhones that use the same chip. Apple would need to do something like &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; (A19), &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Air (A19), &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Pro (A19), and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Pro Max (A19), which is no better for marketing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple might not change &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; numbering at all, given that naming across iPads, Macs, iPhones, and other devices has never exactly been straightforward. Whether Apple intends to streamline device names going forward may become clearer at the June 9 Worldwide Developers Conference. We'll hear about the plan to go from &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; to &zwnj;iOS 26&zwnj; at the keynote event, and the way that Apple frames it might just provide some insight into whether we can expect a similar change for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to match.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/will-apple-rename-iphones-ios-26/">With iOS 18 Jumping to iOS 26, Will Apple Renumber iPhones Too?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/with-ios-18-jumping-to-ios-26-will-apple-renumber-iphones-too.2457896/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store in the Netherlands Temporarily Closing Starting Next Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/apple-den-haag-temporarily-closing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-in-the-netherlands-temporarily-closing-starting-next-month.2457895/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:42:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/apple-den-haag-temporarily-closing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has announced that its <a href="https://www.apple.com/nl/retail/denhaag">Den Haag store</a> in the Netherlands will be temporarily closed for renovations starting this Sunday, June 1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Apple-Store-Den-Haag.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1612" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003475" /><br/>
The store is located in The Hague, the capital city of South Holland.<br/>
<br/>
First opened in 2014, Apple Den Haag is one of the company's flagship stores, located in a covered walkway with historical architecture. The remodeled store will likely feature an Apple Pickup station for online orders, improved accessibility, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not indicated when the store will reopen, but remodeling often takes months.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has two other stores in the Netherlands, in Amsterdam and Haarlem.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Thanks, <a href="https://choreographics.me/">Filip Chudzinski</a>!</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/apple-den-haag-temporarily-closing/">Apple Store in the Netherlands Temporarily Closing Starting Next Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-in-the-netherlands-temporarily-closing-starting-next-month.2457895/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Display Sizes: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/iphone-17-display-sizes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-display-sizes-what-to-expect.2457893/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:38:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/iphone-17-display-sizes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup will include four iPhones, and two of those are going to get all-new display sizes. There's the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, which we've heard about several times, but the standard &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; is also going to have a different display size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iPhone-17-Feature-With-Full-Width-Dynamic-Island.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959827" /><br/>
We've heard a bit about the updated size before, but with most rumors focusing on the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;, it's easy to forget. Display analyst Ross Young today <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1928146088097349832">reiterated the screen sizes</a> expected for the entire &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup, and it serves as a good reminder about what to expect from Apple's lowest-priced flagship.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; will feature a larger 6.27-inch display, which will make it the same size as the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> display. With the 16 Pro and Pro Max, Apple introduced larger displays, while the 16 and 16 Plus stayed the same size as the 15 and 15 Plus.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; - 6.27-inch display, up from 6.12 inches.</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; - 6.55 inches.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> - 6.27-inch display, identical to &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 	<li>&zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max - 6.86-inch display, no change from &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple rounds 6.27 to 6.3 inches and 6.86 to 6.9 inches, so basically, we're going to get an &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; that are 6.3 inches, and the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max at 6.9 inches. The &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; has a new display size that Apple will likely round to 6.6 inches. It will be slightly smaller than the 6.7-inch display of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> Plus it replaces.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from that new display size, the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; is shaping up to be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with the fewest changes in 2025. The &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; models and the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; are rumored to have a new horizontal rear camera bar, but the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; camera will look the same as the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; camera.<br/>
<br/>
There are features to look forward to though, such as the 120Hz ProMotion refresh rate that's rumored to be expanding to the entire &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup, an improved 24-megapixel selfie camera, and a faster A19 chip.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/iphone-17-display-sizes/">iPhone 17 Display Sizes: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-display-sizes-what-to-expect.2457893/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Alogic&#039;s Clarity 5K Touch Delivers a Sharp High-Resolution Display With Touchscreen Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-clarity-5k-touch-delivers-a-sharp-high-resolution-display-with-touchscreen-support.2457890/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:22:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-display&#038;post_date=1748553722/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Alogic</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[I've taken a look at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-pro-touch-displays/">several of Alogic's 4K displays</a> over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-max-touch-display/">past couple of years</a>, but the company has taken things to the next level with its new 27-inch Clarity 5K Touch display. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/12/alogic-5k-touchscreen-display/">Announced nearly a year ago</a>, the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-5k-touch-uhd-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-and-touch-screen/?ref=y2uwzwu">Clarity 5K Touch recently began shipping</a> to deliver not only a high-quality display experience with sufficient pixel density of 218 pixels per inch for full Retina support, but also touchscreen functionality via both stylus and fingers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-mbp.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003432" /><br/>
I've been testing out the Clarity 5K Touch for a few weeks, and I've come away impressed with the display quality and overall functionality, though the regular &#36;1,600 price tag may give some potential customers pause when weighing it against other non-Apple 5K display options.<br/>
<br/>
Alogic's Clarity 5K Touch offers a resolution of 5120 × 2880, and packing that many pixels into a 27-inch display means it can show a 2560 × 1440 HiDPI desktop in excellent true Retina quality at typical viewing distances. This yields crisp text and graphics without potential performance penalties and visual artifacts that can result from non-pixel-perfect scaling at lower pixel densities.<br/>
<br/>
Display quality on the Clarity 5K Touch was excellent in my testing, essentially indistinguishable from my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> (aside from ProMotion support) or my usual LG UltraFine 5K external displays running in Retina mode. Text and images appear super-sharp on the display, with individual pixels not visible until I get quite close to the display, as you'd expect at this pixel density. The display offers a 1,000:1 contrast ratio and up to 400 nits of typical brightness, which is a bit lower than Apple's notebooks and the Studio Display which can offer 500–600 nits of typical SDR brightness indoors, but the Clarity 5K Touch was plenty bright enough in my workspace.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-closeup.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003433" /><br/>
Color calibration appeared excellent out of the box, with everything looking vibrant yet natural and closely matching the other displays in my setup. The Clarity 5K Touch supports 100% of the sRGB gamut and 99% of the Adobe RGB and DCI-P3 gamuts, and it features HDR400 support.<br/>
<br/>
The Clarity 5K Touch is a glossy display, and while Alogic says it features an anti-reflective finish, the glossiness is very evident if you use it in an environment where there is any significant amount of glare such as direct lighting or nearby windows. Depending on the relative locations and angles of those lighting sources and your seating position, the glare can interfere with visibility at times, so that's something to be aware of as you consider where you're planning to use the display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-stand.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003436" /><br/>
The display's construction feels solid, with the stand made primarily of silver aluminum for good heft and stability. A hole in the stand neck helps route cables to minimize their visibility. In addition to adjustable height over a range of 145 mm, the Clarity 5K Touch also supports tilt (5º forward to 20º back), swivel (up to 25º left or right), and pivot adjustments for maximum flexibility. You can pivot the display all the way to 90 degrees if you prefer to use the display in portrait orientation, while tilt and swivel help you get the display in just the right position, which is especially helpful in trying to mitigate glare. Support for 100×100 VESA mounts is also included if you prefer a different mounting solution.<br/>
<br/>
The display body features a silver plastic enclosure on the rear with ventilation holes toward the top and bottom, which is perfectly adequate in my opinion considering I'm hardly ever going to look at the rear of it. Even so, it's a simple and clean design, just without the high-quality aluminum you'd find on an Apple display.<br/>
<br/>
Around the screen itself, the black bezels aren't the thinnest I've encountered, with uniform size around the top and sides and a slightly chunkier bottom bezel, some of which no doubt going toward housing the touchscreen hardware. The bezels are essentially entirely underneath the display glass aside from a very narrow plastic strip around the perimeter, which does help hide them a bit, especially if using a dark desktop and/or dark mode.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003434" /><br/>
One area where the Clarity 5K Touch tops the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Apple Studio Display</a> is in the connectivity department, with Alogic's display offering not only a USB-C connection option but also a pair of HDMI 2.0 ports and a DisplayPort 1.4 port, allowing you to hook up multiple devices and easily switch the display between them or even show multiple sources simultaneously with picture-in-picture modes. The USB-C and DisplayPort ports support up to 5K resolution at 60 Hz, while the HDMI ports support up to 5K resolution at 30 Hz, so while you're not going to get the sharpest gaming response out of this display, I've found it to be perfectly acceptable for less demanding daily work.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003435" /><br/>
Other than some resolution and orientation options managed through the Settings app on your Mac, the various inputs and other display settings are handled through an on-screen display menu system, which is a bit lacking in the visuals department as is par for the course on these types of controls. Buttons hidden along the bottom right edge of the display allow you to move through the various settings, and you'll need to use these buttons to adjust speaker volume and display brightness, as native Mac keyboard control for these is not supported.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to those various connectivity options for display sources, the Clarity 5K Touch also includes a USB-B 3.0 port for upstream data, and the display includes a pair of USB-A 3.0 ports (5 Gbps data, 7.5W charging) to serve as a hub for connecting wired accessories as long as there is either a USB-C or USB-B connection to the computer to facilitate data transfer. There's also a 3.5mm audio jack for connecting headphones or a speaker system, though it is output-only, so microphone input is not supported.<br/>
<br/>
When connected over USB-C, the Clarity 5K Touch can support up to 65 watts of charging to a connected computer, but this drops to 45 watts when the display is in HDR mode. That's enough to keep something like a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, or potentially even a 14-inch &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj;, charged up, but it may not be able to keep up if you start getting into demanding workflows on more powerful machines, especially on a 16-inch &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj;. And you certainly won't be able to fast charge a depleted &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; battery via the display. That said, it was able to keep up with my 16- inch &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; just fine in daily work.<br/>
<br/>
Then there are the unique touchscreen capabilities of the Clarity 5K Touch, as Alogic claims it's the world's first 5K touchscreen display and we've yet to see anything to dispute this among the small number of 27-inch 5K displays on the market. I've already covered much of this functionality in my reviews of Alogic's earlier 4K touchscreen display, and the idea remains essentially the same here.<br/>
<br/>
Install a Mac driver from the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-5k-touch-uhd-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-and-touch-screen/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic product page</a> (Windows machines should support the functionality out of the box) and grant the appropriate permissions, and you'll be able to interact with macOS via up to 5-point multitouch or any active stylus supporting Microsoft Pen Protocol (MPP) 2.0, such as <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-active-stylus-pen/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic's Clarity Active Stylus Pen</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/alogic-updd-commander-settings.jpg" alt="" width="1618" height="1448" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1003431" /><br/>
The UPDD Commander app provided as part of the driver installation isn't the prettiest Mac app you'll ever see, but it offers an array of customization settings to help optimize the touchscreen experience, including setting up functions for a wide variety of tap, press, swipe, and drag gestures with varying numbers of fingers. For example, you can set up a one-finger tap as a traditional mouse click and a two-finger tap as a right click, swipes in various locations can do things like show or hide the Dock, invoke Mission Control, or minimize windows. Two-finger rotation and pinch gestures can also be configured to manipulate on-screen content, and you can even set up different actions for gestures depending on which app you're in.<br/>
<br/>
As with my previous reviews of this family of displays, I still find the touch functionality to be more appropriately used as a secondary input method, as it is not very efficient (not to mention tiring on the arm) to try to use touch input as a full-time control and it is a bit clunky to be constantly shifting from mouse to keyboard to touch. So if you're looking to turn your Mac, into a full touch experience, you'll likely be disappointed.<br/>
<br/>
That's not to say the functionality doesn't come in handy though, and the most useful scenario for touch input in my opinion is in a multi-display setup where the Clarity 5K Touch serves as a secondary monitor. I keep Mail, Slack, and a few other apps perpetually open on a display off to the side of my main display, and it's nice to be able to reach over and quickly tap or swipe to look at emails or scroll through my feeds without having to move my mouse cursor back and forth across multiple displays. Everyone's situation is different, however, so consider how you might use a touch-capable display in both your workflow and your physical setup.<br/>
<br/>
The glossy display will pick up fingerprints over time as you touch it, but it's generally not a big deal as you long as you keep the glare of bright lighting away from the screen. Otherwise, an occasional wipe down with a microfiber cloth cleans it right up.<br/>
<br/>
The built-in 5-watt speakers provide a good amount of volume and provide a surprisingly immersive sound that I think comes from their rearward-firing orientation reflecting off the wall behind my desk, though overall the sound is a bit hollow as is common with integrated display speakers housed in plastic enclosures.<br/>
<br/>
The Clarity 5K Touch does not include a built-in webcam, but Alogic does sell an <a href="https://alogic.co/products/illuminate-usb-c-light-bar-with-4k-webcam/?ref=y2uwzwu">illuminated light bar</a> with 12-megapixel 4K autofocus webcam that connects via USB-C and features touch controls and a magnetic remote control dial to help light up your workspace.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-5k-touch-uhd-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-and-touch-screen/?ref=y2uwzwu">Clarity 5K Touch</a> is normally priced at &#36;1,599.99, though it's currently on sale for 10% off, bringing the price down to &#36;1,439.99. That's just a bit cheaper than the starting price of Apple's Studio Display, though Alogic does give you a much more adjustable stand at no additional charge.<br/>
<br/>
And while Alogic's display lacks the tight macOS integration and built-in webcam found on the &zwnj;Apple Studio Display&zwnj;, Alogic of course delivers the unique touchscreen functionality, so that will likely be a major consideration for potential customers. If you think the touchscreen functionality might be useful, then the Clarity 5K Touch is your only option currently on the market. If not, you might want to consider the &zwnj;Apple Studio Display&zwnj; or potentially one of the few other 27-inch 5K displays that are currently available at sometimes significantly lower prices.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Clarity 5K Touch display for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alogic/">Alogic</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-5k-touch-display/">Review: Alogic&#039;s Clarity 5K Touch Delivers a Sharp High-Resolution Display With Touchscreen Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-alogics-clarity-5k-touch-delivers-a-sharp-high-resolution-display-with-touchscreen-support.2457890/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Offers MacRumors Readers 20% Off Collection of Chargers, Hubs, Batteries, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/anker-macrumors-readers-20-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-offers-macrumors-readers-20-off-collection-of-chargers-hubs-batteries-and-more.2457886/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 10:38:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/anker-macrumors-readers-20-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacRumors readers have a few days left to get <strong>20 percent off</strong> a collection of Anker's best charging accessories before our exclusive code expires on May 31. In order to get this deal, <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">head to Anker's website</a> and add an accessory to your cart, then enter the code <strong>Ankermacrumors2025</strong> at checkout to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/04/anker-spring-deals-compressed.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-998013" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Our exclusive 20 percent off code works on most accessories sitewide, including Anker's <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fanker-high-power%3Fref%3Dhomepage_masterBanner_1">new "high power" charging accessories</a>. This exclusive discount code does not stack with existing discounts on Anker's website, but it can be used on multiple items in the same cart.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">EXCLUSIVE 20% OFF</div>Anker Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In the lists below, we've collected a few examples of the best products available at a discount with our exclusive promo code, but remember that it works sitewide. You have until May 31 to take advantage of this promotion, so be sure to browse <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2F%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker's best products on its website</a> before the end of the month.<br/>
<br/>
It's also worth noting that Anker is hosting a new "on-the-go" summer sale, and some of the discounts in that event are steeper than our 20 percent sitewide discount. Be sure to check and compare both discounts in your cart before you place your order to ensure you have the best deal.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Portable Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1664-maggo-10000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D44058070548630%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">MagGo 10,000 mAh Power Bank</a> - &#36;60.00, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1336-20000mah-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D42691854925974%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank</a> - &#36;104.00, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Wall Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2669-3-port-wall-charger%3Fvariant%3D42691852435606%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">67W 3-Port Wall Charger</a> - &#36;48.00, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2697-anker-charger-140w-4-port%3Fvariant%3D44320558055574%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">140W 4-Port Charger with USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;80.00, down from &#36;99.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Charging Stations</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25m8-maggo-qi2-wireless-charging-station-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D44057193316502%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">MagGo 3-in-1 Foldable Charging Station</a> - &#36;72.00, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25m3-maggo-qi2-wireless-charging-station-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D43028936032406%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">MagGo 3-in-1 Charging Stand</a> - &#36;74.99, down from &#36;110.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fy1811%3Fvariant%3D42206465327254%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale">3-in-1 Cube with MagSafe</a> - &#36;104.00, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fbundle-a2683141-1-a88e2012-1%3Fvariant%3D44036908220566%26ref%3D2025bfcm_discount_zone">200W 6-Port Prime Charger with USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;83.20, down from &#36;103.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2345-anker-prime-charger-250w-6-ports-ganprime%3Fcov%3Db%26ref%3Dearth-day-sale%26variant%3D43931956478102">250W 6-Port Prime Charger</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;169.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address" title="Email Address" /><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value="" title="form" /></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/29/anker-macrumors-readers-20-off/">Anker Offers MacRumors Readers 20% Off Collection of Chargers, Hubs, Batteries, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-offers-macrumors-readers-20-off-collection-of-chargers-hubs-batteries-and-more.2457886/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
