<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 02:03:54 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacBook Air Turns 17 Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/macbook-air-turns-17-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macbook-air-turns-17-today.2447421/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/macbook-air-turns-17-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Steve Jobs <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2008/01/15Apple-Introduces-MacBook-Air-The-Worlds-Thinnest-Notebook/">announced</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> 17 years ago today at the Macworld Conference & Expo in San Francisco, captivating audiences with a groundbreaking design that set new industry standards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/MacBook-Air-17-Years-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-985387" /><br/>
Jobs famously revealed the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; by pulling it out of an interoffice envelope to emphasize its unprecedentedly slim profile. The original model featured a 13.3-inch display, Intel Core 2 Duo processor, and an optional 64GB solid-state drive, which was a rarity for consumer laptops in 2008, in a sleek aluminum unibody design. It lacked features considered standard at the time, such as an optical drive and Ethernet port. The single headphone, USB, and Micro-DVI ports popped out of a small door on the right of the machine. Jobs said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>We've built the world's thinnest notebook — without sacrificing a full-size keyboard or a full-size 13-inch display. When you first see MacBook Air, it's hard to believe it's a high-performance notebook with a full-size keyboard and display. But it is.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Seventeen years later, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; remains a cornerstone of the Mac lineup, providing the entry-level point for customers who want an Apple laptop. In 2020, Apple brought its own custom silicon processor to the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; in the form of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip, enabling a massive leap in performance and energy efficiency. It completely redesigned the machine in 2022, and added a 15-inch model in 2024. In the first half of this year, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-macbook-air/">expected to bring</a> its latest-generation M-series chips to the device.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/macbook-air-turns-17-today/">The MacBook Air Turns 17 Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macbook-air-turns-17-today.2447421/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WaterField Designs Debuts Shield Case for Transporting Mac Mini</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/mac-mini-shield-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/waterfield-designs-debuts-shield-case-for-transporting-mac-mini.2447408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:30:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/mac-mini-shield-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WaterField Designs today introduced the <a href="https://www.sfbags.com/products/mac-mini-shield-case">Shield Case</a>, a small, protective case that's designed for Apple's latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>. The shield case has a rugged ballistic nylon or waxed canvas exterior, along with a soft, padded fleece interior that keeps the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; safe during transport.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/mac-mini-shield-case.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985385" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-mac-mini/">M4 Mac mini</a> is Apple's smallest desktop machine to date, measuring in at just five inches by five inches. It's small enough that it can be easily taken from one desktop setup to another, hence the reason behind a case for a desktop Mac.<br/>
<br/>
There is a plush interior pocket for the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; power cord, along with a rear mesh pocket and a padded, zippered front pocket for SD cards, cords, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> for tracking purposes.<br/>
<br/>
A nylon loop at the top allows the Shield Case to be carried or attached to another bag with a carabiner, and there are waterproof YKK zippers that can be locked with a padlock. A zipper guard ensures the zipper does not damage the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The Shield Case can be <a href="https://www.sfbags.com/products/mac-mini-shield-case">purchased from the WaterField Designs website</a> for &#36;99, and it will ship out to customers this month.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/mac-mini-shield-case/">WaterField Designs Debuts Shield Case for Transporting Mac Mini</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/waterfield-designs-debuts-shield-case-for-transporting-mac-mini.2447408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes Severance Season 2 Premiere With Lumon Industries Pop-Up and Visits From Actors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-severance-season-2-promo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-severance-season-2-premiere-with-lumon-industries-pop-up-and-visits-from-actors.2447405/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 15:47:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-severance-season-2-promo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of the season two premiere of hit TV show Severance, Apple is marketing the show with a fun Severance pop-up at the Grand Central Terminal in New York City.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/severance-new-york-promo-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985377" /><br/>
Apple has assembled a glass cube with workstations that are identical to the setups that Lumon employees use on the show, complete with employees "working," doing yoga, playing catch, throwing paper airplanes, sipping coffee, and performing other activities that we've seen on Severance.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/severance-new-york-promo-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="2161" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985379" /><br/>
At 4:30 p.m. Eastern Time, Severance director Ben Stiller made an appearance at the site, with some of the show's actors visiting as well. Adam Scott, Zach Cherry, Patricia Arquette, Britt Lower, and Tramell Tillman were on hand and spent time in the makeshift office space, with the actors in character as their "innies."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/severance-new-yokr-promo-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="2290" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985380" /><br/>
The performance went on for more two and a half hours, and the actors behaved as if they were actually at work at Lumon Industries. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/severance-new-york-promo-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985381" /><br/>
Severance is set to return to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ on Friday, January 17, three years after the first season of the show premiered.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-severance-season-2-promo/">Apple Promotes Severance Season 2 Premiere With Lumon Industries Pop-Up and Visits From Actors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-severance-season-2-premiere-with-lumon-industries-pop-up-and-visits-from-actors.2447405/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Gains Support for Reminders and Tasks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/chatgpt-task-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gains-support-for-reminders-and-tasks.2447402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 15:31:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/chatgpt-task-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI today said that it added a new "Tasks" beta feature to ChatGPT, allowing ChatGPT to provide reminders for upcoming tasks. The feature supports one-time reminders or recurring actions, with users able to use conversational language to set up notifications for tasks. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
ChatGPT is able to do things like send a weekly global news briefing, provide a daily 15-minute workout, set reminders for completing a task like language practice, send a daily joke, create a meal plan each evening, provide reminders about upcoming events like birthdays, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today we’re rolling out a beta version of tasks—a new way to ask ChatGPT to do things for you at a future time.<br><br>Whether it&#39;s one-time reminders or recurring actions, tell ChatGPT what you need and when, and it will automatically take care of it. <a href="https://t.co/7lgvsPehHv">pic.twitter.com/7lgvsPehHv</a></p>&mdash; OpenAI (@OpenAI) <a href="https://twitter.com/OpenAI/status/1879267274185756896?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 14, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Reminders can be created in chat or through the tasks page under the profile menu, though the "4o with scheduled tasks" model needs to be selected. The new model is still rolling out to subscribers. <br/>
<br/>
At the current time, Tasks is available to Plus, Pro, and Teams subscribers in a beta capacity, and in the future, it will be available to everyone with a ChatGPT account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/chatgpt-task-support/">ChatGPT Gains Support for Reminders and Tasks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-gains-support-for-reminders-and-tasks.2447402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 11.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-11-3-to-developers.2447399/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:09:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 11.3 update for testing purposes, with the beta coming a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/07/apple-releases-watchos-11-3-beta-2/">week after the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
The beta is available to registered developers, and can be downloaded from the Watch app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There were no notable new features found in the update, but code suggests that Apple will add support for robot vacuums to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, which means it will be a supported category in the Home app in watchOS.<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting watchOS 11.3 to be released sometime in late January alongside iOS 18.3, iPadOS 18.3, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 11.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-11-3-to-developers.2447399/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Not Reassessing Apple and Google Antitrust Investigations, But New Administration Could Shift Priorities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/eu-not-reassessing-apple-investigation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-not-reassessing-apple-and-google-antitrust-investigations-but-new-administration-could-shift-priorities.2447397/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 13:28:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/eu-not-reassessing-apple-investigation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The European Union is "reassessing" its investigations into big U.S. tech companies like Apple, Meta, and Google, claims <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/2c1b6bfd-ce73-451d-8123-0df964266ae8">Financial Times</a></em>, though a spokesperson from the European Commission has denied that such a review is taking place.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Tech CEOs like Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and Meta's Mark Zuckerberg have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/03/tim-cook-trump-inauguration-donation/">been cozying up</a> to president-elect Donald Trump as he prepares to take office, and <em>Financial Times</em> suggests that probes launched under the Digital Markets Act could be scaled back. A senior EU diplomat told the site that "So much is up in the air right now," while other officials said that regulators are holding for "political direction" to make final decisions in cases involving Apple, Google, and Meta.<br/>
<br/>
A spokesperson for the European Commission told <em>Financial Times</em> that there is "no such review taking place," but that the EC has "upcoming meetings to assess the general readiness of an investigation." None of the cases are "ready at a technical level," but the EC remains "fully committed to the effective enforcement of its rules."<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission launched an investigation into Apple's compliance with the Digital Markets Act last year, and determined that it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/eu-plans-to-fine-apple-over-dma-report/">not in compliance</a>. A November report suggested that the European Commission is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/eu-apple-fine-anticompetitive-app-store-practices/">gearing up to fine Apple</a> for failing to implement changes allowing developers to steer users to cheaper prices outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple overhauled its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules in Europe in 2024, and made several changes to satisfy regulators. European developers are able to distribute apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and there are new fee structures and policies in place.<br/>
<br/>
The EU in 2024 fined Apple &#36;2 billion for anticompetitive behavior against third-party music services, and if Apple is fined over DMA non-compliance, the fee could be higher. Under the DMA, the European Union is able to fine Apple up to 10 percent of its global annual sales.<br/>
<br/>
Back in October, Trump claimed that <a href="https://www.reuters.com/world/us/trump-says-apple-ceo-cook-called-him-with-concerns-about-eu-penalties-2024-10-17/">Cook called him</a> to complain about penalties from the European Union. At the time, Trump said that he is "not going to let them take advantage of our companies."<br/>
<br/>
With Margrethe Vestager and Thierry Breton having stepped down from the European Commission, priorities could change. The EC's chief spokesperson said that there could be a "political reality" that "puts pressure on the technical work." The EC "will be looking and assessing on the basis of concrete measures and actions from the new administration."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/eu-not-reassessing-apple-investigation/">EU Not Reassessing Apple and Google Antitrust Investigations, But New Administration Could Shift Priorities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-not-reassessing-apple-and-google-antitrust-investigations-but-new-administration-could-shift-priorities.2447397/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Updated MagSafe Charger Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/25w-magsafe-charger-firmware-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-magsafe-charger-firmware.2447390/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 11:30:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/25w-magsafe-charger-firmware-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware designed for the 25W <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> Charger that is compatible with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and later and the latest AirPods and Apple Watch models. The updated firmware is version 2A143, up from the 2A138 firmware that the accessory shipped with. In the Settings app, you'll see a different version number than the internal firmware number.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/new-magsafe-charger.jpg" alt="" width="1764" height="992" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965150" /><br/>
The 2024 &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger was released alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, and it is able to charge them at up to 25W. For the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, charging is capped at 15W.<br/>
<br/>
Because firmware updates are released quietly over the air, Apple does not provide release notes. We do not know what new features or bug fixes might be included in the software.<br/>
<br/>
There is no clear method for updating a ‌&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;‌ charger's firmware, but it needs to be plugged in and connected to an Apple device for a firmware update to initiate. You can check your ‌&zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;‌ Charger's firmware by following the instructions in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/check-firmware-apple-magsafe-charger/">MagSafe Charger how to</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/25w-magsafe-charger-firmware-update/">Apple Releases Updated MagSafe Charger Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-updated-magsafe-charger-firmware.2447390/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pencil Pro Hits &#36;99.00 for the First Time in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-pencil-pro-99-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-hits-99-00-for-the-first-time-in-2025.2447386/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 10:31:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-pencil-pro-99-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Pencil Pro deals were prevalent in the lead-up to Black Friday last year, but quickly disappeared as the holiday season continued. It's now been over a month since we last saw a low price on the accessory, but this week Amazon has the stylus for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is just about &#36;5 higher when compared to the all-time low price on the Apple Pencil Pro, but given that deals have been pretty rare recently, it's a great opportunity for anyone who's been waiting for a discount. This sale does not require any coupon codes to be clipped.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple Pencil Pro debuted last May with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/09/apple-pencil-pro-features/">new features</a> like squeeze gestures, haptic feedback, Find My support, and more. It's compatible with the M2 iPad Air, iPad mini 7, and M4 iPad Pro. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-pencil-pro-99-2025/">Apple Pencil Pro Hits &#36;99.00 for the First Time in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-hits-99-00-for-the-first-time-in-2025.2447386/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 18.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-tvos-18-3-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-18-3-to-developers.2447385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 10:30:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-tvos-18-3-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 18.3 update for testing purposes. The third beta comes a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/07/apple-releases-watchos-11-3-beta-2/">week after the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-4k-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953895" /><br/>
The beta is available to registered developers, and can be downloaded from the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. Apple has also seeded new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 18.3 beta software. <br/>
<br/>
There were no notable new features found in the update, but code suggests that Apple will add support for robot vacuums to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, which means it will be a supported category in the Home app in tvOS 18. <br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/17/whats-new-in-tvos-18-3-so-far/">add a new notice</a> about digital movie and TV show sales in the update. <br/>
<br/>
We are expecting tvOS 18.3 to be released sometime in late January alongside iOS 18.3, iPadOS 18.3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3, watchOS 11.3, and visionOS 2.3.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-seeds-tvos-18-3-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 18.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-18-3-to-developers.2447385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store Plans in Florida Go Beyond New Miami Worldcenter Location</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-store-plans-in-florida/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-plans-in-florida-go-beyond-new-miami-worldcenter-location.2447380/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 09:44:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-store-plans-in-florida/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently announced that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-miami-worldcenter/">opening an all-new retail store at the Miami Worldcenter</a> complex on Friday, January 24.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Miami-Worldcenter-Render.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985330" /><em>A pre-construction render of Apple Miami Worldcenter</em></div><br/>
We have since learned that Apple's retail store plans in Florida go slightly beyond that. In early December, the company closed its store at The Galleria shopping mall in Fort Lauderdale, and opened a new store across the hall from it. We have confirmed that the new store is a temporary location, meaning that the original store is likely undergoing renovations and will eventually reopen with a modernized design.<br/>
<br/>
"We've moved, but let's stay close," says the <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/thegalleria/">page for Apple The Galleria</a>. "Visit us in our new location just across the hall."<br/>
<br/>
We do not know when the original store will reopen.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Store news isn't always especially interesting, but at least Apple released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-miami-worldcenter/">special iPhone, iPad, and Mac wallpaper</a> for the upcoming Miami Worldcenter location. And for an upcoming store in China, there is even <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/apple-store-mixc-hefei/">a special Apple Watch face</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-store-plans-in-florida/">Apple Store Plans in Florida Go Beyond New Miami Worldcenter Location</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-plans-in-florida-go-beyond-new-miami-worldcenter-location.2447380/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s the Latest on Next-Generation CarPlay After Missed 2024 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/next-generation-carplay-status-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-the-latest-on-next-generation-carplay-after-missed-2024-launch.2447376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 09:16:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/next-generation-carplay-status-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple said the first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay would arrive in 2024. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/next-generation-carplay-didnt-arrive-in-2024/">It didn't happen</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/02/carplay-next-gen-hero.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969129" /><br/>
Now what?<br/>
<br/>
We are two weeks into 2025, and Apple has yet to update or remove the 2024 timeframe for next-generation CarPlay advertised on its website. Apple also remains completely silent about whether or not it still plans to launch the system.<br/>
<br/>
There are still a few signs of hope.<br/>
<br/>
First, <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2025/01/07/apple-prepping-next-gen-carplay/"><em>9to5Mac</em> recently reported</a> that additional references to next-generation CarPlay were added in iOS 18.3 beta 2's code. Second, <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris today uncovered some additional <a href="https://x.com/aaronp613/status/1879159569882190069">next-generation CarPlay images</a> that were filed in a EU database last month. Apple previously showed that next-generation CarPlay will feature customizable widgets, and the images provide a closer look at the widget selection screens.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here is an upcoming look at widgets coming to CarPlay 2.0 <a href="https://t.co/2mwg3VjR7H">pic.twitter.com/2mwg3VjR7H</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1879159569882190069?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 14, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Due to Apple's reluctance to comment on future plans, we do not know if next-generation CarPlay is still happening. Hopefully, Apple will finally provide an update about next-generation CarPlay soon to set the record straight.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed next-generation CarPlay at WWDC 2022, more than two and a half years ago. For now, the wait continues.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/next-generation-carplay-status-update/">Here&#039;s the Latest on Next-Generation CarPlay After Missed 2024 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-the-latest-on-next-generation-carplay-after-missed-2024-launch.2447376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Disney World and Disneyland Rolling Out Food Order Tracking on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/disney-world-live-activities-for-mobile-orders/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-world-and-disneyland-rolling-out-food-order-tracking-on-iphones-lock-screen.2447373/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 08:11:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/disney-world-live-activities-for-mobile-orders/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Live Activities</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney today announced that it is rolling out support for the Live Activities feature on iPhones for mobile food and beverage orders at its two big U.S. parks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Disney-Live-Activities-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1931" height="1086" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985288" /><br/>
The feature started rolling out today at select mobile order locations across Walt Disney World and Disneyland Resort, the company said. Where available, the feature allows you to track the status of your mobile order on the iPhone's Lock Screen or in the Dynamic Island, without needing to open the My Disney Experience or Disneyland apps.<br/>
<br/>
You can tap the "I'm Here, Prepare My Order" button to have your order freshly prepared, and view your order number, order status, and pickup location.<br/>
<br/>
Live Activities are available on the Lock Screen on all iPhone models that are updated to iOS 16.1 or later, while the Dynamic Island is limited to the iPhone 14 Pro models, all iPhone 15 models, and all iPhone 16 models. You may also need to ensure that your My Disney Experience or Disneyland app is updated to the latest version.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-activities/">Live Activities</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/disney-world-live-activities-for-mobile-orders/">Disney World and Disneyland Rolling Out Food Order Tracking on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/disney-world-and-disneyland-rolling-out-food-order-tracking-on-iphones-lock-screen.2447373/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New High-Speed Technology Paves Way for Apple Intelligence Upgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-ualink/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-high-speed-technology-paves-way-for-apple-intelligence-upgrades.2447372/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 07:48:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-ualink/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has backed a technology that could contribute to future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> advancements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-iPhone-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964551" /><br/>
The consortium behind the "Ultra Accelerator Link" or "UALink" technology today <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250114920576/en">announced</a> that Apple, Alibaba, and Synopsys have joined its Board of Directors. The three companies will contribute to further development of the technology.<br/>
<br/>
UALink is described as a "high-speed, scale-up interconnect for next-generation AI cluster performance." The consortium is aiming to release UALink 1.0 in the first quarter of 2025, and it will enable data speeds of "up to 200Gbps per lane."<br/>
<br/>
The technology could pave the way for faster and more efficient Apple Intelligence servers.<br/>
<br/>
"UALink shows great promise in addressing connectivity challenges and creating new opportunities for expanding AI capabilities and demands," said Becky Loop, Director of Platform Architecture at Apple. Loop added that "Apple has a long history of pioneering and collaborating on innovations that drive our industry forward."<br/>
<br/>
It is not clear if or when Apple will adopt the technology, or if it is merely interested in helping out the overall AI industry.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence servers are currently powered by the M2 Ultra chip, and they are expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/06/apple-intelligence-servers-with-m4-chips-report/">start using M4 series chips</a> this year. In an eventual move away from Mac chips for server use, <em>The Information</em> recently reported that Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/apple-intelligence-servers-new-chip-report/">developing a new AI server chip</a> that will offer even faster performance for AI workloads.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/apple-ualink/">New High-Speed Technology Paves Way for Apple Intelligence Upgrades</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-high-speed-technology-paves-way-for-apple-intelligence-upgrades.2447372/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Portable Power Stations From Anker and Jackery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/amazon-savings-power-stations-anker-jackery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-portable-power-stations-from-anker-and-jackery.2447371/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 07:21:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/amazon-savings-power-stations-anker-jackery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a big selection of discounts on <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Anker's</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1YF82VRB0VAOP%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1YF82VRB0VAOP_1736866858867">Jackery's</a> best portable power stations on Amazon, with as much as &#36;1,500 in savings on these devices. These accessories are high-capacity portable batteries that can provide backup power to a wide variety of devices, from laptops to RVs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958617" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In most cases, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon before you see the final deal price for deals from both brands. Once you do, the coupon code will be applied to the accessory in your cart, and at the checkout screen you will see the final sale price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1YF82VRB0VAOP%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1YF82VRB0VAOP_1736866858867">Explorer 100 Plus Mini</a> - &#36;199.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FJackery-Generator-Charging-Outdoors-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Solar Generator 240 + Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;269.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FJackery-Generator-Book-sized-Traveling-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCBQ7J%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Solar Generator 300 Plus + Solar Panel</a> - &#36;299.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTUXEYQO6VX0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTUXEYQO6VX0_1736867135900">Explorer 500</a> - &#36;529.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXSPN7D6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_popover_product_title%26th%3D1">Solar Generator 3000 PRO</a> - &#36;2,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;3,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CMDC4S1T%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_popover_product_title%26th%3D1">Explorer 3000 Pro + 200W Solar Panels</a> - &#36;2,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;3,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QVZOTQI4DFQ1%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QVZOTQI4DFQ1_1736866900741">Explorer 2000 Plus Kit with Expandable Battery and Solar Panels</a> - &#36;3,599.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1754-SOLIX-C800-Plus%2Fdp%2FB0C5CBDX2P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C800 Power Station with Camping Lights</a> - &#36;449.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;649.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Generator-UltraFast-Optional%2Fdp%2FB0C5C89QKZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;998.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Generator-Portable-Batteries-Technology%2Fdp%2FB0CBB6HFMM%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,799.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-PowerHouse-Generator-Batteries%2Fdp%2FB0BX64LGFT%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Power Station with 200W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;1,599.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;2,549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Batteries-Ultra-High-Generator-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0C5C9HMQ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F3800 Power Station</a> - &#36;2,699.00, down from &#36;3,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Station-Generator-Emergencies%2Fdp%2FB0CRB3MQT5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F3800 Power Station with 400W Solar Panel</a> - &#36;3,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,899.00</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/amazon-savings-power-stations-anker-jackery/">Amazon Introduces Big Savings on Portable Power Stations From Anker and Jackery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-big-savings-on-portable-power-stations-from-anker-and-jackery.2447371/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First iPhone Chips Made in America Soon to Start Mass Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/first-iphone-chips-to-start-production-in-america/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-iphone-chips-made-in-america-soon-to-start-mass-production.2447360/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 05:01:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/first-iphone-chips-to-start-production-in-america/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Nikkei</category>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>United States</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is nearing the start of mass production for its first U.S.-made A-series chips at TSMC's Arizona plant, <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Tech/Semiconductors/Apple-in-final-stages-of-verifying-TSMC-s-Made-in-USA-chips"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
The report suggests that test production of the chips at the new TSMC plant near Phoenix has already been completed, and Apple is now in the final stages of verifying their quality and performance. The first batch of commercially viable chips could be ready for mass production as early as this quarter, pending the completion of quality assurance processes. <br/>
<br/>
The factory is expected to produce A-series chips used in Apple devices, primarily for older <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/08/apple-watch-chips-now-being-made-in-the-u-s/">recent report</a> suggested the facility would make the A16 Bionic chip for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, and the S9 chip for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>. The commencement of mass production at the Arizona plant will mark the first time Apple silicon chips are manufactured in the United States.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nikkei-com/">Nikkei</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-states/">United States</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/14/first-iphone-chips-to-start-production-in-america/">First iPhone Chips Made in America Soon to Start Mass Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-iphone-chips-made-in-america-soon-to-start-mass-production.2447360/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.2, Preventing Downgrading</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-2-preventing-downgrading.2447342/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 15:26:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 18.2, which means that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users who have upgraded to iOS 18.2.1 can no longer downgrade to iOS 18.2. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/06/apple-releases-ios-18-2-1/">released iOS 18.2.1</a> earlier in January.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Generic-iOS-18.2-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972123" /><br/>
When new versions of iOS are released, Apple typically stops signing the prior version after a week or two. An update that is not signed is not able to be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; because there is a server-side software verification check.<br/>
<br/>
By preventing downgrading to older versions of iOS, Apple ensures that users keep their devices up to date with the newest security improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's iOS 18.2.1 update included unspecified bug fixes, while the now-unsigned iOS 18.2 update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-2-features/">that came out in December</a> added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> ChatGPT integration, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-2/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 18.2, Preventing Downgrading</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-18-2-preventing-downgrading.2447342/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Data Broker Hack Exposes Location Info From Millions of iPhone Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/data-broker-hack-iphone-location-info/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/data-broker-hack-exposes-location-info-from-millions-of-iphone-users.2447334/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 13:55:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/data-broker-hack-iphone-location-info/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Data broker Gravy Analytics has been hacked, and location information from millions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android users is at risk, reports <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2025/01/13/gravy-analytics-data-broker-breach-trove-of-location-data-threatens-privacy-millions/">TechCrunch</a></em>. Gravy Analytics' parent company Unacast disclosed the data breach earlier this month [<a href="https://fido.nrk.no/8a09133d2b14a7e72c31006ef2611b22fd78d7c6bfd7cc62f7d35f13b3c2d338/Datatilsynet_Unacast_Security%20Incident%20Notification_Redacted.pdf">PDF</a>], and said that its AWS cloud storage environment had been accessed by an unauthorized person using a "misappropriated access key."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-security-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1145" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796484" /><br/>
"Some files" were obtained, and preliminary findings suggest those files "could contain personal data" collected from users of third-party services that use Gravy Analytics. According to <em><a href="https://www.404media.co/hackers-claim-massive-breach-of-location-data-giant-threaten-to-leak-data/">404Media</a></em>, hackers are claiming to have customer lists and location data from smartphones that shows peoples' precise movements, with millions of users affected. Some of that data, which does indeed include the historical location of smartphones, has been published on private forums.<br/>
<br/>
Gravy Analytics says that it tracks more than a billion devices around the world daily, and security researchers that saw a sample of the data collected by Gravy Analytics confirmed that the information <a href="https://x.com/fs0c131y/status/1876975966334964076">can be used</a> to track a person's recent locations, with no anonymization.<br/>
<br/>
In December, the United States Federal Trade Commission (FTC) <a href="https://www.ftc.gov/news-events/news/press-releases/2024/12/ftc-takes-action-against-gravy-analytics-venntel-unlawfully-selling-location-data-tracking-consumers">prohibited Gravy Analytics</a> and its subsidiary Venntel from selling, disclosing, or using sensitive location data in any product or service. The FTC warned that the two companies exposed consumers to privacy harms that could include disclosure of health information, political activity, and religious practices, and put people at risk of stigma, discrimination, violence and other harms.<br/>
<br/>
The order required Gravy Analytics to delete all historic location data and any data products developed using data collected from consumers, but it was apparently too late because the company's systems had likely already been breached at the time.<br/>
<br/>
Gravy Analytics collects location data through a real-time ad bidding process that allows companies competing to buy an ad to see customer IP address and more precise location data if enabled. Gravy Analytics' database had location data from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps that include FlightRadar, Grindr, and Tinder, and while the apps did not have a direct relationship with the data broker, user location information was collected through their ads.<br/>
<br/>
Turning off app tracking in the Privacy and Security section of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Settings app keeps ads from being able to obtain a unique device identifier to link location data to a specific device, and preventing apps from using precise location data is also a way to preserve more privacy.<br/>
<br/>
Baptiste Robert, CEO of security firm Predicta Lab, told <em>TechCrunch</em> that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users that had app tracking disabled did not have their data shared.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/data-broker-hack-iphone-location-info/">Data Broker Hack Exposes Location Info From Millions of iPhone Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/data-broker-hack-exposes-location-info-from-millions-of-iphone-users.2447334/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Coming to Illinois</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/iphone-drivers-license-support-illinois/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-coming-to-illinois.2447331/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 12:18:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/iphone-drivers-license-support-illinois/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from Illinois will soon be able to add their driver's licenses and IDs to the Apple Wallet app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch, the Illinois Secretary of State announced today [<a href="https://www.ilsos.gov/news/2025/january/250113d1.pdf">PDF</a>].<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/illinois-digital-id.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985213" /><br/>
An Illinois state law that went into effect on January 1 legalizes mobile IDs and allows places of business to accept digital driver's licenses in lieu of physical licenses.<br/>
<br/>
As of right now, Illinois does not have a mobile license program, and the state is in the beginning process of developing digital driver's licenses. The Secretary of State plans to establish standards of security and conduct "rigorous testing" to make sure data from Illinois residents is kept private. Illinois is aiming to bring driver's licenses and IDs to Apple Wallet by the end of 2025, but that may be ambitious with nothing in place just yet.<br/>
<br/>
Like in other states that have adopted Wallet integration for digital IDs, mobile IDs will be a companion to physical IDs instead of a replacement. Banks, police, and more can still ask for a physical ID.<br/>
<br/>
Select airports in the United States accept digital licenses in the Wallet app instead of requiring a physical version.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced Wallet support for digital IDs in 2022, and states have been slowly adopting the feature since then. So far, Arizona, Colorado, Georgia, Maryland, Hawaii, California, Ohio, Iowa,  New Mexico, and Puerto Rico have implemented support.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to Illinois, Connecticut, Kentucky, Oklahoma, Utah, Montana, and West Virginia are working to implement the feature.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/iphone-drivers-license-support-illinois/">iPhone Driver&#039;s License Support Coming to Illinois</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-license-support-coming-to-illinois.2447331/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: BenQ&#039;s Affordable MA270U 4K Monitor Is Made for MacBooks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-benq-ma270u-4k-mac-monitor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-benqs-affordable-ma270u-4k-monitor-is-made-for-macbooks.2447319/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 08:56:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-benq-ma270u-4k-mac-monitor&#038;post_date=1736798203/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Any typical search for a consumer Mac monitor inevitably leads to the Apple Studio Display – a seamless but prohibitively expensive option for most users at &#36;1,599. That's where BenQ's MA270U steps in, offering Mac-native features at a much more palatable &#36;459.99. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/benq-ma270u-27.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985172" /><br/>
Unlike typical PC monitors that often feel retrofitted for Mac compatibility, this is a 27-inch 4K display that arrives ready for MacBook use out of the box, complete with built-in color matching, keyboard integration, and even Focus mode support. But can a third-party monitor truly deliver Apple-like integration without the Apple price tag?<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Key Display Specifications</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>27-inch IPS panel with Nano Matte coating</li><br/>
<li>3840 x 2160 (4K) resolution</li><br/>
<li>400 nits peak brightness</li><br/>
<li>1200:1 native contrast ratio</li><br/>
<li>99% sRGB, 95% P3 color gamut</li><br/>
<li>60Hz refresh rate</li><br/>
<li>5ms response time</li><br/>
<li>HDR10 with VESA Display HDR 400 certification</li><br/>
<li>178° viewing angles</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Design and Build Quality</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/MA270U-2.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985125" /><br/>
Peeling the protective material off the "Nano Matte" IPS panel reveals a thin black bezel around the top and sides, and a slightly thicker chin with the BenQ logo centered in an inoffensive, almost hidden black finish. The rear of the display is plastic with a metallic finish that curves outwards slightly, while the stand is a brushed metal pipe about 2.5 inches in diameter. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/MA270U-4.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985129" /><br/>
Assembly is extremely simple and requires no tools. You just click the neck of the stand to the back and then use the key-screw to fasten on the rectangular base, which includes a rubber strip along the front for placing accessories. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/MA270U-3.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="768" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985127" /><br/>
Once the monitor was set up alongside my Apple Studio Display, BenQ's design perhaps inevitably looked a little dated. The monitor sports clean lines and thin bezels, but its predominantly plastic construction lacks Apple's signature sophistication. The aluminum-effect back cover tries to bridge this gap, though it can't match Apple's minimalist refinement and keen eye for curves and lines. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-5-1.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985132" /><br/>
That said, build quality impresses where it matters. The steel neck provides rock-solid stability, while the soft-touch area on the base is a nice afterthought. While it won't win any design awards in my book, the construction feels reassuringly robust.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Connectivity and Setup</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/03-ma270u-product-03.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1408" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985163" /><br/>
Connectivity-wise, the monitor is fairly well-accommodated round the back. The 90W USB-C port connects and provides power to your Mac, while an additional 15W USB-C port and one 7.5W USB-A port offer options for connecting other devices (in my case, a Bluetooth receiver for my mouse, and an external USB hard drive). <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270U-6.jpeg" alt="" width="4032" height="2310" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985134" /><br/>
Crucially, the hub can provide power even when the display is off, so you can keep your MacBook and whatever else plugged in and charging regardless. There are also two HDMI 2.0 ports (sadly not 2.1), plus a headphone jack and an extra 7.5W USB-A port located under the panel, next to a glowing power button and a physical toggle to manually set brightness, volume, and display output. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-7.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985138" /><br/>
Getting started couldn't have been easier. I plugged in the supplied USB-C cable and my MacBook Air instantly recognized the display and began drawing 90W of power from it. I also tried connecting to an M4 Mac mini, both directly and via a Ugreen Thunderbolt 4 dock, and had zero issues. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-8.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985142" /><br/>
As I got comfortable with the setup, I was impressed by the flexibility of the MA270U's stand, offering a range of adjustments that make it easy to find your ideal viewing position. The height adjustment provides a generous 115mm of vertical travel, while the tilt mechanism allows the screen to move from -5° backward to 20° forward. Paired with 15° of swivel in each direction, you can fine-tune the display's position to minimize glare and maximize comfort. The robust stand keeps the display stable at any position, and the smooth pivot function rotates 90 degrees in either direction for portrait orientation viewing. <br/>
<br/>
The built-in 3W speakers are adequate for system sounds but won't replace dedicated audio solutions – you won't be surprised to learn that they're noticeably inferior to MacBook speakers, and the less said about them the better.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display Performance and Color Accuracy</h2><br/>
Here's where the MA270U excels. The 60Hz panel's 3,840 x 2,160 resolution delivers crisp, vibrant visuals, while the 5ms response time is perfectly adequate (unless you're a hardcore FPS gamer). Colors pop without appearing oversaturated, and BenQ's color-matching technology is impressive – the difference between my MacBook Air's display and the MA270U was barely perceptible when using the recommended color profile. I even swapped out my Air for a MacBook Pro with a Liquid Retina XDR display, and only the brightness difference was visible. The monitor maintained consistent color reproduction across its 400 nits brightness range. Indeed, I was impressed with how good it looked alongside my Studio Display. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-10.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="4284" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985149" /><br/>
The Nano Matte panel handles glare admirably under normal conditions. However, direct sunlight remains challenging. It's not quite as effective as Apple's nano-texture glass option in this respect, but remember – that's a &#36;300 upgrade on the Studio Display, which also boasts a higher 600 nits of brightness. One other thing worth mentioning is how fast the MA series monitor wakes from sleep – it impressively matched the speed of my Mac and the Studio Display.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display Pilot 2 Software</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-9.jpeg" alt="" width="4032" height="3024" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985146" /><br/>
The Display Pilot 2 software deserves special mention, as it's clear BenQ has put serious effort into making this feel like a natural extension of the Mac experience. I never had to use the physical toggle on the bottom of the display to change settings via the OSD – the menu bar app effectively replaced it, offering native control of the MA270U. You can adjust these settings independently for each connected display, with options to sync them if desired, and you can customize which settings appear in the interface. For color management, Display Pilot 2 provides quick access to different color modes including M-Book (designed to match MacBook displays), Display P3, and sRGB. You can switch between them with a single click when dealing with color-critical work, and you can assign specific color modes to launch automatically with different applications – a nice touch that you'd usually only expect when using a reference monitor.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/benq-display-pilot-app.jpg" alt="" width="1798" height="1350" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984743" /><br/>
On the other hand, the Display Pilot software feels like it's half-baked in some respects, and some of the functions work better than others. I found the HDR option so-so – it blew out the colors when viewing my desktop, and only vaguely improved the movie-watching experience. The app also enables features like automatic display rotation and desktop partitioning, though macOS Sequoia's built-in window management makes the latter a little redundant. Meanwhile, the Low Blue Light mode seemed to have almost no effect. However, credit where credit is due: The Mac keyboard integration works seamlessly – adjusting the brightness and volume of the external panel from your MacBook feels natural, and the syncing is seamless. The ICCSync feature ensures the monitor's colors stay perfectly matched with your MacBook's display, and I particularly appreciated the Brightness Sync feature, which automatically matches the brightness levels between your MacBook and the MA270U. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/benq-display-pilot-2.jpg" alt="" width="1398" height="1050" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984744" /><br/>
FocuSync connects with macOS Focus modes to adjust display settings automatically based on your selected Focus state, while the B.I.+ Gen2 feature uses the monitor's ambient light sensor (located at the top of the panel) to adjust brightness and color temperature based on your environment. FocuSync isn't something I would ever use, but it worked as advertised once I granted the necessary permissions. The same can't be said for BenQ's Brightness Intelligence  feature, which often made everything overly dim and washed out in normal lighting conditions. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-11.jpeg" alt="" width="4032" height="3024" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985156" /><br/>
You can adjust the resolution in the app with a slider, but I found this wanting. In my experience, the native 3,840 x 2,160 resolution made text too small to read comfortably for any length of time, though the 32-inch model may fare better in this regard. My biggest bugbear is that the scaled options were too few and far between for me to find an optimal setting, so I ended up using the Better Display app instead, settling on 2,560 x 1,440 resolution, which paired well alongside the Studio Display (a 5K panel scaled to 2,560 x 1,440). Sat back normally and looking at both monitors, I got a decently uniform picture from them, with only the superior brightness of the Studio Display making the difference. Of course, in most contexts, comparing a 4K panel to a 5K panel is like comparing apples to oranges, but macOS scaling is so good these days that I genuinely can't tell the difference unless my nose is almost touching the screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summing Up</h2><br/>
The BenQ MA270U delivers where it counts – 4K display quality and Mac integration. While its design may not match Apple's aesthetic, its performance-to-price ratio is compelling. The 32-inch MA320U offers higher brightness (550 nits vs 400 nits) and a slightly better color gamut, but the core features remain identical.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ma270u-12.jpeg" alt="" width="5712" height="3714" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985159" /><br/>
This monitor should suit Mac users seeking a quality external display without Studio Display pricing (so long as you bring your own webcam and external speakers). It's especially appealing for productivity work, content consumption, and even light creative tasks, thanks to its excellent color reproduction. Professional creators might prefer BenQ's Thunderbolt PD series or the brighter image of a Apple's 5K Studio Display, but for everyone else, the MA270U represents excellent value.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Where to Buy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/benq-ma270u-27-inch.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985164" /><br/>
The BenQ MA270U is available from <a href="https://www.benq.com/en-us/monitor/home/ma270u/buy.html">BenQ's website</a> and authorized retailers for &#36;459.99/£449.99. The 32-inch MA320U retails for &#36;599.99/£549.99.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: BenQ provided MacRumors with a 27-inch MA270U 4K monitor for the purpose of the review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/review-benq-ma270u-4k-mac-monitor/">Review: BenQ&#039;s Affordable MA270U 4K Monitor Is Made for MacBooks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-benqs-affordable-ma270u-4k-monitor-is-made-for-macbooks.2447319/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;100 Off iPad Mini 7 With Return of All-Time Low Prices, Starting at &#36;399</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/amazon-100-off-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-100-off-ipad-mini-7-with-return-of-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-399.2447309/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 06:29:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/amazon-100-off-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week is providing record low prices on multiple models of the iPad mini 7, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3W4YHS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;499.00. <a href="https://howl.link/ho4257i3vi5ui">Best Buy is also matching</a> every one of these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972027" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has three colors of the 128GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 on sale at this all-time low price, and it's the first time in 2025 that we've seen any deal on the new tablet. You can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3WGKKB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.00</strong></a> and the 512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XHBH9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;699.99</strong></a>, both &#36;100 discounts and available in multiple colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3W4YHS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3WGKKB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3XHBH9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>512GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 7 for &#36;699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Deals on cellular models are a bit rarer on Amazon, with one color of the 128GB cellular iPad mini 7 on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DK3WJTNQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;549.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;649.00. If you prefer shopping at Best Buy, remember that the retailer is <a href="https://howl.link/ho4257i3vi5ui">matching all of these sales on the iPad mini 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/amazon-100-off-ipad-mini-7/">Amazon Takes &#36;100 Off iPad Mini 7 With Return of All-Time Low Prices, Starting at &#36;399</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-100-off-ipad-mini-7-with-return-of-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-399.2447309/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
