<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 03:01:18 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>M5 MacBook Models to Use New Compact Camera Module in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-macbook-models-to-use-new-compact-camera-module-in-2025.2431570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 02:58:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in 2025 will take on a new compact camera module (CCM) supplier for future MacBook models powered by its next-generation M5 chip, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/New-MacBook-Pros-Launching-Tomorrow-With-These-4-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921192" /><br/>
Writing in his latest investor note on <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/舜宇光學2025年營運動能可望顯著受益於成為apple新相機模組供應商與iphone訂單回流-sunny-opticals-2025-business-momentum-to-benefit-509819818c2a">Medium</a>, Kuo said Apple will turn to Sunny Optical for the CCM in its M5 MacBooks. The Chinese optical lens company will mass produce the CCMs in Vietnam, and provide a complete imaging system integrated into a compact form factor for the new laptops. <br/>
<br/>
The primary suppliers of camera modules for MacBooks are currently LG InnoTek and Sharp. In Apple's optical component supply chain, only Sunny Optical can simultaneously supply CCM and lenses in a single package, which gives the company the advantage of vertical integration. If shipments for the MacBooks go smoothly, Kuo predicts that Sunny Optical could also become the new CCM supplier for future iPhone and iPad models. <br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to update the 14-inch MacBook Pro with an M4 chip as soon as late 2024, and we could perhaps see a refresh before the end of the year. The high-end 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models are also expected to see a late 2024 refresh with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-plans-thinner-iphone-slimmer-macbook/">thinner version of the MacBook Pro</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. The ultrathin 2024 iPad Pro serves as a model for Apple's upcoming design philosophy, with the company planning to offer "the thinnest and lightest products" in each category across the tech industry. <br/>
<br/>
It's not clear when a thinner MacBook Pro might come out, since no design changes are rumored for the 2024 refresh, but it's possible that 2025 could be the year that Apple debuts redesigned laptops based on its M5 chip. Apple is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/07/25/face-id-for-mac-couple-of-years/">rumored</a> to be working on Face ID for the Mac, and it's likely that the MacBook Pro will be one of the first Macs to get Face ID, but there are no concrete details about when that might happen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/17/apple-camera-module-supplier-macbook-models-2025/">M5 MacBook Models to Use New Compact Camera Module in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m5-macbook-models-to-use-new-compact-camera-module-in-2025.2431570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Install the macOS Sequoia Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-install-the-macos-sequoia-public-beta.2431566/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 01:16:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta&#038;post_date=1721214995/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has made a macOS 15 Sequoia beta available for its public beta testing group, letting public beta testers try out the software before it launches this fall. Keep reading to learn whether you should install it on your Mac, and if so, how to go about it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-macOS-Sequoia-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954631" /><br/>
Signing up to get the macOS Sequoia beta is simple, and can be done by enrolling a Mac in Apple's free Apple Beta Software Program. The steps you need to complete to install the software on your device are provided towards the end of this article, but before you jump ahead, here are a few things worth considering.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Should I Install macOS Sequoia Public Beta?</h2><br/>
Before downloading the update, it's worth noting that Apple does not recommend installing the macOS Sequoia Beta on your main Mac, so if you have a secondary Mac that has no important data on it, use that. This is beta software, which means there are often bugs and issues that pop up that can prevent software from working properly or cause other problems. <br/>
<br/>
With that caveat in mind, the steps in the remainder of this article show you how to get the macOS 15 beta on your Mac. First though, check that you have a compatible Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will macOS Sequoia run on My Mac?</h2><br/>
macOS 15 Sequoia works with the same Macs as macOS 14 Sonoma other than the 2018 and 2019 MacBook Air. They include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li>MacBook Air (2020 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>MacBook Pro (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Mini (2018 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>iMac Pro (2017 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Pro (2019 and later)</li><br/>
    <li>Mac Studio (2022 and later)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can check your Mac's model by clicking the Apple in the menu bar and choosing About This Mac. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Don't Forget to Back Up Your Mac</h2><br/>
Be sure to back up your Mac using Time Machine before installing the software using the method, otherwise you won't be able to revert back to the previous version of macOS if things go wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Download macOS Sequoia Public Beta</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-beta-software-program.jpg" alt="" width="2774" height="1494" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958873" /><ol><br/>
 	<li>On your Mac, open up Safari and navigate to the <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple Beta Software Program website</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap the <strong>Sign up</strong> button and enter your Apple ID credentials, or sign in with your Apple ID if you've signed up to beta test a previous update.</li><br/>
 	<li>Agree to the Apple Beta Software Program terms and conditions if required.</li><br/>
 	<li>After signing in, you'll see a main screen that's a Guide for Public Betas. Click on <strong>macOS</strong>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Read through Apple's instructions carefully, and then using the link in the "Get Started" section, select <strong>enroll your iOS device</strong>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Make sure to make an backup of your current version of macOS using Time Machine by following Apple's instructions. This will allow you to downgrade back to your earlier version of macOS if necessary and is crucial if you don't enjoy the macOS Sequoia testing experience.</li><br/>
<li>If your Mac is running macOS Ventura 13.4 or later, go to <strong>System Settings -> General -> Software Update</strong> and click the <strong>Info</strong> button next to "Beta updates." Then choose the macOS beta you'd like to install. If your Mac is running macOS Ventura 13.3 or earlier, download Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com/download/1016471">macOS Beta Access Utility</a> and run the installer. Then follow the onscreen instructions to complete installation. Note that your Mac must be signed in with the same Apple ID you used to enroll in the Apple Beta Software Program.</li></ol>Installation of the macOS beta is manually chosen in <strong>System Settings -> General -> Software Update</strong>. If a newly released beta is not available when you check, you will receive a notification when it is available to download.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>macOS Sequoia Features</h2><br/>
macOS Sequoia's standout feature is iPhone Mirroring, enabling you to control your iPhone from your Mac using your keyboard and mouse. This includes viewing notifications and using iPhone apps even when the device is tucked away and locked. Later this year, you'll also be able to drag and drop apps between your Mac and iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
Window tiling has been enhanced for easier management of multiple windows. Safari now offers webpage summaries and highlights, while the Messages app supports message scheduling and Tapback reactions with any emoji. A new Passwords app simplifies managing passwords, logins, and passkeys. The Photos app has a redesigned interface, and the Notes app now includes audio transcription and summarization, along with automatic equation solving.<br/>
<br/>
macOS Sequoia incorporates all new Apple Intelligence features coming to iOS 18, providing various quality of life improvements. These include writing tools for proofreading and polishing your text across apps, the Image Playground for creating unique images, and Genmoji for designing custom emojis. The Photos app features a Clean Up tool for removing unwanted images, and Siri has improved AI for better language understanding and contextual relevance, even consulting ChatGPT for complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Additional features are also coming to macOS Sequoia. More details are available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/install-macos-sequoia-public-beta/">How to Install the macOS Sequoia Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-install-the-macos-sequoia-public-beta.2431566/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-passwords-app-all-the-features.2431538/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:23:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords&#038;post_date=1721183000/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple created a standalone Passwords app that streamlines login and password management. You've been able to store password information on your Apple devices through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain for years, but accessing passwords was a little difficult because the data was tucked away in the Settings app. That's no longer the case, and in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, it's much simpler to create and manage passwords for websites and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Generic-iOS-18-Passwords-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959050" /><br/>
This guide goes over everything you need to know about the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="layout">Layout</h2><br/>
The Passwords app is installed automatically when upgrading to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>. The app has a simple layout with a search bar right at the top, so you can look up the information that you're looking for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959069" /><br/>
If you've already used the &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain feature, all of your saved logins and passwords will be ready to go as soon as you authenticate with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>. There are separate sections for passwords and logins (under All), Passkeys, two-factor authentication codes, Wi-Fi passwords, security warnings, and logins that have been deleted.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-passwords-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957056" /><br/>
You can tap in to any of the sections to see what's listed there, and tapping on an individual entry shows the login and password. Each entry has fields for site or app name, username, login, verification code, websites where the login is used, and notes. There's also a one-tap option for changing your password for any given entry.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app-wifi.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959075" /><br/>
The layout of the Passwords app is similar to what you see in the Passwords section of the Settings app in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="adding_logins_and_passwords">Adding Logins and Passwords</h2><br/>
To add a login or password to the Passwords app, it's as simple as tapping on the "+" button at the bottom of the main interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-add-password.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959071" /><br/>
The Passwords app populates a new entry with a password automatically, and you just need to add the website name and username, then copy the password and put it in the app, website, or service you're signing up for. Tapping on Save will save the information.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to add information to an existing entry, you can tap into the relevant section, such as All, search for the login you want to update, tap it, and then select the "Edit" option to get to the editing interface for adding notes, changing a password, or adding a verification code.<br/>
<br/>
Passwords and logins are added automatically to the Passwords app when you have &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain enabled and you create a new login in Safari or in an app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="changing_passwords">Changing Passwords</h2><br/>
To change a Password, you just need to open up the Passwords app, search for the login you want to update, tap on Edit, and then tap on the "Change Password..." option. You can also browse through Passwords using the "All" section.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping on Change Password opens up the website associated with the login and password, but you will need to initiate the password change process on the site by logging into your account and finding the appropriate option for updating a password.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="deleting_passwords">Deleting Passwords</h2><br/>
To delete a password, go to the "All" section and browse until you find it, or search for a specific login. From the "All" overview, you can swipe from right to left to bring up a delete option. Just tap on delete to remove the password.<br/>
<br/>
You can also tap into any of your logins, choose Edit, and select Delete Password from there. To delete multiple logins, tap on the Select tool at the top right of the display (it looks like a list with a checkmark) and then tap any of the logins you want to delete. When you're done, tap on Delete again to delete them all.<br/>
<br/>
Passwords that you have deleted are stored in a Deleted folder in the Passwords app for 30 days before they're permanently deleted. You can tap into that folder and swipe to delete logins and passwords right away. Alternatively, you can use the select button at the top to delete multiple logins at one time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="authentication_codes">Authentication Codes</h2><br/>
The Passwords app can provide two-factor authentication codes for sites that make additional security options available. To add a two-factor authentication code, tap on the "Codes" section of the main Passwords interface.<br/>
<br/>
From there, tap on the "+" button. You can either scan a QR code with a camera, which is a common way two-factor authentication apps work, or enter a setup key. Once the code is stored in the Passwords app, you can open up the Codes section at any time to get a temporary code to log in to a site or app.<br/>
<br/>
Two-factor authentication codes also show up when you search for a password and login or browse through logins in the "All" section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="passkeys">Passkeys</h2><br/>
Websites have started transitioning from passwords to passkeys, and the Passwords app stores your passkeys as well as your logins and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-passkey.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959070" /><br/>
Passkeys are more secure than passwords, and they let you log into your accounts using &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; authentication on an Apple device. Passkeys basically use a cryptographic key pair, with one public key stored on a server and a private key stored on your device.<br/>
<br/>
Private keys are not shared, they remain on-device only, and can't be sent to other people, protecting your accounts from phishing attempts.<br/>
<br/>
You can see your stored passkeys in the Passkeys section of the Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="password_sharing">Password Sharing</h2><br/>
The Passwords app lets you set up and share select passwords with trusted contacts. You can create one or more groups of people that include family and friends, providing them with access to shared logins and passwords.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-shared-groups.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959072" /><br/>
Creating a group can be done by tapping on the folder on the left hand side of the main Passwords interface. Type in a name, and then select people to add. Note that anyone you add needs to be in your contacts list.<br/>
<br/>
From there, you can select logins and passwords that you want to share. Logins and passwords can be removed at any time, and all members of a group can contribute logins. The group creator can remove people from the group at any time.<br/>
<br/>
To share a password with someone in person, you can search for the login that you want to share and then use the Share Sheet to open up an AirDrop interface that will let you AirDrop the login and password information. The Share Sheet is only designed for this kind of in-person sharing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="autofill">AutoFill</h2><br/>
If you have AutoFill enabled on your devices, your logins and passwords will be entered automatically when you visit a website in Safari that you have stored login information for. AutoFill will pop up an option for the appropriate login and password on any account login field in Safari or in an app.<br/>
<br/>
AutoFill works the same as it did when passwords were limited to the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="sorting">Sorting</h2><br/>
In the "All" section of the Passwords app, you can tap on the icon that features two arrows to get to sorting options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-password-app-sorting.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959073" /><br/>
Sorting options include Date Edited, Date Created, Website, or Title, and each of these can be displayed in a Descending or Ascending list by tapping on the desired option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="syncing">Syncing</h2><br/>
Passwords are synced automatically between all of your Apple devices using &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain. You just need to have the option turned on and you need to be logged in to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> on any device where you want to access your passwords.<br/>
<br/>
You can even get to your logins and passwords on a Windows PC because Apple is adding the Passwords app to iTunes for Windows.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="security">Security</h2><br/>
There is a dedicated Security section in the Passwords app, and it lets you know if you have a password that is reused, too weak, or has been compromised in a data leak.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-passwords-app-security.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1289" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959074" /><br/>
Warnings are accompanied by information letting you know that a password change is in order, and you can tap on the Change Password option to go to the website where you need to update your information.<br/>
<br/>
For any individual login, you'll also see information letting you know if your password is weak or strong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="importing_passwords">Importing Passwords</h2><br/>
Apple plans to provide a tool for importing passwords from other services like 1Password and LastPass, but as of now, this functionality has not yet been implemented.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For more on the new features that Apple is adding in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-passwords/">iOS 18 Passwords App: All the Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-passwords-app-all-the-features.2431538/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Store App Gets Overhaul With Revamped For You Section</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-store-app-overhaul/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-app-gets-overhaul-with-revamped-for-you-section.2431529/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:57:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-store-app-overhaul/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> app to introduce a more personalized For You experience, which offers up more relevant product and service suggestions along with more information on what you can do with your existing devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Apple-Store-App-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886114" /><br/>
The entire navigation bar has been refreshed, replacing Shop with Products and Sessions with Go Further. The For You tab provides relevant offers and suggestions such as free <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> trials, while the Products tab lets you see new products and also shop for accessories for your devices.<br/>
<br/>
The "Go Further" tab shows nearby Today at Apple sessions, provides help with device setup, and offers support for your devices. For these new changes, Apple has a new opt-in data collection feature. Apple says that it collects data about your shopping activity, subscriptions, and more to make suggestions, but there is an option to not provide this information to Apple.<blockquote>To create a personalised shopping experience, we'll collect and use data about your device, Apple account, Apple Store shopping activity and Apple subscriptions.<br/>
<br/>
Privacy is important, and we want to be clear about what we're collecting and how we will use it. You can modify these at any time in Account Settings.</blockquote><br/>
The updated version of the &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; app also includes a new Today at Apple video series with short videos that you can watch to get tips on device features.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's full release notes for the refreshed &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; app are below.<br/>
<blockquote><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>A fresh, more curated experience that makes it easier to quickly find the most relevant content on the For You tab, shop the latest on the Products tab, and make the most of the devices you already own on the Go Further tab.</li><br/>
 	<li>Check out the new video series from Today at Apple with featured guests that will inspire you to do more with your devices.</li><br/>
 	<li>New options to customize your privacy settings and preferences give you enhanced control over how Apple will use the data you share with us.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
</blockquote>The &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; app can be downloaded for free from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-store/id375380948">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-store-app-overhaul/">Apple Store App Gets Overhaul With Revamped For You Section</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-store-app-gets-overhaul-with-revamped-for-you-section.2431529/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Day: Massive Discounts Arrive for M3 MacBook Air, Starting at Just &#36;849</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/prime-day-m3-macbook-air-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-massive-discounts-arrive-for-m3-macbook-air-starting-at-just-849.2431526/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:39:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/prime-day-m3-macbook-air-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has &#36;250 off every model of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple's 2024 M3 MacBook Air</a> for Prime Day, including both the 13-inch and 15-inch models. All of these discounts require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the final deal price, and it's worth mentioning that Best Buy is matching these prices for My Best Buy Plus/Total members.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m3-macbook-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958729" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> for the 8GB RAM/256GB SSD 13-inch MacBook Air, which is down from &#36;1,099.00. For the bigger model, prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a> for the 8GB RAM/256GB SSD 15-inch MacBook Air, down from &#36;1,299.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With the addition of the &#36;50 on-page coupon, these are now the lowest price we've ever seen on the brand new M3 MacBook Air, and they're among the overall best Apple-related deals you can find during Prime Day.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;849.00, down from &#36;1,099.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmGoTmtUwzS">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQBNsFbNk">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX246FNZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQCCPC5E3">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>15-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,049.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDrLzdh5">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,249.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDI1Z9Ul">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BN3L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,449.00, down from &#36;1,699.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQD4AX4A0">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking to spend a little less, and are fine with investing in a previous generation model, Amazon also has great deals on the 2022 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. You can get the 256GB model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;799.00</strong></a> (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQA1aRSRo">matched at Best Buy</a>) and the 512GB model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQBiXyWV2">also matched at Best Buy</a>), and they're both &#36;200 off and all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/prime-day-m3-macbook-air-2/">Amazon Prime Day: Massive Discounts Arrive for M3 MacBook Air, Starting at Just &#36;849</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-massive-discounts-arrive-for-m3-macbook-air-starting-at-just-849.2431526/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Takes Up to 20% Off Select Audio Products in Prime Day-Like Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/sonos-prime-day-like-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-takes-up-to-20-off-select-audio-products-in-prime-day-like-sale.2431515/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:02:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/sonos-prime-day-like-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos today has opened up its own <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Prime Day inspired sale</a>, offering steep discounts on select home theater audio equipment. This includes low prices on the Sonos Roam 2 portable speaker, as well as various discounted bundles, all of which are rare deals we haven't tracked since earlier in the summer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/sonos-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959042" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale has a good balance between individual Sonos products and bundles that should help elevate your home theater setup with various soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers. Highlights of the event include the <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-2">Sonos Roam 2 for &#36;143</a> and <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Sonos Era 100 Smart Speaker for &#36;199</a>, both of which are all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 20% OFF</div>Sonos Home Theater Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've accumulated a few of the devices in the sale below, but be sure to <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">browse this landing page</a> on the Sonos website for everything being discounted.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Speakers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-2">Roam 2 Portable Speaker</a> - &#36;143, down from &#36;199</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-2-charging-set">Roam 2 Charging Set</a> - &#36;192, down from &#36;228</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Era 100 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Bundles</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/two-room-set-era-100">2 Room Set with Era 100</a> - &#36;398, down from &#36;498</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/multiroom-entertainment-set-arc-and-move-2">Arc + Move 2 Speaker Bundle</a> - &#36;1,208, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/personal-entertainment-set-sonos-ace-arc">Arc + Sonos Ace Headphones Bundle</a> - &#36;1,280, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/3-1-entertainment-set-beam-sub">Beam + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,168, down from &#36;1,298</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/surround-set-arc-era-100-pair">Arc + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,257, down from &#36;1,397</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,528, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-beam-sub-era-100-pair">Beam + Sub + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,566, down from &#36;1,796</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/sonos-prime-day-like-sale/">Sonos Takes Up to 20% Off Select Audio Products in Prime Day-Like Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-takes-up-to-20-off-select-audio-products-in-prime-day-like-sale.2431515/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The 9 Best Apple Deals Under &#36;100 for Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/9-best-apple-deals-under-100/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-9-best-apple-deals-under-100-for-prime-day.2431503/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:31:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/9-best-apple-deals-under-100/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As Prime Day continues today, we're highlighting all of the best Apple deals you can get for under &#36;100 on Amazon. This includes AirPods, Apple Pencil 2, AirTags, iPhone cases, USB-C chargers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/primeday2022.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853875" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/"><strong>every Apple deal available during Prime Day</strong></a> in our dedicated post. Remember that you'll need an <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon Prime membership</a> to get Prime Day deals, and you can sign up for Prime on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>&#36;30 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/usb-c-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959021" /><br/>
<br/>
In the cheapest category, you can get Apple's 20W USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;14.99, down from &#36;19.00 and the AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;23.99, down from &#36;29.00<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-20W-USB-C-Power-Adapter%2Fdp%2FB08L5M9BTJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>20W USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;14.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-USB-C-Woven-Charge-Cable%2Fdp%2FB0BJMDHRPS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>60W USB-C Woven Cable (1m) for &#36;15.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Fref%3Dods_ucc_kindle_B0CWXNS552_rc_nd_ucc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;5 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;23.99</div></a></div><h2>&#36;50 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/finewoven-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959020" /><br/>
<br/>
For accessories priced between &#36;30 and &#36;50, there are a few sales on Amazon for Prime Day. You can get the 35W Dual USB-C Port Power Adapter for &#36;44.99, down from &#36;59.00, as well as discounts on iPhone 15 cases.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-USB-C-Compact-Power-Adapter%2Fdp%2FB0D1XRRQZJ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>35W Dual USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;44.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWS35B9%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;24 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro FineWoven Case for &#36;34.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7V9X5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;24 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case for &#36;34.99</div></a></div><h2>&#36;100 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/airtag-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958606" /><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, we're tracking a few deals on Apple products that are just under &#36;100 for Prime Day. You can get an AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;74.98 (&#36;24 off), an Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00 (&#36;50 off), and AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00 (&#36;60 off).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-MX542LL-A-AirTag-pack%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;24 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;74.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/9-best-apple-deals-under-100/">The 9 Best Apple Deals Under &#36;100 for Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-9-best-apple-deals-under-100-for-prime-day.2431503/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Lists Products Eligible for Sales Tax-Free Holidays in 8 U.S. States</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-2024-sales-tax-free-holidays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lists-products-eligible-for-sales-tax-free-holidays-in-8-u-s-states.2431511/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-2024-sales-tax-free-holidays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently updated its website with a list of products <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/campaigns/tax-holiday">eligible for upcoming 2024 sales tax holidays</a> in select U.S. states, including Alabama, Arkansas, Florida, Massachusetts, Missouri, Ohio, Tennessee, and West Virginia.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-Sales-Tax-Free-Holidays.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959038" /><br/>
Sales tax holidays provide a limited-time opportunity to purchase select Apple products online or in stores without paying sales tax. Eligible products and price limits vary from state to state, with complete details <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/campaigns/tax-holiday">outlined on Apple's website</a>. Apple says tax savings may not appear during checkout, but will be reflected on the final receipt.<br/>
<br/>
The tax-free holidays run from July 19 through August 11, with the exact dates varying by state. Some other U.S states are offering tax-free holidays this summer, but they are not listed on Apple's website at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Sales tax holidays are especially beneficial to students, as the tax savings can be combined with Apple's ongoing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-back-to-schoo-promotion-launches/">Back to School promotion</a>, which offers students up to a &#36;150 Apple gift card with the purchase of an eligible Mac or iPad, as well as 20% off AppleCare+ plans. This is in addition to Apple's standard educational discounts on select products.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-2024-sales-tax-free-holidays/">Apple Lists Products Eligible for Sales Tax-Free Holidays in 8 U.S. States</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-lists-products-eligible-for-sales-tax-free-holidays-in-8-u-s-states.2431511/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431507/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:11:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 update to developers, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-3/">released the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macOS-Sonoma-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-957372" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6, and no new features have been discovered in the betas so far.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431507/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431505/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:10:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to developers for testing purposes, with software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/">third iOS and iPadOS 17.6 betas</a> were released.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The features Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no major new additions have been discovered in the betas so far.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431505/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Fourth Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fourth-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2431508/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:09:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the fourth beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.3 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The fourth &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-releases-visionos-1-3-beta-3-to-developers/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3, as well as implement additional bug fixes. No new features were found in the first three &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-4/">Apple Releases Fourth Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-fourth-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2431508/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2431509/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:08:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.6 update to developers for testing purposes, with the fourth beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-3-to-developers/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.6 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.6 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what's included in watchOS 10.6, and with Apple's focus shifting to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, it likely features bug fixes and other minor improvements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-4/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2431509/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431506/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:06:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fourth beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.6 to developers for testing purposes, with the update coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.6 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.6.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-4-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Fourth Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers [Update: Public Beta Available]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers-update-public-beta-available.2431506/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches New Safari Ad Campaign: &#039;A Browser That&#039;s Actually Private&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-safari-ad-campaign/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-safari-ad-campaign-a-browser-thats-actually-private.2431496/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-safari-ad-campaign/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a new privacy-focused Safari ad, which is designed to highlight the ways that Safari protects user privacy compared to other browsers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0HjDpPnxcP0" title="Privacy on iPhone | Flock | Apple" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the spot, security cameras are positioned as pesky birds and bats, hovering around smartphone users as they browse the web. The cameras are everywhere, representing website trackers. Much of the ad is focused on non-iPhone users, but toward the end, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users opens up Safari and all the creepy cameras explode in mid-air.<br/>
<br/>
The video is accompanied by billboards in cities around the world and short digital ads that are being shown on social networks. Apple has also highlighted some of the recent privacy updates made to Safari <a href="https://webkit.org/blog/15697/private-browsing-2-0/">on its WebKit blog</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Safari has long protected advertisers from tracking users across the web with cross-site tracking, and it uses Intelligent Tracking Prevention to suss out and block domains collecting tracking data.<br/>
<br/>
IP addresses are hidden from known trackers in Safari, as this can be used to identify users across websites, plus location information is not shared without express user permission and with optional time limitations. To cut down on fingerprinting, a tracking technique that uses system configuration info, Safari provides limited information to trackers to make devices look more identical.<br/>
<br/>
The Safari Private Browsing mode offers an option to use a different search engine, it strips information added to URLs for tracking purposes, it has a content blocker to block network requests from known trackers, and it restricts web extensions that have access to webpage content and browsing history.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+ subscribers have additional protections with &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Private Relay and Safari Private Browsing, including separate sessions for every tab so sites can't tell if two tabs came from the same device and a non-specific IP location based on country and time zone.<br/>
<br/>
Tracking preventions that Apple designed specifically for Private Browsing mode are enabled by default when in that mode, but they can also be enabled for regular browsing by going to Settings &gt; Apps &gt; Safari &gt; Advanced &gt; Advanced Tracking and Fingerprinting Protection on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and toggling on the "All Browsing" feature. On a Mac, the setting can be found under Safari &gt; Settings &gt; Advanced.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, a number of Safari's protections are not offered by other browsers such as Chrome, which makes Safari the ideal choice for privacy. Safari's unique features include using machine learning to combat cross-site tracking, removing unique trackers from URLs in Private Browsing, hiding IP address from known trackers, preventing web extensions from seeing browsing by default, not sharing location data with search engine, and blocking known trackers in Private Browsing.<br/>
<br/>
More information on Safari's privacy protections can be found on <a href="https://apple.com/privacy">Apple's privacy website</a>, with specific technical information <a href="https://webkit.org/blog/15697/private-browsing-2-0/">available on the WebKit blog</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-safari-ad-campaign/">Apple Launches New Safari Ad Campaign: &#039;A Browser That&#039;s Actually Private&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-safari-ad-campaign-a-browser-thats-actually-private.2431496/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wallet App Now Works With PRESTO Fare Card in Toronto Area</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-wallet-app-presto-card/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-works-with-presto-fare-card-in-toronto-area.2431494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 08:32:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-wallet-app-presto-card/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/newsroom/2024/07/apple-and-metrolinx-introduce-presto-card-for-iphone-and-apple-watch/">Apple</a> and <a href="https://www.prestocard.ca/en/about/presto-in-mobile-wallet/apple">Metrolinx</a> today announced that the PRESTO card can <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/apple-pay/transit/toronto/">now be added to the Wallet app</a>, allowing commuters in Toronto, Canada and the surrounding area to tap an iPhone or Apple Watch to pay for a fare on buses, streetcars, trains, and the subway. Funds can be loaded onto the card directly in the Wallet app for added convenience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-Wallet-PRESTO.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958998" /><br/>
Express Mode allows commuters to simply hold their iPhone or Apple Watch near a payment reader to pay for their ride, without needing to unlock or wake the device. This mode even works for up to five hours after your iPhone runs out of battery power.<br/>
<br/>
Transit agencies that accept the PRESTO card in the Wallet app include the TTC and UP Express in Toronto, HSR in Hamilton, MiWay in Mississauga, Brampton Transit, Burlington Transit, Durham Region Transit, Oakville Transit, and York Region Transit, as well as the GO Transit network. The feature does not work with OC Transpo in Ottawa.<br/>
<br/>
To add the PRESTO card to the Wallet app, tap on the plus sign in the top-right corner, select Transit Card, and select PRESTO. A physical PRESTO card can also be converted for use in the Wallet app, but the physical card will no longer work. The version in the Wallet app supports various fare types, and Ontario's new One Fare program.<br/>
<br/>
Adding a PRESTO card to the Wallet app requires an iPhone 8 or later with iOS 16.4 or later, or an Apple Watch Series 4 or later with watchOS 9.4 or later.<br/>
<br/>
For additional information, read the <a href="https://prestocard.ca/en/about/presto-in-mobile-wallet/apple">PRESTO in Apple Wallet page</a> and <a href="https://prestocard.ca/en/support/faqs/PRESTO-in-Apple-Wallet">FAQ</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://x.com/ApolloZhaoD">Apollo Zhao</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/apple-wallet-app-presto-card/">Apple Wallet App Now Works With PRESTO Fare Card in Toronto Area</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallet-app-now-works-with-presto-fare-card-in-toronto-area.2431494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>2024 Apple Watch Lineup: Key Changes We&#039;re Expecting</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes-were-expecting.2431492/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:59:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is seemingly planning a rework of the Apple Watch lineup for 2024, according to a range of reports from over the past year. Here's everything we know so far. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
Apple is expected to continue to offer three different Apple Watch models in five casing sizes, but the various display sizes will allegedly grow by up to 12% and the casings will get taller. Based on all of the latest rumors, this is what we are expecting to change:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch Lineup 2023–2024</th><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch Lineup 2024–2025</th><br/>
 <th>Price</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch SE (second generation)</strong><br/>
40mm casing<br/>
1.57-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch SE (third generation)</strong><br/>
41mm casing<br/>
1.69-inch display (+7.64%)</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;249</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch SE (second generation)</strong><br/>
44mm casing<br/>
1.78-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch SE (third generation)</strong><br/>
45mm casing<br/>
1.89-inch display (+6.18%)</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;279</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Series 9</strong><br/>
41mm casing<br/>
1.69-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Series 10</strong><br/>
45mm casing<br/>
1.89-inch display (+11.83%)</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;399</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Series 9</strong><br/>
45mm casing<br/>
1.89-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Series 10</strong><br/>
49mm casing<br/>
2.04-inch display (+7.94%)</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;449</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Ultra 2</strong><br/>
49mm casing<br/>
1.99-inch display</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Apple Watch Ultra 3</strong><br/>
~52mm casing?<br/>
2.13-inch display (+7.04%)</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;799</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The first- and second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> models use the design of the Apple Watch Series 4, which was introduced in 2018. With the third generation, Apple is expected to update the SE to the design introduced with the Apple Watch Series 7 in 2021 for a more modern appearance with a larger screen and slimmer bezels.<br/>
<br/>
For Apple's main "Series" line of Apple Watches, the smallest casing size is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">discontinued</a>. The original Apple Watch and Series 1, 2, and 3 were available in a 38mm casing, and this grew to 40mm with the Series 4. With the Series 7, it grew further still to 41mm.<br/>
<br/>
This year, the larger of the two standard Apple Watch casing sizes, the 45mm model, is expected to become the smallest option. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">all-new 49mm casing size</a>, matching the current Apple Watch Ultra, is expected to be introduced as the new larger option. The 49mm Apple Watch Ultra is compatible with bands designed for the 45mm Apple Watch Series models, so it is possible that Apple Watch bands could be compatible across both Series 10 models and the Apple Watch Ultra for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
The design of the Apple Watch Series 10 is expected to be largely the same as that of the Series 9 and its other predecessors, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/">leaked CAD renders</a>, meaning that the all-new 49mm model will be the most striking addition.<br/>
<br/>
DSCC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/07/microled-apple-watch-ultra-2025/">Ross Young</a>, Haitong International Securities's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/02/cheaper-airpods-and-micro-led-apple-watch-rumors/">Jeff Pu</a>, and Omdia's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">David Hsieh</a> have claimed that the next-generation Apple Watch Ultra will feature a larger 2.13-inch display, but it is worth noting that many of these reports related to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">now-canceled</a> introduction of a microLED display. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> says that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">no design changes</a> are expected for the Apple Watch Ultra 3, so the larger display size is far from certain and it could in reality have the same casing and display size as the current model.<br/>
<br/>
If the rumors pan out, all of the 2024 Apple Watch models will be larger than the models they replace in the lineup. New features for the Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch Ultra 3 include the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">S10 chip with AI enhancements</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/01/2024-apple-watch-blood-pressure-sleep-apnea/">hypertension detection, and sleep apnea detection</a>. The entire new Apple Watch lineup is expected to be announced in the fall as usual alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes/">2024 Apple Watch Lineup: Key Changes We&#039;re Expecting</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/2024-apple-watch-lineup-key-changes-were-expecting.2431492/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Lutron Debuts New Diva Smart Dimmer With ELV+, Additional Pico Paddle Remote Colors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/lutron-elv-diva-smart-dimmer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lutron-debuts-new-diva-smart-dimmer-with-elv-additional-pico-paddle-remote-colors.2431490/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/lutron-elv-diva-smart-dimmer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Lutron</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Smart home company Lutron today announced a few new additions to its <a href="https://www.casetawireless.com/us/en/products/dimmers-switches">Caséta line of products</a>, expanding the range of lighting options available to consumers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/lutron-smart-dimmer.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958804" /><br/>
For professional installers, there is now a Diva smart dimmer with ELV+ technology, offering smart control for low-voltage applications like under-cabinet lighting, track lights, and accent lights. The dimmer works with ELV devices and with nearly all residential lighting types and loads, such as LED, MLV, incandescent, and halogen.<br/>
<br/>
Like the Smart Dimmer Switch for ELV+ Lighting, the Diva version uses phase-selectable dimming to enable dimming across a range of load types. Installers can select between forward or reverse-phase dimming in the Lutron app or when installing the light.<br/>
<br/>
The Diva smart dimmer with ELV+ is available in white, ivory, light almond, black, brown, and gray to match other switches and outlets in the home.<br/>
<br/>
Lutron is also introducing new color options for the Pico Paddle Remote, which was previously only available in white. The Pico Paddle Remote now comes in white, ivory, light almond, black, brown, and gray, much like other Caséta accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/lutron-pico-paddle-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1112" height="623" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958805" /><br/>
The Pico Paddle Remote can control Caséta smart switches and dimmers and Serena smart shades and fans, adding extra control options for lights and smart home products. The Pico Paddle Remotes have a 10-year battery life and do not require a hub, app, or Wi-Fi for operation.<br/>
<br/>
The Diva smart dimmer ELV+ and new Pico Paddle Remote options <a href="https://www.casetawireless.com/us/en/products/dimmers-switches">are available through</a> electrical distributors and online retailers that carry Caséta controls.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lutron/">Lutron</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/lutron-elv-diva-smart-dimmer/">Lutron Debuts New Diva Smart Dimmer With ELV+, Additional Pico Paddle Remote Colors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lutron-debuts-new-diva-smart-dimmer-with-elv-additional-pico-paddle-remote-colors.2431490/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Special-Edition Beats Solo 4 Headphones Celebrate 15th Anniversary of Minecraft</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/minecraft-beats-solo-4-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/special-edition-beats-solo-4-headphones-celebrate-15th-anniversary-of-minecraft.2431488/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 07:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/minecraft-beats-solo-4-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Minecraft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Beats brand has done a number of collaborations over the years with fashion designers, artists, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/16/mickey-mouse-beats-solo-3-headphones/">and even Disney</a>, and the latest partnership is with Minecraft for <a href="https://beatsbydre.com/headphones/solo4-wireless/MYJ03/solo4-chargedblack">special-edition Beats Solo 4 headphones</a> in recognition of the game's 15th anniversary.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/beats-solo-4-minecraft-green.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958792" /><br/>
Functionally, these are the same Solo 4 on-ear headphones that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">debuted several months ago</a>, but they come in a unique Minecraft-themed design with the Minecraft text logo on the top of the headband and neon green Minecraft pixelated patterns and accents across the remainder of the band and the outside of the ear cups. Even the iconic Beats "b" logo button for controlling media is in neon green, and there's a hidden neon green creeper on the inside of the headband.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/beats-solo-4-minecraft-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958794" /><br/>
Minecraft branding extends to the case for the Solo 4 headphones, with the Beats logo and raised Minecraft pixelated patterns in neon green on the front panel. As with the standard versions of the Solo 4 headphones, the nylon case zips open to allow the folded headphones to slide in, and there are small pockets inside for the included USB-C to USB-C and 3.5mm to 3.5mm cables.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/beats-solo-4-minecraft-live.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958795" /><br/>
With the purchase of the Beats x Minecraft Special Edition Solo 4 headphones, customers will also receive a unique code that can be redeemed for an in-game headphone character creator item in Minecraft.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/beats-minecraft-characters.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958793" /><br/>
As a refresher, the Beats Solo 4 on-ear headphones support Bluetooth, wired USB-C, and wired 3.5mm connections, as well as support for Personalized Spatial Audio. They offer up to 50 hours of battery life when connected via Bluetooth, and a Fast Fuel charge gives you up to five hours of playback with just ten minutes of charging. There's no active noise cancelation included, but the on-ear design does help to block out a decent amount of ambient sound.<br/>
<br/>
A proprietary Beats chip platform offers tight integration for both iOS and Android users, including support for one-touch pairing, automatic setup across devices via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> or Google, and support for Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> and Android's &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; Device services. iOS users also get access to always-on "Hey <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>" functionality and support for Audio Sharing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7gaAVEFpOso?si=CmwAS_I3Aj3i_qd1" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
As part of the Beats x Minecraft collaboration, there's a new promotional animated short film featuring "Wake Up," the latest track from Imagine Dragons, and Minecraft content creator TinaKitten is curating a Spatial Audio playlist on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>. Finally, Apple will be holding a <a href="https://www.apple.com/today/calendar/fifthavenue/?sn=R095">special Today at Apple session</a> at Apple Fifth Avenue in New York City on July 18 at 6:30 p.m. where TinaKitten and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Radio host Travis Mills will discuss the power of creativity, self-expression, and connection.<br/>
<br/>
The Beats x Minecraft Special Edition Solo 4 headphones are priced at &#36;199.99 in the United States and £199.99 in the United Kingdom. They will be available this Thursday, July 18, on Apple's website, EE's website in the UK, and Target's website. Select <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> locations in the US and EE stores in the UK will also carry them.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/minecraft/">Minecraft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/minecraft-beats-solo-4-headphones/">Special-Edition Beats Solo 4 Headphones Celebrate 15th Anniversary of Minecraft</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/special-edition-beats-solo-4-headphones-celebrate-15th-anniversary-of-minecraft.2431488/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Day: Apple Watch SE (&#36;169.99), Series 9 (&#36;279.99), and Ultra 2 (&#36;699.99) Hit New Best-Ever Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-apple-watch-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-apple-watch-se-169-99-series-9-279-99-and-ultra-2-699-99-hit-new-best-ever-prices.2431486/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:44:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-apple-watch-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking deals on Apple products as Prime Day continues, and right now you can get record low discounts on the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch SE. Across the line, all of the deals shared below are new all-time low prices on each model, and only Amazon has the sales.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/prime-day-series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958519" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ultra 2</h3><br/>
A new low price has arrived for the Apple Watch Ultra 2, now available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXC7YJ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.99</strong></a> in multiple colors and band styles, down from &#36;799.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXC7YJ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3>Series 9</h3><br/>
You can get up to &#36;120 off most Apple Watch Series 9 models right now on Amazon, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-Smartwatch-Aluminum-Fitness-Resistant%2Fdp%2FB0CSVB8BP1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a> for the 41mm GPS watches. We've rounded up all of the deals below, focusing on the aluminum devices, but you can also find &#36;100 discounts on a few stainless steel models as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5F%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTFHP3W%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;309.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSVMMDKQ%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5N%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;409.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3>SE</h3><br/>
Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is a new all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another new record low price on the Apple Watch SE for Prime Day.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-apple-watch-2/">Amazon Prime Day: Apple Watch SE (&#36;169.99), Series 9 (&#36;279.99), and Ultra 2 (&#36;699.99) Hit New Best-Ever Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-apple-watch-se-169-99-series-9-279-99-and-ultra-2-699-99-hit-new-best-ever-prices.2431486/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Day: 10th Gen iPad Drops to Record Low &#36;274.99 Price [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-10th-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-10th-gen-ipad-drops-to-record-low-274-99-price-updated.2431483/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 06:17:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-10th-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has introduced a new record low price on the 10th generation iPad for Prime Day. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;274.99</strong></a> when you clip an on-page coupon, down from &#36;349.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2022-ipad-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958608" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The iPad is available in two colors at this new all-time low price, and about &#36;2-&#36;5 higher in the remaining two colors. All deals in this sale will require you to clip an on-page coupon in order to see the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;74 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;274.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/best-prime-day-apple-products/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This price has expired and the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad is now available for &#36;299.00, a solid second-best price.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/amazon-prime-day-10th-ipad/">Amazon Prime Day: 10th Gen iPad Drops to Record Low &#36;274.99 Price [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-10th-gen-ipad-drops-to-record-low-274-99-price-updated.2431483/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
