<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:10:35 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning: Apple Users Targeted in Advanced Phishing Attack Involving Password Reset Requests</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-password-reset-phishing-attack/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-apple-users-targeted-in-advanced-phishing-attack-involving-password-reset-requests.2422902/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:34:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-password-reset-phishing-attack/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Phishing attacks taking advantage of what appears to be a bug in Apple's password reset feature have become increasingly common, according to a report from <em><a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2024/03/recent-mfa-bombing-attacks-targeting-apple-users/">KrebsOnSecurity</a></em>. Multiple Apple users users have been targeted in an attack that bombards them with an endless stream of notifications or multi-factor authentication (MFA) messages in an attempt to get them to approve an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password change.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/reset-password-request-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="3617" height="2035" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943548" /><br/>
An attacker is able to cause the target's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, or Mac to display system-level password change approval texts over and over again, with the hope that the person being targeted will mistakenly approve the request or get tired of the notifications and click on the accept button. If the request is approved, the attacker is able to change the &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; password and lock the Apple user out of their account.<br/>
<br/>
Because the password requests target the &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;, they pop up on all of a user's devices. The notifications render all linked Apple products unable to be used until the popups are dismissed one by one on each device. Twitter user Parth Patel recently <a href="https://twitter.com/parth220_/status/1771589789143478471">shared his experience</a> being targeted with the attack, and he says he could not use his devices until he clicked on "Don't Allow" for more than 100 notifications.<br/>
<br/>
When attackers are unable to get the person to click "Allow" on the password change notification, targets often get phone calls that seem to be coming from Apple. On these calls, the attacker claims to know that the victim is under attack, and attempts to get the one-time password that is sent to a user's phone number when attempting a password change.<br/>
<br/>
In Patel's case, the attacker was using information leaked from a people search website, which included name, current address, past address, and phone number, giving the person attempting to access his account ample information to work from. The attacker happened to have his name wrong, and he also became suspicious because he was asked for a one-time code that Apple explicitly sends with a message confirming that Apple does not ask for those codes.<br/>
<br/>
The attack seems to hinge on the perpetrator having access to the email address and phone number associated with an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
<em>KrebsOnSecurity</em> looked into the issue, and found that attackers appear to be using Apple's page for a forgotten &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; password. This page requires a user's &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; email or phone number, and it has a CAPTCHA. When an email address is put in, the page displays the last two digits of the phone number associated with the Apple account, and filing in the missing digits and hitting submit sends a system alert.<br/>
<br/>
It is not clear how the attackers are abusing the system to send multiple messages to Apple users, but it appears to be a bug that is being exploited. It is unlikely that Apple's system is meant to be able to be used to send more than 100 requests, so presumably the rate limit is being bypassed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple device owners targeted by this kind of attack should be sure to tap "Don't Allow" on all requests, and should be aware that Apple does not make phone calls requesting one-time password reset codes.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-password-reset-phishing-attack/">Warning: Apple Users Targeted in Advanced Phishing Attack Involving Password Reset Requests</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-apple-users-targeted-in-advanced-phishing-attack-involving-password-reset-requests.2422902/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Maps May Gain Custom Routes With iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-may-gain-custom-routes-with-ios-18.2422896/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:10:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple may be planning to add support for "custom routes" in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, according to code reviewed by <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/apple-maps-3d-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="896" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841030" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; does not currently offer a way to input self-selected routes, with Maps users limited to Apple's pre-selected options, but that may change in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. Apple has pushed an &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; file to its maps back-end labeled "CustomRouteCreation." While not much is revealed by the file except for the name, it does mention that this upcoming feature will be limited to the United States at launch.<br/>
<br/>
Custom routes would allow users to set what specific roads they want to travel down, whether for scenic purposes or for the familiarity of a route. Route options beyond the default have been a <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/252235149">highly requested</a> &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; feature for several years now, and other services like Google Maps allow users to create custom routes on a computer and then view them on an iOS device.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will be introduced at the Worldwide Developers Conference on Monday, June 10. For more details about the update, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/">Apple Maps May Gain Custom Routes With iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-maps-may-gain-custom-routes-with-ios-18.2422896/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WWDC 2024 Will Include In-Person Special Event at Apple Park</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/wwdc-2024-apple-park-special-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2024-will-include-in-person-special-event-at-apple-park.2422883/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 12:12:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/wwdc-2024-apple-park-special-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Apple Park</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple does not plan to hold a traditional in-person WWDC event this year, the company will invite select developers and students to attend a special event at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> campus in Cupertino, California.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-park-special-event-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="844" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943518" /><br/>
On Monday, June 10, Apple will <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc24/special-event/">host a keynote viewing party</a> to let attendees watch the pre-recorded unveiling of new software updates. Apple also promises "exciting new programming," an opportunity to meet with Apple experts, and other "special activities."<br/>
<br/>
At <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/wwdc-2023-apple-park-viewing-event-details/">last year's special event</a>, developers and students were provided with refreshments in the morning, followed by the keynote event. The Platforms State of the Union followed, and there were two &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; tours to choose from. The day ended with the Apple Design Awards and an evening dinner.<br/>
<br/>
Note that there will be a reception event at Apple's Infinite Loop campus on Sunday, June 9, where attendees can pick up their badges early.<br/>
<br/>
Prior to 2020, the Worldwide Developers Conference was an in-person event that was hosted in San Jose, California. Developers were required to pay &#36;1,599 to purchase a ticket to attend, and space was limited. Starting in 2020, Apple turned WWDC into an online event open to all developers, but there have been small in-person events at &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; since 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Lottery Selection</h2><br/>
Apple is inviting a limited number of developers and students to &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; for the special event, and attendees will be selected through a lottery process.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Who is Eligible to Attend</h2><br/>
Current Apple Developer Program or Apple Developer Enterprise Program members can ask to attend, as can Apple Entrepreneur Camp alumni and Swift Student Challenge winners from 2022 to 2024.<br/>
<br/>
350 Swift Student Challenge winners are set to be announced on Thursday, March 28. 50 Distinguished Winners will receive an invite to a special three-day experience that includes the special event on June 10.<br/>
<br/>
Both adults and children aged 13 to 17 can apply, but children will need to be accompanied by a legal guardian.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Register for Apple's Special Event</h2><br/>
Those eligible to enter the lottery can do so on Apple's developer website <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc24/special-event/request/">through the special event request page</a>. Apple is accepting requests to attend through 11:59 p.m. Pacific Time on Wednesday, April 3.<br/>
<br/>
Attendees chosen by the random selection process will be informed about their status by the end of the day on Thursday, April 4.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Costs</h2><br/>
There is no cost to attend the special event at &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj;, but Apple will not cover transportation. Out-of-state attendees will need to purchase plane tickets, accommodations at nearby hotels, and will need to find a way to get to &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; on the day of the event.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Media</h2><br/>
In addition to inviting developers and students, Apple will likely extend invitations to select members of the media. Media invites for the &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event have not yet gone out.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>WWDC Details</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a> will take place from Monday, June 10 to Friday, June 14. Developers who are not selected to attend can watch the June 10 keynote event on Apple's website or on YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
For those unable to watch the live stream, or who prefer to read a text version of the announcements, we'll have live &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; coverage both here on MacRumors.com and through our <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive?lang=en">MacRumorsLive Twitter account</a>, so make sure to follow.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to share all of the WWDC sessions and events in its Developer app and on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/">new Apple Developer YouTube channel</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/wwdc-2024-apple-park-special-event/">WWDC 2024 Will Include In-Person Special Event at Apple Park</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wwdc-2024-will-include-in-person-special-event-at-apple-park.2422883/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Reportedly Won&#039;t Feature Apple&#039;s Own ChatGPT-Like Chatbot</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/ios-18-reportedly-wont-have-apple-chatbot/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-reportedly-wont-feature-apples-own-chatgpt-like-chatbot.2422879/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 11:35:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/ios-18-reportedly-wont-have-apple-chatbot/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-26/apple-set-to-unveil-ai-strategy-at-june-10-developers-conference"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> today reported that Apple is not planning to debut its own generative AI chatbot with its next major software updates, including iOS 18 for the iPhone. Instead, he reiterated that Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">held discussions with companies such as Google, OpenAI, and Baidu</a> about potential generative AI partnerships.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
Recent reports indicated that Apple has considered licensing existing chatbots, such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/">Google's Gemini and OpenAI's ChatGPT</a>, but Apple offering its own chatbot of some kind on iOS 18 had not been explicitly ruled out until now.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman still expects AI to be a major focus at Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">just-announced WWDC 2024 developers conference</a>. He reiterated that Apple plans to announce new AI features that "assist users in their daily lives," but he did not provide any specific details. He has previously reported that generative AI will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">improve Siri's ability to answer more complex questions</a>, and allow the Messages app to auto-complete sentences. Other apps like Apple Music, Shortcuts, Pages, Numbers, and Keynote are also expected to gain generative AI functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already promised that the company would share generative AI announcements <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">later this year</a>, and the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-ios-18-ai-wwdc-2024/">hinted at it again today</a>. WWDC 2024 runs from June 10 through June 14, with video sessions to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/">shared on YouTube for the first time</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The first iOS 18 beta should be made available to developers following the WWDC keynote, and the update is expected to be released to all users in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/ios-18-reportedly-wont-have-apple-chatbot/">iOS 18 Reportedly Won&#039;t Feature Apple&#039;s Own ChatGPT-Like Chatbot</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-reportedly-wont-feature-apples-own-chatgpt-like-chatbot.2422879/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hints at iOS 18 AI Announcements Coming at WWDC 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-ios-18-ai-wwdc-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hints-at-ios-18-ai-announcements-coming-at-wwdc-2024.2422876/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:53:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-ios-18-ai-wwdc-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced official dates for the 35th annual Worldwide Developers Conference, which is set to begin on Monday, June 10. In its announcements, Apple sometimes gives us minor hints on what to expect, and Greg Joswiak is making some not-so-subtle references to AI.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840591" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" /><br/>
In a tweet, Joswiak said that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a> event is going to be "Absolutely Incredible," and he deliberately capitalized the first two letters of each word, AI.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Mark your calendars for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/WWDC24?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#WWDC24</a>, June 10-14. It’s going to be Absolutely Incredible! <a href="https://t.co/YIln5972ZD">pic.twitter.com/YIln5972ZD</a></p>&mdash; Greg Joswiak (@gregjoz) <a href="https://twitter.com/gregjoz/status/1772671384335925493?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 26, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
There have been multiple rumors suggesting that AI will be a major focus in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, macOS 15, and other operating system updates that are set to come out this year. Apple will add AI features to many of its built-in apps, and the company is in talk with Google and other companies about integrating an existing large language model (LLM) into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Over the course of the last few months, Apple executives have confirmed Apple's work on AI, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">said in February</a> that Apple plans to "break new ground" on generative AI in 2024. "We believe it will unlock transformative opportunities for our users," said Cook.<br/>
<br/>
Cook in November confirmed that Apple was "investing quite a bit" in AI, and during Apple's most recent earnings call, he said that Apple was spending a "tremendous amount of time and effort" on AI, with details set to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">come out later in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; is set to take place during the week of June 10, and it will begin with a keynote event that will see the unveiling of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and other operating system updates.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-ios-18-ai-wwdc-2024/">Apple Hints at iOS 18 AI Announcements Coming at WWDC 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hints-at-ios-18-ai-announcements-coming-at-wwdc-2024.2422876/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Announce 2024 Swift Student Challenge Winners on March 28</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-march-28/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-announce-2024-swift-student-challenge-winners-on-march-28.2422871/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:38:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-march-28/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Swift</category>
		<category>Swift Playgrounds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of today's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a> announcement, Apple said that it plans to announce this year's Swift Student Challenge winners on Thursday, March 28. The annual Swift Student Challenge asks students to create an innovative coding project using the Swift Playgrounds app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932478" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/swift-student-challenge-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" /><br/>
While Apple normally starts the Swift Student Challenge when WWDC dates are announced, the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-2024-swift-student-challenge/">launched the challenge early</a> to give students more time to work on their projects.<br/>
<br/>
Submissions were accepted from February 5 to February 25, and are now closed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is selecting 350 winners for the 2024 challenge, all of whom will be eligible to attend the June 10 WWDC Special Event at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> campus in Cupertino, California. Winners will need to enter the lottery process to get a chance to attend.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also choosing 50 Distinguished Winners recognized for "outstanding submissions." The Distinguished Winners will be invited to Cupertino for a three-day experience that will include the Special Event keynote viewing and other activities.<br/>
<br/>
Swift Student Challenge winners will be informed via email if they've won later this week. Projects are judged based on technical accomplishment, creativity of ideas, and the content of written responses explaining the project.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift/">Swift</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift-playgrounds/">Swift Playgrounds</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-swift-student-challenge-winners-march-28/">Apple to Announce 2024 Swift Student Challenge Winners on March 28</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-announce-2024-swift-student-challenge-winners-on-march-28.2422871/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches New Developer YouTube Account to Share WWDC 2024 Videos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-developer-youtube-account-to-share-wwdc-2024-videos.2422870/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:29:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In preparation for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a>, Apple today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@AppleDeveloper/">launched a new Apple Developer YouTube account</a>, which will be used to share WWDC sessions and events that developers can follow along with.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-developer-youtube.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943455" /><br/>
Apple has seeded the new account with a selection of videos from WWDC 2023, and this gives us an idea of the kind of content that we can expect to see during the &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; season.<br/>
<br/>
Videos are organized into playlists by topic, making it easy to find content on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, Swift, Spatial Computing, Safari, and more.<br/>
<br/>
In the &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; announcement, Apple said that developers can experience WWDC24 throughout the week on YouTube, referencing the new YouTube channel. Apple also plans to share content on the developer website and the Apple Developer app. Videos uploaded to YouTube will include all of the different video sessions that Apple holds on the latest software updates.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; is set to kick off on Monday, June 10, and we are expecting to see <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, macOS 15, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8">Dylan</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-developer-youtube-account-wwdc-2024/">Apple Launches New Developer YouTube Account to Share WWDC 2024 Videos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-new-developer-youtube-account-to-share-wwdc-2024-videos.2422870/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces WWDC 2024 Event for June 10 to 14</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-wwdc-2024-event-for-june-10-to-14.2422868/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:02:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that its 35th annual Worldwide Developers Conference is set to take place from Monday, June 10 to Friday, June 14. As with WWDC events since 2020, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a> will be an online event that is open to all developers at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/L6PNMjijLPE" title="Apple Announces WWDC 2024: What to Expect!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
&zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; will include online sessions and labs so that developers can learn about new features and software set to be announced at WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will hold a &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; keynote event on Monday, June 10 to show off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, tvOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2. The keynote event will be available on the Apple Developer app, the Apple website, and YouTube, with Apple also planning to share videos and information all week long.<br/>
<br/>
Though &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; is an online event, Apple is once again <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc24/special-event/">planning a special event</a> for select developers and students, which is set to take place on June 10 at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> campus in Cupertino, California. Attendees will be able to watch the keynote and State of the Union presentations at &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj;, as well as meet Apple employees and attend the Apple Design Awards. <br/>
<br/>
Current Apple Developer Program members, Apple Entrepreneur Camp alumni, prior Swift Student Challenge winners, and current Apple Developer Enterprise Program members can <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc24/special-event/">enter to attend the Apple Park event</a>, with Apple choosing participants through a random lottery.<br/>
<br/>
Apple normally holds a Swift Student Challenge when the WWDC dates are announced, but the challenge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-2024-swift-student-challenge/">kicked off earlier this year</a>. Winners will be announced on Thursday, March 28. Winners will be eligible to attend the special event at &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj;, and 50 Distinguished Winners will be invited to Cupertino for a three-day experience. <br/>
<br/>
Apple will provide developers with additional information about &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; through email, the Apple Developer app, and the Apple Developer website.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">Apple Announces WWDC 2024 Event for June 10 to 14</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-wwdc-2024-event-for-june-10-to-14.2422868/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2422857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:48:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE has dropped to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to its all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in the Silver Aluminum Case with Winter Blue Sport Loop and Starlight Aluminum Case with Starlight Sport Loop, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's available in Silver and Starlight Aluminum options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing and ECG functionality, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189-2/">Get the 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE for Just &#36;189 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-for-just-189-on-amazon.2422857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Canva Acquires Serif&#039;s Affinity Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/canva-acquires-affinity-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/canva-acquires-serifs-affinity-apps.2422854/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:11:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/canva-acquires-affinity-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Affinity Photo</category>
		<category>Affinity Designer</category>
		<category>Affinity Publisher</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Canva has <a href="https://www.canva.com/newsroom/news/affinity/">acquired</a> Serif's Affinity suite of creative apps, marking a significant stride in its competition against Adobe with a deal valued at several hundred million dollars (via <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-26/canva-acquires-affinity-design-suite-in-push-to-rival-adobe"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/affinity-designer-running-on-macos-big-sur.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-769506" /><br/>
Canva is an Australian online design company valued at &#36;26 billion. Its platform offers user-friendly design tools aimed at non-professionals and has a user base of over 175 million people worldwide. The acquisition of the Affinity apps marks a change of strategy for Canva, targeting professional designers and creatives who have traditionally relied on Adobe's suite of products.<br/>
<br/>
Affinity's software, encompassing photo editing, vector illustration, and desktop publishing tools, has been been lauded for its performance, affordability, and one-time purchase model – a stark contrast to Adobe's subscription services. The apps have garnered a strong following among Mac users in particular.<br/>
<br/>
The acquisition includes the transition of Serif's 90-person team to Canva, ensuring continuity in the development and support of Affinity apps. Cliff Obrecht, Canva's co-founder and Chief Operating Officer, emphasized that Affinity's portfolio is the "final piece in our jigsaw," indicating how the apps are expected to complement Canva's existing array of AI-powered design solutions and collaborative online workspaces.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/affinity-photo/">Affinity Photo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/affinity-designer/">Affinity Designer</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/affinity-publisher/">Affinity Publisher</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/canva-acquires-affinity-apps/">Canva Acquires Serif&#039;s Affinity Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/canva-acquires-serifs-affinity-apps.2422854/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Critical&#039; Chinese Apps Coming to Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/chinese-apps-coming-to-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/critical-chinese-apps-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2422850/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:45:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/chinese-apps-coming-to-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chinese tech giant Tencent has agreed to make some of its most important apps available on Apple's Vision Pro headset ahead of its launch in the country later this year, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apples-vision-pro-gets-boost-from-chinas-media-kingmaker"><em>The Information</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-vision-pro-eye.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922615" /><br/>
Tencent is one of the biggest multimedia companies in the world and its apps and services are ubiquitous in China. It owns Weibo, WeChat, QQ, WeBank, Tencent Pictures, and games such as Honor of Kings and PUBG. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> and many other entertainment services such as Disney+ are not available in China. "Without Tencent's contribution, Apple would have faced a greater challenge in marketing the Vision Pro in China," the report explains, calling the company's move "critical" to the device's success in the country.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> confirmed that the Vision Pro will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-this-year/">launch in China this year</a>. It is likely to be more expensive in China due to import taxes and could even be marketed under a different name due to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/vision-pro-trademark-issues-in-china/">trademark dispute with Huawei</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also apparently seeking Chinese partners to help it launch and run &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, and Apple Fitness+ in the country. The company has not launched any new services in China since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> in 2017 due to government restrictions.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/chinese-apps-coming-to-vision-pro/">&#039;Critical&#039; Chinese Apps Coming to Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/critical-chinese-apps-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2422850/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16: Accessory Maker Prepares for All-New Capture Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-case-with-capture-button-cutout/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-accessory-maker-prepares-for-all-new-capture-button.2422849/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:40:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-case-with-capture-button-cutout/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At least one accessory maker is already preparing for the iPhone 16's rumored Capture button, according to an <a href="https://twitter.com/SonnyDickson/status/1772507715694203055?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw%7Ctwcamp%5Etweetembed%7Ctwterm%5E1772507715694203055%7Ctwgr%5E5e7be999487209a61c674e1803ad1f7e3ce7e390%7Ctwcon%5Es1_&ref_url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.macrumors.com%2F2024%2F03%2F26%2Fiphone-16-pro-case-with-capture-button-cutout%2F">image shared today by Sonny Dickson</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPhone-16-Side-New-Action-Button-Emphasis-Bump.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917543" /><br/>
Dickson showed off a third-party iPhone 16 Pro case that includes a cutout below the power button on the right edge, which is where the Capture button is expected to be located. It is unclear if the accessory maker has direct knowledge of the new button, or if it is simply aware of the rumor, but it is betting on the change happening.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> was first to report about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">Apple's plans to add a Capture button</a> to all iPhone 16 models launching later this year. The button reportedly provides <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">quick access to various camera controls</a> for capturing photos and video. Specifically, it was reported that users will be able to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus on a subject with a light press, and start a video recording with a more forceful press.<br/>
<br/>
The button's touch sensitivity, and the fact it is expected to sit flush with the frame, explains why the case has a cutout for the button instead of covering it.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Sonny-Dickson-iPhone-16-Pro-Case.jpeg" alt="" width="2166" height="1020" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943423" /><em>Image Credit: Sonny Dickson</em></div><br/>
The new button would be ideally positioned on the top edge of iPhone 16 models when recording horizontal video, providing users with an easy-to-reach shutter button. The volume buttons currently serve this purpose when the Camera app is open.<br/>
<br/>
The location of the Capture button will require the mmWave 5G antenna window to be moved to the bottom-left edge on iPhone 16 models sold in the U.S., below the volume buttons. This antenna window does not exist in any other countries, as international models of the iPhone 12 through iPhone 15 are limited to sub-6 GHz 5G.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil the iPhone 16 series in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-case-with-capture-button-cutout/">iPhone 16: Accessory Maker Prepares for All-New Capture Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-accessory-maker-prepares-for-all-new-capture-button.2422849/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Dummy Models Showcase Design Changes, New Buttons</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-models-showcase-design-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-dummy-models-showcase-design-changes-new-buttons.2422846/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:03:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-models-showcase-design-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Images comparing purportedly accurate dummy models of the iPhone 16 series have been <a href="https://weibo.com/6315816381/O6DBOij3C?pagetype=profilefeed">shared online</a>, providing a closer look at the rumored design of the upcoming devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-dummies.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943358" /><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are expected to get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">larger display sizes</a> this year, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">multiple sources</a>, while the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus will be the same size as the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-pro-v-iphone-15-pro.jpeg" alt="" width="1290" height="1290" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943364" /><br/>
The first images show the difference in size between the iPhone 16 Pro and last year's iPhone 15 Pro. The iPhone 16 Pro is said to have a 6.3-inch display, while the iPhone 16 Pro Max will have a 6.9-inch display. In contrast, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max have 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro.jpg" alt="" width="690" height="366" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943370" /><br/>
Additional images give a better idea of button placement. Apple plans to replace the Mute Switch on the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus with the Action button that was previously exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro models. However, the images suggest the Action button will be larger than the one found on the current Pro devices.<br/>
<br/>
It's also worth noting the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">redesigned rear camera bump</a> on the iPhone 16 dummy. The pill-shaped bump houses the separate Wide and Ultrawide lenses on both the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus. The microphone sits next to the lenses, while the camera flash is located on the back of the device outside of the bump.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-action-button.jpg" alt="" width="690" height="575" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943366" /><br/>
In addition, all four iPhone 16 models are expected to feature an entirely new button that will be used for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/iphone-16-capture-button-video/">taking photos and videos</a>. The so-called "Capture button" is located on the same side of the iPhone as the Power button, in the space currently occupied by the 5G mmWave antenna in the United States. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-capture-button.jpg" alt="" width="690" height="711" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943371" /><br/>
In the images, the Capture button appears to be almost flush with the iPhone 16 chassis, but rumors say it will be mechanical rather than capacitive. Either way, <em>The Information</em> says that the button will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">respond to pressure and touch</a>. Apple believes the new button will be a major selling point for the ‌iPhone 16‌ lineup, and it is being introduced to further push the ‌iPhone‌ as a camera alternative for shooting horizontal video.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release the iPhone 16 lineup in September. For everything we know about the devices, see our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> roundups.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-models-showcase-design-changes/">iPhone 16 Dummy Models Showcase Design Changes, New Buttons</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-dummy-models-showcase-design-changes-new-buttons.2422846/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Philips Hue Sync TV App for Samsung TVs Gets Subscription Option and Music Mode</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/samsung-philips-hue-subscription-sync-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-sync-tv-app-for-samsung-tvs-gets-subscription-option-and-music-mode.2422845/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/samsung-philips-hue-subscription-sync-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Philips Hue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Philips Hue parent company Signify today announced an expanded relationship with Samsung, bringing the Philips Hue Sync TV app to additional countries, adding a Music Mode, and introducing a monthly subscription option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-philips-hue-sync.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943281" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/04/ces-2023-philips-hue-sync-samsung-tvs/">As of last year</a>, Samsung TV owners have been able to download a Philips Hue Sync app that allows Samsung smart TVs to be linked to HomeKit-connected Hue bulbs and lighting products. With the integration, content played on Samsung TVs is synced to the lighting in the room.<br/>
<br/>
When the feature launched, it was priced at &#36;130 for Samsung TV owners, but starting this spring, there will be a lower-priced subscription option. Customers can choose to pay a monthly fee of &#36;2.99 to use the Hue Sync app on up to three TVs, or a one-time fee to unlock it on a single TV. The Philips Hue Sync TV app is launching in Brazil, Hong Kong, Poland, the Czech Republic, and Slovakia, so Samsung TV owners in those countries can use the functionality.<br/>
<br/>
On compatible 2024 Samsung TV models, there is a new Music Mode option that allows the lights to react to the audio of what's playing on TV rather than the content of the screen. It is compatible with any music played on the TV, and will also be coming to Samsung TVs made in 2022 and 2023 later this year.<br/>
<br/>
For those without Samsung TVs, the &#36;250 Hue Play HDMI Sync Box paired with a streaming device like an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> is the only way to get TV content that's synced to lights, so the Samsung TV app provides a simpler solution for those who have Samsung TVs.<br/>
<br/>
The Philips Hue Sync TV app is available for Samsung Q60 series or higher QLED TVs that were made in 2022 or later.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/philips-hue/">Philips Hue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/samsung-philips-hue-subscription-sync-app/">Philips Hue Sync TV App for Samsung TVs Gets Subscription Option and Music Mode</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-sync-tv-app-for-samsung-tvs-gets-subscription-option-and-music-mode.2422845/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumor: Apple and Baidu &#039;Yet to Reach&#039; Generative AI Partnership</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-baidu-partnership-reportedly-not-reached-yet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-apple-and-baidu-yet-to-reach-generative-ai-partnership.2422843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 05:33:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-baidu-partnership-reportedly-not-reached-yet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has yet to reach a generative AI partnership with Chinese company Baidu, according to a <a href="https://www.chinadaily.com.cn/a/202403/26/WS6602b2c1a31082fc043bec68.html"><em>China Daily</em></a> report citing sources familiar with the matter. Some earlier reports said the two companies had finalized an agreement <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">following discussions</a>. It is possible that the negotiations are still ongoing, but this is not confirmed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
If the partnership does happen, Baidu would likely power some of iOS 18's rumored generative AI features in China only. Generative AI models must receive approval from the Chinese government, and Baidu's Ernie chatbot is permitted in the country. Google's Gemini and OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbots are not available in China.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has reportedly held similar generative AI partnership discussions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/">with Google and OpenAI</a> for the U.S. market, and likely other countries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has repeatedly teased that it has generative AI announcements <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">to share later this year</a>, and this likely refers to iOS 18. The software update is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">rumored to include new generative AI features</a> for a range of iPhone features and apps, including Siri, Spotlight, Apple Music, Health, Messages, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, Shortcuts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 will be previewed at Apple's developers conference <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC</a> in June, so we're just a few months away from learning about the company's plans.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-baidu-partnership-reportedly-not-reached-yet/">iOS 18 Rumor: Apple and Baidu &#039;Yet to Reach&#039; Generative AI Partnership</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-apple-and-baidu-yet-to-reach-generative-ai-partnership.2422843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Could Come in New &#039;Space Black&#039; and &#039;Rose&#039; Colors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-new-space-black-rose-colors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-could-come-in-new-space-black-and-rose-colors.2422839/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 04:10:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-new-space-black-rose-colors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>ShrimpApplePro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max models will come in new "space black" and "rose" titanium colors, claims a new rumor out of China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iphone-16-pro-colors-graybg.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937186" /><br/>
According to a Weibo post <a href="https://x.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1772522408144191732?s=20">shared by leaker ShrimpApplePro on X</a> (Twitter), the Blue Titanium color that iPhone 15 Pro models are currently available in will be dropped from the iPhone 16 Pro lineup in favor of the new rose color. Meanwhile, "space black," which is said to be similar to the iPhone 14 Pro color of the same name, will replace Black Titanium.<br/>
<br/>
The rumor also claims that the Natural and White Titanium colors will be slightly different on the iPhone 16 Pro models. Natural Titanium is said to be returning, but with more of a gray tint to it. Meanwhile, White Titanium will appear more like a "silver white" color, which is also said to be similar to the silver version of the iPhone 14 Pro. <br/>
<br/>
The Weibo user that is the source of the rumor has not previously been tracked by <em>MacRumors</em>. However, ShrimpApplePro claims that the account accurately predicted ahead of launch the Purple color that debuted with the iPhone 14 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple switched its "Pro" models from stainless steel to titanium with last year's iPhone 15 Pro series. The iPhone 15 Pro comes in Black Titanium, White Titanium, Blue Titanium, and Natural Titanium, but Apple surprised by not offering a gold option. Gold was available through the ‌‌iPhone‌‌ 5S to the ‌‌iPhone‌‌ 8, and then on the ‌‌iPhone‌‌ XS to the ‌‌iPhone 14‌‌ Pro. Therefore the rumored new "rose" color could well be the titanium version of a gold-like shade.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-16-pro-colors-rumor.jpeg" alt="" width="1386" height="2048" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943306" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Examples of rumored new iPhone 16 Pro color lineup</em></div><br/>
This is the second rumor we have heard about the ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌'s color options. Last month, the leaker known as "Majin Bu" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-16-pro-two-new-color-options/">claimed</a> that the Pro models would be available in "Desert Titanium" and "Titanium Gray" color options, and those names suggest there could be some overlap with today's rumored rose color and the tweaked Natural Titanium.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shrimpapplepro/">ShrimpApplePro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/iphone-16-pro-new-space-black-rose-colors/">iPhone 16 Pro Could Come in New &#039;Space Black&#039; and &#039;Rose&#039; Colors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-could-come-in-new-space-black-and-rose-colors.2422839/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple vs. the U.S. Department of Justice: What You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vs-the-u-s-department-of-justice-what-you-need-to-know.2422813/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:25:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj&#038;post_date=1711419909/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>Apple vs. DoJ</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On March 21, the United States Justice Department <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/">sued Apple for antitrust violations</a>, concluding a multi-year investigation into Apple's business practices. The U.S. government is also pursuing antitrust cases against Google, Amazon, and Meta, as part of an expansive look into the practices of major tech companies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-vs-DOJ-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943221" /><br/>
Apple plans to "vigorously defend" against the DoJ's lawsuit, which seeks to fundamentally change the way that Apple operates. This will be a legal battle that spans multiple years, and we'll keep this guide updated with the latest news as the case progresses.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="dojs_claims">DoJ's Claims</h2><br/>
The lawsuit that the DoJ filed against Apple is broad ranging, and rather than focusing on one or two issues, it aims to establish a long-running history of anti-competitive behavior. The DoJ tries to establish a pattern of business decisions that have suppressed competition, with the DoJ arguing that Apple has time and time again opted to "make its products worse for consumers to prevent competition from emerging."<br/>
<br/>
It is the opinion of the DoJ that Apple has gotten consumers "hooked" on its platform through these choices, making it unreasonably difficult for customers to switch to another smartphone brand. There is no allowance made for customer preference and the idea that people simply like their iPhones - the DoJ positions Apple as a monopolist that has manipulated people into sticking with its ecosystem by blocking competing apps, services, and products.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="suppressing_technologies">Suppressing Technologies</h3><br/>
While the full lawsuit details a long list of ways Apple has allegedly harmed consumers, the DoJ cites five specific examples of Apple blocking technologies that it claims would decrease barriers to switching and give consumers a "higher-quality user experience on any smartphone."<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ is of the opinion that if Apple did not historically limit cloud gaming, digital wallets, and non-Apple Watch smartwatches, that people would freely choose to purchase less expensive alternative smartphones over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. The DoJ believes that Apple is not facing pressure from "innovative, cross-platform technologies" because Apple "makes other products worse" rather than making its own products better.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Super apps</strong> - The DoJ defines super apps as those that provide a user with "broad functionality" in a single app and have the benefit of providing a consistent user experience across devices. An example of a super app is WeChat, which is widely used in China for communicating, making payments, and more. The DoJ says that Apple has "denied users access to super apps" in the U.S., but it is worth noting that there is a cultural aspect to these apps, and they just haven't caught on in the U.S. the way they have in China. Mini apps are often frequently referenced too, as Apple did have restrictions on apps offering mini games and other multi-app features (these restrictions were eliminated in iOS 17.4).</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Cloud streaming</strong> - The DoJ suggests that Apple is suppressing cloud streaming games by preventing them from being available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. Cloud streaming apps have been usable on Safari, and as of iOS 17.4, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-allows-cloud-gaming-apps-on-app-store/">changed its rules</a> to allow streaming game apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming to offer streaming games through a single &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; app. This argument is no longer entirely relevant, but the DoJ believes that by not allowing cloud gaming apps, Apple prevented consumers from buying cheaper phones. The idea here is that customers had to opt in to expensive iPhones to play "high-compute" games because they weren't available to play using cloud services.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Messaging apps</strong> - The DoJ thinks that third-party apps should be able to send and receive SMS messages, rather than these messages being routed to the Messages app. This would let users switch phones without changing the way they communicate. The filing takes issue with the lack of an iMessage app for Android, Apple's efforts to block the Beeper Mini app, green bubbles, and the adoption of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Smartwatches</strong> - Apple suppresses key functions of third-party smartwatches, preventing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users from getting Apple Watch-like functionality from smartwatches with "better user interfaces and services." The DoJ says that Apple locks customers in to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with the Apple Watch, because the Apple Watch can't be used on other smartphones. A user who wants to switch from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; must also purchase an Android-compatible smartwatch.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Digital Wallets</strong> - Apple does not let banking apps access NFC and provide digital payments services, and customers are not able to choose their "trusted banking apps" as their digital wallet. Apple also prevents developers from creating cross-platform wallets that would make it easier to switch from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Android, and alternative wallets could also be used for in-app purchases. The DoJ claims that the payments that banks make to Apple for using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> would otherwise be used for features and benefits for smartphone users.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="privacy_and_security">Privacy and Security</h3><br/>
The DoJ suggests that Apple justifies its anticompetitive conduct with privacy and security concerns.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple spends billions on marketing to promote "the self-serving premise that only Apple can safeguard consumers' privacy and security interests."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple selectively compromises privacy and security interests when it is in Apple's financial interest. The examples used here include the lack of end-to-end encryption between Android and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; messages and the making Google the default browser engine when "more private options" are available.</li><br/>
 <li>The safe, secure experience on Mac is evidence that Apple's control over app distribution and creation is "substantially more restrictive than necessary to protect user privacy and security."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple makes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; less secure if that helps it maintain monopoly power. The DoJ cites unencrypted text messages sent from iPhones to Android phones as an example. "If Apple wanted to," it could let &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users send encrypted messages to Android users.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="the_app_store">The App Store</h3><br/>
The DoJ mentions Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; policies and fees, but it is not the main focus of the lawsuit. While the DoJ was preparing its case, the Apple vs. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> lawsuit took place, and Apple was found not to have a mobile gaming monopoly. That undoubtedly influenced the DoJ filing, but there is wording here<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple uses &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules to "extract monopoly rents" from third-party developers.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple prohibits the creation and use of alternative app stores, and has arbitrary enforcement of its own &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules.</li><br/>
 <li>Developers are not able to offer web apps as an alternative to &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; apps because &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users "do not look for or know how to find web apps."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple uses &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules and restrictions to penalize and restrict developers that threaten its monopoly. It does allow apps to use private APIs, and requires web browsers to use WebKit.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple's efforts to restrict super apps and cloud streaming apps may have slowed the development of innovative apps related to education, artificial intelligence, and productivity. It has also kept app developers for creating features prohibited by Apple on other platforms.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="iphone_cost_and_development">iPhone Cost and Development</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple inflates the price for buying and using iPhones.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple spent more than twice as much on stock buybacks and dividends as it did on research and development (&#36;30B vs. &#36;77B in fiscal 2023).</li><br/>
 <li>Apple slowed down innovation on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to extract revenue from customers using subscriptions and cloud services.</li><br/>
 <li>Powerful, expensive hardware is unnecessary if consumers can play games through cloud streaming apps.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="services">Services</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple's subscription services increase the cost of switching from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to another smartphone. The DoJ references <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, Apple's cloud storage, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+ because these are exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. This results in "significant frictions" for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who want to switch.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple uses its "rapidly expanding" role as a TV and movie producer to control content and affect the "flow of speech."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="green_bubbles_and_imessage">"Green Bubbles" and iMessage</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>By using green bubbles, Apple "signals to users" that rival smartphones are lower quality because the experience of messaging non-iPhone users is worse. The DoJ says this is because conversations are not encrypted, videos are grainy, and users cannot edit messages or see typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Non-iPhone users experience "social stigma, exclusion, and blame" for "breaking" chats with where other participants own iPhones. This is "particularly powerful" for teenagers, and "social pressure" causes teens to switch to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>While the DoJ's comments on messaging largely ignore that Apple plans to bring feature parity with &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, it says that won't be enough because third-party apps still won't be able to be set as the default app for SMS/&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messages.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ speculates that because &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; improves over time, Apple might not support later versions of &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, so cross-platform messages "could soon be broken on iPhones" after Apple adds &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support later in 2024.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/apple-confirms-it-shut-down-beeper-mini/">references Beeper Mini</a>, an app that gained access to Apple's iMessage servers by exploiting fake credentials. The DoJ claims that it was a solution that "fixed" the broken cross-platform messaging experience. Apple made &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users less secure because it also supported end-to-end encryption.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="carplay">CarPlay</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> forces an iPhone-centric experience by taking over "all of the screens, sensors, and gauges" in a car in order to use &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; features. The DoJ suggests Apple is leveraging the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user base to exert power over American carmakers and restrict innovation, but Apple has so far not seen a lot of traction with &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; 2 and many car makers, such as Tesla and GM, are opting out of &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="competitors">Competitors</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The DoJ claims that Apple is the reason that only Google and Samsung remain as meaningful competitors in the premium smartphone market.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ blames Apple's market dominance for failed smartphones that include the Amazon Fire Phone and the Microsoft Windows Phone.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_doj_claims">Other DoJ Claims</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The iPod was successful because of the DoJ's antitrust case against Microsoft because it allowed Apple to launch iTunes on Windows PCs. "Microsoft did not charge Apple a 30 percent fee for each song downloaded from the iTunes Store."</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ holds itself responsible for Apple's success. U.S. vs. Microsoft "created new opportunities for innovation," and without this case, Apple would have had more difficulty achieving success with the iPod and the subsequent &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple made smartphones other than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; worse by stifling the growth of cloud gaming apps and interactive AI services.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ says that Apple copied the idea of a smartwatch from third-party developers.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ warns that Apple may "use its power to force its own users (and their data to become its next profitable product."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="dojs_market_definition">DoJ's Market Definition</h2><br/>
The DoJ suggests that Apple violated Section 2 of the Sherman Act, which says that it is illegal to acquire or maintain monopoly power "through improper means." To make this argument, the DoJ needs to prove that Apple is a monopoly power in a relevant market, and that Apple used anticompetitive conduct to achieve and maintain that monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
Sherman Act claims failed in Epic vs. Apple because &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; was not successful narrowing down the defined market in which Apple had a supposed monopoly. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; argued that the relevant market was apps on Apple devices, but the court decided it was all digital mobile gaming transactions. Apple was not found to have a monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ is also using a narrowed market definition that may not hold up. It has created a "performance smartphone market" defined as a "more expensive segment of the broader smartphone market." In this "performance market," Apple's U.S. market share by revenue is over 70 percent. In the "broader smartphone market" in the U.S., Apple has a 65 percent share.<br/>
<br/>
It could be tough for the DoJ to prove that Apple has a monopoly with only a 65 percent share of the market. 70 percent market share is a more solid argument for a monopoly, but the case against Apple won't be as strong as the case against Google. Google, for example, has a 90 percent share of the search engine market.<br/>
<br/>
Apple claims that it operates in a global market, and that the market share that should be considered is the global market share. Apple only has around a 20 percent cut of the global market.<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ also argues that Apple has a larger share "among key demographics" such as higher-income households and among young people.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_the_doj_wants">What the DoJ Wants</h2><br/>
The DoJ wants the court to find that Apple has acted unlawfully to monopolize or attempt to monopolize the U.S. smartphone market. It has asked for "relief as needed" to address anticompetitive harm and restore competitive conditions, and a ruling that prevents Apple from continuing to engage in anticompetitive practices.<br/>
<br/>
According to the DoJ, Apple should be prevented from using its control of app distribution to undermine cross-platform technologies, that it should not be able to use private APIs to undermine cross-platform technologies like messaging and smartwatches, and that Apple should be prevented from using the terms and conditions of its contracts with developers, consumers, and accessory makers to maintain a monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apples_response">Apple's Response</h2><br/>
Apple has an official statement on the DoJ's lawsuit:<blockquote>At Apple, we innovate every day to make technology people love--designing products that work seamlessly together, protect people's privacy and security, and create a magical experience for our users. This lawsuit threatens who we are and the principles that set Apple products apart in fiercely competitive markets. If successful, it would hinder our ability to create the kind of technology people expect from Apple--where hardware, software, and services intersect. It would also set a dangerous precedent, empowering government to take a heavy hand in designing people's technology. We believe this lawsuit is wrong on the facts and the law, and we will vigorously defend against it.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has also held media briefings and shared information on key facts in the lawsuit. Some highlights:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The DoJ has changed the scope of its case six times due to the results in &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; v. Apple and other lawsuits. Several theories were considered and had to be abandoned because of a lack of evidence.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple says that the lawsuit won't be successful because it does not get the facts right. It would set a dangerous precedent for government interference in technology, and would make the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; less private, less secure, and more vulnerable to malware. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; would not be able to operate as well with other Apple products, and user information would be put at risk.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims the DoJ wants to turn the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; into an Android, and that the case goes after the key features that make the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; experience unique.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple does not believe the lawsuit has a basis in antitrust law and seems to be suggesting that Apple has an obligation to design its products in a way that would help competitors.</li><br/>
 <li>In a recent ruling in the AliveCor v. Apple dispute, the court said that it cannot oversee technology and innovation, and it is not for the court to analyze algorithms.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ ignored changes to streaming game apps and plans to implement &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, and Apple says that super apps have always been permitted.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims the DoJ is trying to fit Apple into the theories that were successful in the antitrust case against Microsoft 20 years back, but Apple does not agree with the parallels. Microsoft had a 95 percent share of the market, and Apple says that business decisions are made to provide consumers with maximum privacy and safety.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple says the DoJ misses that customers are loyal because they are satisfied with their devices and love Apple products.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims it spent three years looking at whether it made sense to make an Apple Watch for Android, but ultimately chose not to make one because it would be inferior and would have limits impacting privacy and security.</li><br/>
 <li>iMessage has not been designed for other platforms because Apple doesn't have a way to verify that a third-party device has encryption and authentication procedures that meet its standards, and that security issues on third-party devices could expose the content of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users' messages, leading to fraud and spam issues.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_the_full_lawsuit">Read the Full Lawsuit</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe class="scribd_iframe_embed" title="United States et al v Apple Inc" src="https://www.scribd.com/embeds/717095810/content?start_page=1&view_mode=scroll&access_key=key-FCk4OGhTWJoCqsIVOd5Y" tabindex="0" data-auto-height="true" data-aspect-ratio="0.7729220222793488" scrolling="no" width="100%" height="600" frameborder="0"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="whats_next">What's Next</h2><br/>
Now that the DoJ has filed a lawsuit, Apple will have a 60-day period to respond. Apple plans to move to dismiss the complaint.<br/>
<br/>
If that doesn't happen, the case will move forward. There will be briefings, hearings, and a discovery period. It will be a few months before there are additional filings, and the entire legal process will span for multiple years. Apple says that it plans to vigorously fight the case.<br/>
<br/>
Should the judge assigned to the case rule in the DoJ's favor, there will be appeals and then remedies for the anticompetitive behavior will need to be determined.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">Apple vs. the U.S. Department of Justice: What You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vs-the-u-s-department-of-justice-what-you-need-to-know.2422813/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s A18 Pro Chip Rumored to Boost AI, Retain 6-Core GPU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-a18-pro-chip-rumored-to-boost-ai-retain-6-core-gpu.2422808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:47:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">A18 Pro chip</a> for iPhone 16 Pro models will feature a larger die size for boosted artificial intelligence performance, according to Jeff Pu, an investment analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
In a research note with Hong Kong-based investment firm Haitong International Securities this week, Pu added that the A18 Pro chip will be equipped with a 6-core GPU, which would be equal to the A17 Pro chip in iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Generative AI</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">rumored to include new generative AI features</a> for a range of iPhone features and apps, including Siri, Spotlight, Apple Music, Health, Messages, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, Shortcuts, and more. Apple has reportedly considered partnering with companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">such as Google, OpenAI, and Baidu</a> for at least some of these features.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 16 Pro models are rumored to feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> with "significantly" more cores, which could result in some of iOS 18's generative AI features being exclusive to those models. Pu previously said the larger die size would be related to the Neural Engine, which could power on-device generative AI features.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has used a 16-core Neural Engine since the iPhone 12 series. However, it has still improved the Neural Engine's performance over the years, even when core counts have not changed. For example, Apple says the A17 Pro chip has up to a 2x faster Neural Engine compared to the one in the iPhone 14 Pro's A16 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has promised to make generative AI announcements <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">later this year</a>. iOS 18 will be previewed at Apple's developers conference <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC</a> in June, so we're just a few months away from learning about the company's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6-Core GPU</h2><br/>
With the A17 Pro chip, iPhone 15 Pro models have significantly improved graphics capabilities compared to previous models. Apple said the new 6-core GPU is up to 20% faster and also more power efficient than the 5-core GPU in the A16 Bionic chip. iPhone 15 Pro models also support hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for improved graphics rendering, which results in more realistic graphics in games.<br/>
<br/>
Pu believes Apple will stick with a 6-core GPU for the A18 Pro chip, so graphics improvements may be more limited for iPhone 16 Pro models this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wrap Up</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 series in September. For more details, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro roundups</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/">iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s A18 Pro Chip Rumored to Boost AI, Retain 6-Core GPU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-a18-pro-chip-rumored-to-boost-ai-retain-6-core-gpu.2422808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Update Your iPhone Now: iOS 17.4.1 Includes These Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/update-your-iphone-now-ios-17-4-1-includes-these-security-fixes.2422792/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:36:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided details about the security fixes</a> included in last week's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-releases-ios-17-4-1/">iOS 17.4.1 and iPadOS 17.4.1 software updates</a> for the iPhone and iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.4.1-Includes-These-Security-Fixes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943212" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214097">support document</a>, Apple said the updates patch an image-related security vulnerability that "may lead to arbitrary code execution."<br/>
<br/>
The full details:<blockquote><strong>CoreMedia</strong><br/>
<br/>
Available for: iPhone XS and later, iPad Pro 12.9-inch 2nd generation and later, iPad Pro 10.5-inch, iPad Pro 11-inch 1st generation and later, iPad Air 3rd generation and later, iPad 6th generation and later, and iPad mini 5th generation and later<br/>
<br/>
Impact: Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution<br/>
<br/>
Description: An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation.<br/>
<br/>
CVE-2024-1580: Nick Galloway of Google Project Zero<br/>
<br/>
<strong>WebRTC</strong><br/>
<br/>
Available for: iPhone XS and later, iPad Pro 12.9-inch 2nd generation and later, iPad Pro 10.5-inch, iPad Pro 11-inch 1st generation and later, iPad Air 3rd generation and later, iPad 6th generation and later, and iPad mini 5th generation and later<br/>
<br/>
Impact: Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution<br/>
<br/>
Description: An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation.<br/>
<br/>
CVE-2024-1580: Nick Galloway of Google Project Zero</blockquote>To update your iPhone or iPad, open the Settings app and tap General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said it has patched the same vulnerability in <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT214096">macOS 14.4.1</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT214093">visionOS 1.1.1</a> as well.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/">Update Your iPhone Now: iOS 17.4.1 Includes These Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/update-your-iphone-now-ios-17-4-1-includes-these-security-fixes.2422792/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Outlines &#039;Reasons to Upgrade&#039; Your iPhone on New Website</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-reasons-to-upgrade-your-iphone-on-new-website.2422789/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:53:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone/why-upgrade/">added a "Why Upgrade" section</a> to its website, which is aimed at encouraging customers with older iPhones to upgrade to a newer model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-reasons-to-upgrade.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943185" /><br/>
The website allows customers to compare the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 11, 11 Pro, 11 Pro Max, 12, 12 mini, 12 Pro, and 12 Pro Max to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, or &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
Each comparison shows what new features someone with an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will get when upgrading to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup. With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, for example, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; offers 4x better photo resolution, more base storage, Action and Cinematic mode for video, USB-C, a 60 percent faster GPU, 5G, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The site highlights differences in display technology, design, sizing, connectivity, and more. Apple also provides details on the trade-in value of each older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; so customers know what kind of discount they can get when trading a device in with the purchase of a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
To further soften the costs of upgrading, Apple advertises <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> Monthly Installments and carrier deals that can drop the price of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; to &#36;0. Apple also details the ease of upgrading to a new device with features like Quick Start and eSIM.<br/>
<br/>
Much of the smartphone market in the United States is saturated, and there are few new customers for Apple. Upgraders are an important market segment, and Apple is continually seeking ways to get customers to regularly purchase new iPhones to maintain sales momentum.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/">Apple Outlines &#039;Reasons to Upgrade&#039; Your iPhone on New Website</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-reasons-to-upgrade-your-iphone-on-new-website.2422789/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
