<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 03:04:25 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Big Summer Movie Expanding to More IMAX Theaters Due to &#039;Overwhelming Popularity&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-f1-movie-expanded-imax-screenings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-big-summer-movie-expanding-to-more-imax-theaters-due-to-overwhelming-popularity.2457429/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-f1-movie-expanded-imax-screenings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Warner Bros. Pictures today <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250520194753/en/By-Popular-Demand-Warner-Bros.-Pictures-and-IMAX-Expand-Their-Fan-First-Premiere-Screenings-of-Apple-Original-Films-Summer-Event-Feature-F1-The-Movie-to-400-IMAX-Theaters-Worldwide">announced</a> that it will be premiering Apple's upcoming F1 film in more IMAX theaters than it originally planned to.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-TV-F1.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994845" /><br/>
There will now be advanced screenings of F1: The Movie at <a href="https://www.f1themovie.com/">400 IMAX theaters around the world</a> on Monday, June 23 at 7:00 p.m. local time, ahead of the film's wider release on June 25 internationally and on June 27 in the U.S. and Canada. Warner Bros. Pictures decided to offer additional IMAX screenings due to "overwhelming popularity" for the film so far, with the initial 25 screenings that it offered all sold out.<br/>
<br/>
Tickets for the early IMAX screenings and general showings go on sale starting tomorrow, May 21.<br/>
<br/>
The film will tell a familiar underdog story. Brad Pitt stars as an F1 driver who was an up-and-coming talent in the 1990s, until an accident on the track nearly ended his career. Thirty years later, Pitt is invited to join a former teammate's struggling F1 team, in a last-shot bid to save the team and become the best in the world.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/n-MDGqexqjQ?si=fvybg9fvmfBi1FQt" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The film is directed by Joseph Kosinski, who is known for other popular action films, including "Tron: Legacy" and "Top Gun: Maverick."<br/>
<br/>
F1: The Movie will be available to stream on Apple TV+ at a later date. In the U.S., Apple TV+ costs &#36;9.99 per month, or &#36;99 per year. The streaming service is available through the Apple TV app on a wide variety of devices, and <a href="https://tv.apple.com/">on the web at tv.apple.com</a>, with a free seven-day trial available. Apple TV+ is also available in Apple One bundles.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-f1-movie-expanded-imax-screenings/">Apple&#039;s Big Summer Movie Expanding to More IMAX Theaters Due to &#039;Overwhelming Popularity&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-big-summer-movie-expanding-to-more-imax-theaters-due-to-overwhelming-popularity.2457429/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything Interesting Google Announced at I/O Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-i-o-announcements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-interesting-google-announced-at-i-o-today.2457428/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:49:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-i-o-announcements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Gemini</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google I/O</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today held its annual <a href="https://io.google/2025/">I/O developer conference</a>, where it shared a number of new features and tools that are coming to its products in the coming weeks and months. There was a heavy focus on AI capabilities, and Google is deeply integrating Gemini and other AI tools into its software.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B2VfAmBdbfI?si=HRjzrNUjPvxEtoRI" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<h2>New Gemini Features</h2><br/>
Gemini is Google's AI product, equivalent to Anthropic's Claude and OpenAI's ChatGPT. Apple has no equivalent at the current time, but Gemini could soon be integrated into iOS like ChatGPT. There are multiple new capabilities coming to Gemini, some of which are available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users this week.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Gemini Live</strong> - Gemini Live is available in the Gemini app for iOS starting today, and it's free to use. It uses screen sharing or the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s camera so that you can communicate with Gemini in real-time and ask questions about what you're seeing. It's useful for identifying objects, asking questions about things around you, getting help with DIY projects, shopping, organizing, and more. Gemini Live integrates with Google Calendar, Maps, Tasks, and Keep.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Gemini Agent Mode</strong> - Agent Mode in Gemini can do things like find sports game tickets at an ideal price, or help you locate the right apartment with specific requirements on price and layout. It's coming soon to Gemini.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Gemini Personal Context</strong> - Gemini will be able to incorporate search history for more personalized results, along with pulling information from other Google apps. Google is also aiming to make Gemini more proactive, with reminders about upcoming events and tools that can help with preparations. Gemini Personal Context sounds similar to the personalized features that Apple is planning to add to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> at some point in the future, but Gemini is further along.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>AI Ultra</strong> - Google has a new AI plan called AI Ultra, and it costs &#36;250 per month. It includes expanded access to Google's latest AI tools with high rate limits, and all of the newest features, plus YouTube Premium and 30TB of storage. Google AI Premium, which is &#36;19.99, has been renamed Google AI Pro. At &#36;250, AI Ultra is more expensive than top tier plans from Anthropic and OpenAI. Apple doesn't charge for any <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> functionality as of yet, and it's not clear if that'll happen in the future.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Veo 3</strong> - Google is updating its Veo video generation model with new capabilities, and it is now able to create videos that include sound effects, background noise, and dialogue. It can, for example, generate a video of birds with realistic sounds, and it is designed to be good at mimicking real-world physics. Veo 3 is limited to AI Ultra subscribers, but it is available starting today.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Imagen 4</strong> - Google's new image generating tool, Imagen 4 is coming to Gemini. Imagen 4 can create more photorealistic images with improved details for things like hair, fur, and fabric. It's also better at generating text, and incorporating creative ideas like making a word out of dinosaur bones when the image being created involves a dinosaur party. Imagen 4 is available in Gemini as of today.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Deep Research</strong> - Gemini supports uploading private PDFs and images for research reports, with Google Drive and Gmail integration coming soon.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Google Search</h2><br/>
Gemini is being integrated more deeply into search, starting with a dedicated AI Mode that's rolling out in the U.S. this week.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Ask Search Anything" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sxUBThVQLjU" width="1046" height="589" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>AI Mode in Search</strong> - Google is adding a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search/">new AI Mode to search</a> that is entirely AI, rather than just the AI suggestions that show up in the AI Overviews that are shown with Google searches. It uses a query fan-out technique that breaks down questions into multiple searches for a deeper dive than traditional search. AI Mode is rolling out to everyone in the United States starting today as a dedicated section in Search, and it will use the latest Gemini 2.5 model. It will soon incorporate more personalized suggestions that take into account your preferences and your actions in other Google apps, and agentic capabilities will let it do things like purchase concert tickets.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Deep Search</strong> - AI Mode has a Deep search option that uses the same query fan-out technique, but it is able to conduct hundreds of searches at one time, reason across multiple results, and craft an "expert-level" report in minutes. AI Mode will also be able to analyze complex datasets and create graphics and charts.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>AI Mode for Shopping</strong> - AI Mode will be able to help you find specific items that you're looking for, and it can let you "try on" clothes that you're shopping for. It scans your body using a photo of you and then puts a realistic looking clothing item on you so you can see what it might look like. It can show depth, and how the material will look draped over a body. AI Mode can make purchases, alert you to deals, and more. These features will launch in the coming months.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Google Search Live</strong> - Google Search is getting a feature that's basically Gemini Live, and users will be able to ask questions about what's being viewed through a smartphone camera. It's an AI Mode feature coming this summer.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Google Apps</h2><br/>
Gmail, Chrome, and Meet are all getting new Gemini capabilities that are rolling out starting today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Meet Gemini in Chrome" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BBjM0SHg-aU" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Gmail Personal Context</strong> - With permission, Gemini will be able to use relevant context across Google apps to make AI responses in Gmail sound more like you. Gemini will be able to scan past emails, look up notes, and view documents in Google Drive. With the info, it can match greetings, capture tone and style, and mimic favorite word choices. It's coming this summer for Gemini subscribers.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Google Meet</strong> - Google Meet is getting a real-time translation option. Initally, it'll work in English and Spanish, but Google has plans to add more languages. It's available to Google Pro and Ultra subscribers.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Google Chrome</strong> - Chrome is getting integrated Gemini starting tomorrow. It can answer questions about what you're doing and the tabs that you've got open, with the first version able to clarify complex information on any webpage or summarize long pages. You can get to Gemini from the task bar. Chrome is also being updated with a new password feature that can automatically change passwords compromised in a leak, for participating websites.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>FireSat</strong> - Google is developing a FireSat feature that will watch for fires to break out in areas as small as 270 square feet. It could be particularly useful in California, where Google is headquartered.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Android XR Glasses</h2><br/>
Google already announced Android XR as a platform for companies that are building VR headsets, but today, Google said that it's also developing Android XR for augmented reality glasses. Google last tried this kind of product with Google Glass, but it didn't go over so well and Google Glass was discontinued after several years.<br/>
<br/>
Google showed off a set of lightweight glasses that incorporate an in-lens display. On stage, Google demonstrated the glasses offering a live translation feature with words that appeared on the lenses, and providing turn-by-turn directions.<br/>
<br/>
The glasses have cameras, microphones, and speakers, and are connected to Gemini. The AI is able to see and hear what the wearer hears to answer questions, offer image recognition capabilities, provide tailored directions, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The smart glasses could compete with Apple's future smart glasses, as Apple is rumored to be working on a pair of lightweight augmented reality glasses that could eventually replace the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Apple is still far off from being able to release AR glasses, so the Android XR version is likely to come out first.<br/>
<br/>
Gentle Monster and Warby Parker <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250520232084/en/Warby-Parker-Partners-with-Google-To-Develop-Intelligent-Eyewear">are partnering with Google</a> for Android XR glasses that are lightweight and stylish.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's XR headset will still be the first device that runs Android XR, and it's launching later this year. Samsung will also build Android XR glasses.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/gemini/">Gemini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-io/">Google I/O</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-i-o-announcements/">Everything Interesting Google Announced at I/O Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-interesting-google-announced-at-i-o-today.2457428/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fortnite Returns to U.S. App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/fortnite-returns-to-u-s-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-returns-to-u-s-app-store.2457427/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:19:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/fortnite-returns-to-u-s-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular game Fortnite is once again available in the U.S. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, as Apple has finally approved <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>' app submission. This is the first time that Fortnite has been on the iOS &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; since 2020. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite-apple-logo-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-756080" /><br/>
Apple initially did not plan to allow Fortnite back in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but the judge overseeing the ongoing legal battle between the two companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/19/apple-fortnite-us-app-store-dispute/">yesterday suggested</a> that Apple and &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; work things out or face more time in court. The judge threatened to require the Apple official that oversees app decisions to appear in person in court, which apparently was enough to spur Apple to allow the game back on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
Fortnite is available from the iOS &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in the United States, and from the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store alternative app marketplace in the European Union. It is not available on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in other countries. The U.S. version of Fortnite includes an option for players to purchase in-app currency using the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; website, with no in-app purchases. <br/>
<br/>
Apple initially planned to prevent Fortnite from returning to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; until the legal dispute was entirely settled. As of now, Apple is appealing the court's ruling that forced it to change its U.S. &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules to allow developers to link customers to purchase options available outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/fortnite-returns-to-u-s-app-store/">Fortnite Returns to U.S. App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fortnite-returns-to-u-s-app-store.2457427/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Shows Off Android XR Smart Glasses With In-Lens Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-android-xr-smart-glasses/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-shows-off-android-xr-smart-glasses-with-in-lens-display.2457426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:12:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-android-xr-smart-glasses/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google <a href="https://blog.google/products/android/android-xr-gemini-glasses-headsets/">today showed off</a> a set of lightweight smart glasses that have deep Gemini integration and an optional in-lens display that can offer up relevant information like turn-by-turn directions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/google-smart-glasses.jpg" alt="" width="1392" height="783" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002382" /><br/>
Made to rival the Meta Ray-Bans and smart glasses coming from Apple in the future, Google's XR glasses feature a camera, microphones, and speakers. They connect to a smartphone for app access, and with Gemini integration, the glasses can answer questions about the wearer's surroundings, provide directions, and offer up live translations.<br/>
<br/>
Gemini is able to use the cameras in the glasses to see what's around the wearer to provide feedback, and Google says the glasses will "see and hear what you do" so they'll understand context and "help you throughout your day." On stage at Google I/O, Google executives demonstrated how the Android XR glasses will be able to send messages to friends, make appointments, snap photos, and translate conversations in real-time.<br/>
<br/>
Google plans to work with companies like Warby Parker and Gentle Monster to create stylish smart glasses that consumers will want to wear.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-android-xr-smart-glasses/">Google Shows Off Android XR Smart Glasses With In-Lens Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-shows-off-android-xr-smart-glasses-with-in-lens-display.2457426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Siri Can Clean Your House With the Roborock Saros 10R</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/roborock-saros-10r/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-siri-can-clean-your-house-with-the-roborock-saros-10r.2457425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:00:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/roborock-saros-10r&#038;post_date=1747789213/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 18.4, Apple added support for robot vacuums to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, and some of the companies that make robot vacuums have started offering products with Matter integration. Matter-compatible robot vacuums can be added to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; and controlled via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands and the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-saros-10r.jpg" alt="" width="2070" height="1164" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002357" /><br/>
Roborock is one of the companies that's adopting Matter, and the Roborock Saros 10R now works with &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;. The Saros 10R is one of Roborock's flagship vacuums and it's relatively new, so like most of these Matter-enabled vacuum options, it does not come cheap. It's &#36;1,600, but it does have Roborock's most advanced feature set.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Design and Size</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R is just over three inches tall, so it's compact enough to fit under all of my furniture. I have a TV stand that's about four inches that a different robot vacuum isn't able to fit underneath, but I haven't run into that problem with the Saros 10R.<br/>
<br/>
There are a lot of components in robot vacuums, so the thin build is a feat of engineering, and having a robot that can get under all of my furniture is a major plus. When I manually vacuum with a Dyson stick, I can't reach all of the areas that the Saros 10R can, so my house ends up cleaner when the robot handles the vacuuming and mopping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/saros-10r-roborock-sensors.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002366" /><br/>
While the Saros 10R is thin, it's still on the larger side, measuring in at around 13 inches. If you have a smaller space with a lot of furniture, it might be too large to effectively clean, but I've been impressed with the narrow spaces it can maneuver through. Since it's round, it can get itself into and out of some tight fits.<br/>
<br/>
I mostly use the app to send the Saros 10R off to clean or to resume cleaning after a pause, but there are buttons on the device itself. The power button turns it on or sends it to clean if it's already on, and the dock button sends it home. A long press on the dock button activates a spot cleaning feature.<br/>
<br/>
All of the robot vacuums have base stations, and the Saros 10R base station is fairly large, but it kind of blends into the background, like a vacuum or a mop might. The base station is black plastic and it includes several components. There's a dust bag that collects the dust and hair the robot picks up, a clean water bin for wetting and washing the mop, a section for floor cleaning solution, a dirty water bin for collecting the water used to wash the mop, a dryer for drying the mop, and a ramp that helps the robot get up onto the base to charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/saros-10r-dock-top-down.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002369" /><br/>
The dock weighs around 25 pounds, so it's probably not something you're going to want to cart around if you have multiple floors in your home. I'm not sure if people who have multi-story homes purchase more than one vacuum, but carrying the robot and base station upstairs would be a workout. The dock has an LED on it that turns red if there's a problem or white when the robot is charging, and it needs to be placed on a hard surface with about two feet around it to make sure there's space for the robot to dock itself.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/saros-10r-dust-bin.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002371" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The dust bin in the Saros 10R where dust and debris collect. It empties into the dock</em></div><br/>
Roborock says to use its proprietary cleaning solution because other solutions can damage the internals of the vacuum. Some companies like Bona make cleaning solutions specifically for robot vacuums, and I didn't have an issue using that kind of cleaning fluid.<br/>
<br/>
There are rubber wheels at the bottom of the robot, and they come out far enough to help it get over thresholds and to lift it over carpets. I have a threshold that's about an inch in one spot, and it's able to navigate it fine. The mops are able to lift up enough that it can vacuum rugs while mopping without getting the rugs wet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Navigation</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R has what Roborock calls its "StarSight" autonomous system, which is basically several sensors. It has a front camera and sensor for detecting obstacles, and it has a wall sensor for determining where walls are located.<br/>
<br/>
The first cleaning with the Saros 10R starts off with a mapping feature where the robot maps all of the rooms that it is able to access, and then while cleaning, it continually scans for and identifies pet messes, pets, cords, furniture that's hard to navigate, and other obstacles. You can opt in to have the robot take a picture whenever it encounters an obstacle, so you can see what it's avoiding.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/saros-10r-robot-and-dock.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1195" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002370" /><br/>
Its sensors do a good job mapping out a room and even identifying the furniture in the room, which helps it determine what a room is. If it sees a dining table, for example, it'll label that room as a dining room.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-obstacle-detection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002373" /><br/>
It's able to identify pet messes so that it doesn't drag a mess around the entire house, and it's also excellent at detecting cables that should be avoided, so it doesn't get tangled up. It doesn't run into walls or furniture, and the extending mops and the side brush let it get into nooks, crannies, corners, and the sides of walls when cleaning even as it's avoiding obstacles.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Cleaning Features</h2><br/>
Most of the robot vacuums have the same general vacuuming features, with variations in suction and the roller bar design. The Saros 10R has what Roborock calls a "DuoDivide" anti-tangle brush, and I haven't seen it get tangled. I have wood floors, four cats, and two people with long hair, and there hasn't been clogging or tangling. Hair and fuzz can get wrapped around the bearings of the rubber wheels on the bottom and that's not fun to remove, but it hasn't stopped the vacuum from functioning.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-saros-10r-top.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002368" /><br/>
As for suction, it picks up every speck of dust and cat hair from my floors, which are wood. It hasn't damaged my wood floors, which is always a concern with a vacuum, and it does a good job keeping them almost spotless. It also does well with my large rugs, but it can struggle with smaller rugs that get stuck. It's never been entirely tripped up by a rug unlike my other robot vacuum from a different brand, so it's not a problem that requires my interference. There is a side brush that's able to sweep dust from corners, curves, around furniture, and along walls so that it can be vacuumed up, and it's effective.<br/>
<br/>
Of note, I have one large rug that sheds continually and the robot can keep it clean. My Dyson vacuum has a hard time with this rug because the fluff clogs it up. I have another rug in my laundry room that is a lint and fur magnet. The standard hard floor attachment on my Dyson that I use 99 percent of the time can't clean it, but the Saros 10R sucks up all the lint that's become one with the rug with no problem. It's at least on par with my Dyson (a V15 Detect), and better for some areas.<br/>
<br/>
I want to point out that I have all hard flooring with just rugs and no rooms with carpet, so I haven't tested the vacuum on carpet. If you have carpet, check out other reviews too, because I don't want to speak to its carpet performance with just rugs to test with.<br/>
<br/>
The Saros 10R doesn't just vacuum, it also mops, and the mopping functions are what distinguish robot vacuums from one another. Roborock is using a set of dual spinning mops for the Saros 10R, each of which is about-palm sized. The two mops work in unison, and the robot can cover a good amount of floor space with no real gaps, providing a thorough clean.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/saros-10r-dust-bag-dock.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1343" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002372" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The dust bag that dust from the vacuum empties into. I've had the robot a couple of months now, but it hasn't filled up yet.</div></em><br/>
The mops can clean well around chair legs and other furniture, because they can extend out from the robot somewhat for a closer clean. Dried on stains like ketchup can take a few passes, but everything else comes up immediately. The Saros 10R goes back to the base station to wash the mop, and the default time is 15 minutes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Noise Levels</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R is quiet when mopping, but when it's vacuuming, it sounds like a vacuum. You're not going to want to run it while you're trying to work or watch TV, but noise cancelling headphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> block it out enough to run it while you're home.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Roborock App</h2><br/>
Robot vacuums seem to have apps with endless settings, and the Roborock app is no exception. Setup is simple, and the app walks you through the steps (basically just connecting to Wi-Fi), and through the mapping, cleaning, and maintenance process.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002376" /><br/>
The built-in sensors in the Saros 10R can map all accessible areas, and can also detect furniture to determine room type. There are also settings that allow it to detect objects on the ground and snap photos, so you can see what it's avoiding and how the AI is working. After a map has been completed, the Saros 10R is ready to clean. There are multiple cleaning modes that combine vacuuming and mopping, and you can select different suction settings for the vacuum and water settings for the mopping. There are also modes for quick, standard, and deep cleaning.<br/>
<br/>
You can follow along on the map to see where the robot has cleaned, the pattern it used, and areas that it might have skipped due to obstacles. It's super detailed, and the feature to show pictures of what the robot noticed and skipped is useful. It detects pets (and can avoid them), cables, furniture where it can become trapped, pet messes, fabric, extra dirty areas, and more. I have rarely had an issue with the Saros 10R getting itself stuck because the AI to avoid cables and other obstacles is excellent.<br/>
<br/>
The Map created by the robot can be edited, so if it doesn't do a great job separating out rooms, it's possible to manually fix it. I have an open floor plan, so I went in and sectioned things out so that I could have it clean specific rooms. If you have multiple floors, you can create more than one map. You can add areas, remove areas, and block areas for customized cleaning.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-vacuum-map.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002377" /><br/>
There is an option in the app to watch the Saros 10R camera live so you can see what it's doing and check in on pets. I didn't have many instances where there were issues, but if it does catch a cord or something, the app sends an alert so it can be addressed. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-app-alerts.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002374" /><br/>
The app supports setting up a cleaning schedule, so I have assigned it to clean different areas on Monday, Tuesday, and Wednesday, which splits up the cleaning so it doesn't need to be running for hours a day. I also have different cleaning scenarios that group rooms together with variable cleaning parameters that change factors like suction power for rooms without rugs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomeKit Integration</h2><br/>
Thanks to Matter support, the Roborock Saros 10R can be added to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; and it shows up in the Home app. It can be controlled with the Home app, or with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-homekit.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002379" /><br/>
&zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; is more limited than what's possible with the Roborock app, but &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; integration has proven more useful than expected. When the kitchen is messy after eating, I can say "Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, clean the kitchen," and the Saros 10R is able to do that based on the rooms I setup in the Roborock app.<br/>
<br/>
In the Home app, there's support for automations that rely on other &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; products. If for some reason I want the Saros 10R to vacuum when I turn on a light, I can set that up. The Home app can also be used to have the robot clean at specific times, when a sensor detects something, or when people leave the home, which is perhaps the most useful option.<br/>
<br/>
For starting a random cleaning, the Home app is less useful. It doesn't include all of the various cleaning modes and settings, but you can choose to vacuum, mop, or vacuum and mop. You can have the robot clean the entire house or specific rooms.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Maintenance</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R is a complicated piece of machinery that does require some maintenance, though it hasn't been too overwhelming yet. So far, I've had to empty the dirty water tank, fill the clean water tank, replace cleaning fluid, clean the sensors, and clean the base.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-saros-10r-bottom.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002367" /><em><div class="center-wrap">The bottom of the Saros 10R after 61 total hours of operation. I haven't cleaned it.</div></em><br/>
Eventually I'll need to replace the filter and the dust bag (which should be done once a month), and swap in new mop heads. There are estimated lifespans for some of the hardware like the side brush, while others suggest replacing on an as-needed basis. The mop and bristles of the various brushes can wear out over time, with replacements available from Roborock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/roborock-maintenance.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002375" /><br/>
<h2>Battery and Cleaning Time</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R can't clean my entire house on a single charge, and it typically needs to charge at least once if I'm not splitting up the cleaning by room. Cleaning time can vary based on settings, such as suction power and whether it's set to "deep" clean with multiple passes, but here are a couple of scenarios.<br/>
<h3>Cleaning 1</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Started at 12:30, full cleaning. 150 square meters total.</li><br/>
 	<li>Ran out of battery at 14:47 and had to charge.</li><br/>
 	<li>Resumed cleaning at 16:59.</li><br/>
 	<li>Finished at 20:07. Total cleaning time: 244 minutes, 1 charge.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Cleaning 2</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Started at 10:31. Deep clean, 199 square meters.</li><br/>
 	<li>Ran out of battery at 13:21, and had to recharge.</li><br/>
 	<li>Resumed at 15:32, finished at 17:49. Total cleaning time: 291 minutes.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Cleaning 3</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Started at 18:23, three main rooms, 81 square meters. Standard clean.</li><br/>
 	<li>Finished at 21:49. Total cleaning time: 133 minutes.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Cleaning 4</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Started at 10:00 on schedule. Full clean, 101 square meters.</li><br/>
 	<li>Finished at 14:38. Total cleaning time: 164 minutes.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The Saros 10R is not quick unless I have it in the quick mode that leaves more space between passes. It takes a significant amount of time for a clean, and it can and will run almost all day if I set it to clean the entire house and it needs to charge. Cleaning in sections means it doesn't need to charge as often.<br/>
<br/>
It takes around 2.5 hours for it to charge up, but it will always resume when it runs out of battery.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R is one of Roborock's newest cleaning bots, and of the few that I've tried, it's the most impressive. My floor looks and feels much cleaner, and it takes almost no interaction from me. There have been a few instances where the robot gets itself tangled in cords and loses a mop, but the obstacle avoidance is good enough that it avoids a lot of cable issues, stays away from any pet messes, and knows not to get itself trapped in furniture that's hard to navigate. It doesn't struggle with my rugs, or the thresholds between rooms.<br/>
<br/>
It's the most hands-off cleaning experience that I've had, and that has value. I don't have to spend over an hour a week vacuuming and more when I mop, I don't have to fuss with the robot, and the floor is clean throughout the week. I do wish the battery lasted longer because it can't get through the house on a single charge when it's vacuuming and mopping, but that's manageable by splitting up the areas cleaned each day.<br/>
<br/>
At this price, a robot vacuum needs to be essentially perfect, and able to hold up to longterm daily use. I tested the Saros 10R by using it daily for a little over two months, because I wanted to give it more time than I would the average review. It's so far held up and continues to work well, but I'm going to keep using it to give updates on its longevity.<br/>
<br/>
It definitely cleans super well, navigates almost perfectly, and is easy to use, but I expect something priced this high to work for a long time, and that's not a metric I can judge just yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Saros 10R can be <a href="https://us.roborock.com/products/roborock-saros-10r">purchased from the Roborock website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DHCJ571Z">from Amazon</a> for &#36;1,600.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Roborock provided MacRumors with a Saros 10R for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/roborock-saros-10r/">Review: Siri Can Clean Your House With the Roborock Saros 10R</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-siri-can-clean-your-house-with-the-roborock-saros-10r.2457425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nanoleaf Launches New Rope Light and Solar Garden Lights</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/nanoleaf-rope-light-solar-lights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-new-rope-light-and-solar-garden-lights.2457422/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:25:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/nanoleaf-rope-light-solar-lights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nanoleaf, known for its range of iPhone-connected lighting products, today announced the launch of two new devices. The Nanoleaf Rope Light is a super flexible LED light strip that can be bent into almost any shape.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/nanoleaf-rope-light.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002361" /><br/>
It is more flexible than Nanoleaf's traditional light strips, and it has a silicone cover that diffuses the light so it does not need to be under or behind a TV, display, or other device. It can be crafted into a specific shape, manipulated into an abstract design, or used to outline furniture and decor.<br/>
<br/>
Each &#36;70 rope light is five meters long (16 feet), and it can display multiple colors at one time. Nanoleaf ships it with mounting clips so that it can be securely mounted to a wall in a myriad of designs. There are 420 total LEDs inside the light, and it is 300 lumens, so more of an ambient lighting product than a lamp replacement.<br/>
<br/>
The Matter Smart Multicolor Rope Light can be controlled via the Nanoleaf app, and it is also able to connect to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> over Matter so that it can be controlled with the Home app and with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands. Matter integration also allows it to be controlled alongside other &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; products in scenes and automations. More than 16 million colors are supported, with customizable colors and patterns available in the Nanoleaf app.<br/>
<br/>
Nanoleaf's Solar Garden Lights are an affordable solar accent lighting option, priced at &#36;50 for two. Unlike most Nanoleaf products, the Solar Garden Lights do not connect to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; or the Nanoleaf app, and they are instead controlled via an included remote control.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/nanoleaf-solar-garden-light.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002362" /><br/>
There are eight bulbs per Solar Garden light, along with a solar panel that can be placed in the sun to keep the lights charged up. Alternatively, the lights include a USB-C port and can also be charged that way.<br/>
<br/>
We were able to test out the Solar Garden Lights ahead of launch, and found that they worked well. A quick USB-C charge provided enough power to get them up and running, and charging in the sun kept them powered. The lights are not designed to come on during the day, and like many solar lights, will activate only at night.<br/>
<br/>
While app controls would be nice, the remote cycles through 11 animated scenes with different colors, and eight solid color options. There are also warm and white light settings for those who don't care for multicolored lights. The stems for the bulbs can be manipulated into an ideal shape, and Nanoleaf ships stakes in two sizes so you can adjust height to your liking. The lights look nice positioned around plants given the spray design.<br/>
<br/>
The Solar Garden Lights feature IP65 weatherproofing so they will hold up to rain and the elements, and there are controls to run them for 4, 6, and 8 hour increments. Compared to the inexpensive solar lights that are easy to find at big box stores, Nanoleaf's have a sturdier solar attachment and quality, flexible bulbs with a unique look. Up to 20 lights can be controlled at once, and Nanoleaf has multi-packs available.<br/>
<br/>
Both of the new products can be purchased from Nanoleaf's website starting today. The Solar Garden Lights <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/solar-garden-lights/?size=2">are priced starting at &#36;50</a>, and <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/products/multicolor-rope-light/?size=each">the Rope Light</a> is &#36;70.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to introducing new products today, Nanoleaf also announced that it is <a href="https://www.walmart.com/brand/nanoleaf/10025653">expanding into 2,500 Walmart retail locations</a> across the United States. Nanoleaf products will be available for purchase at Walmart in addition to Amazon, the <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/">Nanoleaf website</a>, Best Buy, and other retailers.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/nanoleaf-rope-light-solar-lights/">Nanoleaf Launches New Rope Light and Solar Garden Lights</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nanoleaf-launches-new-rope-light-and-solar-garden-lights.2457422/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Launches Dedicated AI Mode in Search</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search.2457417/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:44:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google I/O</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today announced that it is adding a dedicated AI Mode to Google Search, which is an expansion of the existing AI Overviews feature that Google provides for standard searches. AI Mode is able to handle longer, harder search queries with multiple facets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/google-ai-mode-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002347" /><br/>
Questions are broken down into different parts, with multiple searches run simultaneously on separate databases to provide a timely answer that takes into account personal context to make results more relevant to each user. It can generate images, including custom charts, and it supports follow-up questions.<br/>
<br/>
AI Mode is rolling out to all users in the United States starting today, and it will be accessible through a new tab in Google Search for desktop and the Google Search apps. It will let users make more complex queries that are designed to leverage AI capabilities. <br/>
<br/>
Google CEO Sundar Pichai said that AI Mode's predecessor, AI Overviews, has been "one of the most successful launches for search in the last decade." Pichai did not address the impact that AI Overviews have had on publishers. AI Overviews and AI Mode pull content from websites, giving people little reason to click on links to source information directly where it came from. AI Mode will display links, much like AI Overviews, but with detailed summaries that are provided, there's little reason for people to visit websites from the search interface. <br/>
<br/>
AI Mode will incorporate AI agent capabilities, so it will be able to field requests like "find two affordable tickets for this Saturday's Reds game," and it will also work for shopping. AI Mode will be able to help users find specific items, such as a rug, with refinements that take into account factors like children or pets, colors, and more. Google's AI Mode will be able to track prices on items, and let you know when something you want is on sale. <br/>
<br/>
For clothing shopping, AI Mode includes a virtual try-on option. It can use a photo of the user to create a preview of what an item of clothing will look like when worn. The feature works by generating an AI model of the user's body, and displaying how clothing will drape in a realistic way. There's also a "buy it for me" option that can be used for making purchases directly from search. The new shopping features are set to arrive in the coming months, though try on is available in Labs now.<br/>
<br/>
This summer, AI Mode will adopt personal context, aggregating past searches and information from apps like Gmail to provide more customized responses. <br/>
<br/>
AI Mode will now power AI Overviews in the standard search interface, and some of the new AI Mode capabilities will be incorporated into AI Overviews.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-io/">Google I/O</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search/">Google Launches Dedicated AI Mode in Search</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-launches-dedicated-ai-mode-in-search.2457417/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-releases-airpods-max-firmware-7e108/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware.2457415/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 11:27:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-releases-airpods-max-firmware-7e108/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the USB-C version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones. The new firmware is version 7E108, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/02/airpods-max-7e101-firmware/">prior 7E101 firmware</a> the device was previously running.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936393" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Green-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
There is no word on what's new in the firmware as of yet, if anything. It is likely that the update focuses on under-the-hood performance improvements.<br/>
<br/>
With the prior 7E101 firmware, Apple added support for lossless audio and ultra low-latency audio for the USB-C &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;, so there could also be a bug fix related to this capability.<br/>
<br/>
The USB-C &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; now support 24-bit 48 kHz lossless audio, which is designed to allow listeners to experience music the way the artist created it in the studio.<br/>
<br/>
Firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/27/airpods-firmware-update-instructions/">can be installed</a> by putting the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in Bluetooth range of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi, and then plugging them in to charge. It can take up to 30 minutes for firmware to update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your firmware version by going to Settings &gt; Bluetooth and selecting the Info button next to the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; when they are connected to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, or Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update</b>: Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106340">release notes</a> state only that the update delivers "bug fixes and performance improvements" without providing any detail on what has changed.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-releases-airpods-max-firmware-7e108/">Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware.2457415/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gemini App for iOS Gets Live View Feature for Real-Time Visual Help</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-gemini-live-ios-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gemini-app-for-ios-gets-live-view-feature-for-real-time-visual-help.2457413/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:48:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-gemini-live-ios-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Gemini</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google I/O</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google is bringing a new live view feature to its Gemini apps on iOS and Android, allowing users to live stream their surroundings to Gemini to get feedback on what they're seeing. Integration is rolling out starting today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/gemini-live.jpg" alt="" width="2096" height="1178" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002343" /><br/>
In a demo, Gemini identified objects that the user was looking at, corrected wrong assumptions about what an object was, and provided context by answering questions. Gemini's live view can identify objects in real-time, provide assistance with DIY or home improvement projects, help organize spaces, assist with shopping, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can also share your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> screen with Gemini to get feedback on something that you see online.<br/>
<br/>
Gemini's Live option could be helpful for those who are blind or who have low vision, as it can provide a live vocal feed of a person's surroundings. Live is built on Project Astra, which Google previewed at I/O last year, and it previously rolled out to Pixel devices.<br/>
<br/>
This summer, Google also plans to add personal context to Gemini for features like Gmail's smart reply. Gemini will be able to use relevant information across Google apps to provide a more personalized experience. For example, the AI reply feature in Gmail can sound like you, rather than having a generic voice. It is able to scan past emails to match tone, style, and word choice, plus it can look up notes, documents from Google Drive, and more to add context to emails.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/gemini/">Gemini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-io/">Google I/O</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/google-gemini-live-ios-app/">Gemini App for iOS Gets Live View Feature for Real-Time Visual Help</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gemini-app-for-ios-gets-live-view-feature-for-real-time-visual-help.2457413/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Outlines WWDC 2025 Labs and Community Events</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/wwdc-2025-labs-and-community-events/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-wwdc-2025-labs-and-community-events.2457409/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/wwdc-2025-labs-and-community-events/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule/">sharing a complete WWDC 2025 schedule</a> today, Apple has outlined details about <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/sessions-and-labs/">developer labs</a> and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/community">community events</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/Apple-WWDC25-event-branding_big.jpg.large_2x.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-996564" /><br/>
Apple will be hosting free group labs from Tuesday, June 10 through Friday, June 13. During these labs, developers will be able to join Apple engineers online to discuss and ask questions about WWDC 2025 announcements. Developers can <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/sessions-and-labs/">register starting today</a>, with available topics ranging from Apple Intelligence to SwiftUI.<br/>
<br/>
Developers will also be able to set up one-on-one appointments with Apple experts online for guidance on various topics, such as app design, privacy, accessibility, and more. Apple says one-on-one lab requests will open immediately after the WWDC 2025 keynote on Monday, June 9 via <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/sessions-and-labs/">this page</a> and the Apple Developer app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/labs/overview/">shared helpful tips</a> for both the group and one-on-one labs.<br/>
<br/>
During the week of WWDC, Apple's engineers will answer questions and help to solve technical issues in the Apple Developer Forums.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/community">listed various community events</a> that will be held around the world leading up to, during, and shortly after WWDC 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/wwdc-2025-labs-and-community-events/">Apple Outlines WWDC 2025 Labs and Community Events</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-wwdc-2025-labs-and-community-events.2457409/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Will Let Developers Use Apple&#039;s AI Models in Their Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/ios-19-apple-ai-models-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-let-developers-use-apples-ai-models-in-their-apps.2457408/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 09:18:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/ios-19-apple-ai-models-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will make its artificial intelligence models available to developers to use in their apps, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-05-20/apple-to-open-ai-models-to-developers-betting-that-it-will-spur-new-apps">Bloomberg</a></em>. The company plans to introduce a new software development kit (SDK) in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> that will make it easier for app creators to add AI features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963424" /><br/>
The SDK will feature the same large language models that Apple is using for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features like notification summaries, Writing Tools, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, but Apple will first focus on the smaller models that are able to run on-device.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has faced criticism for its failure to deliver &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features in a timely manner. Apple announced a new personalized &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; experience at WWDC 2024 and intended to release the new capabilities as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, but the functionality <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-intelligence-siri-features-delayed/">was not ready in time</a> and is now being held until &zwnj;iOS 19&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Some of Apple's other features, like Writing Tools and &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;, haven't seen widespread adoption. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, Apple is hoping that opening up its AI models to developers will provide use cases that better attract consumers. Currently, developers can integrate notification summaries, Writing Tools, &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;, and &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; into their apps, but they aren't able to create new AI features using Apple's framework. Instead, developers who want to include AI integrate third-party models, which Apple is aiming to change.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's AI announcements will come at the Worldwide Developers Conference, which is set to take place on Monday, June 9.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also been working on in-house large language models (LLMs), and eventually the company plans to introduce a version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; that relies on LLMs and is more like ChatGPT, Claude, and other chatbots. The LLM version of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; isn't expected until 2026 at the earliest, and it will likely be part of iOS 20.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/ios-19-apple-ai-models-developers/">iOS 19 Will Let Developers Use Apple&#039;s AI Models in Their Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-will-let-developers-use-apples-ai-models-in-their-apps.2457408/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces WWDC 2025 Schedule, Including Keynote Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule-including-keynote-time.2457402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:13:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/05/apples-worldwide-developers-conference-kicks-off-june-9/">announced</a> a more detailed schedule for its annual developers conference WWDC, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/25/apple-wwdc-2025/">runs from June 9 through June 13</a>. The schedule confirms that Apple's keynote will begin on Monday, June 9 at 10 a.m. Pacific Time, with a live stream to be available on Apple.com, in the Apple TV app, and on YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/WWDC-2025-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002300" /><br/>
During the keynote, Apple is expected to announce iOS 19, iPadOS 19, macOS 16, watchOS 12, tvOS 19, visionOS 3, and other software updates, along with new Apple Intelligence features. In some years, there are also hardware announcements at WWDC, but there has yet to be any rumors about new devices being unveiled at this year's conference.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has reminded developers that WWDC 2025 is "on the horizon" on its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=wafsmat3">developer news page</a>, where developers can now register for <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/sessions-and-labs/">group labs</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The keynote will be followed by the Platforms State of the Union video on June 9 at 1 p.m. Pacific Time. This video will provide a deeper dive into the latest features and tools for developers across Apple's software platforms. Apple says the video will be available to stream via the Apple Developer website, app, and YouTube channel.<br/>
<br/>
Both the keynote and the Platforms State of the Union will be available for on-demand playback after each live stream concludes.<br/>
<br/>
In the past, the WWDC schedule included an in-person Apple Design Awards event, but Apple moved to pre-announcing the winning apps last year.<br/>
<br/>
WWDC 2025 will primarily take place online, with more than a hundred videos to be shared across the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/wwdc25/sessions-and-labs/">Apple Developer website</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/14/apple-wwdc-2025-developer-app-update/">Apple Developer app</a>, and YouTube for free. There will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/03/apple-wwdc-developer-special-event/">also be an in-person component</a>, as more than 1,000 developers and students have been invited to attend a special day at Apple Park on June 9 to watch the keynote video together, meet some of Apple's teams, socialize, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2025</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule/">Apple Announces WWDC 2025 Schedule, Including Keynote Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-wwdc-2025-schedule-including-keynote-time.2457402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Can Now Deliver Your Next iPhone With a Drone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/amazon-drone-delivery-for-iphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-can-now-deliver-your-next-iphone-with-a-drone.2457403/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 08:12:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/amazon-drone-delivery-for-iphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you told someone in the 1960s that one day a flying robot would be able to deliver a computer that fits in their pocket to their backyard, they might think it was a scene from The Jetsons. However, that is now a very real possibility.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/iPhone-and-Drone-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002299" /><br/>
Amazon today <a href="https://www.aboutamazon.com/news/transportation/amazon-drone-deliver-package">announced</a> that it recently received approval from the U.S. Federal Aviation Administration to offer drone delivery for several new categories of items, including Apple products like iPhones, AirPods, and AirTags.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon launched its Prime Air drone delivery in 2022, promising drop-offs to a backyard or other specified location in less than an hour. However, the service is currently limited to parts of the Phoenix, Arizona and College Station, Texas areas in the U.S., and it is only offered during daylight hours and favorable weather conditions. In addition, drone delivery is only available for a single item that weighs up to five pounds.<br/>
<br/>
The delivery location must be clear of obstacles and reachable by a drone.<br/>
<br/>
While this cutting-edge technology is currently limited to just two cities in the U.S., Amazon promises to expand it to additional cities over time. The company has also promised to launch the service in the UK and Italy, subject to regulatory approval.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon's announcement was earlier reported <a href="https://www.theverge.com/news/670434/amazon-prime-drone-delivery-approval-iphone-lithium-ion">by <em>The Verge</em></a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/amazon-drone-delivery-for-iphones/">Amazon Can Now Deliver Your Next iPhone With a Drone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-can-now-deliver-your-next-iphone-with-a-drone.2457403/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts USB-C AirPods Max to &#36;479.99 in Every Color (&#36;69 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/usb-c-airpods-max-to-479/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-usb-c-airpods-max-to-479-99-in-every-color-69-off.2457399/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:41:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/usb-c-airpods-max-to-479/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the USB-C AirPods Max on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;479.99</strong></a> in every color, down from &#36;549.00. This sale started over the weekend with just one color at this price, but now Amazon has expanded it to include all five colors of the AirPods Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Max-Discount-Feature-Warm-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895400" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
All colors are still available to be delivered in May, with most providing a delivery estimate around May 26 for free shipping options. Prime members in certain cities should be able to see same-day delivery options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHYDZSD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;479.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Right now this is one of the only notable AirPods discount on Amazon. The AirPods Pro 2 are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> this week, down from &#36;249.00, but that's not all that close to the record low price on the model. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/usb-c-airpods-max-to-479/">Amazon Discounts USB-C AirPods Max to &#36;479.99 in Every Color (&#36;69 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-usb-c-airpods-max-to-479-99-in-every-color-69-off.2457399/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS 16: Everything We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/macos-16-everything-we-know-so-far/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-16-everything-we-know-so-far.2457398/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:31:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/macos-16-everything-we-know-so-far/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC), Apple's annual developer and software-oriented event, is less than three weeks away. We haven't heard a great deal about macOS 16 ahead of its announcement this year, so we could be in for some major surprises when June 9 rolls around. Here's what we know so far about the next major update to Apple's Mac operating system.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/macOS-16-visionOS-Inspired-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994383" /><br/>
<h2>macOS 16 Name?</h2><br/>
Every year heading into WWDC, one question on many Mac fans' minds is what Apple will choose as the name for the next version of macOS. The tradition dates all the way back to the beginning of Mac OS X with its big cat names, and then in 2013 Apple shifted to Calfornia-themed names with the unveiling of OS X Mavericks.<br/>
<br/>
Back in the early days after the debut of OS X Mavericks, we discovered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/04/24/future-os-x-names-california/">total of over 20</a> California-themed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/05/30/future-os-x-names-discovered/">trademark applications</a> filed by various limited liability companies that were all but certain to be shell companies created by Apple to hide its identity.<br/>
<br/>
Over time, some of the trademarks like Yosemite, Sierra, Mojave, and Monterey were indeed used by Apple for its major Mac operating system updates, while trademark applications for several other names have been abandoned.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has previously used names from abandoned trademark filings  such as Big Sur in 2020  for macOS releases. So, macOS 16 could still adopt a name Apple sought to protect years ago.<br/>
<br/>
The below list covers the remaining macOS name possibilities that Apple had filed to protect:<div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><ul><br/>
  <li>California</li><br/>
  <li>Condor</li><br/>
  <li>Diablo</li><br/>
  <li>Farallon</li><br/>
  <li>Grizzly</li><br/>
  <li>Mammoth</li><br/>
  <li>Miramar</li></ul></div><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Pacific</li><br/>
  <li>Redtail</li><br/>
  <li>Redwood</li><br/>
  <li>Rincon</li><br/>
  <li>Shasta</li><br/>
  <li>Skyline</li><br/>
  <li>Tiburon</li><br/>
</ul></div><br/>
<div style="clear:both;"></div><h2>Compatibility</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-2024-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983350" /><br/>
Apple began transitioning the Mac lineup to Apple Silicon in 2020 and completed it by 2023. Since then, support for Intel Macs has steadily declined with each new macOS release. <br/>
<br/>
Only a few Intel-based machines are supported in Apple's last update, macOS Sequoia:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>2018 Mac mini</li><br/>
  <li>20192020 iMac models</li><br/>
  <li>2017 iMac Pro</li><br/>
  <li>2020 MacBook Air</li><br/>
  <li>20182020 MacBook Pro models</li><br/>
  <li>2019 Mac Pro</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
With the increasing prevalence of AI features, it could be that macOS 16 is the last version to support at least some Intel-based Macs, minus Apple Intelligence features that require Macs with Apple silicon chips. If Apple dropped support for the oldest models in the above list, that would see Apple stay faithful to delivering at least five years of software support for its devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Rumored Design Changes</h2><br/>
Apple is planning a radical redesign of macOS with version 16, and it could be the most significant visual refresh since macOS Big Sur was introduced in 2020, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-03-10/apple-readies-dramatic-design-overhauls-for-ios-19-ipados-19-and-macos-16">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/macOS-16-visionOS-Inspired.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994384" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>MacRumors concept render</em></div><br/>
The upcoming Mac operating system will reportedly be part of Apple's sweeping effort to create a more consistent interface across all of its platforms, including iPhone, iPad, and Apple Vision Pro. The redesign will update the "style of icons, menus, apps, windows, and system buttons" throughout the system.<br/>
<br/>
According to people familiar with the project, which is dubbed "Cheer" internally, Apple aims to simplify navigation and device control while bringing design elements from visionOS to the Mac experience. While specific details remain limited, some of the changes could include:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Complete refresh of icons, menus, and system buttons</li><br/>
  <li>New window styles and management features</li><br/>
  <li>Simplified navigation system</li><br/>
  <li>Visual elements inspired by visionOS (possible circular app icons?)</li><br/>
  <li>More translucent interface elements</li><br/>
  <li>Greater visual consistency with iOS and iPadOS</li><br/>
</ul>The redesign is described as "loosely based" on the Vision Pro's software interface, while being adapted for traditional displays. Bloomberg notes that some "immersive" elements from the Vision Pro experience won't translate to the 2D world of macOS.<br/>
<br/>
The design overhaul is reportedly a major focus for Apple's software engineering organization and user interface team within its design group. Alan Dye, who helped craft iOS 7's revolutionary redesign in 2013, is said to be overseeing software design for the project.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple is working to make its operating systems look more consistent, the company is deliberately avoiding merging them completely. <em>Bloomberg</em> reports that Apple believes it can create better Macs and iPads by maintaining separate operating systems, while also encouraging consumers to purchase both types of devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<h3>Captive Wi-Fi Data Syncing</h3><br/>
Apple is developing a new feature that will synchronize captive Wi-Fi portal login information across devices, according to <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/ios-19-sync-captive-wi-fi-data-between-devices/">Bloomberg</a></em>. The system will allow users to enter login details for captive Wi-Fi networks  commonly found in hotels, airports, and coffee shops  just once, then automatically sync that information across their iPhone, iPad, and Mac devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is reportedly readying the feature in time for WWDC 2025, suggesting it will likely arrive with iOS 19, iPadOS 19, and macOS 16.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Google Gemini</h3><br/>
According to Google CEO Sundar Pichai, Google <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/30/ios-19-google-gemini-integration-likely/">could reach a deal</a> with Apple to add Google Gemini to the iPhone in the middle of 2025. That timing suggests the functionality could be added in iOS 19, iPadOS 19, and macOS 16. Google Gemini would be added as an alternative to ChatGPT for Siri requests.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Set Default Digital Assistant (EU Only)</h3><br/>
Apple is planning to give users in the EU the ability to set a default voice assistant other than Siri, according to <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/18/apple-to-let-eu-users-switch-away-from-siri/">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple reportedly plans to introduce the change across multiple software platforms, so expect it to turn up on iPhone, iPad, and Mac at a minimum.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>AI Battery Management?</h3><br/>
<em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/12/ios-19-ai-battery-management/">Bloomberg</a></em> reports that Apple plans to use AI to help users better manage their iPhone's battery life. In iOS 19, there will be an AI-powered battery management option that will analyze how a device is used and make adjustments where possible to cut down on battery usage. The battery option will be included in the Apple Intelligence suite of features, with Apple drawing on battery data that it has collected from users over time.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear if Apple plans to bring an equivalent AI-based battery-saving feature over to MacBooks in macOS 16, but it's hard to imagine a reason why the company would choose not to. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Possible Siri Updates</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/03/siri-personal-awareness-change-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-994347" /><br/>
Apple has delayed some of the new Siri features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/03/07/apple-ios-19-siri-delay/">originally planned for macOS 15</a> as part of its Apple Intelligence suite of tools. These updates may now debut with macOS 16, possibly in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/04/11/apple-delayed-siri-features-this-fall/">fall of 2025</a> or even in a later macOS 16 update in 2026. Apple is working on a more intelligent and personalized Siri, capable of understanding context, interacting with onscreen content, and integrating more deeply with apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Personal Context</h3><br/>
Siri will be able to track emails, messages, files, photos, and morelearning from your data to assist with tasks and recall information.<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Show me the files Eric sent me last week.</li><br/>
  <li>Find the email where Eric mentioned ice skating.</li><br/>
  <li>Find the books Eric recommended to me.</li><br/>
  <li>Where's the recipe Eric sent me?</li><br/>
  <li>What's my passport number?</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3>Onscreen Awareness</h3><br/>
Siri will recognize whats on your screen and act on it. For example, if someone texts you an address, you can ask Siri to save it to their contact. Or if youre viewing a photo, Siri can send it for you.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Deeper App Integration</h3><br/>
Siri will handle more complex tasks across apps, enabling actions previously unavailable through voice commands.<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Move files from one app to another.</li><br/>
  <li>Edit a photo and send it to someone.</li><br/>
  <li>Get directions home and share the ETA with Eric.</li><br/>
  <li>Send the email I drafted to Eric.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Accessibility Features</h2><br/>
Each May, Apple shares details on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/13/apple-previews-ios-19-accessibility-features/">new Accessibility features</a> that it plans to add to upcoming versions of its software. This year, Apple detailed several new Accessibility options that will be coming to macOS 16.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Vehicle Motion Cues</h3><br/>
Apple in macOS 16 will expand the iPhone's Vehicle Motion Cues feature to the Mac. The optional feature shows moving dots on an iPhone's screen, in order to help reduce motion sickness while using the device in a moving vehicle. In addition, Apple is going to provide new ways to customize the on-screen dots on a Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/Vehicle-Motion-Cues-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001863" /><br/>
<h3>Magnifier on Mac</h3><br/>
Magnifier on Mac uses the iPhone camera's zoom feature, beaming the feed to a Mac through Continuity Camera. There are options for creating multiple live session windows for tracking a presentation while also zooming in on a textbook, and each view can be customized with different brightness levels and color and contrast filters to suit individual needs. Magnifier on Mac is an extension of the existing Magnifier option on the iPhone, which allows the iPhone to be used to zoom in on text and detect objects.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/mac-magnifier-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1001423" /><br/>
<h3>Other Features</h3><br/>
<ul><li>Accessibility Nutrition Labels in the App Store, which will highlight accessibility features within apps and games.</li><br/>
<li>A new system-wide Accessibility Reader tool will make text easier to read for users with low vision or dyslexia. The feature will give users new ways to customize text and focus on content they want to read, with extensive options for font, color, and spacing.</li><br/>
<li>Braille Access will turn the Mac into a full-featured braille note taker.</li><br/>
<li>Personal Voice will become faster and easier to use, thanks to advancements in on-device machine learning and artificial intelligence. Apple says the feature will be able to create a smoother, more natural-sounding replication of your voice in less than a minute, using only 10 recorded phrases.</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple typically previews its next-generation operating system for Macs during its annual Worldwide Developers Conference in early June, and releases the first developer betas shortly after the event. Typically (but not always), Apple releases all of its new platform software updates in the fall, so we expect to see macOS 16 around September.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What Do You Want to See in macOS 16?</h2><br/>
What new features or improvements would you like to see in the next version of Apple's Mac operating system? Let us know in the comments.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/macos-16-everything-we-know-so-far/">macOS 16: Everything We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-16-everything-we-know-so-far.2457398/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OWC&#039;s New Sale Includes Big Discounts on Mac Docks, Memory, Accessories, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/owcs-new-sale-mac-docks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-new-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-mac-docks-memory-accessories-and-more.2457397/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:20:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/owcs-new-sale-mac-docks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC kicked off a new <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">"Spring productivity event"</a> this week, offering solid discounts on a variety of USB-C docks, memory cards, external drives and enclosures, and Mac accessories. Some of these deals won't be applied until you add the items to your cart, at which time an automatic coupon will be applied to your order.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/owc-dock-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1000898" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
There are a few notable deals in this sale, including the popular <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"><strong>14-Port Thunderbolt Dock for Mac</strong></a>, available for &#36;169.00 once you add it to your cart, down from &#36;279.99. If you purchase a <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fsearch%2F%3Ffilter.rebates%3DOWC.INSTANT.10743.2">qualifying new or used Mac</a> at the same time as this dock, you can get an additional &#36;20 off the accessory at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fshop%2Fspecials"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>OWC Spring Sale</div></a></div><h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDK5P2SG%2F">OWC USB-C Travel Dock</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;99.99 when added to cart, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;169.00 when added to cart, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;199.99 when added to cart, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory Cards</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCFXA4P00480%2F">480GB OWC Atlas Pro</a> - &#36;159.99 when added to cart, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCFXA4P00960%2F">960GB OWC Atlas Pro</a> - &#36;329.99 when added to cart, down from &#36;399.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FUS4EXP1MT02%2F">2TB OWC Express SSD</a> - &#36;299.99 when added to cart, down from &#36;399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3ENVPFX02%2F">2TB Envoy Pro FX SSD</a> - &#36;329.99, down from &#36;379.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;3.99, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;69.00</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/owcs-new-sale-mac-docks/">OWC&#039;s New Sale Includes Big Discounts on Mac Docks, Memory, Accessories, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-new-sale-includes-big-discounts-on-mac-docks-memory-accessories-and-more.2457397/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins Rolling Out Refurbished 2024 iPad Air Models at a Discount</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/refurbished-ipad-air-m2-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-rolling-out-refurbished-2024-ipad-air-models-at-a-discount.2457393/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 07:00:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/refurbished-ipad-air-m2-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last week added iPad Air models with the M2 chip to its <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/refurbished/ipad/ipad-air">refurbished store in the UK</a>, for the first time since the device was released in May 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M2-iPad-Air-Hero-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949535" /><br/>
As usual, the refurbished models are discounted by approximately 15% to 20% compared to Apple's original pricing for the equivalent brand-new models. For example, the 13-inch iPad Air with the M2 chip, 128GB of storage, and Wi-Fi only is <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/product/FV273ZN/A/Refurbished-13-inch-iPad-Air-M2-Wi-Fi-128GB-Space-Gray">currently available for 639</a>, compared to 799 when it was first released last year.<br/>
<br/>
For now, availability is limited to the UK, but inventory should expand to the U.S. and other countries over the next several weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says its refurbished iPads include a new battery and outer shell, a new white box, and all manuals and accessories, including a USB-C charging cable. Apple says it puts refurbished devices through a "thorough cleaning process and inspection," and it performs full functionality testing to ensure that no defective units are sold.<br/>
<br/>
All refurbished iPads are covered by Apple's one-year limited warranty and 14-day return policy, and AppleCare+ coverage is available.<br/>
<br/>
While some savings can be had here, better <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-deals/">iPad deals are often available through Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple updated the iPad Air with the M3 chip in March this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/refurbished-ipad-air-m2-chip/">Apple Begins Rolling Out Refurbished 2024 iPad Air Models at a Discount</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-rolling-out-refurbished-2024-ipad-air-models-at-a-discount.2457393/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Swift Powers the New Things 3 Cloud System</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/swift-powers-new-things-cloud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-swift-powers-the-new-things-3-cloud-system.2457387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 05:18:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/swift-powers-new-things-cloud/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Cultured Code</category>
		<category>Swift</category>
		<category>Things 3</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Cultured Code today <a href="https://culturedcode.com/things/blog/2025/05/a-swift-cloud/">announced</a> that it has overhauled the cloud backend of the popular task management app Things 3 using Apple's Swift programming language, with the new system now live across all users' devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/swift-things-3-cultured-code.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1002223" /><br/>
Cultured Code explained that the transition to the new Swift-based infrastructure occurred seamlessly and without any disruption to users. Although the app's behavior remains unchanged on the surface, the underlying service that synchronizes to-do lists across the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, Apple Watch, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> has been rewritten entirely using Swift and deployed in production for over a year.<br/>
<br/>
The legacy system was originally built using Python 2 and Google App Engine, and had served as the foundation for Things Cloud for more than a decade. While the original synchronization algorithms remain intact and are based on a mathematical model capable of resolving offline edits and conflicts, the aging technology stack was increasingly seen as a barrier to future development. According to Cultured Code, challenges included rising infrastructure costs, slow response times, and the risks associated with dynamic typing in Python.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced Swift in 2014; it has since been widely adopted for iOS and macOS app development, but has seen limited uptake in server environments. Cultured Code began experimenting with Swift on the server in 2021, initially rewriting isolated components before committing to a full-scale rebuild.<br/>
<br/>
To ensure a seamless migration, the new Swift system was initially run in parallel with the legacy system, receiving and processing the same data but without taking over user-facing operations. This dual-processing arrangement allowed engineers to validate the new implementation under production-like conditions. Once the team was satisfied with the accuracy and performance of the Swift backend, they transitioned all users to the new system in early 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Cultured Code reports that the new system has achieved significant performance improvements. Traffic peaks of up to 500 requests per second are now handled by a Kubernetes cluster consisting of four nodes, each with two virtual CPUs and 8GB of RAM. This setup has led to a more than threefold reduction in compute costs compared to the legacy system. Synchronization response times have also improved substantially, and the new architecture delivers a fourfold increase in sync request processing speed.<br/>
<br/>
Things has won two Apple design awards. The app is highly regarded for its design consistency and reliable syncing experience across the Apple ecosystem. Read more about the change in Cultured Code's <a href="https://culturedcode.com/things/blog/2025/05/a-swift-cloud/">full blog post</a> or its <a href="https://www.swift.org/blog/how-swifts-server-support-powers-things-cloud/">post on Apple's Swift.org blog</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cultured-code/">Cultured Code</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift/">Swift</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/things-3/">Things 3</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/swift-powers-new-things-cloud/">Apple&#039;s Swift Powers the New Things 3 Cloud System</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-swift-powers-the-new-things-3-cloud-system.2457387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Large-Sized Foldable Device Could Have an Amazon Rival</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apples-large-sized-foldable-amazon-rival/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-large-sized-foldable-device-could-have-an-amazon-rival.2457386/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 04:27:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apples-large-sized-foldable-amazon-rival/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is developing a large-sized foldable device similar to the one Huawei <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/19/huawei-matebook-fold/">unveiled on Monday</a>, according to industry analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/05/huawei-matebook-fold-menu-bar.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1002182" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Huawei MateBook Fold</em></div><br/>
"My research indicates that Amazon is also internally developing a similar product, which has not yet officially kicked off," said Kuo in a <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1924786064914579735">post on X (Twitter)</a>. Kuo added that the device is projected to enter mass production in late 2026 or 2027 if development progresses on schedule.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">planning a foldable device</a> of a similar vein. Rumors suggest that the dual-screen foldable will be around 13 inches when folded and 18.8 inches when unfolded. Rumors are conflicting on whether it will be an iPad or a MacBook, but the defining factor will be the operating system.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes Apple's large-sized foldable is scheduled to enter mass production in late 2027 or 2028. Apple is concurrently developing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">foldable iPhone</a> that is expected to launch towards the end of 2026.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/05/20/apples-large-sized-foldable-amazon-rival/">Apple&#039;s Large-Sized Foldable Device Could Have an Amazon Rival</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-large-sized-foldable-device-could-have-an-amazon-rival.2457386/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Automate iPhone Low Power Mode Based on Battery Level</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/make-low-power-mode-turn-on-automatically-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/automate-iphone-low-power-mode-based-on-battery-level.2457385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 03:53:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/make-low-power-mode-turn-on-automatically-iphone&#038;post_date=1747749217/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If your iPhone regularly runs out of battery later in the day, Low Power Mode is one way to make it last longer. You can also make Low Power Mode automatically turn on when your battery reaches a certain custom level. Keep reading to learn how.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/low-power-mode.jpg" alt="low power mode" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950287" /><br/>
Most iPhone users are familiar with the way iOS throws up a prompt to turn on Low Power Mode when the battery reaches 20%. Low Power Mode can also be turned on manually at any time by going to <strong>Settings -> Battery</strong> and toggling on the switch next to <strong>Low Power Mode</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
If you find yourself constantly having to turn on Low Power Mode late in the day, you can save some time by setting it up to run automatically when your battery is depleted to a specific custom level. This can be done in the Shortcuts app, as the following steps show.<br/>
<br/>
Bear in mind that Low Power Mode reduces your iPhone's performance and cuts out some background activities. For example, mail must be fetched manually, background app refresh is disabled, and motion and brightness are reduced.<br/>
<br/>
If you're okay with those limitations, follow the steps below to automate the setting on your iPhone.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Shortcuts</strong> app and select the <strong>Automation</strong> tab at the bottom of the screen, then tap the <strong>+</strong> button in the top-right corner.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and select <strong>Battery Level</strong> from the options.</li><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/1set-low-power-mode.jpg" alt="shortcuts" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950295" /><br/>
<li>Check <strong>Falls Below 50%</strong> and then drag the slider to adjust the percentage level for when Low Power Mode should be activated.</li><br/>
<li><li>To ensure the automation runs in the background, tap <strong>Run Immediately</strong>, then tap <strong>Next</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Search for "Set Low Power Mode" and select the card from the results, then tap <strong>Next</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Lastly, tap <strong>Done</strong> in the top-right of the screen.</li><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2set-low-power-mode.jpg" alt="shortcuts" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950296" /></ol>Your "Set Low Power Mode" personal automation should now be listed in the automation list, and will automatically trigger whenever your iPhone reaches the threshold you selected.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Use a Focus Instead</h2><br/>
If you don't want to use the Shortcuts app, you can set up a Focus to come on at a set time of day with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/activate-low-power-mode-with-focus/">Low Power Mode system filter enabled</a>. Follow the link to learn how it's done.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/make-low-power-mode-turn-on-automatically-iphone/">Automate iPhone Low Power Mode Based on Battery Level</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/automate-iphone-low-power-mode-based-on-battery-level.2457385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
