<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:00:22 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Adds AI-Powered Google Lens and Tab Compare to Chrome for Desktop</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-adds-ai-powered-google-lens-and-tab-compare-to-chrome-for-desktop.2432693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today announced three new AI features that are coming to its Chrome browser, with Google taking advantage of the latest Google AI and Gemini models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
Google Lens is now available for the Chrome desktop browser, allowing users to search for what they see on the browser screen with a quick drag and search gesture. Google says that Chrome users can select anything on the page to search for visual matches, including text and images.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing the new Google Lens in Chrome desktop" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/43YUCNEHBHU" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Searches can be refined by color, brand, and other details, and follow up questions are available for a deeper dive into a topic.<br/>
<br/>
Tab compare is a new feature that is designed to let users see an AI-generated overview of products from across multiple tabs in one spot. Google says that this is useful for comparing reviews, prices, and other elements of multiple products when deciding what to purchase.<br/>
<br/>
Google is also introducing a natural language search option for Chrome browsing history, allowing Chrome users to quickly find a site that they visited in the past with a phrase like "What was that ice cream shop I looked at last week?" Conversational search is optional, and can be turned on or off in the Chrome settings. It will not include data from incognito mode.<br/>
<br/>
The AI-powered Google Lens feature will be available with the latest Chrome update that's rolling out over the next few days, while the other two features will be available in the next few weeks. Tab compare and the browser search option will both be rolled out in the U.S. to begin with.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-lens-ai-chrome-desktop/">Google Adds AI-Powered Google Lens and Tab Compare to Chrome for Desktop</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-adds-ai-powered-google-lens-and-tab-compare-to-chrome-for-desktop.2432693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;500 Off M3 MacBook Pro With Amazon and Best Buy&#039;s New Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-m3-macbook-pro-with-amazon-and-best-buys-new-sales.2432691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:31:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">Best Buy</a> today have introduced major discounts on the 14-inch and 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro, providing up to &#36;500 off select models of the 2023 computer. In regards to Best Buy's prices, these deals are available to all members and do not require a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-pro-blue-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935646" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's and Amazon's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch models, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 on Amazon and Best Buy, which are solid second-best prices. You'll also find up to &#36;300 off the 14-inch computers at both retailers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;500 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for the MacBook Air, we're also tracking a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/best-buy-macbook-air-back-to-school/">massive collection of discounts on the M2 and M3 MacBook Air models</a> this week. The M2 MacBook Air is available for just &#36;799.00, while the M3 models start at &#36;849.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.99 (&#36;199 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KB9M3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,999.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5L3PPZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,399.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MKMD4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,999.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5K7BCR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,499.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">matched at Best Buy</a>]</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/500-off-m3-macbook-pro/">Get Up to &#36;500 Off M3 MacBook Pro With Amazon and Best Buy&#039;s New Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-m3-macbook-pro-with-amazon-and-best-buys-new-sales.2432691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You&#039;re Outside the US</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-enable-apple-intelligence-if-youre-outside-the-us.2432686/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:47:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us&#038;post_date=1722530854/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is introducing a set of AI features in iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 under the banner "Apple Intelligence." These features are officially only currently available in beta to developers in the US, but it's actually pretty easy to get it up and running on iPhones and iPads in most other locations with the exception of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-intelligence-europe-delay/">European Union</a> and China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
The main reason Apple has limited region access to Apple Intelligence is that it only supports US English at this time, but if you can work with that – and you have a compatible device – then there's no technical reason why you can't start exploring the new AI features. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Supported Devices</h2><br/>
Apple Intelligence encompasses a range of capabilities, including composing text and emails, automating actions across various apps, generating images, summarizing documents and texts, and more. However, these features require a lot of on-device computing power, so before you do anything, it's worth checking if your device is compatible. iPhone users need either an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max to run Apple Intelligence, while only iPads powered by M1 or later Apple silicon processors are compatible. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Install Beta Software</h2><br/>
If your device is supported, the first thing you need to do is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/get-ios-18-developer-beta-iphone/">install the developer beta for your device</a>. Once you've followed the instructions provided in the linked article and your device is up and running with the latest beta, follow these steps on your iPhone or iPad.<br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Open <strong>Settings</strong>, then tap through to <strong>General ➝ Language & Region</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Add Language..</strong> and choose <strong>English (US)</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Region</strong> and choose <strong>United States</strong>. (Note that this won't affect your App Store regions or purchases.)<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/settings-region.jpg" alt="settings" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960491" /><br/>
  <li>Return to the main <strong>Settings</strong> menu and tap <strong>Apple Intelligence & Siri</strong>.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap <strong>Language</strong> and choose <strong>English (United States)</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>You will now be able to join the Apple Intelligence waitlist, which in most cases gets accepted in just a few minutes. Under the Apple Intelligence header text, tap <strong>Join Waitlist</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-intelligence-join-waitlist.jpg" alt="" width="1391" height="807" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960498" /><br/>
<li>After what should hopefully be a short wait, the message will change to <strong>Turn On Apple Intelligence</strong>. Tap it, and a welcome message should appear, indicating you have sucessfully enabled the AI features on your device. </li></ol><br/>
<br/>
You can learn more <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">here</a> about all of the Apple Intelligence features available in the iOS 18.1 developer beta. Note that some of the Apple Intelligence additions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">won't be coming until later</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/">How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You&#039;re Outside the US</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-enable-apple-intelligence-if-youre-outside-the-us.2432686/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Frustrations Persist for Game Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-game-developers.2432682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 06:17:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some developers continue to be unhappy working with Apple's subscription-based mobile gaming service <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, <a href="https://mobilegamer.biz/inside-apple-arcade-again-late-payments-stonewalled-studios-terrible-tech-support-and-vision-pro-woes/"><em>mobilegamer.biz</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/apple-arcade-orange-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-748620" /><br/>
Talking to the website, some developers said that studios have to wait up to six months to receive payments from &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;. They also pointed out difficulties getting responses to routine emails, unsatisfactory technical support, and poor discoverability. One developer said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>We were able to sign a good deal for our titles which covered our whole development budget. Things have changed since the early times, it's a very difficult and long process to sign a deal with Apple these days. The lack of vision and clear focus of the platform is frustrating and if there is any goal, it keeps changing every year or so. Also technical support is pretty miserable.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Most developers pointed out that &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; pays well, particularly during its first few years:<blockquote>Whatever anyone else says, the advances were fantastic. They were off the charts compared to what we're used to being paid. And you got royalties on top of that.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
While initially developers benefited from prompt monthly payments from the Bonus Pool of ongoing royalty payments, there is now a five month backlog. One developer claims to have almost gone out of business as a result of the slow payments, while others have had to chase for payments for months.<br/>
<br/>
Developers also pointed out general communication issues, and when they do receive a response, the results are often disappointing. One developer shared:<blockquote>We can go weeks without hearing from Apple at all and their general response time to emails is three weeks, if they reply at all. We're supposed to be able to ask product, technical and commercial questions, but often half the Apple team won't turn up and when they do they have no idea what's going on and can't answer our questions, either because they don't have any knowledge on how to answer it, or are not able to share that info for confidentiality reasons.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
There are also apparently significant issues with developing &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games for the Vision Pro headset. Developers expressed their frustration with Apple's technical support for the  Vision Pro, which they described as inadequate and unhelpful. One developer said:<blockquote>The technical support is awful – the worst I have seen anywhere. They are unable to offer any insights into how the hardware and the software it runs on works, or how essential middleware is meant to work with it.<br/>
<br/>
Developing for Vision Pro is like going back in time 10 years because despite the advertised power – and the cost – it is not a machine built for gaming. Getting any complex games working on the platform is difficult.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Other sources told mobilegamer.biz that while they had been approached by Apple to make a game for the Vision Pro, they were offered no financial incentives and no guarantees of promotion. This contrasts with competitors like Meta, which offers generous financial incentives and marketing guarantees to developers creating content for its platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Developers also pointed out issues with quality assurance and updates, claiming that a prolonged discussion with Apple over a single update cost their team two months of work. "Submitting updates is so painful our developers started trying to avoid it," they said. Likewise, there are apparently issues with discoverability. Other developers shared their frustration, stating:<blockquote>It feels like the game's been in a morgue for the last two years. It doesn't matter what we put in the game, Apple won't feature us, it's like we don't exist. So as a developer you think, well, they've given us this money for exclusivity… I don't want to give them the money back, but I do want people to play my game. It's like we're invisible.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
One developer concluded with a broader critique of &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;'s strategic direction:<blockquote>Arcade has no clear strategy and feels like a bolt-on to the Apple company ecosystem rather than like it is truly supported inside the company. Apple 100% does not understand gamers – they have little to no info on who plays their games that they can share with developers, or how they interact with games on the platform already.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
I believe Apple Arcade is a good idea in general, but they need a clear goal for where it should go and what it is for. That's a question they need to answer and then act accordingly.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Another developer offered a slightly more positive perspective:<blockquote>I think Arcade knows who its audience is much more today than at the outset. If that doesn't turn out to be high concept artful indie games, that's not Apple's fault. If they can build a business on family games, good for them and good for the devs who can chase that opportunity.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; launched in September 2019, giving users access to a large library of games for a monthly fee of &#36;6.99. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is also available as part of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundle, which combines multiple Apple services into a single monthly plan. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-developers/">Apple Arcade Frustrations Persist for Game Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-frustrations-persist-for-game-developers.2432682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Maps and Waze Updated With New iPhone and CarPlay Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-maps-waze-new-carplay-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-and-waze-updated-with-new-iphone-and-carplay-features.2432673/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:46:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-maps-waze-new-carplay-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google Maps</category>
		<category>Waze</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google has <a href="https://blog.google/products/maps/maps-waze-new-features-information-on-the-go/">announced</a> new Waze and Google Maps features rolling out for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> users that aim to keep them safer and more informed on the go. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/google-maps-waze-updates.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960484" /><br/>
First up, changes to Maps aim to make it easier to report incidents and helpful information, like nearby construction, lane closures, objects and police presence. These reports come from the Maps and Waze communities, and users will now see which app a report came from. There are larger reporting icons that are designed to be easier to tap for quickly sharing updates, and other drivers can also confirm the incident with a quick tap.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Google Maps gains new destination guidance to make it less confusing when users don't know where to enter or park when they arrive somewhere, especially if it's nighttime. When driving to a place, Maps' new destination guidance will automatically light up your building and its entrance as you approach it, in addition to showing you nearby parking lots. <br/>
<br/>
Over on Waze, Google is adding the ability to see new camera types that enforce things like speed limits and carpool lanes. For example, drivers now see an alert if they're approaching a camera that snaps pictures for things like speeding, running a red light, using the wrong lane (like bus, HOV or carpool), not wearing a seatbelt, or using phones while driving.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Waze is getting a new traffic events feature, which is meant to give users a better understanding of how things like parades, concerts, and sporting events are impacting nearby traffic. If a driver recently went through an impacted area or has places saved near the area in Waze, they will now get a notification once the event has started. This will include details like the cause of the event, if there are road closures and real-time traffic conditions. To help your friends and family, these details are also easily shareable, allowing others to be more prepared for their own ride. <br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Waze drivers will soon get navigation guidance like turn-by-turn directions and real-time traffic updates while their phone is locked. Google says Lock Screen navigation for Waze is coming to iOS this fall, while the other updates to Google Maps and Waze are rolling out globally now on Android and iOS, cars with Google built-in, Android Auto, and Apple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-maps/">Google Maps</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/waze/">Waze</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/google-maps-waze-new-carplay-features/">Google Maps and Waze Updated With New iPhone and CarPlay Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-and-waze-updated-with-new-iphone-and-carplay-features.2432673/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro White, Gray, and Dark Black Colors Shown in New Image</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/iphone-16-pro-colors-shown-leaked-image/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-white-gray-and-dark-black-colors-shown-in-new-image.2432671/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 02:26:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/iphone-16-pro-colors-shown-leaked-image/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Leaker <a href="https://x.com/sonnydickson/status/1818820084762292243">Sonny Dickson</a> is back today with a new dummy unit image showing three alleged iPhone 16 Pro color variants, including a seemingly darker Black Titanium unit compared to the color of the same name on existing iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-16-pro-colors-sonny.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960477" /><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro models are expected to come in black, white or silver, gray or "Natural Titanium," and a rose or rose gold color replacing Blue Titanium, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://x.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1772522408144191732">other leakers</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Dickson's image shows the white, black, and gray versions, but there is no sign of the much-rumored rose gold variant, which was recently described by one leaker as having more of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/">bronze-like hue</a>. Apple did not include a gold option in the iPhone 15 lineup, so a similar variant could see heightened demand.<br/>
<br/>
One <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">rumor</a> suggests that Apple is using an improved process for finishing and coloring titanium, which will result in a glossier look than the brushed aluminum finish of the iPhone 15 Pro models. The glossy finish could look much more like the stainless steel that Apple used in prior years, but it will be more resistant to scratches.<br/>
<br/>
We don't actually know the official color names yet, but Apple may choose to stick with the Titanium colorway branding it used for the iPhone 15 Pro models. The next-generation iPhone 16 lineup is due to arrive around mid-September, so we will know for sure soon. Dickson revealed the colors for the standard (non-Pro) iPhone 16 models on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/">Wednesday</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/01/iphone-16-pro-colors-shown-leaked-image/">iPhone 16 Pro White, Gray, and Dark Black Colors Shown in New Image</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-white-gray-and-dark-black-colors-shown-in-new-image.2432671/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Considers &#039;Forever Mouse&#039; With Subscription Fee</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/logitech-forever-mouse/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-considers-forever-mouse-with-subscription-fee.2432653/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:33:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/logitech-forever-mouse/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Logitech</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Logitech has worked on a "forever mouse" that could come with a subscription fee for regular software updates, according to Logitech CEO Hanneke Faber.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/logitech-mouse.jpg" alt="" width="1187" height="668" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960435" /><br/>
There are no plans to release such a product at the current time, but Faber explained the concept during a recent appearance on <a href="https://www.theverge.com/24206847/logitech-ceo-hanneke-faber-mouse-keyboard-gaming-decoder-podcast-interview"><em>The Verge</em>'s Decoder podcast</a> with Nilay Patel. Apparently, the Logitech innovation center team in Ireland showed Faber a "forever mouse" that is designed to be used for many years. It's a "little heavier" than a standard mouse, and it has "great software and services" that get constantly updated.<blockquote>The other day, in Ireland, in our innovation center there, one of our team members showed me a forever mouse with the comparison to a watch. This is a nice watch, not a super expensive watch, but I'm not planning to throw that watch away ever. So why would I be throwing my mouse or my keyboard away if it's a fantastic-quality, well-designed, software-enabled mouse. The forever mouse is one of the things that we'd like to get to.</blockquote>Logitech is aiming to increase the longevity of its products through more premium devices that can be updated over time. Of course, as a mouse is a one-time purchase, continual software updates would need to be funded through some kind of service model.<br/>
<br/>
Patel asked Faber if she could "envision a subscription mouse," and she responded "possibly." Faber went on to explain that customers would "never have to worry about [their mice] again," which is similar to Logitech's video conferencing services.<br/>
<br/>
When asked whether Logitech had some other model for monetization than subscription fees or advertising, Faber said no, and that she was "intrigued" by a forever mouse that has an accompanying business model around software updates.<blockquote>We're continuing to recycle and refurbish products. All of that is good. But that said, I am intrigued by a forever mouse or forever video conferencing solution that you just update with software and create a business model around that.</blockquote><br/>
Later in the interview, Faber said that there could also be a model where customers trade in a mouse for a newer version, similar to something like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Upgrade Program.<blockquote>The forever mouse, and the forever mouse could be the mouse that you keep and we just send you software updates, but it could also be the mouse that you turn in at Best Buy and we get it back or Best Buy takes it back and refurbs and resells it, which is another business model. We're starting to do that but not yet at the scale that we need to.</blockquote><br/>
Faber pointed out that customers spend around &#36;26 on a mouse or keyboard on average, which is "really so low" for "stuff you use every day." She said there's "so much room to create more value in that space as we make people more productive."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/logitech/">Logitech</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/logitech-forever-mouse/">Logitech Considers &#039;Forever Mouse&#039; With Subscription Fee</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-considers-forever-mouse-with-subscription-fee.2432653/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Steve Jobs Auction Features Apple-1, Bomber Jacket, Sealed Original iPhone, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/steve-jobs-auction-apple-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steve-jobs-auction-features-apple-1-bomber-jacket-sealed-original-iphone-and-more.2432646/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:08:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/steve-jobs-auction-apple-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several Apple and Steve Jobs collectibles <a href="https://www.rrauction.com/auctions/auction-details/698?page=1&amp;itemQty=24&amp;view=gallery&amp;sort=hp&amp;cat=0">are up for sale</a> at RR Auction as part of a "Steve Jobs and the Apple Revolution" event, including an Apple-1 Computer, a 4GB original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple-1 Polaroids from Jobs' pitch deck, Jobs' bomber jacket, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/steve-jobs-auction.jpg" alt="" width="1270" height="715" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960438" /><br/>
A <a href="https://www.rrauction.com/auctions/lot-detail/348973406984025-apple-1-computer-from-apple-employee-dana-redington-from-the-trade-in-pile-in-steve-jobs-office-gifted-by-jobs-and-woz-to-apples-first-applications-engineer/">functional Apple-1 Computer</a> is being auctioned off, and this one is sourced from former Apple employee Dana Redington. It initially came from a "trade-in" pile that was in Steve Jobs' office, and it was gifted to Redington by Jobs and Wozniak. Apple-1 expert Corey Cohen restored the machine. Bids are close to &#36;100,000 now, with the Apple-1 expected to sell for over &#36;300,000.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-a-auction.jpg" alt="" width="1271" height="942" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960439" /><br/>
Several original Polaroids that Jobs used when presenting the Apple-1 to Paul Terrell <a href="https://www.rrauction.com/auctions/lot-detail/348985606984001-steve-jobs-3-apple-1-prototype-polaroid-photographs-given-to-paul-terrell-of-the-byte-shop-in-1976/?cat=668">are being sold off</a>. Terrell famously ordered the Apple-1 machines to sell in The Byte Shop, and the Polaroids were part of the pitch deck. The images are expected to sell for over &#36;30,000.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/jobs-polaroids-auction.jpg" alt="" width="1180" height="664" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960440" /><br/>
An original 4GB &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is also for sale, with the device in original condition and still in the box. Original iPhones have been selling for upwards of &#36;50,000, and the rare 4GB models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/rare-original-iphone-record-auction-price/">have sold for</a> over &#36;190,000. RR Auction expects the latest 4GB &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to sell for &#36;80,000+.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-auction.jpg" alt="" width="552" height="751" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960442" /><br/>
A <a href="https://www.rrauction.com/auctions/lot-detail/349028906984005-steve-jobs-middle-finger-to-ibm-leather-bomber-jacket/">bomber jacket</a> that Jobs wore in an iconic 1983 photograph is being auctioned off, and the jacket is well-known because Jobs was flipping the bird to an IBM sign in New York City in the image. The jacket could sell for up to &#36;75,000.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/jobs-jacket-auction.jpg" alt="" width="1254" height="1771" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960441" /><br/>
Other items in the auction include two Apple Computer checks signed by Steve Jobs, a Steve Jobs NeXT ID badge Polaroid, a Steve Jobs business card, Jobs' 1972 high school yearbook, several vintage magazines with Jobs on the cover, and several classic Apple Macs and memorabilia.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/steve-jobs-auction-apple-1/">Steve Jobs Auction Features Apple-1, Bomber Jacket, Sealed Original iPhone, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steve-jobs-auction-features-apple-1-bomber-jacket-sealed-original-iphone-and-more.2432646/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Fixes Bug Causing Battery Drain on iPhone and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/sonos-fixes-battery-drain-bug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-fixes-bug-causing-battery-drain-on-iphone-and-ipad.2432641/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:10:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/sonos-fixes-battery-drain-bug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos today rolled out a fix for a bug with the Sonos app that has been causing it to drain a significant amount of battery on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. If you've been having battery life issues and are a Sonos user, you may want to install the update ASAP.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/sonos-redesigned-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947528" /><br/>
Sonos community manager Keith Nieves <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/sonos/comments/1egnm5m/sonos_app_update_available/">confirmed the bug fix on Reddit</a> (via <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/7/31/24210410/sonos-iphone-battery-drain-fix-now-available">The Verge</a></em>), stating that the latest version of the app addresses an unspecified issue that was causing excessive battery use on some Apple devices. There have been several complaints about the app's battery usage over the course of the last week, with the Sonos app running constantly in the background.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, several Reddit users have since said they're having issues with the update, which seems to be causing a "No System Found" error message. This is a bug that existed previously, but the update seems to have increased the frequency of the error. Other users have had to re-add their speakers to the Sonos app.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos has committed to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/sonos-app-update-apology/">providing bi-weekly updates</a> for its iOS app in an effort to fix an ill-received design overhaul. Back in May, Sonos introduced a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/redesigned-sonos-app/">redesigned iPhone and iPad app</a> that was meant to provide a more personalized and customizable experience, but it brought several bugs and also removed key features that Sonos customers rely on.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos users have been unhappy with the app, and last week, Sonos CEO Patrick Spence penned an apology and outlined the updates that Sonos will introduce over the next few months. Music Library configuration is set to return in August, while user interface improvements and system stability will be addressed in September.<br/>
<br/>
Alarm consistency will improve in September as well, and in October, Sonos will reintroduce edit mode for playlists and queues.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/sonos-fixes-battery-drain-bug/">Sonos Fixes Bug Causing Battery Drain on iPhone and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-fixes-bug-causing-battery-drain-on-iphone-and-ipad.2432641/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 200 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-200/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-200-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2432640/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:43:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-200/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser that was <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to allow users to test features that are planned for future release versions of the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Safari-Technology-Preview-Updated-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960117" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 200 includes fixes and updates for CSS, JavaScript, Rendering, and Web Extensions.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta. Set to launch this fall, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; is the newest version of macOS that Apple is working on. The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; browser numbering is sequential, so Apple has released 200 updates to its test browser in the last eight years.  <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a> from Apple's website. Complete release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while it is designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download and use. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-200/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 200 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-200-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2432640/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Mophie&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Offer MagSafe Speeds at Slightly Lower Prices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/mophie-qi2-chargers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-mophies-qi2-chargers-offer-magsafe-speeds-at-slightly-lower-prices.2432638/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 14:37:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/mophie-qi2-chargers&#038;post_date=1722472658/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mophie</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Accessory makers have been adopting the new Qi2 standard in recent months because it offers the benefits of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> without the need to license &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; technology from Apple. <a href="https://www.zagg.com/mophie/">Mophie</a> launched its first Qi2 devices in May, debuting a car charger, a 3-in-1 charger, and a battery pack.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Mophie-Qi2-accessories.jpg" alt="" width="1829" height="1029" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908525" /><br/>
All of Mophie's new accessories charge an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W, the same as &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;. The first version of Qi limited wireless charging to 7.5W, but Qi2 supports 15W, and it also includes the same magnetic connection that Apple uses for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;. For context, Apple contributed to Qi2's development, providing insight into the Magnetic Power Profile that's included in the Qi2 standard.<br/>
<br/>
iPhones that support &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; also work with Qi2, so you can use Mophie's chargers with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models. With the exception of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini (which are limited to 12W charging), iPhones will charge at up to 15W with Qi2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Snap+ Powerstation Mini with Stand</h2><br/>
Priced at &#36;70, the <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-powerstation-mini-with-stand/">Snap+ Powerstation Mini</a> is a battery pack that's designed to charge the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; while on the go. It has a 5,000mAh battery inside, and it snaps right on to the back of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; like Apple's now-discontinued <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-magnetic-charger-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960448" /><br/>
At about 4 inches long and 2.75 inches wide, the Powerstation Mini fits well on the back of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max. With the magnetic ring, it pops on to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and stays in place. The Powerstation Mini is 0.25 inches thick and it weighs close to half a pound, so I didn't find this to be the most svelte charging option available. It adds a good amount of bulk to the back of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but it's still small enough to tuck into a bag so you have an extra battery when needed.<br/>
<br/>
At the back of the Powerstation Mini, there's a fold-out stand that you can use to prop the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; upright for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls, gaming, watching videos, and more. It works in either landscape or portrait mode, so you can use it with StandBy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-magnetic-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960449" /><br/>
The Powerstation Mini's body is made from a black plastic, but the stand component is made from aluminum. The front of the device has a soft silicone material that won't scratch an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when it's charging, and the overall design is what you might expect from a battery pack. There are four LED lights so you can see the charge level and monitor charging, and a USB-C port that's used for recharging.<br/>
<br/>
During my testing, I had one of the PowerStation Mini battery packs outright fail after a few days of use. I couldn't get it to charge no matter what I tried, and I ultimately sent it back to Mophie and they sent me another one for testing. Mophie says that this isn't a problem that it's seen before, and the new Powerstation Mini has been working as expected with no failure.<br/>
<br/>
In my testing, the Powerstation Mini was able to charge my &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max to 38 percent in an hour, and that's about the same charging speed I get from a &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charger. It charged to 59 percent in two hours, but it maxed out at a 61 percent charge, which was starting from a dead &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-magnetic-charger-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960450" /><br/>
That means it adds 61 percent battery life to an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, which is what I'd expect from a 5,000mAh battery pack. Depending on which &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; you have, you could get more out of it, but it's not a full charge on Apple's largest &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
When my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery was low, the Powerstation Mini did feel warm to the touch, but it didn't get hot.<br/>
<br/>
For the price, I don't think the Powerstation Mini is a good option for the larger &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. It's not going to provide a full charge, and I'd rather spend that money on a bigger battery pack with charging over USB-C (Mophie has a <a href="https://www.zagg.com/powerstation-apple-2022">10,000mAh battery pack</a> for &#36;60, and there are options from other brands that are even cheaper). You're definitely paying a premium for the stand, so I'd avoid that unless you need that functionality.<br/>
<br/>
For iPhones that have smaller battery capacities, I think the Powerstation Mini makes more sense because you can get more out of it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Snap+ Wireless Charging Vent Mount</h2><br/>
Mophie's <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-charging-vent-mount/">Snap+ Wireless Charging Vent Mount</a> is available for &#36;70 as well, and it's a good option for charging in the car. There's a magnetic charging pad where the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; attaches, a rotating pivot point for changing the angle, and a ring that attaches to the vents in a vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-car-charger-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960451" /><br/>
The mount attaches to a vent using adjustable clips, and I had a surprisingly hard time getting the charger situated and adjusted properly. You need to slide the metal hook between the vent blades and then tighten it up. It feels more secure than rubber clips, but setup is a little more involved and if you want to take the charger off of your vents, it's difficult.<br/>
<br/>
I don't think that's a dealbreaker, but it's not the one I would get if I wanted to regularly remove the mount from the vent. On the plus side, the hook is adjustable, so it should fit well in just about any vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-car-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960452" /><br/>
There's an optional extension arm on the charger so you can change the angle to be above or below the vent, or position it to the left or the right. It's nice to have the add-on arm to get an ideal viewing angle, plus you can further refine with the ball joint that tilts the phone forward or backward a bit.<br/>
<br/>
Mophie includes a 1.5m USB-C cable and a 30W USB-C car adapter, so this is ready to go right out of the box. You just need to pop it out of the box, decide whether you need the adjustable arm, and then attach it to your vent and it's ready to go. There are even two adhesive cable management clips so you can route the cable neatly from the vent to the car charging port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-car-charger-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960453" /><br/>
The Snap+ Charging Vent Mount charges at up to 15W, and the magnetic attachment is strong enough that the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; feels stable and unlikely to come loose while the vehicle is in motion. I had no issues with Mophie's vent mount, aside from needing to fuss with it a few times to make sure it was staying at the proper angle. It charged and worked as expected, and I think it's a good option if you've had trouble with the fit or functionality of other in-car mounting options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Snap+ 3-in-1 Wireless Charge Stand</h2><br/>
Mophie's <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-3-in-1-wireless-charge-stand/">Snap+ 3-in-1 Wireless Charge Stand</a> is priced at &#36;130, and it's my favorite of Mophie's new Qi2 products. It's made from a sturdy white plastic, and it's compact in size thanks to the design.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-3-in-1-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1282" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960454" /><br/>
There's a magnetic &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charging pad at the front, an Apple Watch charger behind that, and a small AirPods charging surface at the bottom. It's one of the more streamlined 3-in-1 charging designs that I've seen, and I appreciate how little space it takes up on my desk.<br/>
<br/>
The charger measures in at about four inches wide and six inches tall, and with the angled design of the arm that holds the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charger, the Apple Watch charger is about flush with the back. The Apple Watch charger is upright rather than sideways so you can't charge an Apple Watch in Nightstand mode, but the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be charged in either portrait or landscape orientation, so it does support StandBy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-3-in-1-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1259" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960455" /><br/>
You can change the tilt of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charger, angling it up or downward to get it at an ideal viewing angle, but the arm itself does not fold so this isn't a charger that's great for travel. At the bottom, there's a built-in Qi charger with a shallow depression for the AirPods. You can get a second &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to charge there, but the fit is not ideal because of the indentation and the charging is slow.<br/>
<br/>
The Qi2 &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charging pad charges an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at up to 15W, while the Apple Watch charger charges at 7.5W, so you're getting the fastest wireless charging speeds for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch (that is fast charging for fast charge-compatible Apple Watch models). The AirPods charge at 5W. A power adapter and charging cable are included.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/mophie-3-in-1-charger-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960456" /><br/>
In my testing, the Snap+ 3-in-1 charged my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from 1 percent to 39 percent in an hour period. The second time around, it charged from 1 percent to 34 percent in an hour, which is a bit of an outlier. The third test was closer to the first test at 38 percent. These are the same charging speeds that I get with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
One of the assumptions about Qi2 was that it would make wireless chargers more affordable because there would be no need to pay Apple to license &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; technology, but so far that hasn't been reflected in the pricing of Qi2 accessories.<br/>
<br/>
Maybe Qi2 prices will go down in the future as the standard is more widely adopted, but there isn't much in the way of savings compared to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, which is disappointing. Mophie's Qi2 devices are solid and Mophie is a trustworthy brand, but I wish these products were more affordable. On the plus side, there is a back to school sale right now, with a 25 percent discount available site wide. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-powerstation-mini-with-stand/">Snap+ PowerStation Mini with Stand</a>, <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-charging-vent-mount/">Snap+ Charging Vent Mount</a>, and <a href="https://www.zagg.com/snap-3-in-1-wireless-charge-stand/">Snap+ 3-in-1 Wireless Charge Stand</a> can be purchased from the Mophie website.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Mophie provided MacRumors with a its Qi2 chargers for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mophie/">Mophie</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/mophie-qi2-chargers/">Review: Mophie&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Offer MagSafe Speeds at Slightly Lower Prices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-mophies-qi2-chargers-offer-magsafe-speeds-at-slightly-lower-prices.2432638/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CarPlay Contributes to Higher Vehicle Satisfaction in Latest Survey</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-carplay-jd-power-study/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-carplay-contributes-to-higher-vehicle-satisfaction-in-latest-survey.2432631/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:48:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-carplay-jd-power-study/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>J.D. Power</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A <a href="https://www.jdpower.com/business/press-releases/2024-us-automotive-performance-execution-and-layout-apeal-study">new survey released last week by J.D. Power</a> shows that U.S. consumers continue to prefer vehicles with support for Apple CarPlay.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-CarPlay-Dash.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934995" /><br/>
The market research firm's annual U.S. Automotive Performance, Execution, and Layout (APEAL) Study found overall satisfaction with in-vehicle infotainment systems to average 805 on a 1,000-point scale. However, satisfaction was higher among owners who use Android Auto (832), and even higher for those who use CarPlay (840). <br/>
<br/>
The study is based on responses from 99,144 owners of new 2024 model-year vehicles in the U.S. who were surveyed after 90 days of ownership, according to J.D. Power. The study was conducted from July 2023 through May 2024.<br/>
<br/>
CarPlay has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/04/12/apple-carplay-android-auto-owner-satisfaction/">routinely fared well</a> in vehicle satisfaction studies since launching in 2014, so this latest one is no surprise. However, it comes after General Motors last year controversially decided to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/31/general-motors-to-phase-out-apple-carplay/">stop offering CarPlay</a> and Android Auto in its new electric vehicles, in favor of its own software system. Electric vehicle maker Rivian <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/23/rivian-explains-why-no-apple-carplay/">also prefers its own software over CarPlay</a>. J.D. Power's study reinforces that these automakers are betting against a consumer preference, and it remains to be seen if they will ever reverse course.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/wwdc-2024-next-generation-carplay-images/">next-generation version of CarPlay</a> that Apple announced in 2022 has yet to become available in any vehicles, but Apple's website says the rollout will begin this year. Next-generation CarPlay will be more deeply integrated across multiple screens in a vehicle, offer a built-in FM radio app and climate controls, and more. It will also be highly customizable, allowing automakers to tailor the design of the system to uniquely match their vehicles.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/j-d-power/">J.D. Power</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-carplay-jd-power-study/">Apple CarPlay Contributes to Higher Vehicle Satisfaction in Latest Survey</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-carplay-contributes-to-higher-vehicle-satisfaction-in-latest-survey.2432631/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Now Available in Ohio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/iphone-drivers-licenses-ohio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-licenses-now-available-in-ohio.2432625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:04:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/iphone-drivers-licenses-ohio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch users in Ohio are <a href="https://www.bmv.ohio.gov/dl-mobile-id.aspx">now able to add</a> their digital IDs and driver's licenses to the Wallet app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, providing a convenient alternative to a physical card.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-ohio-wallet-id.jpg" alt="" width="978" height="550" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960405" /><br/>
Ohio is the fifth state to add support for digital IDs in the Wallet app, following Arizona, Maryland, Colorado, and Georgia.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced plans to add support for digital IDs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/01/apple-shares-us-states-adopting-wallet-ids/">way back in September 2021</a>, but the feature requires states to implement support, and so far, the rollout has been quite slow.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today’s <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Ohio?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Ohio</a>’s lucky day! Ohio Mobile ID has finally come to the <a href="https://twitter.com/Apple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Apple</a> Wallet on iOS + WatchOS.<br><br>Takes just a few minutes answer questions. Digital ID gets delivered about a minute later with this very nice holographic effect when you tilt you phone.<br><br>Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/Ohio_BMV?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@Ohio_BMV</a>! <a href="https://t.co/LJA4rQXLhi">pic.twitter.com/LJA4rQXLhi</a></p>&mdash; Henry Molski (@HankMolski) <a href="https://twitter.com/HankMolski/status/1818689395798446290?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 31, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Connecticut, Hawaii, Iowa, Kentucky, Mississippi, Oklahoma, and Utah are also supposedly working on support for adding a driver's license or ID to the Wallet app, but it has been over two years and none of these states have added the feature. In 2021, Apple said that it was in "discussions with many more states" and was hoping Wallet IDs would be available nationwide in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="How To Add ID" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aRAjyvdYidw" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
IDs and licenses stored in the Wallet app can be used in select U.S. airports at TSA checkpoints.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airport (BWI)</li><br/>
 	<li>Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA)</li><br/>
 	<li>Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX)</li><br/>
 	<li>Denver International Airport (DEN)</li><br/>
 	<li>Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport (ATL)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Wallet app IDs can also be used for showing proof of age or identity at certain businesses and venues, but adoption of this functionality is also limited. Ohio says that businesses and organizations with "compliant mobile ID readers" can accept digital IDs.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/iphone-drivers-licenses-ohio/">iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Now Available in Ohio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-drivers-licenses-now-available-in-ohio.2432625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Quarterly Earnings Report This Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-quarterly-earnings-report-this-week.2432616/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:38:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will report its earnings results for the third quarter of its 2024 fiscal year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/aapl-q3-2024-earnings-report-date/">on Thursday, August 1</a> at 1:30 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple's CEO Tim Cook and CFO Luca Maestri will discuss the results on a conference call with analysts a half hour later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-iPad-Air-and-iPad-Pro-11-inch-and-13-inch-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949648" /><br/>
Keep reading for some key things to know about the quarter, including a recap of new products announced, revenue expectations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Products During Quarter</h2><br/>
The quarter ran from March 31 through June 29, according to Apple's fiscal calendar. The following products launched during this period:<ul><li>11-inch iPad Pro with M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>13-inch iPad Pro with M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>11-inch iPad Air with M2 chip</li><br/>
<li>13-inch iPad Air with M2 chip</li><br/>
<li>Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li>Vision Pro pre-orders in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/vision-pro-launching-in-more-countries/">eight additional countries</a></li></ul><h2>Revenue Expectations</h2><br/>
Apple has not provided formal revenue guidance since before the COVID-19 pandemic, but the average Wall Street estimate for Apple's third quarter revenue is &#36;84.5 billion, according to data compiled by <a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/quote/AAPL/analysis/"><em>Yahoo Finance</em></a>. This would be around a 3% increase over the &#36;81.8 billion revenue the company reported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/03/apple-3q-2023-results/">in the year-ago quarter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This would be in line with the outlook that Apple's CFO provided on last quarter's earnings call:<blockquote>We expect our June quarter total company revenue to grow low-single-digits year-over-year in spite of a foreign exchange headwind of about 2.5 percentage points.</blockquote><h2>Conference Call</h2><br/>
Cook and Maestri will hold a conference call at 2:00 p.m. Pacific Time on Thursday to discuss the company's quarterly earnings results. The call should last around one hour, and it will include a Q&A segment with analysts.<br/>
<br/>
A live audio stream of the conference call will be available on <a href="https://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">Apple's Investor Relations page</a>, and a recording will be available later in the day for replay.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What's Next</h2><br/>
Apple's current quarter runs through September 28, and the company has yet to announce any new products during this period.<br/>
<br/>
AAPL is trading for around &#36;223 as of writing, down from a 52-week high of &#36;237.23.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-q3-2024-earnings-preview/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s Quarterly Earnings Report This Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-quarterly-earnings-report-this-week.2432616/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iStat Menus 7.0 Brings Comprehensive Redesign and New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/istat-menus-7-0-brings-comprehensive-redesign-and-new-features.2432615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:15:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iStat Menus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Version 7.0 of the popular system monitoring tool iStat Menus is <a href="https://bjango.com/mac/istatmenus/">now available</a>, bringing a comprehensive redesign and range of new features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/istat-menus-7.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960370" /><br/>
The redesign of iStat Menus 7.0 includes an updated interface with new menu bar modes, such as stacked labels and values, and new menu bar items, such as the Wi-Fi network name and GPU frames per second. For users of Apple silicon Macs, the update brings frequency monitoring and additional sensor support. Users can now choose from more theme options and menu background colors. Fan speeds can be controlled with greater precision, allowing for gradual ramp-up and complete control over the speed curve.<br/>
<br/>
The time menu has been enhanced with 7-day and 14-day rolling calendar modes, providing users with flexible scheduling options. The combined mode has undergone a major overhaul, allowing any item to be displayed in the menu bar with unique settings and more menu sections available in the dropdown menu.<br/>
<br/>
Weather monitoring has also seen improvements, offering a detailed view of current conditions, hourly forecasts, and weekly overviews. Users can access information such as temperature, wind speed and direction, chance of rain, humidity, UV index, and more, with data available for their current location or almost anywhere in the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/menus-1.jpg" alt="" width="2576" height="773" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960379" /><br/>
iStat Menus 7.0 offers more extensive notification capabilities, allowing users to set alerts for a wide range of events related to CPU, GPU, memory, disks, network, sensors, battery, power, and weather. Notifications can be customized to inform users about changes such as public IP updates, internet connection issues, CPU usage spikes, low disk space, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The app also provides detailed CPU information, including usage for individual cores, history graphs, load averages, uptime, and CPU frequency. GPU monitoring covers processor usage, memory, temperature, and frequency. Memory statistics include usage, history, memory pressure, compressed memory, swap, and a list of apps using the most memory.<br/>
<br/>
Disk usage and activity monitoring are also enhanced, showing used space, free space, and disk activity. S.M.A.R.T. status monitoring and detailed per-app disk usage are now available. Network monitoring features include history graphs, current bandwidth usage, a bandwidth breakdown for top apps, detailed connection info, IP addresses, and an internet connectivity indicator.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/menus-2.jpg" alt="" width="2576" height="790" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-960380" /><br/>
Battery and power information is extensive, providing detailed current state information and configurable menu items that change based on whether the device is draining, charging, or fully charged. Battery levels for Bluetooth devices like AirPods, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad are also displayed. Real-time sensor listings include temperatures, fan speeds, voltages, current, and power, with customizable fan speed control based on temperature and battery state.<br/>
<br/>
The date and time features are highly customizable, with menu bar clocks, a calendar with upcoming events, and world clocks that include detailed sun and moon information. Each world clock can be given a custom name, making it easier to track time for colleagues or family members in different time zones. Combined mode is particularly useful for laptops, allowing multiple items to be combined into a single menu bar item to save space while still providing access to all relevant information.<br/>
<br/>
iStat Menus 7.0 is <a href="https://bjango.com/mac/istatmenus/">available for download</a> with a 14-day free trial, allowing users to explore its new features and enhancements before committing to a purchase. Additionally, it is available via Setapp, a subscription service that offers access to iStat Menus and over 250 other Mac apps for &#36;9.99 per month, with no additional fees or ads.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/istat-menus/">iStat Menus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/istat-menus-7-0-brings-new-features/">iStat Menus 7.0 Brings Comprehensive Redesign and New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/istat-menus-7-0-brings-comprehensive-redesign-and-new-features.2432615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has Every M4 iPad Pro on Sale With Multiple Record Low Prices for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-every-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale-with-multiple-record-low-prices-for-members.2432613/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:03:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a large collection of discounts on the <a href="https://howl.me/cmMGdhEepJe">2024 M4 iPad Pro</a> at Best Buy, which includes multiple all-time low prices on both 11-inch and 13-inch models. The majority of these deals will only be available to My Best Buy Plus/Total members, but there are a few instances of record low prices being matched at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
For the smaller 11-inch M4 iPad Pro, Best Buy has introduced a new best-ever price on the entry-level 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, available for <a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> for members, down from &#36;999.00. Best Buy has every model of the 11-inch iPad Pro on sale right now, including both Wi-Fi and cellular versions, and you'll find steeper discounts for members.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFPxxvE8h">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;899.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFQmy1Gei">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,099.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,199.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,349.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFRPRre0A">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,549.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,699.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFSDWvQXy">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,849.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFTEJUxTd">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,949.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,099.00</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
Similar to the 11-inch models, Best Buy has every Wi-Fi and cellular version of the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro on sale this week. Prices start at <a href="https://howl.me/cmMFUSaNsv1"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, and totals up to &#36;150 off these devices. Amazon is also matching the prices of quite a few 13-inch iPad Pro models without the need for a special membership.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFUSaNsv1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,199.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,299.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFWz9v0xi">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,389.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,499.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMFYk8pTUn">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;1,899.00 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6S6LS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;1,839.00 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMF0zTcj8I">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,149.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmMF1Y7ND7f">2TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> - &#36;2,249.00 for Best Buy members, down from &#36;2,399.00</li></ul>  Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/best-buy-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale/">Best Buy Has Every M4 iPad Pro on Sale With Multiple Record Low Prices for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-every-m4-ipad-pro-on-sale-with-multiple-record-low-prices-for-members.2432613/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Pro&#039;s Tandem OLED Display Tech Could Extend to Future Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pros-tandem-oled-display-tech-could-extend-to-future-vision-pro.2432610/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 07:34:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG and Samsung have prototyped micro-OLED displays with tandem OLED technology, according to <a href="https://www.sisajournal-e.com/news/articleView.html?idxno=404430">Korean publication <em>Sisa Journal</em></a>, paving the way for a future model of Apple's Vision Pro mixed-reality headset to potentially adopt the technology.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-lenses.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898584" /><br/>
The report said it is unclear if or when LG and Samsung will begin mass production of tandem micro-OLED displays, but with a second-generation Vision Pro not expected to be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/no-apple-vision-pro-2-before-end-of-2026/">until late 2026 at the earliest</a>, there is still time for the two companies to commercialize the technology for potential inclusion in the next model.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple released new iPad Pro models with tandem OLED displays, which have two organic light-emitting layers stacked together for increased brightness, improved power efficiency, and longer longevity compared to single-layer OLED displays. These same benefits would extend to a future Vision Pro that adopts the technology.<br/>
<br/>
Here is how Apple described the iPad Pro's tandem OLED technology:<blockquote>The Ultra Retina XDR display features state-of-the-art tandem OLED technology that uses two OLED panels and combines the light from both to provide phenomenal full-screen brightness. The new iPad Pro supports an incredible 1000 nits of full-screen brightness for SDR and HDR content, and 1600 nits peak for HDR. No other device of its kind delivers this level of extreme dynamic range. Tandem OLED technology enables sub-millisecond control over the colour and luminance of each pixel, taking XDR precision further than ever. Specular highlights in photos and video appear even brighter, and there's more detail in shadows and low light than ever before on iPad — all while delivering even more responsiveness to content in motion.</blockquote>The current Vision Pro is equipped with two 4K micro-OLED displays supplied by Sony.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, the technology now exists for the next-generation Vision Pro to feature even brighter and more power efficient displays in a few years from now.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/vision-pro-tandem-oled-report/">iPad Pro&#039;s Tandem OLED Display Tech Could Extend to Future Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-pros-tandem-oled-display-tech-could-extend-to-future-vision-pro.2432610/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Beta Users Invited to &#039;Rate Your Experiences&#039; and Earn Points</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-beta-users-invited-to-rate-your-experiences-and-earn-points.2432605/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 05:37:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In the latest macOS 15.1, iOS 18.1, and iPadOS 18.1 betas, Apple has introduced a new "Rate Your Experiences" feature in its Feedback Assistant app that lets users rate the generative content served by Apple Intelligence across apps, with the aim of using the feedback to refine and train Apple's generative models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/rate-your-experiences-apple-intelligence.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960329" /><br/>
Apple describes the new feature like so:<br/>
<blockquote>Help improve Apple products and services! Content such as your emails from the Mail app and messages from the Messages app will be displayed to you, along with content generated from them for Apple Intelligence features. This data always remains on your device unless you choose to submit it to Apple, after rating your experience.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
In the new section, users are asked to "thumbs up" or "thumbs down" recent generated content to indicate their level of satisfaction with the results. If the "experience" shown was not good, users are invited to optionally offer more details for submission to Apple. This can be done by choosing from pre-defined feedback presented as a checkmark list, and by providing additional typed information for context.<br/>
<br/>
In the case of a summarized email in the Mail app, for example, users can choose from the following issues:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>Hard to understand</li><br/>
  <li>Missed key detail</li><br/>
  <li>Incorrect attributions</li><br/>
  <li>Too long</li><br/>
  <li>Irrelevant additions</li><br/>
  <li>Stereotyping or bias</li><br/>
  <li>Overly suggestive or sexual</li><br/>
  <li>Vulgar or offensive</li><br/>
  <li>Other</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are similar pre-set feedback options for other Apple Intelligence features such as Smart reply, Notifications summary, prioritized emails, Image Playground, Writing Tools, and more. The new section also includes a scoring system that lets users level up their score by providing feedback to Apple, although it's not explained what any points earned could be used for. <br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the first version of Apple Intelligence in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 developer betas. While the betas include some useful Apple Intelligence features like Writing Tools, some of the Apple Intelligence additions <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">won't be coming until later</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/apple-intelligence-beta-users-rate-experiences/">Apple Intelligence Beta Users Invited to &#039;Rate Your Experiences&#039; and Earn Points</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-beta-users-invited-to-rate-your-experiences-and-earn-points.2432605/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone 16 Pro Color Could Have Bronze Appearance</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-pro-color-could-have-bronze-appearance.2432596/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:00:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Fixed Focus Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several iPhone 16 Pro rumors have suggested that Apple will eliminate the Blue Titanium option that it used for the iPhone 15 Pro devices and replace it with a rose or gold color. Now, the latest claim is that the new color is actually bronze or has a bronze-like appearance. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-16-pro-rose.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960320" /><br/>
According to the Weibo-based leaker "<a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/Oq4eJxISx">Fixed focus digital</a>," a new iPhone 16 Pro Max color resembles a "bronze hue," while the surrounding frame has a titanium-like appearance. Earlier this month, another Chinese leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-16-pro-rose-color-coming/">suggested</a> that the color code for the new iPhone 16 Pro color is simply "Rose," not the previous "Rose Gold" color that Apple first offered back in 2015 for the iPhone 6S. <br/>
<br/>
It could well be that the two claims are not contradictory and are in fact referring to the same color, but as seen under different lighting conditions. It's worth mentioning that today's leaker only mentions the iPhone 16 Pro Max in relation to the new color, but it is reasonable to assume that it will come to both Pro models. Other colors that the iPhone 16 Pro and ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">expected</a> to be available in include black, white or silver, and gray or "Natural Titanium." <br/>
<br/>
Another rumor suggests that Apple plans to use an improved process for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">finishing and coloring titanium</a>, which will result in a glossier look than the brushed aluminum finish of the iPhone 15 Pro models. The glossy finish could look much more like the stainless steel that Apple used in prior years, but it will be more resistant to scratches.<br/>
<br/>
Apple typically releases its new iPhone series around mid-September, which means we are about six weeks out from the launch of the iPhone 16 series. Like the iPhone 15 series, this year's lineup is expected to stick with four models, but with the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max handsets getting slightly bigger display sizes. You can learn about plenty of other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">rumored design differences and new features</a> by following the link.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fixed-focus-digital/">Fixed Focus Digital</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/new-iphone-16-pro-color-bronze-appearance/">New iPhone 16 Pro Color Could Have Bronze Appearance</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-pro-color-could-have-bronze-appearance.2432596/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Revealed: iPhone 16 Colors and Redesigned Camera in Leaked Image</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revealed-iphone-16-colors-and-redesigned-camera-in-leaked-image.2432593/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 02:00:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Leaker Sonny Dickson today <a href="https://x.com/SonnyDickson/status/1818474212090429828">shared an image</a> displaying a selection of iPhone 16 dummy models that reveal Apple's planned new color options and the rumored redesigned camera bump coming to its iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-16-colors-dummies.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960310" /><br/>
The picture showcases five new colorways for the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, and they match the descriptions previously predicted by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>: White, Black, Blue, Green, and Pink.<br/>
<br/>
The new colors suggest Apple is going for a less muted, less desaturated color palette for the standard iPhone 16 models this year, although there could be differences in materials used compared to the dummy models shown. As a reminder, the current iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus devices are available in Blue, Pink, Yellow, Green, and Black.<br/>
<br/>
For the 6.1- and 6.7-inch iPhone 16 models, Apple is also planning a new vertical camera lens arrangement that is a departure from the prior diagonal lens setup. The new orientation, evidenced in the dummy units, will presumably allow the standard iPhone 16 models to capture Spatial Video for the Vision Pro headset, something only the iPhone 15 Pro models are currently capable of doing. Prior iPhones have used a square-shaped camera bump to accommodate the diagonal lenses, but Apple is able to slim down the camera bump with the new lens arrangement.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus are anticipated to include an A18 chip, 8GB of RAM, a new "Capture" button on the right side for photo and video, the Action button previously exclusive to iPhone 15 Pro models, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">more</a>. All four devices in the iPhone 16 series are expected to launch around mid-September. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/31/revealed-iphone-16-colors-redesigned-camera/">Revealed: iPhone 16 Colors and Redesigned Camera in Leaked Image</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revealed-iphone-16-colors-and-redesigned-camera-in-leaked-image.2432593/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
