<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 05:03:54 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Event Preview, iPad Pro With M4 Chip Rumor, New Beats Headphones, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/04/top-stories-ipad-pro-m4-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-preview-ipad-pro-with-m4-chip-rumor-new-beats-headphones-and-more.2425435/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/04/top-stories-ipad-pro-m4-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been a long time since the last one, but an Apple event is finally right around the corner! While it's anticipated to be a fairly short pre-recorded affair, we're expecting to see the first updates to the iPad lineup in over a year and half, so make sure to tune in to see what Apple has in store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/top-stories-4may2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949129" /><br/>
Other news and rumors this week included a couple of product introductions from Apple's Beats brand, a roundup of rumors about updates to Apple's stock apps coming in iOS 18, and more changes to Apple's policies in the EU related to the Digital Markets Act, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What to Expect From the May 7 Apple Event</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">first event of 2024 kicks off on Tuesday, May 7,</a> at 7 a.m. Pacific Time, and we've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-may-7-event/">put together our usual pre-event guide</a> outlining what we're expecting to see on Tuesday. Several new products are expected to be unveiled, including two new iPad Pro models, two new iPad Air models, an updated Apple Pencil, and a redesigned Magic Keyboard for iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Let-Loose-Event-What-to-Expect-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949123" /><br/>
One rumor was particularly surprising this week, as <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said there is a "strong possibility" that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/">new iPad Pro models will be equipped with Apple's next-generation M4 chip</a>, rather than the M3 chip that debuted in the MacBook Pro and iMac six months ago. Gurman believes the M4 chip will have an upgraded Neural Engine that is able to process artificial intelligence (AI) tasks faster.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/">new Apple Pencil is rumored to feature haptic feedback</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Will the New iPad Pro Really Have the M4 Chip?</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">Will the next iPad Pro models be equipped with the M4 chip</a> instead of the M3 chip, or will this rumor end up being as wrong as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/19/prosser-apple-watch-series-7-design/">flat-edged Apple Watch Series 7</a> from a few years ago?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/M4-iPad-Pro-Thumb-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949125" /><br/>
While it would be unprecedented for an M-series chip to debut in an iPad before a Mac, there is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">some evidence to suggest that the rumor might be true</a>, so check out our story for more details about this possibility.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Beats Solo Buds Launching in June for Just &#36;79.99</h2><br/>
Apple unveiled two new Beats headphone models this week, including the on-ear <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">Beats Solo 4</a> and the compact <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">Beats Solo Buds</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/beats-solo-buds-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948605" /><br/>
Launching in June, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">Beats Solo Buds are particularly interesting</a> given their competitive &#36;79.99 price point. Key features include ear tips with four size options, up to 18 hours of battery life, a USB-C carrying case, and Find My support on iOS and Android. However, the Solo Buds lack active noise cancellation, and the carrying case does not have a built-in battery.<br/>
<br/>
In other Beats news, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">LeBron James</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/unreleased-beats-pill-daniel-ricciardo/">Daniel Ricciardo</a> have been seen in public carrying an unreleased speaker very clearly descended from the discontinued Beats Pill family, so it looks like the popular portable speaker may be making a comeback in the not too distant future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 Rumored to Add New Features to These 16 Apps on Your iPhone</h2><br/>
Apple's annual developers conference WWDC is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">now under six weeks away</a>, and that means the iOS 18 beta is just around the corner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Apple-Music-Messages-and-Notes-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948782" /><br/>
iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">rumored to include major upgrades to many built-in iPhone apps</a>, including Apple Music, Messages, Calculator, Notes, Safari, and others. We recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">recapped new features that are expected on a per-app basis</a>, so check out the list for a complete overview.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Confirms iPadOS Will Get Same EU App Changes as iOS This Fall</h2><br/>
All of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">app-related changes</a> recently introduced on iPhones in the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/ipados-eu-app-changes-fall/">will also be available on iPads in the EU starting later this fall</a>, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPad-Air-5.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938463" /><br/>
This news comes after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/">EU ruled that the iPad is a "gatekeeper" platform</a>. Apple has six months to comply with the Digital Markets Act on the iPad, so alternative app marketplaces, support for web browser engines other than WebKit, and more will likely be available by iPadOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/may-2-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/04/top-stories-ipad-pro-m4-chip/">Top Stories: Apple Event Preview, iPad Pro With M4 Chip Rumor, New Beats Headphones, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-preview-ipad-pro-with-m4-chip-rumor-new-beats-headphones-and-more.2425435/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sends Congratulatory Letters to 2024 Swift Student Challenge Winners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/swift-student-challenge-letters-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sends-congratulatory-letters-to-2024-swift-student-challenge-winners.2425417/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:43:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/swift-student-challenge-letters-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		<category>Swift Playgrounds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some Swift Student Challenge winners today began receiving congratulatory certificates from Apple, with one Distinguished Winner sharing a images of the letter he received from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/swift-student-challenge-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921665" /><br/>
<blockquote>We're honored to recognize you as a Distinguished Winner of the 2024 Swift Student Challenge. Your app playground stands among the best of the best in this year's challenge, demonstrating your creativity, passion for coding, and commitment to building great apps.<br/>
<br/>
You've truly inspired us and we can't wait to see what you do next!</blockquote>Apple this year picked a total of 350 winners, including 50 Distinguished Winners. Winners are meant to receive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones, but Apple appears to be sending that reward in a separate shipment.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It’s here! The certificate for the 2024 Swift Student Challenge! &#x1f929;<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/SwiftStudentChallenge?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#SwiftStudentChallenge</a> <a href="https://t.co/KzoiOH8HEz">pic.twitter.com/KzoiOH8HEz</a></p>&mdash; Vedant (@vedantapps) <a href="https://twitter.com/vedantapps/status/1786535607818494174?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 3, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
While all 350 Swift Student Challenge winners were eligible to apply to attend Apple's June 10 WWDC special event at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>, the Distinguished Winners are being invited to Cupertino for a three-day &zwnj;Apple Park&zwnj; event that also includes time to interface with Apple engineers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's annual Swift Student Challenge tasks students with creating an innovative coding project using the Swift Playgrounds app. Projects are judged based on technical accomplishment, creativity of ideas, and the content of the written responses that explain the project.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift-playgrounds/">Swift Playgrounds</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/swift-student-challenge-letters-2024/">Apple Sends Congratulatory Letters to 2024 Swift Student Challenge Winners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sends-congratulatory-letters-to-2024-swift-student-challenge-winners.2425417/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From the May 7 Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-may-7-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-the-may-7-apple-event.2425411/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:31:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-may-7-event&#038;post_date=1714779069/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>May 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to hold its first event of the year next Tuesday, and the focus will be on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models are set to be updated, and Apple also plans to refresh some of its &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oZ05z2YhFyY" title="What to Expect From Apple&#39;s May 7th iPad Event!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
This guide features details on everything that we're expecting to see at the "Let Loose" event that will take place on May 7.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad_pro">iPad Pro</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will be the star of Apple's event, featuring the first larger form factor OLED displays. OLED display technology will bring deeper blacks, better contrast, more vibrant colors, and better power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/ipad-pro-best-oled-panels/">said to be using</a> the "best OLED panels on the market" with higher brightness, extended battery life, 120Hz ProMotion refresh rates, and a long lifetime for the OLED technology. OLED displays have pixels that can be controlled individually, so high dynamic range content looks more realistic and true-to-life.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/iPad-Pro-2024-Will-Be-a-Huge-Upgrade-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936070" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will be available in 11.1-inch and 12.9-inch sizes, and both models will be thinner with slimmed down bezels. The 11.1-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is expected to be 5.1mm thick, down from 5.9mm, while the 12.9-inch model will be 5mm thick, down from 6.4mm. The tablets will be roughly the same size as the current models, with small changes to the length and width.<br/>
<br/>
It's not entirely clear which M-series chip the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will use, and there is a possibility that these will be the first devices equipped with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">AI-focused next-generation M4 chip</a>. If that doesn't happen, Apple will use the M3 that's in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>. Either way, it'll mark a massive improvement.<br/>
<br/>
Along with slimmed down bezels, the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s front-facing camera is expected to be relocated to the side of the device rather than the top, so the camera will be upright when the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is in a landscape orientation. That makes more sense for video calls and filming done when the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is used with a keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">possible MagSafe charging support</a> and up to 4TB of storage, and we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/how-much-oled-ipad-pro-models-cost/">could also see prices go up</a>. Multiple sources have said that the OLED technology will make the 2024 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models more expensive, but just how much more expensive remains to be seen. Rumors have ranged from &#36;160 more to &#36;700 more.<br/>
<br/>
For more on the rumors that we've heard so far about the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, we have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">dedicated 2024 iPad Pro guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad_air">iPad Air</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will get a refresh alongside the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, and for the first time, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/05/apple-two-ipad-air-models/">splitting the Air lineup</a> and introducing two models. The first &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be a direct successor to the current version, measuring in at 10.9 inches. The second model will come in at 12.9 inches, similar to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
Offering the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; in two screen sizes will allow customers who want a large screen at a more affordable price than the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; to have that option. The 10.9 and 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models will not have the same OLED screen technology Apple is bringing to the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, instead using LCD, and that will keep costs lower.<br/>
<br/>
We are not expecting design changes to the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, except for the new, larger size. Both models will look like the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; 4, featuring an edge-to-edge display with slim bezels and an aluminum chassis with flat, rounded edges. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be thicker than the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, and it will have thicker bezels.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/next-gen-ipad-air-with-12-9-inch-display-and-redesigned-camera-unit-revealed-in-cad-renders/">Leaked iPad Air images</a> point to a rear camera with a protruding pill-shaped camera bump that's similar to the design we're expecting to see with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>. The front camera could be repositioned so that it will be at the top of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; when it's in landscape mode, allowing it to be in the right orientation for video calls when it's used with a keyboard. The current version has the camera at the top when it is in portrait mode.<br/>
<br/>
While we won't see notable design updates, Apple may introduce new color options. The existing model comes in a range of pastel shades, so Apple could tweak the color selection.<br/>
<br/>
We have more on what's expected for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/">in our iPad Air guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_pencil">Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will be accompanied by an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil-3/">updated version of the Apple Pencil</a>, which Apple might call the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> 3. It isn't yet clear if there will be design changes, but it is expected to be the first &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; that supports haptic feedback.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/black-and-white-apple-pencil-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2664" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-744328" /><br/>
How that haptic feedback will be used remains to be seen, but code in iOS 17.5 suggested there will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-apple-pencil-4-rumor/">a "squeeze" gesture</a> that could do things like activate different tools and settings in apps.<br/>
<br/>
There were rumors of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">interchangeable magnetic tips</a> at one point, but we don't know if that's actually a feature that's coming or an inaccurate rumor. Deeper integration with the Vision Pro is a possibility, and it could perhaps work with drawing apps that support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>. There's also a chance that we could see the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; come in both black and white rather than just white.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="magic_keyboard">Magic Keyboard</h2><br/>
Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/magic-keyboard-apple-pencil-rumors/">overhaul the Magic Keyboard</a>, introducing a sturdier frame <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">made from aluminum</a> rather than the polyurethane material used for the current version. While the frame and area around the keyboard will be made from aluminum, the exterior shell will still be made from silicone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/magic-keyboard-yellow-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-844768" /><br/>
With the aluminum build, an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Magic Keyboard combo will more closely resemble a MacBook, both in terms of looks and functionality. There will be a larger trackpad that is similar to the trackpad on a MacBook, so the keyboard will offer a MacBook-like typing and navigating experience.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is using more premium materials for the new Magic Keyboard, so it could be more expensive. The current model is priced starting at &#36;299 for the 11-inch version. The new Magic Keyboard is likely to work with both the upcoming &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models as they are similar in size (11.1 and 12.9 inches for the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and 10.9 and 12.9 inches for the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;).<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_accessories">Other Accessories</h2><br/>
Apple refreshes its selection of Apple Watch bands, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases, and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; cases regularly, introducing new color options. We could see new summer colors for many accessories, and Apple will need to update its &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; cases to accommodate the new designs. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="vision_pro_expansion">Vision Pro Expansion</h2><br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">will expand the Vision Pro headset</a> to additional countries before WWDC, and we're getting short on time. We could see Apple bring the Vision Pro to countries like the UK, Canada, China, and more as part of the May 7 event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
<h2 id="how_to_watch">How to Watch</h2><br/>
The "Let Loose" event is set to take place on Tuesday, May 7 at 7:00 a.m. Pacific Time or 10:00 a.m. Eastern Time. Apple will <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">live stream the event</a> on its website <a href="https://youtu.be/2O7X1Lkphuo">and on YouTube</a>, plus there is an option to watch it on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Those unable to watch or those who want to follow along with MacRumors can visit <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a> for the liveblog or follow us on Twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">at MacRumorsLive</a> for live tweet coverage.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/may-2024-apple-event/">May 2024 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/what-to-expect-may-7-event/">What to Expect From the May 7 Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-the-may-7-apple-event.2425411/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get Low Prices on Anker and Eufy Accessories, AirPods, Apple Pencil, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-3-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-low-prices-on-anker-and-eufy-accessories-airpods-apple-pencil-and-more.2425398/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:47:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-3-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best deals include great discounts on both Apple products and third-party accessories, ranging from all-time low prices on Apple Pencil and the Studio Display, to steep markdowns on Anker's popular USB-C charging accessories. You'll also find OWC's ongoing discount on its best Thunderbolt docks and hubs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0012.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848002" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>OWC</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/owc-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949024" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;150 off OWC's 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">OWC</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
OWC is still hosting a big sale on its docks, hubs, and other Mac accessories, highlighted by the 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;129.99, down from &#36;279.99. This accessory features two Thunderbolt 3 ports, five USB Type-A ports, one USB Type-C port, one Mini DisplayPort port, one gigabit Ethernet port, one S/PDIF digital audio output port, and one 3.5mm stereo audio input/output port.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker and Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/new-anker-eufy-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949022" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker and Eufy accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/amazon-discounts-accessories-anker/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714660094244"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Link 4-Pack for &#36;48.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for &#36;89.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we also started tracking discounts on Anker and Eufy accessories on Amazon, including savings for Prime members on Eufy's Find My-compatible SmartTrack Bluetooth trackers. You can find the full list of items on sale <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/amazon-discounts-accessories-anker/">in our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/airpods-pro-2-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949019" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;59 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/airpods-weekend-deals/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week also saw numerous discounts across the AirPods lineup, including the AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00 and AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99. The Pro model did briefly hit &#36;179.99 earlier in the week, but that all-time low price has since expired.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/studio-display-april.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948662" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;299 off Apple Studio Display</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/amazon-apple-sale-airpods-pencil/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Apple Studio Display (Standard Glass) for &#36;1,299.97</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HP4KL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Apple Studio Display (Nano-texture Glass) for &#36;1,599.97</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week introduced the first discount on the Apple Studio Display that we've seen in months, including &#36;299 off both Standard and Nano-texture Glass models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-pencil-2-april.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948664" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;50 off Apple Pencil</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/amazon-apple-sale-airpods-pencil/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil 2 for the record low price of &#36;79.00, down from &#36;129.00. The Apple Pencil 2 is compatible with the iPad mini (6th generation), iPad Air (4th generation and later), 12.9-inch iPad Pro (3rd generation and later), and 11-inch iPad Pro (1st generation and later).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/airtag-april.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948663" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;19 off AirTag</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/amazon-apple-sale-airpods-pencil/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag (1-Pack) for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag (4-Pack) for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the 1-Pack for &#36;24.99 and the 4-Pack for &#36;79.99. These are both solid second-best prices on each AirTag model, and they're the first time we've seen notable AirTag discounts in a few weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-3-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get Low Prices on Anker and Eufy Accessories, AirPods, Apple Pencil, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-low-prices-on-anker-and-eufy-accessories-airpods-apple-pencil-and-more.2425398/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: New iPad Pro With the M4 Chip for AI?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-pro-m4-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-pro-with-the-m4-chip-for-ai.2425388/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:43:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-pro-m4-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/new-ipad-pro-with-the-m4-chip-for-ai/id1602394741?i=1000654446813">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the possibility of the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> featuring the M4 chip and what else to expect at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">Apple's "Let loose" event</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/E-_X7QiOpbk?si=325F4iU3xFJphpZe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div> <br/>
While Apple's upcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models have been expected to feature the M3 chip for over a year, recent reports have unexpectedly suggested that the new devices will instead contain the as-yet-unannounced M4 chip and that a key new feature of the processor will be an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> optimized for AI tasks. Introducing the M4 chip in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and only six months after the previous chip generation would be unprecedented moves, but there is evidence to suggest that it is a plausible possibility. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">Will the New iPad Pro Really Have the M4 Chip?</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple's "Let loose" event is expected to focus on the unveiling of redesigned &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models with OLED displays, two new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, a high-end Magic Keyboard accessory, and a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>. We also talk through the three other announcements that Apple could have in store for the event. <br/>
<br/>
The special event will take place on Tuesday, May 7, at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time), with a live stream to be available on Apple.com and on YouTube as usual. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/the-macrumors-show-ipad-event-announced/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the announcement of Apple's "Let loose" event.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-pro-m4-chip/">The MacRumors Show: New iPad Pro With the M4 Chip for AI?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-pro-with-the-m4-chip-for-ai.2425388/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Lineup Could Feature Slimmer MagSafe Components</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-16-slimmer-magsafe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-could-feature-slimmer-magsafe-components.2425387/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 08:33:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-16-slimmer-magsafe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup could see a slight change to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> alignment magnets compared to previous generations, according to <a href="https://shop.appsystem.fr/blogs/blog/exclusivite-maquette-iphone16-anneau-magsafe">images shared by French case company ShopSystem</a> [<a href="https://shop-appsystem-fr.translate.goog/blogs/blog/exclusivite-maquette-iphone16-anneau-magsafe?_x_tr_sl=auto&_x_tr_tl=en&_x_tr_hl=en-US">Google Translate</a>].<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iphone-16-magsafe-blue-molds.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949110" /><br/>
Casemaking molds for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup appear to show a thinner design for the attachment ring magnets and for the single alignment magnet, relative to equivalent molds for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup. The report suggests &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessory manufacturers may need to adapt their products to fit the new system, but this seems very unlikely as any updated &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; system will almost certainly be backwards compatible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iphone-16-15-magsafe-comparison.jpg" alt="" width="1302" height="1305" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949111" /><br/>
Presuming the thinner magnets depicted in these molds are accurate, it's unclear if there are additional changes to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; in the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup that could extend to the charging technology. One rumor has, however, indicated the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/iphone-15-could-feature-stacked-battery-technology/">could see increased MagSafe charging speeds</a> with support for up to 20 watts compared to the current standard of 15 watts.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-16-slimmer-magsafe/">iPhone 16 Lineup Could Feature Slimmer MagSafe Components</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-could-feature-slimmer-magsafe-components.2425387/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes iPhone 15&#039;s &#039;Find Your Friends&#039; Feature in Star Wars-Themed Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-15-find-your-friends-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-iphone-15s-find-your-friends-feature-in-star-wars-themed-ad.2425385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 07:19:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-15-find-your-friends-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yk6UVnMn9ts">video ad</a> promoting the "Find Your Friends" feature available in the Find My app on all iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yk6UVnMn9ts?si=hj__OJHCisMl8l4R" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the ad, a person dressed as a Mandalorian from the Star Wars universe uses the feature to find other Mandalorians in a crowded convention center.<br/>
<br/>
How to use the Find Your Friends feature:<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-locate-friends-with-precision-finding/">iPhone 15: How to Locate Friends With Precision Finding</a></li></ul>Both you and the other person must have an iPhone 15 in order to use Find Your Friends. Similar to an AirTag, the feature supports Precision Finding, which provides an on-screen directional arrow and exact distance to the other person's location.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/iphone-15-find-your-friends-ad/">Apple Promotes iPhone 15&#039;s &#039;Find Your Friends&#039; Feature in Star Wars-Themed Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-iphone-15s-find-your-friends-feature-in-star-wars-themed-ad.2425385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 14 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 50+ Upgrades to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-50-upgrades-to-expect.2420302/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 06:20:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro&#038;post_date=1714753200/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 14 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> is set to succeed 2023's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">over 25 new features</a> and improvements to Apple's high-end smartphones. With many users adopting two-year upgrade cycles, plenty of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro owners will be looking to upgrade to the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; later this year, so this guide breaks down every major difference you should be aware of between the two generations based on rumors. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-14-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-937778" /></div><br/>
In 2022, Apple unveiled the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro as the successor to the popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> Pro, introducing an always-on display, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, a 48-megapixel camera, the A16 Bionic chip, longer battery life, and more. Two years later, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to offer over 50 upgrades. All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to feature compared to their 2022 predecessor are listed below, using information from reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">previously covered</a>. We will update this article as more rumors emerge in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
The design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to be a relatively significant evolution over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro, iterating on the titanium frame and slightly rounded edges introduced on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models last year. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Surgical-grade stainless steel chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aerospace-grade titanium chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thermal design with copper heatsink and black foil battery casing</td><br/>
 <td>New thermal design with graphene heatsink and metal battery casing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More repairable design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Space Black, Silver, Gold, and Deep Purple color options</td><br/>
 <td>Black Titanium/Space Black, White Titanium, Desert Titanium, Titanium Gray, and potentially Rose Gold color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
To accommodate larger displays, both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to grow in height and width. In addition to last year's increase in depth, the devices are due to be considerably larger, but with a notable reduction in weight thanks to the adoption of a titanium frame. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7.85mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>8.25mm depth (0.4mm thicker)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14 Pro</strong>: 147.5mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Pro Max</strong>: 160.7mm height</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 149.6mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 163.0mm height</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14 Pro</strong>: 71.5mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Pro Max</strong>: 77.6mm width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 71.45mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 77.58mm width</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14 Pro</strong>: 206g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Pro Max</strong>: 240g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 194g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 225g weight</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="displays">Displays</h2><br/>
Both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature larger displays than their predecessors, pushing the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max to be the biggest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> ever offered. There are also reportedly improvements to the underlying OLED technology in store, in addition to last year's slimmer bezels, making for a noticeable overall display upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.1- or 6.7-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>6.3- or 6.9-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Slimmer borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="performance">Performance</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to bring notable improvements in processing power, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> Apple silicon chip and 33% more memory.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N4P" 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 Pro chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated AV1 decoder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="connectivity">Connectivity</h2><br/>
Connectivity is also due to get a significant upgrade on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, bolstering the device's 5G, Wi-Fi, Thread, and Ultra Wideband specifications.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X65 5G modem</td><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X75 5G modem</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 7 connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="cameras">Cameras</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are slated to receive a range of substantial camera enhancements, such as a larger main camera sensor, a 48-megapixel sensor on the ultra wide camera, and a dedicated hardware button for photography and videography on the side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>"Capture Button" to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1/1.28-inch main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max</strong>: 1/1.14-inch main camera sensor (12% larger)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sony IMX-803 main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: Sony IMX-903 main camera sensor with stacked design for better performance, a 14-bit Analog-to-Digital Converter (ADC) for high-quality image data conversion, and Digital Gain Control (DCG) for better dynamic range and noise control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7P main camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>8P main camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with second-generation sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>77mm maximum focal length</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 120mm maximum focal length<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: "Super" telephoto camera with focal length above 300mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>5P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel ultra wide camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>6P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating on camera lenses</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>13mm, 24mm, 28mm, 35mm, and 120mm focal length picker</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Shoot and instantly transfer 48-megapixel ProRAW images to Mac via USB 3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record video directly to an external drive</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 60 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Action mode</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Action mode and low-light video</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Log video recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Academy Color Encoding System</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record spatial video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting bigger, denser batteries and faster charging capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 14 Pro</strong>: 3,200 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 14 Pro Max</strong>: 4,323 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 3,355 mAh mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 4,676 mAh battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h2><br/>
While many of Apple's devices are rumored to receive a series of new AI-based features via software updates later this year, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to take these further with exclusive capabilities and an upgraded microphone.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></td><br/>
 <td>Upcoming support for new AI features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, plus a suite of device-exclusive AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>USB 2 transfer speeds (up to 480Mb/s)</td><br/>
 <td>USB 3 transfer speeds (up to 10Gb/s, 20x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>DisplayPort support for up to 4K HDR video output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 2TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is expected to launch in the fall. Apple usually hosts an event every September to unveil new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, with launch following just over a week later. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro in 2023, introducing a titanium chassis, slimmer bezels, the Action button, and a USB-C port. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will build on these upgrades, offering larger displays, the Capture button, and improved cameras. With over 50 upgrades likely to be in store, many &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro users will find upgrading to an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; model worthwhile.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 50+ Upgrades to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-50-upgrades-to-expect.2420302/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18&#039;s Rumored AI Features for Siri, Spotlight, and More Revealed in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/ios-18-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-rumored-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-and-more-revealed-in-new-report.2425378/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 05:42:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/ios-18-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>AppleInsider</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple system features such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and Spotlight Search are set to receive new AI features that work across apps like Messages, Mail, and Safari, <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/03/siri-for-ios-18-to-gain-massive-ai-upgrade-via-apples-ajax-llm?utm_medium=rss"><em>AppleInsider</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947745" /><br/>
Safari will apparently gain a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">text summarization tool called Intelligent Browsing</a> that allows users to generate a short summary of any webpage, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; could gain a similar feature that works in the Messages app. Apple's AI technology can apparently analyze message content and generate responses. Spotlight search will be enhanced with more intelligent results and improved sorting, working across apps like Contacts and Calendar to generate responses.<br/>
<br/>
Crucially, Apple's AI tools run-on device, with the ability to generate responses without any cloud-based processing, to maximize privacy and minimize delays. More advanced replies and summaries seem to require sever-side processing. Apple is widely expected to unveil the suite of AI features when it previews major updates to its operating systems at WWDC in June.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/appleinsider-com/">AppleInsider</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/ios-18-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-revealed/">iOS 18&#039;s Rumored AI Features for Siri, Spotlight, and More Revealed in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18s-rumored-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-and-more-revealed-in-new-report.2425378/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Five Things Apple Won&#039;t Announce at Its Event Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/five-things-apple-wont-launch-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-five-things-apple-wont-announce-at-its-event-next-week.2425376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 04:30:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/five-things-apple-wont-launch-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>May 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is holding at least five announcements for later in the year that will not arrive at the company's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">"Let loose" special event</a> next week, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-03/apple-ipad-event-2024-new-ipad-pro-air-magic-keyboard-pencil-coming-may-7"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Event-Let-Loose-Pastel-Green.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947825" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-03/apple-ipad-event-2024-new-ipad-pro-air-magic-keyboard-pencil-coming-may-7">report</a> detailing his expectations for Apple's upcoming event, Gurman noted that there are a total of five things that the company is holding for later in the year:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li><strong>AI features</strong>: While Apple may tease new AI capabilities with the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, Apple will not "formally unveil" the features until WWDC in June where iPadOS 18 will be previewed.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Lower-cost entry-level iPad</strong>: Apple is apparently working on a version of the 10th-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> introduced in 2022 with a lower price. The current model is &#36;449, sitting in the lineup above the &#36;329 ninth-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; that remains in the lineup. The company is likely to phase out this older model and bring the price down of the redesigned model, but Gurman says this "isn't expected until the end of the year at the earliest."</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Seventh-generation iPad mini</strong>: A refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> is said to be in the works featuring improved performance thanks to a faster chip, but it is not due to be announced next week.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>New Macs</strong>: While the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/will-the-new-ipad-pro-really-have-m4/">may contain the M4 chip</a>, a processor that will later come to the Mac, Apple is not planning to unveil any new Mac models at the "Let loose" event.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Fourth-generation AirPods</strong>: Apple is said to be nearing production of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">fourth-generation AirPods</a>, but these will not launch until the fall alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple's "Let loose" event is expected to focus on the unveiling of redesigned &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models with OLED displays, two new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, a high-end Magic Keyboard accessory, and a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>. It will take place on Tuesday, May 7 at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time), with a live stream to be available on Apple.com and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1J38FlDKxo">on YouTube</a> as usual.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/may-2024-apple-event/">May 2024 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/five-things-apple-wont-launch-next-week/">Report: Five Things Apple Won&#039;t Announce at Its Event Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-five-things-apple-wont-announce-at-its-event-next-week.2425376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2025 M4 MacBook Air: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2025-m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect.2425353/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:05:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1714701957/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2025 MacBook Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working to introduce a new fourth-generation Apple silicon chip across the Mac lineup, and while the first M4 Macs are coming in 2024, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> won't get updated until 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-m2-13-inch.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939833" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything that we know about the next-generation &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m4_chips">M4 Chips</h2><br/>
The 13-inch and 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models were just updated with M3 chips in March 2024, so it's no surprise that they're not going to be the first devices to get the M4 chip. Apple plans to wait until 2025, so there will be about a year between the M3 and M4 chip lineups.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945901" /><br/>
Rumors suggest that the M4 chip will have a focus on artificial intelligence to support AI features that are coming with the next round of software updates. Most AI talk has been about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, but Apple is expected to roll out AI integrations across its platforms. The M4 chip is expected to have a Neural Engine with more cores, with the Neural Engine handling AI and machine learning tasks. The M3 chip has a 16-core Neural Engine.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple is working on M4, M4 Pro, M4 Max, and M4 Ultra chips, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are expected to get only the standard M4 chip. There will likely be at least two variants of the M4, with the difference being the number of GPU cores. For the current &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, for example, the base M3 chip has an 8-core GPU, but there is also a 10-core GPU option. The M3 CPU is the same for all versions, and that should be the case with the M4 as well.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 will be built on Apples 3-nanometer process, much like the M3. There won't be as big of a performance improvement between M3 and M4 as there was between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> and M3 because there's no change in node size, but we can still expect modest GPU and CPU speed boosts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple overhauled the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; design in 2022, and we're not expecting the design to be tweaked with the 2025 refresh. Apple often waits several years between design changes, and there are no rumors that there will be a refreshed look.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/macbook-air-m3-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945032" /><br/>
Apple is likely to stick with the 15.3 and 13.6-inch size options, and we can expect to see the same flat, MacBook Pro-style body with Force Touch trackpad, and display with notch. As of now, it looks like the 2025 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; refresh will be focused on internal updates.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; will get an update in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">the spring of 2025</a>. Spring starts on March 20, 2025, and ends on June 20, 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-macbook-air/">Apple&#039;s 2025 M4 MacBook Air: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2025-m4-macbook-air-what-to-expect.2425353/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Q2 2024 Earnings Call Takeaways</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-q2-2024-earnings-call-takeaways/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q2-2024-earnings-call-takeaways.2425346/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:05:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-q2-2024-earnings-call-takeaways/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today held its earnings call for the second fiscal quarter of 2024 (first calendar quarter), with Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and Apple CFO Luca Maestri providing us with some details on Apple's performance, Vision Pro sales, services growth, AI plans, and other topics.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834994" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/Apple-Logo-Cash-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1504" /><br/>
We've highlighted the most interesting takeaways from today's earnings call.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next Week's Announcements</h2><br/>
Apple CEO &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; said Apple is prepping for "an exciting product announcement" that the company thinks "customers will love."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Generative AI</h2><br/>
Apple CEO &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; said that Apple is making "significant investments" in AI, and that it has some "very exciting things" to share with customers "soon."<br/>
<br/>
Cook also said that he believes Apple has "advantages that will differentiate" the company, including Apple's hardware and software integration, Apple silicon with Neural Engine, and focus on privacy.<br/>
<br/>
There's a "big opportunity" for generative AI across all of Apple's devices, and Cook said he is "extremely optimistic" about future consumer demand.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Digital Markets Act</h2><br/>
Cook said that it's too early to determine the security risks and privacy implications of the changes that it has made to the app ecosystem in Europe. Apple is focused on complying while mitigating impacts to user privacy and security.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Vision Pro</h2><br/>
Leading enterprise companies have been investing in Vision Pro, and Apple is seeing it used for things like aircraft engine maintenance, real-time collaboration for racing, and immersive kitchen design. Cook said that Apple "couldn't be more excited about the spatial computing opportunity in enterprise."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Services</h2><br/>
Apple's services segment set a new all-time revenue record of &#36;23.9 billion, up 14 percent from &#36;20.9 billion in the year-ago quarter. Transacting accounts and paid accounts reached a new all-time high, with paid accounts and subscriptions showing double digit growth.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has more than 1 billion paid subscriptions, more than double the number from four years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac Sales</h2><br/>
With the launch of new M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models in March, Mac revenue saw growth, reaching &#36;7.5 billion. Mac sales were at &#36;7.17 billion in the year-ago quarter, for four percent growth.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Sales</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> revenue continued to drop with no new iPads released in 2024 as of yet. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue was at &#36;5.6 billion, down 17 percent from &#36;6.7 billion a year ago. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; sales should see some improvement next quarter as Apple next week is planning to unveil new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wearables</h2><br/>
Wearables, Home and Accessories came in at &#36;7.9 billion, down 10 percent compared to last year. Last year, Apple had launched the USB-C version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, and there was a "difficult compare" this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>June Quarter</h2><br/>
Maestri said that Apple expects June quarter revenue to grow low single digits year-over-year, but Services is expected to grow double digits, as is &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-q2-2024-earnings-call-takeaways/">Apple&#039;s Q2 2024 Earnings Call Takeaways</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-q2-2024-earnings-call-takeaways.2425346/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook on Generative AI: &#039;We Have Advantages That Will Differentiate Us&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/tim-cook-on-generative-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-on-generative-ai-we-have-advantages-that-will-differentiate-us.2425341/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 14:11:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/tim-cook-on-generative-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[During today's earnings call covering the second fiscal quarter of 2024, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> again spoke about Apple's work on generative AI. He said that Apple has "advantages" that will "differentiate" the company in the era of AI, and some "very exciting things" will be shared with customers in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947754" /><br/>
<blockquote>We continue to feel very bullish about our opportunity in generative AI. We are making significant investments and we're looking forward to sharing some very exciting things with our customers soon.<br/>
<br/>
We believe in the transformative power and promise of AI and we believe we have advantages that will differentiate us in this new era, including Apple's unique combination of seamless hardware, software and services integration, groundbreaking Apple silicon with our industry leading neural engines, and our unwavering focus on privacy, which underpins everything we create.</blockquote><br/>
Rumors have suggested that Apple's first AI features are designed to run on-device rather than contacting a cloud service, which would make Apple's AI much more private and secure than an online AI option. Apple's plan to have generative AI available on-device will require significant CPU and GPU power, and Apple is planning to focus on AI with the upcoming M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
We could see the M4 chip as soon as next week in new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, with <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/">indicating last weekend</a> that there is a chance Apple will unveil the chip in the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/tim-cook-on-generative-ai/">Tim Cook on Generative AI: &#039;We Have Advantages That Will Differentiate Us&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-on-generative-ai-we-have-advantages-that-will-differentiate-us.2425341/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reports 2Q 2024 Results: &#36;23.6B Profit on &#36;90.8B Revenue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-2q-2024-earnings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-2q-2024-results-23-6b-profit-on-90-8b-revenue.2425337/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:38:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-2q-2024-earnings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Jordan Golson</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Earnings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-reports-second-quarter-results/">announced</a> financial results for the second fiscal quarter of 2024, which corresponds to the first calendar quarter of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/aapl-2q24-line.jpg" alt="" width="1800" height="772" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949054" /><br/>
For the quarter, Apple posted revenue of &#36;90.8 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;23.6 billion, or &#36;1.53 per diluted share, compared to revenue of &#36;94.8 billion and net quarterly profit of &#36;24.1 billion, or &#36;1.52 per diluted share, in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/04/apple-2q-2023-earnings/">year-ago quarter</a>. Apple set an all-time quarterly record for Services revenue at &#36;23.9 billion, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> revenue dropped by over &#36;5 billion compared to the year-ago quarter.<br/>
<br/>
Gross margin for the quarter was 46.6 percent, compared to 44.3 percent in the year-ago quarter. Apple's board of directors also authorized an additional &#36;110 billion for share repurchases and declared an increased dividend payment of &#36;0.25 per share, up from &#36;0.24 per share. The dividend is payable May 16 to shareholders of record as of May 13.<blockquote>"Today Apple is reporting revenue of &#36;90.8 billion for the March quarter, including an all-time revenue record in Services," said Tim Cook, Apple's CEO. "During the quarter, we were thrilled to launch Apple Vision Pro and to show the world the potential that spatial computing unlocks. We're also looking forward to an exciting product announcement next week and an incredible Worldwide Developers Conference next month. As always, we are focused on providing the very best products and services for our customers, and doing so while living up to the core values that drive us."</blockquote>As has been the case for over four years now, Apple is once again not issuing guidance for the current quarter ending in June.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/aapl-2q24-pie.jpg" alt="" width="2180" height="1120" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949055" /><br/>
Apple will <a href="http://www.apple.com/investor/earnings-call/">provide live streaming</a> of its fiscal Q2 2024 financial results conference call at 2:00 pm Pacific, and <em>MacRumors</em> will update this story with coverage of the conference call highlights.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Conference call recap ahead...</b><br/>
<!--more--><br/>
<b>1:40 pm</b>: After closing up over 2% in regular trading today, Apple's share price is up another 6% in after-hours trading following the earnings release.<br/>
<br/>
<b>1:43 pm</b>: Services and Mac were Apple's only segments that saw year-over-year growth, with Services increasing by almost &#36;3 billion and Mac increasing by around &#36;300 million. But with &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; dropping by over &#36;5 billion, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> dropping by &#36;1.1 billion, and Wearables dropping by &#36;800 million, Apple's overall revenue declined by roughly &#36;4 billion. Increased gross margin meant, however, that Apple's net income declined by only around &#36;500 million, and with Apple's share count continuing to decline as it buys back shares, earnings per share actually increased by a penny year-over-year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:01 pm</b>: The call is beginning with the usual caveats about forward-looking statements. On the call is Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and CFO Luca Maestri.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:02 pm</b>: Tim is on the call, reporting revenue of &#36;90.9 billion and an earnings per share record of &#36;1.53 for the March quarter.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:03 pm</b>: He is touting revenue records in a number of countries and regions, including March quarter records in Latin America, the Middle East, Canada, India, Spain and Turkey.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:03 pm</b>: He notes that in the year-ago quarter, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; demand was increased because of supply disruptions and a refill of channel inventory — "We estimate this one time impact added close to &#36;5 billion to the March quarter revenue last year. If we remove this from last year's results, our March quarter total company revenue this year would have grown."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:04 pm</b>: Now talking up <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, revealing that half of Fortune 100 companies have bought &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; units and are exploring ways to use them for business. "An exciting product announcement" next week "that we think our customers will love."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:05 pm</b>: Mentions WWDC in June, and says: "We continue to feel very bullish about our opportunity in generative AI. we are making significant investments and we're looking forward to sharing some very exciting things with our customers soon. We believe in the transformative power and promise of AI and we believe we have advantages that will differentiate us in this new era, including Apple's unique combination of seamless hardware, software and services integration, groundbreaking Apple silicon, with our industry-leading neural engines, and our unwavering focus on privacy, which underpins everything we create."<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:06 pm</b>: Now going over &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; revenue, &#36;46 billion, down 10% year over year, but notes growth in mainland China and that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 15 Pro Max were the best-selling smartphones in Urban China.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:06 pm</b>: Reveals that he visited China, Vietnam, Indonesia and Singapore and that customers and communities have a great affinity for Apple and it's one of the many reasons he is so optimistic about the future.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:07 pm</b>: Moving to Mac, revenue &#36;7.5 billion, up 4% year over year. Launched the new 13- and 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> with M3.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:07 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, &#36;5.6 billion, down 17% year over year following <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and 10th-gen &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; last fiscal year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:08 pm</b>: Wearables, Home and Accessories revenue was &#36;7.9 billion, down 10% thanks to a difficult compare on Apple Watch and AirPods. He notes that Apple is harnessing AI and machine learning to power fall detection and heart rhythm notifications.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:09 pm</b>: Services appear to the the most successful category in the quarter, at &#36;23.9 billion, up 14% year over year with all-time revenue records across several categories and geographic segments.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:09 pm</b>: Mentions Apple Sports &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:10 pm</b>: Now to Retail, mentions the new Shanghai store and that the "energy and enthusiasm from our customers was something to behold." Vision Pro demos have delighted customers and given the profound and emotional experience of using it for the very first time.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:10 pm</b>: Apple wants to enrich user lives, with making <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> more accessible with the new transcript feature, new encryption protections in iMessage, and environmental work towards making products carbon neutral.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:12 pm</b>: Apple is investing in new solar and wind power, working with partners in India and the US to replenish water usage, and has committed &#36;200 million to nature-based carbon removal projects.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:12 pm</b>: He calls this a year of unprecedented innovation.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:12 pm</b>: CFO Luca Maestri is coming on to discuss results in more detail.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:13 pm</b>: Revenue was &#36;90.8 billion, down 4% year over year. Foreign exchange had a negative impact of 140 basis points.<br/>
<br/>
Products was &#36;66.9 billion, down 10% year over year, thanks to a challenging compare on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, partially offset by Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:14 pm</b>: Gross margin was 46.6%, up 70 basis points sequentially, driven by cost savings, favorable mix to service, partially offset by leverage. Products gross margin was 36.6%, down 180 basis points sequentially. Services gross marging was 74.6%, up 180 basis points from last quarter. OpEx was &#36;14.4 billion, midpoint of guidance range and up 5% year over year. &#36;23.6 billion net income, diluted EPS was &#36;1.53, a March quarter record. Operating cashflow was &#36;22.7 billion.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:15 pm</b>: Adjusting for one-time &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; impact, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; revenue would be roughly flat to last year. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; active installed base grew to a new all-time high, in total and across every geographic segment. In March quarter, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; was the top selling model in the US, China, Australia, UK, France, Germany, and Japan. &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; continues to be very popular with customers, with 99% customer satisfaction in the US.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: Mac Revenue was &#36;7.5 billion, up 4% year over year, driven by the strength of the new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with M3 chip. Mac installed base reached a new all-time high, with half of &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; buyers being new to the customer. Mac customer satisfaction was 96%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:16 pm</b>: &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; made &#36;5.6 billion, down 17% year over year. Half of buyers are new to the product, 96% customer satisfaction.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:17 pm</b>: Wearables, Home and Accessories was &#36;7.9 billion, down 10% year over year, had launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2nd gen last year, plus Watch SE and the Apple Watch Ultra. Apple Watch install base went to a new all-time high, with two-thirds of customers being new to the product. Customer satisfaction at 95%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:18 pm</b>: Services reached &#36;23.9 billion, up 14% year over year. The installed base of active devices continued to grow. Transacting and paid accounts reached a new all-time high, with paid accounts growing double digits year over year. More than 1 billion paid subscriptions, more than double the number of four years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:18 pm</b>: Mentions new games on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> and new shows on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:18 pm</b>: In the enterprise, customers keep embracing the Mac. In healthcare, Epic recently launched its native app for the Mac, allowing hospitals to transition to the Mac for clinical use.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:19 pm</b>: KLM is using &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; to train aircraft engine mechanics and Lowes is using it for immersive kitchen design.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:20 pm</b>: Apple revenue was roughly flat in the first half of the fiscal year, in spite of having one less week of sales and FX headwinds. There were first-half revenue records in Latin America, the Middle East, India, Indonesia, the Philippines and Turkey. First half diluted EPS record of &#36;3.71/share was up 9% from last year.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:21 pm</b>: Ended quarter with &#36;162 billion in cash and marketable securities. &#36;105 billion in debt, with &#36;58 billion in net cash. &#36;27 billion returned to shareholders, with &#36;3.7 billion in dividends and &#36;23.5 billion through open market repurchases of 130 million shares. &#36;110 billion for share repurchases was approved by the board, plus an increase of the dividend by 4% to &#36;0.25/share.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:22 pm</b>: Expects June revenue to grow low single digits year over year, despite 2.5% of FX headwinds. Services to grow low double digits, similar to what was reported in the first half of the year. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to grow double digits. Gross margin between 45.5 and 46.5. OpEx of &#36;14.3 to &#36;14.5 billion. Tax rate to be around 16%.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:22 pm</b>: Q&A with analysts is beginning.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:24 pm</b>: Q: Re the June quarter guidance, revenue outlook for low single digit growth, can you go through product assumptions, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, what gives you confidence around that? What was better than expected in Services?<br/>
<br/>
A: We expect to grow low single digits for the company, and expect services to grow double digits at a rate similar to the first half of the fiscal year. &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; should grow double digits. This is the color that we're providing for the June quarter.<br/>
<br/>
In services, we see a very strong performance across the board, records in several categories and geographic segments. It's very broad-based. Subscription business is going well. Transacting and paid accounts are growing double digits. Seeing strong performance in both developed and emerging markets.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:26 pm</b>: Q: Should we expect changes to historical capex cadence with changes to AI, changes to how we've thought about the split between tooling, data centers and facilities?<br/>
<br/>
A: We are excited about the opportunity, pushing hard on innovation on every front and we've been doing that for many years. We've spent more than &#36;100 billion on R&D in the last five years. On CapEx, we have a hybrid model where we make some investments ourselves and share some with suppliers and partners, we purchase some of the tools and manufacturing equipment, and some of our suppliers buy things. Same with data centers. It's a model that has worked for us historically and we plan to continue on the same lines going forward.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:27 pm</b>: Q: What are the changes and implications to Apple from the EU third-party app stores, can hurt user experience but also result in lower revenue for Apple. What are developers and consumers doing?<br/>
<br/>
A: It's too early to answer the question, just implemented in March in the EU. We're focused on complying while mitigating the impacts to user privacy and security. That's our focus.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:28 pm</b>: Q: On product gross margin, you noted mix and leverage... are people mixing down across product lines? Trying to get some color on customer behavior.<br/>
<br/>
A: On a sequential basis, we were down, it's primarily the fact that we had a slightly different mix of products than the previous one. Leverage plays a big role as we move from the holiday quarter into a more typical quarter. Primarily leverage and a different mix of products. We haven't seen anything particuluar.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:29 pm</b>: Q: Mentioned excitement around GenAI a couple of times. There have been a few different ways to monetize and historically Apple hasn't made a lot of revenue from software upgrade cycles, any color you can share on that?<br/>
<br/>
A: Don't want to get in front of our announcements. We see generative AI as a key opportunity across our products, and we believe we have advantages that set us apart and we'll be talking more about it as we go through the weeks ahead.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:31 pm</b>: Q: A broad concern about headwinds at rising commodity costs having a hit on your gross margins. Thinking of all commodities that go into products collectively, are they rising or falling and what tools do you have to mitigate?<br/>
<br/>
A: During the last quarter, commodity and component costs behaved favorably to us. On the memory front, prices are starting to go up. They've gone up slightly during the March quarter. It's been a period, not only during this quarter but the last several that commodities have behaved well to us. They go in cycles, so always that possiblity — we are starting from a very high level of gross margin — 46.6% is something we haven't seen in decades, starting from a good point. We try to buy ahead when the cycles are favorable to us, so we will try to mitigate if there are headwinds but particularly for this cycle, we are in good shape.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:33 pm</b>: Q: Any more color from your visit to China, I know you continue to be confident there in the long term, but any color as to when the tide turns?<br/>
<br/>
A: If you look at our results in Q2, for Greater China we were down 8%, an acceleration from Q1. The primary driver was &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and if you look at &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; within mainland China, we grew on a reported basis, before any kind of normalization for supply disruptions. If you look at the top-selling smartphones, the top two in urban China were iPhones. While I was there, it was a great visit and we opened a new store in Shanghai, and the reception was very warm and highly energetic. I left there having a fantastic trip and enjoyed being there. I maintain a great view of China in the long term, I don't know how each quarter and week goes, but over the long haul I have a very positive viewpoint.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:34 pm</b>: Q: There's a fear out there that you may lose some traffic acquisition revenue, and I'm wondering if you thought AI, from a big picture, on a long term basis, is AI an opportunity for you to continue to monetize mobile real estate from a big picture. Is there a big picture color you can give and how to monetize that?<br/>
<br/>
A: I think AI, generative AI and AI, both are big opportunities for us across our products. We'll talk more about it in the coming weeks, but I think there are numerous ways there that are great for us. We think that we're well positioned.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:36 pm</b>: Q: Last quarter you spoke about getting traction in enterprise, is your AI going to be both consumer and enterprise?<br/>
<br/>
A: Our focus on enterprise has been, through the quarter and the quarters that preceded it, have been on selling iPhones and iPads and Macs and recently added Vision Pro to that. We're thrilled with what we see there in terms of interest and big companies buying some to explore ways they can use it. I see enormous opportunity in enterprise. I wouldn't want to cabin that to AI only. I think there's a great opportunity for us around the world in enterprise.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:37 pm</b>: Q: Seen a bias towards Pro model, seen growth in Services but weakness in product?<br/>
<br/>
A: Customers want to purchase the best product we offer in each category, we've done what we can to make it easier for customers through financing and other programs. Customers want to buy at the top of the range, but in developing markets where affordability issues are more pronounced, we have seen a trend where this is more sustainable.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:39 pm</b>: Q: On Capital Allocation, &#36;58 billion of net cash, as you get closer to net cash neutral, would you ever take leverage on the balance sheet or once you get to neutral, how do you feel about leverage or returning free cash to shareholders?<br/>
<br/>
A: I would say one step at a time. We put out the target to get to net cash neutral, we've worked hard to get there, our cash flow generation has been very strong. We've increased our allocation to the buyback, let's get there first, it's going to take a while still. We'll reassess what the optimal capital structure for the company when we get there.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:41 pm</b>: Q: On China discussion, could you step back, these numbers are still declining on a year over year basis. What are you seeing from a macro basis in China, do you think this is macro or micro driven over there?<br/>
<br/>
A: I can only tell you what we're seeing, I don't want to present myself as an economist so I'll steer clear of that. What we saw was an acceleration from Q1 and it was driven by &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in Mainland China before we adjust for this &#36;5 billion impact did grow. Other products didn't fare as well, so we clearly have work to do there. I think it has been and is through last quarter the most competitive market in the world. I wouldn't say anything other than that, I've said that before, I think it was last quarter as well.<br/>
<br/>
If you step back from the 90-day cycle, what I see is a lot of people moving into the middle class, we've tried to serve customers very well there and have a lot of happy customers and you can kind of see that in the latest store opening over there. I continue to feel very optimistic.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:44 pm</b>: Q: How are you thinking of the competitive landscape outside of China, what's the consumer demand and receptivity to new devices? Is this an AI thing or are there other drivers?<br/>
<br/>
A: There's a big opportunity with generative AI across all our devices, that's not within the next quarter and we don't guide at the product level, but I'm extremely optimistic. That's kind of how I view it. If you step back on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and you make this adjustment from the previous year, our Q2 results would be flat-ish on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. That's how we performed in Q2.<br/>
<br/>
On outlook, I'll repeat what we said before, the color for the quarter, we expect to grow in total, expect services to grow, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to grow, for the rest I'll let you make assumptions and then we'll report 3 months from now.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:46 pm</b>: Q: Services growth accelerated, what parts of services did you see that, and why isn't it more sustainable as you're guiding a little lower?<br/>
<br/>
A: Number of things on services, first of all, the overall performance was very strong. As I said earlier, all-time records in both developed and emerging markets, so Services do well across the world. Records in many of our services categories, there are some growing very fast because they're relatively small in the scheme of services, Cloud, Video, Payments. Those set all-time revenue records. We feel very good about the progress that we're making in services. As we go forward, if you look at our growth rates at year ago, they improved during the course of our fiscal year last year. The comps become more challenging as we go through the year but we expect to grow double digits in the June quarter at a rate that's similar for the first half.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:48 pm</b>: Q: For this India market, how much of the momentum you're seeing would you associate with retail expansion strategy versus supply chain or manufacturing changes and strategies?<br/>
<br/>
A: We did grow strong double-digits so we were very pleased about it, it was a new March revenue record for us. As I said before, I see it as an incredibly exciting market and it's a major focus for us. In terms of the operational side, we are producing there. From a pragmatic point of view, you need to produce there to be competitive. Yes, the two things are linked from that point of view, but we have both operational things going on and we have go-to-market initiatives going on. We opened a couple stores last year and we see enormous opportunity there. We're continuing to expand our channels and also working on developer ecosystem as well. We've been very pleased that there's a rapidly growing base of developers there and so we're working all of the entire ecosystem from developer to the market to operations, the whole thing. I could not be more excited and enthusiastic about it.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:49 pm</b>: Q: At a high level, when we look at the data points reported through the quarter, what are people missing in Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; traction in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; market, given data points from the last quarter?<br/>
<br/>
A: I can't address the data points, I can only address what our results are. We did accelerate last quarter and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; grew in mainland China so that's what the results were. I can't bridge to numbers we didn't come up with.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:50 pm</b>: Q: How would you characterize channel inventory dynamics for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;?<br/>
<br/>
A: We decreased inventory during the quarter, which we usually do during Q2 so that's not unusual. We're very comfortable with overall channel inventory.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:52 pm</b>: Q: Is Apple approaching a point where all emerging markets might become bigger than current Greater China segment?<br/>
<br/>
A: I think you're asking a really interesting question. We were looking at something similar recently. Obviously China is by far the largest emerging market we have, but when we start looking at India, Saudi, Mexico, Turkey, Brazil, Indonesia, the numbers are getting large. We're very happy because these are markets where our market share is low, the populations are large and growing, and our products are really making a lot of progress in those markets. The level of excitement for the brand was very high. It's very good for us and certainly the numbers are getting larger all the time, the gap to China is reducing and hopefully that trajectory continues for a long time.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:54 pm</b>: Q: Do you see ways to deploy capital more to spur replacement demand either with greater device financing, more investment in marketing, more promotions, do you need to produce those sorts of margins or more important to spur growth with replacements?<br/>
<br/>
A: Innovation spurs the upgrade cycle. There's economic factors as well that play in there but what kind of offerings from our carrier partners and so forth, but we work all of those. We price our products for the value that we're delivering. That's how we look at it.<br/>
<br/>
One of the things, at the long arc of time that maybe isn't fully understood, we've gone through a long period of very strong dollar and what that means, given that our company sells 60% of revenue outside the US, the demand for our products in the US is stronger than the results that we report just because of the translation of local currency into dollars. That is something to keep in mind as you look at our results. Innovation, obviously, financing solutions, trade in programs, and we will continue to make all those investments.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:56 pm</b>: Q: For enterprise, what are some of the top two or three cases for Vision Pro, what are you hearing about?<br/>
<br/>
A: I wouldn't say one emerges at the top right now, the most impressive is the way people use the Mac is the way they use it for everything. People are using it for everything, field service, training, healthcare things like preparing a doctor for surgery or advanced imaging. Command and control centers, it's an enormous number of different verticals and our focus is on growing that ecosystem and getting more apps and more enterprises engaged. The event that we had recently, can't overstate the enthusiasm in the room. It was extraordinary. We're off to a good start with enterprise.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:57 pm</b>: Q: March quarter, commodity pricing was favorable, for memory and such for June and the full year?<br/>
<br/>
A: We just provide guidance for the current quarter. We are guiding to a very high level of gross margin, 45.5-46.5, within that guidance we expect memory to be a slight headwind (not a very large one), and the same applies for foreign exchange. Negative impact sequentially of about 30 basis points.<br/>
<br/>
<b>2:57 pm</b>: That's the end of the call.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earnings/">Earnings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-2q-2024-earnings/">Apple Reports 2Q 2024 Results: &#36;23.6B Profit on &#36;90.8B Revenue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reports-2q-2024-results-23-6b-profit-on-90-8b-revenue.2425337/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker Teased by F1 Driver Daniel Ricciardo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/unreleased-beats-pill-daniel-ricciardo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unreleased-beats-pill-speaker-teased-by-f1-driver-daniel-ricciardo.2425332/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 12:41:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/unreleased-beats-pill-daniel-ricciardo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following this past weekend's sighting of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">NBA superstar LeBron James carrying an unreleased Beats speaker</a> reminiscent of the former Beats Pill, F1 driver Daniel Ricciardo has also been seen <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/C6eY884oXAH/">teasing the unreleased speaker</a> at this week's Grand Prix stop in Miami.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/beats-pill-f1-daniel-ricciardo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949043" /><br/>
Details on the unreleased speaker remain unknown, but it features a similar pill-shaped design to the rest of the Pill family and includes a lanyard that has not been present on previous models. The most recent model in the Pill family was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">discontinued in 2022</a>, and this new one will likely include a USB-C port, updated Bluetooth specs, and other improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Beats has yet to officially announce the upcoming Beats Pill, so a release date similarly remains unknown.<br/>
<br/>
The Beats Pill teases come as part of a busy week for Apple's speaker and headphone brand, as Beats this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">introduced the Solo 4 on-ear headphones</a> and announced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">all-new Solo Buds earphones</a> that will be launching in June.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/unreleased-beats-pill-daniel-ricciardo/">Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker Teased by F1 Driver Daniel Ricciardo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unreleased-beats-pill-speaker-teased-by-f1-driver-daniel-ricciardo.2425332/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Siri on HomePod Seems to Have Forgotten How to Give the Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/homepod-siri-time-bug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-on-homepod-seems-to-have-forgotten-how-to-give-the-time.2425324/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:23:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/homepod-siri-time-bug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At some point in the last 24 hours, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> seems to have forgotten how to relay the time. When asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; "what time is it?" &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is unable to answer and directs users to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-and-Mini-feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-882635" /><br/>
"I found some web results, I can show them if you ask again from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;," is &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s full response to the time question. If you ask what time it is in a specific location, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is able to respond, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac provides the time as usual when asked.<br/>
<br/>
This is a bug that Apple will be able to fix server side, so it will likely be addressed quickly. In the meantime, to get the time from &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; without having to swap to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, include your location.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has long been ridiculed for failing to understand requests and not providing the expected information, and small bugs like this are a bit embarrassing as Apple prepares for a major AI update.<br/>
<br/>
For the last several months, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has also been struggling with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> commands, and there have been many complaints from smart home users. Asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to "turn off the lights in the living room," for example, often results in the lights being turned on or turned off in another room entirely. Hopefully some of these issues will be solved with a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; overhaul in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and its sister updates.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> Apple seems to have fixed the issue somewhat. Asking "what time is it?" provides the time, but &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is still not able to give the time if you ask "what's the time?" or "can you tell me the time?"<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Ben!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/homepod-siri-time-bug/">Siri on HomePod Seems to Have Forgotten How to Give the Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-on-homepod-seems-to-have-forgotten-how-to-give-the-time.2425324/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Confirms iPadOS Will Get Same EU App Changes as iOS This Fall</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/ipados-eu-app-changes-fall/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-ipados-will-get-same-eu-app-changes-as-ios-this-fall.2425320/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/ipados-eu-app-changes-fall/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today confirmed that it will be bringing all of the app ecosystem changes made to iOS in the European Union to iPadOS in the fall. Earlier this week, the European Commission said that iPadOS is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/">also a gatekeeper platform</a> under the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-pro-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940265" /><br/>
EU developers will be able to distribute <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> apps outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> using alternative app marketplaces or websites, and all of the same terms will apply. The Core Technology Fee will be charged for apps that are distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and have more than one million first annual installs, though there are exceptions for small developers, which Apple also announced today.<br/>
<br/>
With iPadOS being added to the mix, Apple has also confirmed that users who install the same app on both iOS and iPadOS in a 12-month period will only generate one first annual install for that app rather than two, which should help developers keep below the CTF threshold.<br/>
<br/>
As with the changes to iOS, the upcoming changes to iPadOS only apply to developers who distribute apps in the European Union and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users in the EU. For the rest of the world, there are no changes and apps will continue to be available only from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/ipados-eu-app-changes-fall/">Apple Confirms iPadOS Will Get Same EU App Changes as iOS This Fall</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-ipados-will-get-same-eu-app-changes-as-ios-this-fall.2425320/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Tweaks EU Core Technology Fee to Avoid Bankrupting Unexpectedly Viral Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-updates-core-technology-fee-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-eu-core-technology-fee-to-avoid-bankrupting-unexpectedly-viral-apps.2425319/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-updates-core-technology-fee-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it is tweaking the terms of the 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee (CTF) that apps distributed using the new EU business terms must pay, introducing a solution that would keep small apps that go viral from being charged unreasonable fees. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
First, independent and small developers who earn no revenue at all will not have to pay the CTF. Students, hobbyists, and freeware app developers who distribute free apps and earn no money will not be charged the fee. Developers will need to declare their non-commercial status on an annual basis, and to maintain this status, developers must have no revenue in or out of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for their app product.<br/>
<br/>
Second, to address fears of the CTF causing outrageous fees for an app that suddenly goes viral, Apple has implemented a three year on-ramping process for small developers. The three year period begins when a developer agrees to the new &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; business terms, and during this time, if an app goes viral and exceeds the one million annual install threshold that triggers the CTF, the CTF won't be charged if the developer earns less than 10 million euros in global business revenue, and the fee is reduced after that.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Under 10 million euros: No CTF during the three year period.</li><br/>
 	<li>Between 10 million and 50 million euros: CTF must be paid, but it is capped at one million euros per year for the three year period.</li><br/>
 	<li>Beyond 50 million euros: Benefit is no longer available, and the full CTF has to be paid.</li><br/>
<li>After three years: Developers will pay for each first annual install after the initial one million first annual installs per year.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Note that this ramp up period is only available to small developers who have not previously exceeded one million first annual installs, and it is calculated based on global business revenue rather than just &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; revenue. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says that 99 percent of developers will not be subject to the CTF to begin with, but the new ramp up period will go further to make sure that small developers who get a breakout hit will have time to scale their businesses before having to pay fees.<br/>
<br/>
Back in March, developer Riley Testut spoke with Apple officials at a workshop on the Digital Markets Act, and he asked what would happen if a young developer had an app go viral and unwittingly racked up millions in fees. Testut asked the question because when he was a high school student, he released GBA4iOS outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. It was unexpectedly downloaded more than 10 million times, and that would have bankrupted him had he been subject to the Core Technology Fee.<br/>
<br/>
In response, Apple VP of regulatory law Kyle Andeers said that Apple was working on a solution because the company is not trying to stifle innovation. Apple believes that a free app going viral and being subject to exorbitant fees will be a rare occurrence, but the changes will keep that from happening. The CTF update will also be a welcome change for those who want to release entirely free apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The CTF is only applicable to apps that have opted in to the new &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; business terms in the European Union. Apps in the EU are now able to be distributed through alternative app stores and developer websites without having to rely on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has more information about the new changes to the CTF on its <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/core-technology-fee">updated CTF support page</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/apple-updates-core-technology-fee-eu/">Apple Tweaks EU Core Technology Fee to Avoid Bankrupting Unexpectedly Viral Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-eu-core-technology-fee-to-avoid-bankrupting-unexpectedly-viral-apps.2425319/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/amazon-discounts-accessories-anker/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery.2425318/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:56:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/amazon-discounts-accessories-anker/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a few deals offered by <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056">Anker</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">Eufy</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Jackery</a>, including a wide array of wall chargers, Bluetooth trackers, and other USB-C accessories. All of the products in this sale can be found on Amazon, and some will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-purple-may.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949011" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This week Eufy has a pair of discounts on its Find My-compatible SmartTrack Bluetooth tracker accessories exclusively for Prime members, including the SmartTrack Card for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.99. You can also get the SmartTrack Link in multiple pack options if you have Amazon Prime, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659794010"><strong>&#36;15.99</strong></a> for the 1-Pack, down from &#36;19.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714660094244"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Link 4-Pack for &#36;48.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the Anker deals, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056">20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> for &#36;89.98, down from &#36;129.99. If you need a bigger battery, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> for &#36;109.99 with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99. Additionally, below you'll find more Anker accessories including speakers and USB-C products.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for &#36;89.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;109.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker is also hosting a BOGO sale this week on Amazon, allowing you to save 15 percent on select charging accessories when you purchase two at once. You can find the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fpromotion%2Fpsp%2FA1XLK5JR9AUNRG%3Fref%3Dpsp_pc_cart_collapse_cpi_t1">full lineup on this landing page</a>, and it includes the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1714660272222">MagGo 10,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Display</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9CSG3B7%3Fm%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26ref%3Dpsp_pc_a_A1XLK5JR9AUNRG%26th%3D1">Nano 10,000 mAh Power Bank with Built-in USB-C Cable</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Highlights of Jackery's deals include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a>, available for just &#36;119.99, down from &#36;149.00. This is a miniature-sized portable power station that can fit in the palm of your hand and weighs just 2.13 lbs, while featuring a 31,000 mAh capacity and 128W output.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;119.99</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659902126">SmartTrack Link 1-Pack</a> - &#36;15.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659917907">SmartTrack Link 2-Pack</a> - &#36;26.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727">SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;19.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;29.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;64.99, down from &#36;79.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,499.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.49, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;74.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;119.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P_1713373339383">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E_1713373175628">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;599.00, down from &#36;799.00</li> <br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB083KBKJ8Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW_1713373227768">Explorer 1000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;649.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM_1713373287626">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,259.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.B0BZ8DZ3HR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3M5389ELMN7TD_1713385917457%26th%3D1">Explorer 3000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/amazon-discounts-accessories-anker/">Amazon Discounts Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery.2425318/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 and 15 Plus Proving Less Popular With Buyers This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/cirp-iphone-15-vs-14-sales-q1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-15-plus-proving-less-popular-with-buyers-this-year.2425315/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 07:44:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/cirp-iphone-15-vs-14-sales-q1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models were its most purchased smartphones in the U.S. in the first quarter of this year, according to the latest <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/iphone-15-winners-and-losers">Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP) report</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/iPhone-14-vs-iPhone-15-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-863031" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max accounted for 22% and 23% of all iPhones sold in Q1 2024, for a 45% combined share. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Plus took a 9% share of all iPhones sold, while the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> were the third most popular, each taking 14% of the share. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max share hardly changed compared to the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and Pro Max the same quarter a year ago. However, Apple saw sales of the base model &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; decline relative to a year ago. The overall mix of &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models was lower, accounting for 68% of all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales. <br/>
<br/>
By contrast, in Q1 2023 the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; series had a 7% higher share of all iPhones sold, taking 75% combined. The percentages suggest that the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus were more popular than the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus over the equivalent quarter the previous year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/CIRP-iphone-14-15-quarters-compared.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="827" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948990" /><br/>
Noting the change, CIRP comments:<br/>
<blockquote>We see this as a continuation of a trend from the past couple of quarters, as the lower- priced current models give up some share to older models. The once flagship, now base iPhone 15, is no longer the leading-edge choice, as the Pro and Pro Max models take that role.</blockquote>Last week, CIRP released a report indicating that new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; activations are down to a low not seen in the U.S. smartphone market <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/25/iphone-activation-market-share-decline/">for the last six years</a>. <br/>
<br/>
CIRP said that Apple's installed smartphone base was higher than recorded activations, but Apple's share of new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; activations fell from 40% to 33% over the past year, suggesting a shift away from the higher market shares Apple enjoyed in previous years.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/cirp-iphone-15-vs-14-sales-q1/">iPhone 15 and 15 Plus Proving Less Popular With Buyers This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-and-15-plus-proving-less-popular-with-buyers-this-year.2425315/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
