<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 03:00:51 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Drops OpenAI Board Observer Role Amid Regulatory Scrutiny</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-drops-openai-board-observer-role/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-openai-board-observer-role-amid-regulatory-scrutiny.2431034/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 01:59:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-drops-openai-board-observer-role/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will not take an observer role on OpenAI's board as part of a deal to integrate ChatGPT into its devices, according to the <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ecfa69df-5d1c-4177-9b14-a3a73072db12">Financial Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> last week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-schiller-openai-board-observer/">reported</a> that Apple Fellow and App Store chief Phil Schiller would to take the position as part of its agreement with OpenAI, which will see ChatGPT integrated into iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia.<br/>
<br/>
A board observer is an informal board position where the participant is able to attend and contribute to board meetings, but is not allowed to vote and has no control. <br/>
<br/>
However, <em>FT</em> today reported that both Apple and Microsoft have given up their seats as observers on the board, amid increased scrutiny by regulators of Big Tech's investments in AI startups.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI will instead host regular meetings with partners as part of "a new approach to informing and engaging key strategic partners," an OpenAI spokesperson said. The meetings will be held with Sarah Friar, the company's chief financial officer.<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission last month said it was exploring the possibility of an antitrust investigation into Microsoft and OpenAI's partnership. The U.S. Federal Trade Commission is also looking at investments made by companies including Microsoft, Amazon, and Google into generative AI start-ups.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and OpenAI's deal will see Siri able to hand complicated user requests over to ChatGPT with explicit user permission. OpenAI is not paying Apple to integrate ChatGPT in its operating systems, nor is Apple paying OpenAI. No money is being exchanged under the terms of the arrangement at the current time. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-drops-openai-board-observer-role/">Apple Drops OpenAI Board Observer Role Amid Regulatory Scrutiny</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-openai-board-observer-role-amid-regulatory-scrutiny.2431034/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Latest iOS 18 and tvOS 18 Betas Add Apple TV InSight Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-insight-ios-18-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/latest-ios-18-and-tvos-18-betas-add-apple-tv-insight-feature.2431021/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:52:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-insight-ios-18-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-3/">third betas</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and tvOS 18, Apple has added InSight to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app. InSight was announced as a new addition in the latest software updates at WWDC, but it was not implemented in earlier betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-insight-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="1943" height="1093" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957062" /><br/>
Available for some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> shows and movies, InSight provides details on the actors in each scene and any music that's playing. InSight is located at the bottom of the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app interface when a show is playing, and it updates dynamically.<br/>
<br/>
Actor names are displayed in a list, and if you tap on one, the show is moved to picture-in-picture mode and the TV app displays other shows and moves that person has appeared in. Tapping on a song name adds it to a "Saved Songs" section in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<br/>
<br/>
InSight is particularly useful on an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; running tvOS 18 because if you connect an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, you can see InSight information in the Remote app without interrupting the show or movie.<br/>
<br/>
InSight is similar to the Amazon X-Ray feature available for Prime Video content, but it does not provide trivia or full cast information. As of right now, InSight is not available for all &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; shows, and appears to be limited to newer series. Apple will likely bring the feature to additional content prior to when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, and tvOS 18 launch.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-insight-ios-18-beta-3/">Latest iOS 18 and tvOS 18 Betas Add Apple TV InSight Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/latest-ios-18-and-tvos-18-betas-add-apple-tv-insight-feature.2431021/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Gives Tips on Avoiding Phishing Scams Amid Warnings of New SMS Threat</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-phishing-avoidance-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-tips-on-avoiding-phishing-scams-amid-warnings-of-new-sms-threat.2431018/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:24:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-phishing-avoidance-tips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this month <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102568">refreshed the security support document</a> that provides <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac users with tips on how to recognize and avoid social engineering schemes like phishing messages and fake support calls.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/iPhone-12-Security-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-778674" /><br/>
The updated information <a href="https://www.broadcom.com/support/security-center/protection-bulletin/apple-ids-targeted-in-us-smishing-campaign">follows recent reports</a> of "smishing" attacks targeting Apple IDs. Malicious actors have been sending out SMS text messages that attempt to get users to provide their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> usernames and passwords on a fake <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's guidelines provide key information that all users should be aware of to protect themselves, such as a recommendation to ignore messages with suspicious links. Apple says that it will not ask for &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; passwords or verification codes, and users should contact Apple directly rather than answering a suspicious phone call or message claiming to be from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Further, Apple will not ask users to log into any website, to tap Accept in the two-factor authentication dialog, or to enter a two-factor code into a website. Apple will also not request that users disable features like two-factor authentication, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, or Stolen Device Protection. Apple's security tips:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Never share personal data or security information like passwords or security codes, and never agree to enter them into a webpage that someone directs you to.</li><br/>
 	<li>Protect your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;. Use two-factor authentication, always keep your contact information secure and up to date, and never share your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; password or verification codes with anyone. Apple never asks for this information to provide support.</li><br/>
 	<li>Never use Apple Gift Cards to make payments to other people.</li><br/>
 	<li>Learn how to <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201679">identify legitimate Apple emails</a> about your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> or iTunes Store purchases.</li><br/>
 	<li>Learn how to <a href="https://www.apple.com/privacy/control/">keep your Apple devices and data secure</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Download software only from sources you can trust.</li><br/>
 	<li>Don't follow links or open or save attachments in suspicious or unsolicited messages.</li><br/>
 	<li>Don't answer suspicious phone calls or messages claiming to be from Apple. Instead, contact Apple directly <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/106932">through official support channels</a>.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Scammers will go to great lengths to get personal information, so Apple recommends watching out for tricks like creating a sense of urgency through scare tactics like stolen personal information or unauthorized charges. Scammers are after login information and security codes, so that information should not be entered on a website accessed through a link in a text or an email.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also warns against downloading unrecognized, unsafe software and configuration profiles and following instructions on pop-ups. Users who receive a pop-up should ignore the message and close the entire window or tab.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102568">has further instructions</a> on how to spot social engineering schemes, the forms those schemes can take, and how to report suspicious emails, messages, and phone calls. There is a separate support document on <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120569">what to expect from Apple Support</a> and the kinds of information Apple will not request.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-phishing-avoidance-tips/">Apple Gives Tips on Avoiding Phishing Scams Amid Warnings of New SMS Threat</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-tips-on-avoiding-phishing-scams-amid-warnings-of-new-sms-threat.2431018/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Trailer for Upcoming Taika Waititi Series &#039;Time Bandits&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-plus-time-bandits/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-trailer-for-upcoming-taika-waititi-series-time-bandits.2431017/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 15:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-plus-time-bandits/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared the first trailer for upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> series Time Bandits, which is based on the 1981 movie that has the same name. Time Bandits was created by Taika Waititi, Jemaine Clement, and Iain Morris, all of whom are known for popular shows.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Time Bandits -- Official Trailer Apple TV+" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BCA9jpc4R74" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Waititi and Clement previously teamed up for What We Do in the Shadows, and Waititi has recently worked on Reservation Dogs and Our Flag Means Death. Morris is known for creating The Inbetweeners.<br/>
<br/>
Time Bandits will see an eleven-year-old history nerd teaming up with a ragtag group of thieves to journey through time and space to hunt down treasure. In the trailer, eleven-year-old Kevin finds a portal in the wardrobe in his closet, and is seen journeying through historic locations across time.<br/>
<br/>
The first two episodes of the 10-episode show are set to premiere on Wednesday, July 24, with two additional episodes to follow each week.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-tv-plus-time-bandits/">Apple Shares Trailer for Upcoming Taika Waititi Series &#039;Time Bandits&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-trailer-for-upcoming-taika-waititi-series-time-bandits.2431017/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Aqara Launches Smart Lock U200 With Apple Home Key Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/aqara-smart-lock-u200/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aqara-launches-smart-lock-u200-with-apple-home-key-support.2431016/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 15:18:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/aqara-smart-lock-u200/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Aqara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Smart home device maker Aqara <a href="https://www.aqara.com/en/product/smart-lock-u200/">today announced</a> the launch of the Smart Lock U200, its latest HomeKit-compatible lock option. The U200 has a number of smart features, including compatibility with home key for hands-free door unlocking.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/aqara-u200-smart-lock.jpg" alt="" width="1781" height="1002" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958130" /><br/>
Aqara's latest smart lock uses the Matter smart home protocol, so it works with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> and other Matter-compatible smart home platforms. Aqara says the Smart Lock U200 is one of the first Matter-over-Thread locks that supports the NFC-based home key feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Home key is designed to allow the U200 to unlock when an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or Apple Watch is tapped against the lock, with a digital key stored in the Wallet app. The feature can be set up to allow for unlocking without authentication thanks to an Express Mode feature for quick entry, and unlocking works even if the user's Apple Watch or &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; runs out of battery.<br/>
<br/>
Like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/aqara-u100-smart-lock/">last year's U100 Smart Lock</a>, the U200 is able to sense if the door is open, sending an alert if someone forgets to close the door. It is also able to lock the door automatically after it is shut, which is a handy option.<br/>
<br/>
Multiple entry methods are supported, including unlocking with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or Apple Watch, a mechanical key, PIN code, fingerprint scan, Aqara app, or an NFC card. There are options for providing one-time passwords and periodic passwords to guests. When enabled, the U200's Quiet Unlock mode disables all beeping and other notifications that typically accompany an unlock, with noise limited to the whir of the motor.<br/>
<br/>
The U200 is sleeker and less industrial looking than the U100 Smart Lock, and it is designed to fit over existing locks without needing modification. There is a rechargeable battery inside that is designed to last for up to six months, and the keypad is powered by AAA batteries or a hardwired connection.<br/>
<br/>
As a Matter-over-Thread device, using the Aqara U200 with a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; setup will require a home hub like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K Wi-Fi + Ethernet.<br/>
<br/>
The Smart Lock U200 is <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1C75J4F">available from Amazon</a> for &#36;270. It comes in either black or silver.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aqara/">Aqara</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/aqara-smart-lock-u200/">Aqara Launches Smart Lock U200 With Apple Home Key Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aqara-launches-smart-lock-u200-with-apple-home-key-support.2431016/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Teases Severance Season 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-teases-severance-season-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-teases-severance-season-2.2431010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 14:00:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-teases-severance-season-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Fans of popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> series Severance have been waiting for news about the second season of the show, and it looks like Apple will soon deliver.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Severance-Apple-TV-Plus-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877229" /><br/>
A teaser for the new season was <a href="https://x.com/AppleTV/status/1810645085941383335">shared on social media today</a>, featuring a dim hallway with a red blinking light. The blinking light is Morse code that <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/tvPlus/comments/1dz23ad/apple_announces_severance_news_for_tomorrow_in/">appears to translate</a> to "tomorrow." Severance cast members including Adam Scott have also been teasing an upcoming announcement, so all signs point to an imminent news release about the series two premiere date.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="zxx" dir="ltr"><a href="https://t.co/046vNV03vz">pic.twitter.com/046vNV03vz</a></p>&mdash; Apple TV (@AppleTV) <a href="https://twitter.com/AppleTV/status/1810645085941383335?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 9, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Season two finished filming in April, so it is unlikely that the show is ready to debut tomorrow. Apple is probably teasing the first trailer for season two and a possible launch date announcement.<br/>
<br/>
With its mysterious work environment and workers that agree to separate "innie" and "outie" personas, Severance has become one of the most discussed &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; shows.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-teases-severance-season-2/">Apple Teases Severance Season 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-teases-severance-season-2.2431010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2431003/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 11:46:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware/">second beta firmware</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, including both the Lightning and USB-C versions. The updated firmware has a build number 7A5244b and it is available to developers at the current time. This is the second firmware update that Apple has released since announcing new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 features in June.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803705" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Pro-Beta-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" /><br/>
There are several new features that are coming to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and these features are included in the firmware update.<br/>
<br/>
With head gestures, users can control <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a shake or a nod of the head. If you get a phone call, for example, you can shake your head no if you don't want to answer it, or nod to accept the call. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interactions can be used for responding to incoming messages, calls, and notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is adding Voice Isolation to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, and there is a new Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming. Game developers will be able to incorporate spatial audio into their games for a more immersive audio experience.<br/>
<br/>
The new firmware requires a device running &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; to install, and it won't be available to the public until this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-2/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware With Support for iOS 18 Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-with-support-for-ios-18-features.2431003/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430991/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:06:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 update to developers, with the software coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-2/">released the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6, and no new features have been discovered in the betas so far.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-6-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-6-to-developers.2430991/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430990/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:05:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to developers for testing purposes, with software coming a little over a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-2-to-developers/">second iOS and iPadOS 17.6 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The features Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no major new additions have been discovered in the betas so far.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple focusing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-6-and-ipados-17-6-to-developers.2430990/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-releases-visionos-1-3-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430997/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:03:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-releases-visionos-1-3-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.3 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The third &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 beta comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-visionos-1-3-beta-2-to-developers/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3, as well as implement additional bug fixes. No new features were found in the first two &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.3 betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-releases-visionos-1-3-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Releases Third Beta of visionOS 1.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-beta-of-visionos-1-3-to-developers.2430997/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430996/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.6 update to developers for testing purposes, with the third beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-2/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.6 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.6 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what's included in watchOS 10.6, and with Apple's focus shifting to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, it likely features bug fixes and other minor improvements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-6-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-6-to-developers.2430996/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430993/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:01:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.6 to developers for testing purposes, with the update coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/01/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.6 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.6.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-6-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.6 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-6-to-developers.2430993/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 18 Hints at HomePod With Touchscreen Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/tvos18-homepod-touchscreen-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-hints-at-homepod-with-touchscreen-display.2430988/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:40:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/tvos18-homepod-touchscreen-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There have been multiple rumors about Apple's work on various <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> hybrid devices with a touchscreen over the last few years, and new findings in the tvOS 18 update further hint at the development that Apple is doing in the home space.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Second-Generation-HomePod-With-Top-LCD-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931490" /><br/>
A unique touchscreen interface was allegedly found buried in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/apple-seeds-tvos-18-beta-3-to-developers/">tvOS 18 beta 3</a> by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/07/09/touchscreen-interface-tvos-homepod/">9to5Mac</a></em>, and the finding is actually relevant to the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; because the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;'s software is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/04/13/homepod-tvos-operating-system/">offshoot of the tvOS software</a>. The interface is called "PlasterBoard" internally, and PlasterBoard is in line with the naming for other Apple interfaces, which include SpringBoard for iOS and iPadOS, PineBoard for tvOS, SoundBoard for &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, and SurfBoard for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>. The interface appears to feature just a Lock Screen with a touch-based keyboard for entering passcodes as of right now, with little else discovered about it.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; does not include an option for locking it with a passcode, nor does the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; because as of right now, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; only supports simple control gestures. The design that was found in the beta closely resembles the on-screen keypad that you see on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors have suggested that Apple is working on several home control devices, and the mix of rumors we've heard indicate that multiple development paths and prototypes are being explored. There have been rumors of a simple &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a touch display at the top, a hybrid &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">Apple TV device</a> with a camera, a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/22/apple-speakers-with-screens-and-cameras-report/">a screen and a camera</a>, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-smart-home-ipad-display/">iPad/HomePod sort of combo</a> that works as a centralized home hub.<br/>
<br/>
A standard &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with an LED touch-based display at the top of the device could potentially be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/27/touchscreen-homepod-everything-we-know/">first HomePod and display combo</a> that we see. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">HomePod with 7-inch display</a> would launch at some point in 2024, and there have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/">leaked prototype images</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, <em>MacRumors</em> found code referencing a "Home Accessory" device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/04/leak-confirms-apples-work-on-home-accessory/">with a HomeAccessory17,1 identifier</a>. No existing &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; or &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; devices use the HomeAccessory identifier, but it is similar to the AudioAccessory identifier that Apple uses internally for the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;. Based on the numbering, this upcoming device is equipped with the same A18 chip we expect to see in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/tvos18-homepod-touchscreen-display/">tvOS 18 Hints at HomePod With Touchscreen Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-18-hints-at-homepod-with-touchscreen-display.2430988/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Models Rumored to Have Face ID-Related Design Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/iphone-16-face-id-design-changes-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-rumored-to-have-face-id-related-design-changes.2430987/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:15:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/iphone-16-face-id-design-changes-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 16 models coming later this year could have some Face ID-related "design changes," supply chain publication <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240705PD211.html"><em>DigiTimes</em> said</a> this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Beyond-iPhone-13-Better-Blue-Face-ID.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793993" /><br/>
The original source of this information is <a href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/business/2024/05/25/british-microchip-plant-faces-closure-apple-pulls-plug/">British newspaper <em>The Telegraph</em></a>, which six weeks ago reported that Face ID component supplier Coherent was considering selling or repurposing a manufacturing facility in Newton Aycliffe, a small town in England, after losing a supply deal with a large customer believed to be Apple. The report claimed Apple was expected to "overhaul" the Face ID system on iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear what changes Apple may be planning for the Face ID system on iPhone 16 models, if any. Early rumors indicated that iPhone 16 Pro models could feature an under-screen Face ID system, but reputable display industry source Ross Young later indicated that this change is no longer expected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/09/under-display-face-id-2025-ross-young/">until next year at the earliest</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Other changes to Face ID are still possible for iPhone 16 models, but it is unclear if this would lead to any noticeable improvements, such as faster authentication. Apple routinely makes changes to internal components in new generations of iPhones, and this does not always lead to new features or other obvious benefits for customers.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, expect some potential Face ID-related changes on iPhone 16 models, but details are vague right now. Perhaps some more rumors about this topic will surface between now and the devices launching in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/iphone-16-face-id-design-changes-rumor/">iPhone 16 Models Rumored to Have Face ID-Related Design Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-models-rumored-to-have-face-id-related-design-changes.2430987/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches 65W Dual USB-C Power Adapter With Built-In Apple Watch Charger</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/nomad-usb-c-power-adapter-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-65w-dual-usb-c-power-adapter-with-built-in-apple-watch-charger.2430986/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/nomad-usb-c-power-adapter-apple-watch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nomad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today announced the launch of its latest product, the <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/ac-adapter-65w-usb-c-watch-edition">65W AC Power Adapter Apple Watch Edition</a>. Ideal for travel, the power adapter includes two USB-C ports and an Apple Watch charging puck.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/nomad-charger-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957897" /><br/>
Like most modern chargers, Nomad's 65W Apple Watch Power Adapter uses Gallium Nitride (GaN) technology, so it's compact. It's a little thicker than Apple chargers, but it's much smaller than the comparable 61W charger from Apple and overall more portable. The prongs fold down when the charger is not in use, which increases portability.<br/>
<br/>
The two USB-C ports offer up to 65W total power, so if only one is in use, you get the full 65W. If two are in use, the top port can charge a device at 45W and the bottom port can charge a device at 20W. There is an Apple Watch charging puck at the top, and it supports fast charging for charging Apple's latest Apple Watch models at the maximum speed.<br/>
<br/>
We were able to test Nomad's new power adapter ahead of launch, and it works as expected. Pop it into an outlet and the top can charge an Apple Watch (or the AirPods) with the magnetic charging puck, while the two USB-C ports can charge a MacBook, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, AirPods, or other device that charges over USB-C. At 65W max, you're not getting the best charging speeds for the 16-inch MacBook Pro, but it's enough for slower charging, and plenty for an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, or smaller MacBook.<br/>
<br/>
The power adapter works best in a wall outlet where the Apple Watch charging puck is at the top of the device, but it can be used with tabletop chargers where the charging puck is at the side because of the magnetic attachment. Nomad does not include USB-C cables with the power adapter, so you'll need to supply your own.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/nomad-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957898" /><br/>
With some short cables, it makes for a useful travel charger. It's more compact than a lot of other travel charging options, and it can fast charge an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and Apple Watch, which isn't true of on-the-go <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> chargers. It's also versatile, because the two ports can charge other devices like Samsung phones and handheld game consoles.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad is known for premium devices, and the main downside to the Apple Watch Power Adapter is the price. It's &#36;100, and that's expensive for a dual-port USB-C charger that maxes out at 65W. You're getting the benefit of a built-in Apple Watch charger, a portable build, and a sleek design at that price point, but the cost is going to turn away some buyers. Still, Nomad makes reliable products and this is a high-quality power adapter that's worth checking out if you're in the market for something that's useful for travel or bringing between locations like home and work.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad's 65W AC Power Adapter Apple Watch Edition <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/ac-adapter-65w-usb-c-watch-edition">can be purchased from the Nomad website</a> for &#36;100.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nomad/">Nomad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/nomad-usb-c-power-adapter-apple-watch/">Nomad Launches 65W Dual USB-C Power Adapter With Built-In Apple Watch Charger</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-65w-dual-usb-c-power-adapter-with-built-in-apple-watch-charger.2430986/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Maps for iOS and Apple CarPlay Gains Live Speedometer Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/google-maps-for-ios-gains-speedometer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-for-ios-and-apple-carplay-gains-live-speedometer-feature.2430984/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 08:07:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/google-maps-for-ios-gains-speedometer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Google Maps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Google Maps app for iOS and Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> now features a live speedometer, <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/07/09/google-maps-is-rolling-out-speedometer-speed-limits-on-iphone-and-carplay-globally/">TechCrunch</a></em> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/Google-maps-feaure.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-793593" /><br/>
The feature, which was previously only available on Google Maps for Android, helps users to stay within the speed limit while driving. Now, when a user begins navigation, the vehicle's speed is shown in miles or kilometers per hour, depending on the region. The icon changes color depending on the speed indicator to subtly encourage drivers to remain within the speed limit.<br/>
<br/>
Google confirmed to <em>TechCrunch</em> that the speedometer display is now rolling out to iOS users globally, but it cautions that the feature is for "informational use only" and drivers should still rely on their vehicle's speedometer to confirm its actual speed. To turn on the speedometer and speed limits in the Google Maps app, users should navigate to their profile, Settings, Navigation, and Driving options. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-maps/">Google Maps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/google-maps-for-ios-gains-speedometer/">Google Maps for iOS and Apple CarPlay Gains Live Speedometer Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-maps-for-ios-and-apple-carplay-gains-live-speedometer-feature.2430984/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Adding These New Games in August</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-arcade-games-in-august-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-adding-these-new-games-in-august.2430981/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:26:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-arcade-games-in-august-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/three-new-games-come-to-apple-arcade-in-august-including-temple-run-legends/">announced</a> three new games coming to Apple Arcade next month, including award-winning roguelike game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/vampire-survivors/id6478975337">Vampire Survivors+</a> and level-based runner <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/temple-run-legends/id1670483159">Temple Run: Legends</a> on August 1, and physics-based puzzle game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/castle-crumble/id1616814625">Castle Crumble</a> for the Vision Pro on August 29. Apple Arcade games are ad-free and do not offer in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Temple-Run-Legends.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958056" /><br/>
More details can be found <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/three-new-games-come-to-apple-arcade-in-august-including-temple-run-legends/">in the Apple Newsroom press release</a>. We have pasted Apple's description of each game below.<br/>
<br/>
Vampire Survivors+ for iPhone and iPad:<blockquote>As players fight for their lives in the toxic, devil-ridden environment of Vampire Survivors+, a whole new world of horror is unleashed. From dusk to dawn, night creatures will cross their paths, forcing them to rely on the goodwill of their fellow survivors in order to prevail. While garlic, a cross, and a magic wand are useful tools to defeat their enemies, the responsibility ultimately lies in their capable hands as they test their strength against these deadly creatures from their touchscreens. This multistage game has a wide array of settings, including a multiplayer mode where up to four players can slay the undead on the same device by connecting game controllers to play together.</blockquote>Temple Run: Legends for the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Apple TV:<blockquote>Run, swim, jump, and join a legion of heroes in Temple Run: Legends. In addition to the classic infinite run mode, players can explore ancient Aperion with fresh gameplay modes, dynamic challenges and rewards, and over 500 levels in story mode. Players should prepare to traverse exciting climates, interact with fascinating inhabitants and creatures, and encounter a unique, all-new cast of characters as they conquer their next adventure.</blockquote>Castle Crumble, expanding to the Apple Vision Pro:<blockquote>Players will embark on an adventure across a variety of kingdoms and unique biomes to take down the enemy's castles in this physics-based puzzle game. Unique controls allow players to use their hands to precision target the castles' weak points using powerful explosives, mystical spells, and mysterious unlockable boosts, and watch the castles blast apart across their living rooms. <br/>
</blockquote>Accessible through the App Store, Apple Arcade is a subscription-based service that provides access to hundreds of games across the iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple TV, and Vision Pro, all free of ads and in-app purchases. The service <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">received its first price increase</a> last year, with U.S. pricing rising from &#36;4.99 to &#36;6.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/apple-arcade-games-in-august-2024/">Apple Arcade Adding These New Games in August</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-adding-these-new-games-in-august.2430981/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirTag 4 Pack Drops to &#36;74.98 on Amazon, Alongside Low Prices on Eufy&#039;s SmartTrack Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airtag-4-pack-amazon-eufy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airtag-4-pack-drops-to-74-98-on-amazon-alongside-low-prices-on-eufys-smarttrack-accessories.2430980/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 07:13:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airtag-4-pack-amazon-eufy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a collection of Bluetooth tracker discounts on Amazon, which include low prices on Apple's AirTag and Eufy's SmartTrack accessories. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airtag-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916645" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4 Pack available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;74.98</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This is a rare match of the all-time low price on the AirTag 4 Pack on Amazon, and a deal we haven't seen in months. The AirTag 4 Pack can be delivered as soon as July 11 for Prime members, and the AirTag 1 Pack is also available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;24.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;24 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;74.98</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/eufy-smarttrack-card.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956422" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want to save more money, Eufy's SmartTrack Card Bluetooth tracker is on sale right now on Amazon. This accessory is priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1718290256476"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;29.99. <strong>You'll need to enter the code EUFYTRACKER at checkout to see this price</strong>. The SmartTrack Card is compatible with Apple's Find My app, allowing you to track the device within the app and receive left behind alerts and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1718290256476"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, Amazon has Eufy's SmartTrack Link accessories on sale this week, with best-ever prices on every model. For the 1 Pack you'll need to enter the coupon code EUFYTRACK4 at checkout, while the 4 Pack requires you to have a Prime membership in order to see the deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1720533507949">SmartTrack Link 1 Pack</a> - &#36;15.99 with coupon code EUFYTRACK4, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1720533518416">SmartTrack Link 2 Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1720533562146">SmartTrack Link 4 Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/airtag-4-pack-amazon-eufy/">AirTag 4 Pack Drops to &#36;74.98 on Amazon, Alongside Low Prices on Eufy&#039;s SmartTrack Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airtag-4-pack-drops-to-74-98-on-amazon-alongside-low-prices-on-eufys-smarttrack-accessories.2430980/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Public Beta Coming Soon: How to Get Your iPhone Ready</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon-how-to-get-your-iphone-ready.2430977/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:30:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last month <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/ios-18-makes-iphone-more-personal-capable-and-intelligent-than-ever/">announced</a> that the first public beta of iOS 18 would be released in July, so it should be available to try out soon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Below, we outline everything you need to know about the upcoming iOS 18 public beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
The first iOS 17 and iOS 16 public betas came out in the first half of July in the past two years.<br/>
<ul><li><strong>iOS 16:</strong> Monday, July 11, 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>iOS 17:</strong> Wednesday, July 12, 2023</li></ul><br/>
<h2>How to Get Ready</h2><br/>
Enrolling in <a href="https://beta.apple.com/">Apple's free public beta testing program</a> is simple: visit <a href="https://beta.apple.com/">beta.apple.com</a>, sign in to your Apple ID account, and accept the terms and conditions. <br/>
<br/>
After signing up, open the Settings app on your iPhone and tap General → Software Update → Beta Updates. This is where the iOS 18 public beta will be listed once available, and you will be able to tap on it to begin the installation process. Note that the iPhone must be signed in to the same Apple ID enrolled in the public beta program.<br/>
<br/>
Due to software bugs and other potential issues, we recommend installing the iOS 18 public beta on a secondary iPhone, rather than the device that you use daily. We also highly recommend <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/iphone/iph3ecf67d29/ios">backing up your iPhone to your Mac</a> before installing beta software on the device, to prevent data loss in the event something goes wrong.<br/>
<br/>
We will be sharing a more detailed step-by-step guide on installing the iOS 18 public beta following its release later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatible iPhones</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17 is:<ul><div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max </li><br/>
</div></ul><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><ul><li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro </li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max </li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR </li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation or later) </li></ul> </div><div style="clear:both;"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Home-Screen.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954462" /><br/>
iOS 18 introduces new customization options for the Home Screen and Control Center, a redesigned Photos app, the ability to use any emoji as a Tapback in the Messages app, an option to lock apps behind Face ID or Touch ID, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
The tentpole feature of iOS 18 is the Apple Intelligence suite of AI features. These features will help you improve your writing, summarize your notifications, generate custom emoji and images, and much more. Apple Intelligence will also power a smarter version of Siri with on-screen awareness, deeper per-app controls, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features have yet to be added to any iOS 18 developer betas, so they might not be available in the first iOS 18 public beta.<br/>
<br/>
Read our in-depth <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> to learn more about the update.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Skipping the Beta?</h2><br/>
iOS 18 should be widely released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon/">iOS 18 Public Beta Coming Soon: How to Get Your iPhone Ready</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon-how-to-get-your-iphone-ready.2430977/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Early Prime Day Discounts on AirPods Pro 2 (&#36;169) and AirPods Max (&#36;399)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/amazon-prime-day-airpods-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-early-prime-day-discounts-on-airpods-pro-2-169-and-airpods-max-399.2430973/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 06:16:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/amazon-prime-day-airpods-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Day isn't until next week, but the company is already providing new record low prices across multiple AirPods models right now. This includes the AirPods 2, AirPods Pro 2, AirPods Max, and the AirPods 3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/airpods-3-all-time-low-price-3/">which we covered yesterday</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Combo-Discount-Feature-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895383" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Deals start with the AirPods 2 at just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is one of the first times the AirPods 2 have hit this best-ever price in 2024, and only Amazon has the deal. Similarly, the AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00, another all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, the AirPods Max have dropped to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;549.00. This is a new record low price on the AirPods Max, beating the previous best price by about &#36;20. Amazon has all five colors of the headphones at this price as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/amazon-prime-day-airpods-pro-2/">Amazon Introduces Early Prime Day Discounts on AirPods Pro 2 (&#36;169) and AirPods Max (&#36;399)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-early-prime-day-discounts-on-airpods-pro-2-169-and-airpods-max-399.2430973/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
