<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:02:43 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple vs. the U.S. Department of Justice: What You Need to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vs-the-u-s-department-of-justice-what-you-need-to-know.2422813/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:25:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj&#038;post_date=1711419909/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>Apple vs. DoJ</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On March 21, the United States Justice Department <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/">sued Apple for antitrust violations</a>, concluding a multi-year investigation into Apple's business practices. The U.S. government is also pursuing antitrust cases against Google, Amazon, and Meta, as part of an expansive look into the practices of major tech companies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-vs-DOJ-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943221" /><br/>
Apple plans to "vigorously defend" against the DoJ's lawsuit, which seeks to fundamentally change the way that Apple operates. This will be a legal battle that spans multiple years, and we'll keep this guide updated with the latest news as the case progresses.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="dojs_claims">DoJ's Claims</h2><br/>
The lawsuit that the DoJ filed against Apple is broad ranging, and rather than focusing on one or two issues, it aims to establish a long-running history of anti-competitive behavior. The DoJ tries to establish a pattern of business decisions that have suppressed competition, with the DoJ arguing that Apple has time and time again opted to "make its products worse for consumers to prevent competition from emerging."<br/>
<br/>
It is the opinion of the DoJ that Apple has gotten consumers "hooked" on its platform through these choices, making it unreasonably difficult for customers to switch to another smartphone brand. There is no allowance made for customer preference and the idea that people simply like their iPhones - the DoJ positions Apple as a monopolist that has manipulated people into sticking with its ecosystem by blocking competing apps, services, and products.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="suppressing_technologies">Suppressing Technologies</h3><br/>
While the full lawsuit details a long list of ways Apple has allegedly harmed consumers, the DoJ cites five specific examples of Apple blocking technologies that it claims would decrease barriers to switching and give consumers a "higher-quality user experience on any smartphone."<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ is of the opinion that if Apple did not historically limit cloud gaming, digital wallets, and non-Apple Watch smartwatches, that people would freely choose to purchase less expensive alternative smartphones over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. The DoJ believes that Apple is not facing pressure from "innovative, cross-platform technologies" because Apple "makes other products worse" rather than making its own products better.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Super apps</strong> - The DoJ defines super apps as those that provide a user with "broad functionality" in a single app and have the benefit of providing a consistent user experience across devices. An example of a super app is WeChat, which is widely used in China for communicating, making payments, and more. The DoJ says that Apple has "denied users access to super apps" in the U.S., but it is worth noting that there is a cultural aspect to these apps, and they just haven't caught on in the U.S. the way they have in China. Mini apps are often frequently referenced too, as Apple did have restrictions on apps offering mini games and other multi-app features (these restrictions were eliminated in iOS 17.4).</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Cloud streaming</strong> - The DoJ suggests that Apple is suppressing cloud streaming games by preventing them from being available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. Cloud streaming apps have been usable on Safari, and as of iOS 17.4, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-allows-cloud-gaming-apps-on-app-store/">changed its rules</a> to allow streaming game apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming to offer streaming games through a single &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; app. This argument is no longer entirely relevant, but the DoJ believes that by not allowing cloud gaming apps, Apple prevented consumers from buying cheaper phones. The idea here is that customers had to opt in to expensive iPhones to play "high-compute" games because they weren't available to play using cloud services.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Messaging apps</strong> - The DoJ thinks that third-party apps should be able to send and receive SMS messages, rather than these messages being routed to the Messages app. This would let users switch phones without changing the way they communicate. The filing takes issue with the lack of an iMessage app for Android, Apple's efforts to block the Beeper Mini app, green bubbles, and the adoption of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Smartwatches</strong> - Apple suppresses key functions of third-party smartwatches, preventing &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users from getting Apple Watch-like functionality from smartwatches with "better user interfaces and services." The DoJ says that Apple locks customers in to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with the Apple Watch, because the Apple Watch can't be used on other smartphones. A user who wants to switch from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; must also purchase an Android-compatible smartwatch.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Digital Wallets</strong> - Apple does not let banking apps access NFC and provide digital payments services, and customers are not able to choose their "trusted banking apps" as their digital wallet. Apple also prevents developers from creating cross-platform wallets that would make it easier to switch from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Android, and alternative wallets could also be used for in-app purchases. The DoJ claims that the payments that banks make to Apple for using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> would otherwise be used for features and benefits for smartphone users.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="privacy_and_security">Privacy and Security</h3><br/>
The DoJ suggests that Apple justifies its anticompetitive conduct with privacy and security concerns.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple spends billions on marketing to promote "the self-serving premise that only Apple can safeguard consumers' privacy and security interests."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple selectively compromises privacy and security interests when it is in Apple's financial interest. The examples used here include the lack of end-to-end encryption between Android and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; messages and the making Google the default browser engine when "more private options" are available.</li><br/>
 <li>The safe, secure experience on Mac is evidence that Apple's control over app distribution and creation is "substantially more restrictive than necessary to protect user privacy and security."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple makes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; less secure if that helps it maintain monopoly power. The DoJ cites unencrypted text messages sent from iPhones to Android phones as an example. "If Apple wanted to," it could let &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users send encrypted messages to Android users.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="the_app_store">The App Store</h3><br/>
The DoJ mentions Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; policies and fees, but it is not the main focus of the lawsuit. While the DoJ was preparing its case, the Apple vs. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> lawsuit took place, and Apple was found not to have a mobile gaming monopoly. That undoubtedly influenced the DoJ filing, but there is wording here<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple uses &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules to "extract monopoly rents" from third-party developers.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple prohibits the creation and use of alternative app stores, and has arbitrary enforcement of its own &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules.</li><br/>
 <li>Developers are not able to offer web apps as an alternative to &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; apps because &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users "do not look for or know how to find web apps."</li><br/>
 <li>Apple uses &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules and restrictions to penalize and restrict developers that threaten its monopoly. It does allow apps to use private APIs, and requires web browsers to use WebKit.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple's efforts to restrict super apps and cloud streaming apps may have slowed the development of innovative apps related to education, artificial intelligence, and productivity. It has also kept app developers for creating features prohibited by Apple on other platforms.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="iphone_cost_and_development">iPhone Cost and Development</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple inflates the price for buying and using iPhones.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple spent more than twice as much on stock buybacks and dividends as it did on research and development (&#36;30B vs. &#36;77B in fiscal 2023).</li><br/>
 <li>Apple slowed down innovation on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to extract revenue from customers using subscriptions and cloud services.</li><br/>
 <li>Powerful, expensive hardware is unnecessary if consumers can play games through cloud streaming apps.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="services">Services</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple's subscription services increase the cost of switching from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to another smartphone. The DoJ references <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, Apple's cloud storage, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+ because these are exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. This results in "significant frictions" for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who want to switch.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple uses its "rapidly expanding" role as a TV and movie producer to control content and affect the "flow of speech."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="green_bubbles_and_imessage">"Green Bubbles" and iMessage</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>By using green bubbles, Apple "signals to users" that rival smartphones are lower quality because the experience of messaging non-iPhone users is worse. The DoJ says this is because conversations are not encrypted, videos are grainy, and users cannot edit messages or see typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Non-iPhone users experience "social stigma, exclusion, and blame" for "breaking" chats with where other participants own iPhones. This is "particularly powerful" for teenagers, and "social pressure" causes teens to switch to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>While the DoJ's comments on messaging largely ignore that Apple plans to bring feature parity with &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, it says that won't be enough because third-party apps still won't be able to be set as the default app for SMS/&zwnj;RCS&zwnj; messages.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ speculates that because &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; improves over time, Apple might not support later versions of &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, so cross-platform messages "could soon be broken on iPhones" after Apple adds &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; support later in 2024.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/apple-confirms-it-shut-down-beeper-mini/">references Beeper Mini</a>, an app that gained access to Apple's iMessage servers by exploiting fake credentials. The DoJ claims that it was a solution that "fixed" the broken cross-platform messaging experience. Apple made &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users less secure because it also supported end-to-end encryption.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="carplay">CarPlay</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> forces an iPhone-centric experience by taking over "all of the screens, sensors, and gauges" in a car in order to use &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; features. The DoJ suggests Apple is leveraging the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user base to exert power over American carmakers and restrict innovation, but Apple has so far not seen a lot of traction with &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; 2 and many car makers, such as Tesla and GM, are opting out of &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="competitors">Competitors</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The DoJ claims that Apple is the reason that only Google and Samsung remain as meaningful competitors in the premium smartphone market.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ blames Apple's market dominance for failed smartphones that include the Amazon Fire Phone and the Microsoft Windows Phone.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_doj_claims">Other DoJ Claims</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The iPod was successful because of the DoJ's antitrust case against Microsoft because it allowed Apple to launch iTunes on Windows PCs. "Microsoft did not charge Apple a 30 percent fee for each song downloaded from the iTunes Store."</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ holds itself responsible for Apple's success. U.S. vs. Microsoft "created new opportunities for innovation," and without this case, Apple would have had more difficulty achieving success with the iPod and the subsequent &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple made smartphones other than the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; worse by stifling the growth of cloud gaming apps and interactive AI services.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ says that Apple copied the idea of a smartwatch from third-party developers.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ warns that Apple may "use its power to force its own users (and their data to become its next profitable product."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="dojs_market_definition">DoJ's Market Definition</h2><br/>
The DoJ suggests that Apple violated Section 2 of the Sherman Act, which says that it is illegal to acquire or maintain monopoly power "through improper means." To make this argument, the DoJ needs to prove that Apple is a monopoly power in a relevant market, and that Apple used anticompetitive conduct to achieve and maintain that monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
Sherman Act claims failed in Epic vs. Apple because &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; was not successful narrowing down the defined market in which Apple had a supposed monopoly. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; argued that the relevant market was apps on Apple devices, but the court decided it was all digital mobile gaming transactions. Apple was not found to have a monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ is also using a narrowed market definition that may not hold up. It has created a "performance smartphone market" defined as a "more expensive segment of the broader smartphone market." In this "performance market," Apple's U.S. market share by revenue is over 70 percent. In the "broader smartphone market" in the U.S., Apple has a 65 percent share.<br/>
<br/>
It could be tough for the DoJ to prove that Apple has a monopoly with only a 65 percent share of the market. 70 percent market share is a more solid argument for a monopoly, but the case against Apple won't be as strong as the case against Google. Google, for example, has a 90 percent share of the search engine market.<br/>
<br/>
Apple claims that it operates in a global market, and that the market share that should be considered is the global market share. Apple only has around a 20 percent cut of the global market.<br/>
<br/>
The DoJ also argues that Apple has a larger share "among key demographics" such as higher-income households and among young people.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_the_doj_wants">What the DoJ Wants</h2><br/>
The DoJ wants the court to find that Apple has acted unlawfully to monopolize or attempt to monopolize the U.S. smartphone market. It has asked for "relief as needed" to address anticompetitive harm and restore competitive conditions, and a ruling that prevents Apple from continuing to engage in anticompetitive practices.<br/>
<br/>
According to the DoJ, Apple should be prevented from using its control of app distribution to undermine cross-platform technologies, that it should not be able to use private APIs to undermine cross-platform technologies like messaging and smartwatches, and that Apple should be prevented from using the terms and conditions of its contracts with developers, consumers, and accessory makers to maintain a monopoly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apples_response">Apple's Response</h2><br/>
Apple has an official statement on the DoJ's lawsuit:<blockquote>At Apple, we innovate every day to make technology people love--designing products that work seamlessly together, protect people's privacy and security, and create a magical experience for our users. This lawsuit threatens who we are and the principles that set Apple products apart in fiercely competitive markets. If successful, it would hinder our ability to create the kind of technology people expect from Apple--where hardware, software, and services intersect. It would also set a dangerous precedent, empowering government to take a heavy hand in designing people's technology. We believe this lawsuit is wrong on the facts and the law, and we will vigorously defend against it.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has also held media briefings and shared information on key facts in the lawsuit. Some highlights:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>The DoJ has changed the scope of its case six times due to the results in &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; v. Apple and other lawsuits. Several theories were considered and had to be abandoned because of a lack of evidence.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple says that the lawsuit won't be successful because it does not get the facts right. It would set a dangerous precedent for government interference in technology, and would make the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; less private, less secure, and more vulnerable to malware. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; would not be able to operate as well with other Apple products, and user information would be put at risk.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims the DoJ wants to turn the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; into an Android, and that the case goes after the key features that make the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; experience unique.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple does not believe the lawsuit has a basis in antitrust law and seems to be suggesting that Apple has an obligation to design its products in a way that would help competitors.</li><br/>
 <li>In a recent ruling in the AliveCor v. Apple dispute, the court said that it cannot oversee technology and innovation, and it is not for the court to analyze algorithms.</li><br/>
 <li>The DoJ ignored changes to streaming game apps and plans to implement &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, and Apple says that super apps have always been permitted.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims the DoJ is trying to fit Apple into the theories that were successful in the antitrust case against Microsoft 20 years back, but Apple does not agree with the parallels. Microsoft had a 95 percent share of the market, and Apple says that business decisions are made to provide consumers with maximum privacy and safety.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple says the DoJ misses that customers are loyal because they are satisfied with their devices and love Apple products.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple claims it spent three years looking at whether it made sense to make an Apple Watch for Android, but ultimately chose not to make one because it would be inferior and would have limits impacting privacy and security.</li><br/>
 <li>iMessage has not been designed for other platforms because Apple doesn't have a way to verify that a third-party device has encryption and authentication procedures that meet its standards, and that security issues on third-party devices could expose the content of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users' messages, leading to fraud and spam issues.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_the_full_lawsuit">Read the Full Lawsuit</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe class="scribd_iframe_embed" title="United States et al v Apple Inc" src="https://www.scribd.com/embeds/717095810/content?start_page=1&view_mode=scroll&access_key=key-FCk4OGhTWJoCqsIVOd5Y" tabindex="0" data-auto-height="true" data-aspect-ratio="0.7729220222793488" scrolling="no" width="100%" height="600" frameborder="0"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="whats_next">What's Next</h2><br/>
Now that the DoJ has filed a lawsuit, Apple will have a 60-day period to respond. Apple plans to move to dismiss the complaint.<br/>
<br/>
If that doesn't happen, the case will move forward. There will be briefings, hearings, and a discovery period. It will be a few months before there are additional filings, and the entire legal process will span for multiple years. Apple says that it plans to vigorously fight the case.<br/>
<br/>
Should the judge assigned to the case rule in the DoJ's favor, there will be appeals and then remedies for the anticompetitive behavior will need to be determined.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-vs-doj/">Apple vs. the U.S. Department of Justice: What You Need to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vs-the-u-s-department-of-justice-what-you-need-to-know.2422813/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s A18 Pro Chip Rumored to Boost AI, Retain 6-Core GPU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-a18-pro-chip-rumored-to-boost-ai-retain-6-core-gpu.2422808/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:47:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">A18 Pro chip</a> for iPhone 16 Pro models will feature a larger die size for boosted artificial intelligence performance, according to Jeff Pu, an investment analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
In a research note with Hong Kong-based investment firm Haitong International Securities this week, Pu added that the A18 Pro chip will be equipped with a 6-core GPU, which would be equal to the A17 Pro chip in iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Generative AI</h2><br/>
iOS 18 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">rumored to include new generative AI features</a> for a range of iPhone features and apps, including Siri, Spotlight, Apple Music, Health, Messages, Numbers, Pages, Keynote, Shortcuts, and more. Apple has reportedly considered partnering with companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">such as Google, OpenAI, and Baidu</a> for at least some of these features.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 16 Pro models are rumored to feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> with "significantly" more cores, which could result in some of iOS 18's generative AI features being exclusive to those models. Pu previously said the larger die size would be related to the Neural Engine, which could power on-device generative AI features.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has used a 16-core Neural Engine since the iPhone 12 series. However, it has still improved the Neural Engine's performance over the years, even when core counts have not changed. For example, Apple says the A17 Pro chip has up to a 2x faster Neural Engine compared to the one in the iPhone 14 Pro's A16 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has promised to make generative AI announcements <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">later this year</a>. iOS 18 will be previewed at Apple's developers conference <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC</a> in June, so we're just a few months away from learning about the company's plans.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6-Core GPU</h2><br/>
With the A17 Pro chip, iPhone 15 Pro models have significantly improved graphics capabilities compared to previous models. Apple said the new 6-core GPU is up to 20% faster and also more power efficient than the 5-core GPU in the A16 Bionic chip. iPhone 15 Pro models also support hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for improved graphics rendering, which results in more realistic graphics in games.<br/>
<br/>
Pu believes Apple will stick with a 6-core GPU for the A18 Pro chip, so graphics improvements may be more limited for iPhone 16 Pro models this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wrap Up</h2><br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 series in September. For more details, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro roundups</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/iphone-16-pro-a18-pro-chip-details/">iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s A18 Pro Chip Rumored to Boost AI, Retain 6-Core GPU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-a18-pro-chip-rumored-to-boost-ai-retain-6-core-gpu.2422808/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Update Your iPhone Now: iOS 17.4.1 Includes These Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/update-your-iphone-now-ios-17-4-1-includes-these-security-fixes.2422792/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:36:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided details about the security fixes</a> included in last week's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-releases-ios-17-4-1/">iOS 17.4.1 and iPadOS 17.4.1 software updates</a> for the iPhone and iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.4.1-Includes-These-Security-Fixes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943212" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214097">support document</a>, Apple said the updates patch an image-related security vulnerability that "may lead to arbitrary code execution."<br/>
<br/>
The full details:<blockquote><strong>CoreMedia</strong><br/>
<br/>
Available for: iPhone XS and later, iPad Pro 12.9-inch 2nd generation and later, iPad Pro 10.5-inch, iPad Pro 11-inch 1st generation and later, iPad Air 3rd generation and later, iPad 6th generation and later, and iPad mini 5th generation and later<br/>
<br/>
Impact: Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution<br/>
<br/>
Description: An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation.<br/>
<br/>
CVE-2024-1580: Nick Galloway of Google Project Zero<br/>
<br/>
<strong>WebRTC</strong><br/>
<br/>
Available for: iPhone XS and later, iPad Pro 12.9-inch 2nd generation and later, iPad Pro 10.5-inch, iPad Pro 11-inch 1st generation and later, iPad Air 3rd generation and later, iPad 6th generation and later, and iPad mini 5th generation and later<br/>
<br/>
Impact: Processing an image may lead to arbitrary code execution<br/>
<br/>
Description: An out-of-bounds write issue was addressed with improved input validation.<br/>
<br/>
CVE-2024-1580: Nick Galloway of Google Project Zero</blockquote>To update your iPhone or iPad, open the Settings app and tap General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said it has patched the same vulnerability in <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT214096">macOS 14.4.1</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT214093">visionOS 1.1.1</a> as well.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/ios-17-4-1-security-fix-notes/">Update Your iPhone Now: iOS 17.4.1 Includes These Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/update-your-iphone-now-ios-17-4-1-includes-these-security-fixes.2422792/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Outlines &#039;Reasons to Upgrade&#039; Your iPhone on New Website</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-reasons-to-upgrade-your-iphone-on-new-website.2422789/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:53:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone/why-upgrade/">added a "Why Upgrade" section</a> to its website, which is aimed at encouraging customers with older iPhones to upgrade to a newer model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-reasons-to-upgrade.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943185" /><br/>
The website allows customers to compare the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 11, 11 Pro, 11 Pro Max, 12, 12 mini, 12 Pro, and 12 Pro Max to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, or &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
Each comparison shows what new features someone with an older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will get when upgrading to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup. With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, for example, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; offers 4x better photo resolution, more base storage, Action and Cinematic mode for video, USB-C, a 60 percent faster GPU, 5G, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The site highlights differences in display technology, design, sizing, connectivity, and more. Apple also provides details on the trade-in value of each older &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; so customers know what kind of discount they can get when trading a device in with the purchase of a new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
To further soften the costs of upgrading, Apple advertises <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> Monthly Installments and carrier deals that can drop the price of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; to &#36;0. Apple also details the ease of upgrading to a new device with features like Quick Start and eSIM.<br/>
<br/>
Much of the smartphone market in the United States is saturated, and there are few new customers for Apple. Upgraders are an important market segment, and Apple is continually seeking ways to get customers to regularly purchase new iPhones to maintain sales momentum.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-why-upgrade-site/">Apple Outlines &#039;Reasons to Upgrade&#039; Your iPhone on New Website</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-outlines-reasons-to-upgrade-your-iphone-on-new-website.2422789/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4.1 With Fix for USB Hub Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4-1-with-fix-for-usb-hub-bug.2422775/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 10:10:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4.1, a minor update for the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that launched last September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4.1 comes three weeks after &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The ‌‌‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌‌ 14.4‌.1 update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings. There's also a macOS 13.6.6 release for those who are still running macOS Ventura.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4.1 update fixes an issue that could cause USB hubs connected to external displays not to be recognized. It also addresses an issue that could cause apps with Java to quit unexpectedly, and it fixes an issue that could cause Audio Unit plug-ins for professional music apps not to open.<br/>
<br/>
All three of these bugs are notable issues that Mac users <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/">have been complaining about</a> since the launch of macOS 14.4. Oracle <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/16/oracle-warns-about-macos-14-4-java-issues/">warned users about the Java issue</a> last week, letting customers know that Apple silicon Mac users relying on Java should hold off on updating to macOS 14.4 if possible, and there were a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/">number of reports about problems</a> with hubs and monitors from customers who had installed 14.4. <blockquote>This update provides bug fixes for your Mac, including:<br/>
- USB hubs connected to external displays may not be recognized<br/>
- Copy protected Audio Unit plug-ins designed for professional music apps may not open or pass validation<br/>
- Apps that include Java may quit unexpectedly<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>More on all of the features that are included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">can be found in our dedicated roundup</a>. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4-1/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.4.1 With Fix for USB Hub Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4-1-with-fix-for-usb-hub-bug.2422775/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s New Sitewide Sale Has Record Low Prices on iPads and MacBooks, Plus &#36;50 Off PlayStation 5</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/best-buys-sale-ipads-playstation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-new-sitewide-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-ipads-and-macbooks-plus-50-off-playstation-5.2422771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 09:01:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/best-buys-sale-ipads-playstation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has kicked off the week with the introduction of a <a href="https://howl.me/clUjj1Kcba2">new sitewide sale</a> that includes big discounts on video game consoles, TVs, headphones, and Apple products. Specifically, you can find all-time low prices on the iPad Air and M2 MacBook Air during this event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/best-buy-new-image.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943156" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Video Games</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ps5-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943158" /><br/>
Sony's PlayStation 5 Slim console launched last November and Best Buy and other retailers have been hosting solid deals on the hardware for a few weeks now. At Best Buy, you can get the PS5 Slim (Disc Edition) Spider-Man 2 Bundle for <a href="https://howl.me/clUh1erQcL6"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a>, down from its launch price of &#36;499.99.<br/>
<br/>
The PS5 Slim (Digital Edition) Spider-Man 2 Bundle is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clUh0j2gc8v"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.99. Sony increased the price of the Digital Edition by &#36;50 at the launch of the new Slim consoles, so this deal effectively brings the price back down to the level of the original PS5 Digital Edition.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clUh1erQcL6"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>PS5 Slim Spider-Man 2 Bundle for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Both bundles also include the Spider-Man 2 game as a digital download, which is an extra value worth &#36;69.99 when not on sale. You can also find video game gift cards on sale at Best Buy this week, as well as Nintendo Switch consoles and games.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clUh0j2gc8v">PlayStation 5 Slim Console Digital Edition (Spider-Man 2 Bundle)</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;449.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clUh1erQcL6">PlayStation 5 Slim Console Disc Edition (Spider-Man 2 Bundle)</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clUh2IRVS3a">Gaming gift cards</a> - BOGO 15% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clUh7fsEqDX">Nintendo Switch consoles</a> - Get up to &#36;30 off Geek Squad refurbished devices</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clUh43zrxW5">Nintendo Switch games</a> - Get up to &#36;35 off popular titles</li></ul><h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-air-blue-new.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940259" /><br/>
Best Buy has every model of the 5th generation iPad Air on sale at an all-time low price right now, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;599.00. These are &#36;150 off across the board, and also include best-ever prices on both cellular models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940258" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for <a href="https://howl.me/clEafckZntZ"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> this week, down from &#36;499.00, and the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clHYsjeNRxs"><strong>&#36;549.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;649.00. Both of these are solid second-best prices on the iPad mini 6.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clEafckZntZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clHYsjeNRxs"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-macbook-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940257" /><br/>
Best Buy has both the 13-inch and 15-inch M2 MacBook Air models on sale at all-time low prices right now. The steepest discounts can be found on the larger display model, with the 256GB M2 15-inch MacBook Air priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. You can also get the 512GB M2 model on sale at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clUiqmQewga"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clUiqOThUJw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/best-buys-sale-ipads-playstation/">Best Buy&#039;s New Sitewide Sale Has Record Low Prices on iPads and MacBooks, Plus &#36;50 Off PlayStation 5</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-new-sitewide-sale-has-record-low-prices-on-ipads-and-macbooks-plus-50-off-playstation-5.2422771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple Pencil With Vision Pro Support in Testing Ahead of visionOS 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-pencil-visionon-support-in-testing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-with-vision-pro-support-in-testing-ahead-of-visionos-2.2422753/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 07:10:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-pencil-visionon-support-in-testing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the Apple Pencil is currently compatible with iPads only, a future version of the accessory may work with Apple's Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Vision-Pro-and-Apple-Pencil-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943128" /><br/>
Apple has internally tested a new Apple Pencil with visionOS support, according to a source familiar with the matter. This would allow the Apple Pencil to be used with drawing apps on the Vision Pro, such as Freeform and Pixelmator.<br/>
<br/>
No specific details are known about this project, but one possibility is that users would be able to draw with the Apple Pencil on a desk or another flat surface, and the drawing would appear in the open visionOS app. This would essentially turn a person's surroundings into a giant canvas, complete with pressure and tilt sensitivity.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">new Apple Pencil is rumored</a> to launch alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">new iPad Pro and iPad Air models in April</a>, but we have not confirmed if it will support visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Pencil compatibility with the Vision Pro would also require updated software, but it is unclear which version might add support. The first beta of visionOS 1.2 will likely be made available to developers as early as this week, and Apple is expected to announce visionOS 2 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June.<br/>
<br/>
As with any product that Apple develops, there is no guarantee that the company will move forward with releasing an Apple Pencil with visionOS support.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-pencil-visionon-support-in-testing/">New Apple Pencil With Vision Pro Support in Testing Ahead of visionOS 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-with-vision-pro-support-in-testing-ahead-of-visionos-2.2422753/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Pro Again Rumored to Feature Landscape Front-Facing Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/new-ipad-pro-to-feature-landscape-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-again-rumored-to-feature-landscape-front-facing-camera.2422746/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 05:43:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/new-ipad-pro-to-feature-landscape-camera/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> will feature a landscape-oriented front-facing camera for the first time, according to the Apple leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Pro-2024-Landscape-Camera-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-940262" /><br/>
Instant Digital reiterated the design change earlier today on Weibo with a simple accompanying 2D image. The post reveals that the entire TrueDepth camera array will move to the right side of the device, while the microphone will remain on the top and simply be centered.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, the front-facing camera of both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; resides on the top of the device, which means that the camera is positioned to the left when the device is being used in landscape, such as with a Magic Keyboard. Apple relocated the front-facing camera of the 10th-generation ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>‌ to the side of the device to provide a better experience in landscape and the company has not launched a new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; since then. <br/>
<br/>
In January, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ipad-pro-landscape-face-id-camera/">code discovered in iOS 17.4</a> suggested the next &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s TrueDepth camera array would be moved to the side of the device. "During ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>‌ setup, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; needs to be in landscape with the camera at the top of the screen," the code read. <br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Instant Digital suggested that the switch to a landscape front-facing camera could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">also be made on the next-generation iPad Air</a>. How Apple will achieve this switch to a landscape camera on the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models is unclear, since the second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> connects to both the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; using an inductive magnetic charger located where it seems the camera will need to move to. Both the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are expected to launch within weeks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/new-ipad-pro-to-feature-landscape-camera/">New iPad Pro Again Rumored to Feature Landscape Front-Facing Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-again-rumored-to-feature-landscape-front-facing-camera.2422746/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Opens Non-Compliance Investigations into Apple, Meta, and Google</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/eu-to-investigate-apple-dma-compliance/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-opens-non-compliance-investigations-into-apple-meta-and-google.2422739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 03:53:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/eu-to-investigate-apple-dma-compliance/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's compliance with new EU laws designed to rein in the market power of big tech companies is set to be investigated by regulators, the European Commission has <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/ip_24_1689">announced</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-EU-iOS-Changes.jpg" alt="" width="1312" height="738" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933094" /><br/>
The Commission said on Monday that non-compliance investigations have been opened against Apple, Google, and Meta, under the new <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/api/files/document/print/en/ip_24_1689/IP_24_1689_EN.pdf">Digital Markets Act (DMA)</a>. <br/>
<br/>
The probe into Apple will look at whether the company allows developers to "steer" users away from its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, as well as its default web browser choice screen. Google's rules on steering in Google Play and self-preferencing in Google searches are also being looked at, as is Meta's "pay or consent model."<br/>
<blockquote>The Commission has opened proceedings to assess whether the measures implemented by Alphabet and Apple in relation to their obligations pertaining to app stores are in breach of the DMA. Article 5(4) of the DMA requires gatekeepers to allow app developers to "steer" consumers to offers outside the gatekeepers' app stores, free of charge.<br/>
<br/>
The Commission is concerned that Alphabet's and Apple's measures may not be fully compliant as they impose various restrictions and limitations. These constrain, among other things, developers' ability to freely communicate and promote offers and directly conclude contracts, including by imposing various charges.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
The Commission has opened proceedings against Apple regarding their measures to comply with obligations to (i) enable end users to easily uninstall any software applications on iOS, (ii) easily change default settings on iOS and (iii) prompt users with choice screens which must effectively and easily allow them to select an alternative default service, such as a browser or search engine on their iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
The Commission is concerned that Apple's measures, including the design of the web browser choice screen, may be preventing users from truly exercising their choice of services within the Apple ecosystem, in contravention of Article 6(3) of the DMA.</blockquote>The Commission said it is also taking other investigatory steps to gather facts and information to clarify whether Apple's new fee structure and other terms and conditions for alternative app stores and distribution of apps from the web (sideloading) may be defeating the purpose of its obligations under the DMA.<br/>
<br/>
The Commission has also adopted five retention orders addressed to Alphabet, Amazon, Apple, Meta, and Microsoft, asking them to retain documents which might be used to assess their compliance with the DMA obligations. The Commission intends to conclude the proceedings opened today within 12 months. <br/>
<br/>
In cases of infringement, the Commission can impose fines up to 10% of the company's total worldwide turnover. Such fines can go up to 20% in case of repeated infringement under the DMA. The Commission also has the power to adopt "additional remedies" such as "obliging a gatekeeper to sell a business or parts of it," or banning the company from acquisitions of additional services related to the non-compliance.<br/>
<br/>
Apple earlier this month implemented several major changes to the way the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and apps operate in the EU in order to comply with the DMA. These changes are included in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">iOS 17.4</a>, but are generally limited to countries that are in the European Union.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/eu-to-investigate-apple-dma-compliance/">EU Opens Non-Compliance Investigations into Apple, Meta, and Google</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-opens-non-compliance-investigations-into-apple-meta-and-google.2422739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Readying In-Box iPhone Software Update System for Retail Stores</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-iphone-in-box-update-system-rollout/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-readying-in-box-iphone-software-update-system-for-retail-stores.2422738/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 03:42:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-iphone-in-box-update-system-rollout/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is set to roll out a new system that allows retail store staff to wirelessly update the software on iPhones prior to sale, without having to take them out of their packaging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Store-Vancouver-Canada.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901784" /><br/>
Writing in the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-24/how-strong-is-the-justice-department-case-against-apple-it-could-be-stronger-lu5ii64n">Power On newsletter</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said the new proprietary system, called "Presto," relies on MagSafe and other wireless technologies, and "looks a bit like a metal cubby for shoes." It will begin rolling out widely across the U.S. in April, with Apple's intention to have the technology in all U.S. retail stores by early summer, he added.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman first reported on the wireless system in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/retail-stores-to-update-iphones-with-new-system/">October</a>, describing it as a "proprietary pad-like device" on which retail store staff can place a sealed ‌iPhone‌ box. The system wirelessly turns on the iPhone inside, updates its software to the latest version available, and then powers it off. <br/>
<br/>
Apple developed "Presto" as a way to avoid selling iPhones in retail stores with outdated software. For example, the iPhone 15 series shipped with iOS 17, but Apple subsequently released iOS 17.0.1 before the devices launched. The point update was required to fix an issue that prevented the transfer of data directly from another iPhone during the initial setup process.<br/>
<br/>
That meant new iPhone 15 owners had to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/warning-update-your-iphone-15-to-ios-17-0-2/">update the devices themselves</a> as part of the setup process, or manually via the Settings app under General → Software Update if they opted to set up the device as new and transfer data later. Following the rollout of "Presto," such a scenario will be avoidable, making the setup process more straightforward for end users.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-iphone-in-box-update-system-rollout/">Apple Readying In-Box iPhone Software Update System for Retail Stores</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-readying-in-box-iphone-software-update-system-for-retail-stores.2422738/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sources: iOS 18 Lets Apps Be Placed Anywhere on Home Screen Grid</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sources-ios-18-lets-apps-be-placed-anywhere-on-home-screen-grid.2422709/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:33:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Home Screen</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will give iPhone users greater control over Home Screen app icon arrangement, according to sources familiar with the matter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPhone-Home-Screen-Gradient-Blank-Spaces-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943087" /><br/>
While app icons will likely remain locked to an invisible grid system on the Home Screen, to ensure there is some uniformity, our sources say that users will be able to arrange icons more freely on iOS 18. For example, we expect that the update will introduce the ability to create blank spaces, rows, and columns between app icons.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman was first to report that the iPhone would get a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/">"more customizable" Home Screen</a> starting with iOS 18. It is already possible to customize the Home Screen and create blank app icons with apps such as Shortcuts and Widgetsmith, but Apple's own personalization options will be more convenient and official.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone users have already been able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/customize-lock-screen-ios/">customize the Lock Screen</a> since iOS 16, and we expect the Home Screen to receive similar treatment with iOS 18. The update will introduce additional customization options for the Home Screen, according to our sources, and this could result in the biggest Home Screen revamp in several years.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hUFAhbm0Rbg" title="iOS 18 Will Be Apple&#39;s BIGGEST Update Yet" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Apple will announce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June. Other features and changes rumored for the update include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality</a> for Siri and multiple apps, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a> for improved messaging between iPhones and Android devices, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">design changes</a>, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/">Sources: iOS 18 Lets Apps Be Placed Anywhere on Home Screen Grid</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sources-ios-18-lets-apps-be-placed-anywhere-on-home-screen-grid.2422709/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to Feature &#039;More Customizable&#039; Home Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-feature-more-customizable-home-screen.2422676/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 07:10:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will feature a revamped Home Screen that is "more customizable," according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-24/how-strong-is-the-justice-department-case-against-apple-it-could-be-stronger-lu5ii64n"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. He revealed this information in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-03-24/how-strong-is-the-justice-department-case-against-apple-it-could-be-stronger-lu5ii64n"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, but he did not provide any specific details.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/hUFAhbm0Rbg" title="iOS 18 Will Be Apple&#39;s BIGGEST Update Yet" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Apple will announce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June. Other features and changes rumored for the software update include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI functionality</a> for Siri and multiple apps, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">RCS support in the Messages app</a> for improved messaging between iPhones and Android devices, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/ios-18-design-changes-rumors/">design changes</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 18, Gurman believes Apple will focus on new "AI tools that help manage your daily life" more than "ChatGPT-like generative AI features."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman reiterated that at least some Apple employees believe that iOS 18 will be the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/">biggest software update in the iPhone's history</a>.<br/>
<br/>
For more details about the update, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/ios-18-rumors-so-far/">latest rumor recap</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/">iOS 18 Rumored to Feature &#039;More Customizable&#039; Home Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-feature-more-customizable-home-screen.2422676/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro to Launch in China Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-later-this-year.2422670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 04:46:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today confirmed that the Vision Pro headset will go on sale in China later this year (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-vision-pro-hit-mainland-china-this-year-state-media-says-2024-03-24/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
Responding to a question from the press at the China Development Forum in Beijing, Cook confirmed that Apple's first spatial computer will launch in the country in 2024. He added that Apple will continue to increase research and development investment in China. Earlier this week, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/tim-cook-visits-shanghai/">Cook visited</a> Apple's new Jing'an store in Shanghai.<br/>
<br/>
This is the first explicit confirmation of a specific country other than the United States that the Vision Pro will launch in this year. Apple says that the Vision Pro will launch in additional countries later in 2024, but the company has not provided a more specific timeframe or, until now, indicated exactly where the headset will become available. Last month, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said he believed the Vision Pro would launch internationally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">before Apple's annual developers conference WWDC</a>, which typically takes place in the first week of June.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-this-year/">Apple Vision Pro to Launch in China Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-later-this-year.2422670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s First Store With Dedicated Pickup Station in Canada Now Open</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/relocated-apple-square-one-opens/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-store-with-dedicated-pickup-station-in-canada-now-open.2422633/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:40:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/relocated-apple-square-one-opens/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has a new home at Canada's second-largest indoor shopping mall. Following months of construction, the new Apple Square One retail store opened its doors today in Mississauga, Ontario, just west of Toronto. The store is now located above the Food Central food court on the second floor of the mall, across from Sephora.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Square-One-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942854" /><em>The new Apple Square One via <a href="https://twitter.com/theartistchair">Kyle</a></em></div><br/>
The store's first visitors were greeted with a round of applause from Apple's team members. <em>MacRumors</em> reader <a href="https://twitter.com/theartistchair/status/1771534704568623371">Kyle attended the grand opening</a> and shared photos with us, providing a first look at the curved glass facade and expansive interior.<br/>
<br/>
On the positive side, the new store is much larger than Apple's previous location in the mall, which was often overcrowded. The original store closed its doors for good on Thursday evening, after nearly 15 years of serving customers. Another plus is that the store is the first in Canada to offer a dedicated Apple Pickup station where customers can conveniently collect their online orders placed on Apple.com and in the Apple Store app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Pickup-Square-One.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942858" /><em>Apple Pickup in the new Apple Square One via <a href="https://twitter.com/theartistchair">Kyle</a></em></div><br/>
On the negative side, the store lacks some of Apple's latest retail design elements that were first introduced last year at the relocated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/apple-tysons-corner-store-now-open/">Apple Tysons Corner in Virginia</a> and all-new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/15/apple-battersea-opens-today/">Apple Battersea in London, England</a>, such as a Genius Bar with varied table and seating heights for improved accessibility, and an Apple Watch Studio for mixing and matching case and band combinations. Customers can still receive hardware support from a Genius at the store, and participate in free creative sessions through the <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/today/squareone/">Today at Apple program</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The new Apple Square One is the company's fourth modern store in Canada, alongside Apple Fairview and Apple Eaton Centre in Toronto, and Apple Pacific Centre in Vancouver. All of Apple's other stores in Canada have a classic design. A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/01/apple-store-update-plans/">leaked document last year</a> revealed that Apple has considered relocating its Sainte-Catherine store in Montréal, Québec as early as 2025, but the company has not publicly confirmed these plans.<br/>
<br/>
"Come say hello," says Apple, on the <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/retail/squareone/">Apple Square One page</a>. "We can't wait to see you there."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/relocated-apple-square-one-opens/">Apple&#039;s First Store With Dedicated Pickup Station in Canada Now Open</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-store-with-dedicated-pickup-station-in-canada-now-open.2422633/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock for Mac Hits Record Low &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/owcs-thunderbolt-dock-record-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-for-mac-hits-record-low-99-99-price-180-off.2422619/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 07:30:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/owcs-thunderbolt-dock-record-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC has again knocked the price of the popular <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock</a> down to &#36;99.99, from its original price of &#36;279.99. This is a match of the all-time low price on the accessory, which we last tracked earlier in March. Besides this dock, you'll find a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">large collection of accessories on sale</a> at this time on OWC, including USB-C hubs, external drives and enclosures, and internal memory upgrade kits for Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/owc-dock-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939882" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock, this accessory features two Thunderbolt 3 ports, five USB Type-A ports, one USB Type-C port, one Mini DisplayPort port, one gigabit Ethernet port, one S/PDIF digital audio output port, and one 3.5mm stereo audio input/output port. There are also two memory card slots for microSD and SD cards.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;180 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
All of the devices listed below are in new condition at OWC, although the retailer does provide various item condition options for anyone who might want to save money by purchasing open box items. Be sure to visit <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">OWC's sale landing page</a> to browse the full sale, which also features deals on cables, Mac accessories, keyboards, and headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDSDRDR%2F">Atlas Dual SD Card Reader</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T04C%2F">4TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T12C%2F">12TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;199.99, down from &#36;369.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T16C%2F">16TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T08C%2F">8TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;193.99, down from &#36;394.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T24C%2F">24TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;78.99, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;154.99, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;3.98, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/owcs-thunderbolt-dock-record-low/">OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock for Mac Hits Record Low &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-for-mac-hits-record-low-99-99-price-180-off.2422619/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 18&#039;s Generative AI Features to Rely on Google?, Latest on New iPads, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/top-stories-ios-18-ai-google-gemini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18s-generative-ai-features-to-rely-on-google-latest-on-new-ipads-and-more.2422617/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/top-stories-ios-18-ai-google-gemini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're getting closer to the launch of new iPad Pro and iPad Air models, while rumors about iOS 18 are continuing to ramp up with this week's surprise revelation that Apple has been talking to Google and others about potentially helping power the generative AI features expected to be a major part of this year's update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/combine_images.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942701" /><br/>
Other news this week saw the release of iOS 17.4.1 and iPadOS 17.4.1 updates with bug fixes, but we're still awaiting an update to address some of the problems introduced in macOS 14.4 earlier this month. We've also been continuing to keep our eye on the iPhone 16 lineup due in September and upcoming AirPods updates, so read on for details on all of these stories!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18: Apple in Talks With Google to Bring Gemini AI Features to iPhone</h2><br/>
Apple is in active discussions with Google to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">license some of its Gemini generative AI technology for the iPhone</a> starting as early as iOS 18 later this year, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. Apple has also been talking to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/">OpenAI</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">Baidu</a> about their generative AI models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/google-gemini.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941761" /><br/>
iOS 18 is widely rumored to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI features for Siri</a> and a range of built-in Apple apps on the iPhone, including Messages, Apple Music, Health, Shortcuts, Pages, Keynote, Numbers, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iPads Likely to Begin Shipping in April</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">new iPad Pro models with OLED displays will likely begin shipping to customers in April</a>, according to Ross Young, CEO of display industry research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
Young expects Apple to announce new iPads <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">in late March or early April</a>. Alongside the new iPad Pro models, he also expects an updated 10.9-inch iPad Air and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">first-ever 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> to be released.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases iOS 17.4.1 Update for iPhone</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-releases-ios-17-4-1/">released iOS 17.4.1 for the iPhone and iPadOS 17.4.1 for the iPad</a>. The minor software updates includes bug fixes and security improvements, such as a fix for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/ios-17-4-1-qr-code-scanning-bug/">QR code issue on the iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.4.1-Feature-Joe-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940545" /><br/>
We're still waiting on the first beta of iOS 17.5 to be released as of the time this newsletter was sent out. That update is expected to introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-announces-app-downloads-from-websites/">new Web Distribution option for qualifying iPhone apps in the EU</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Every iPhone 16 Rumor We've Covered So Far</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16 series is still months away from being unveiled, there are already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far/">many rumored features and changes</a> for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
We've recently updated our list of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far/">every iPhone 16 rumor that we have covered so far</a>, so be sure to check it out for the latest expectations. One recent rumor is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/iphone-16-ultra-thin-bezels-rumor/">even thinner bezels</a> for the iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 16 series in September.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>macOS Sonoma 14.4: Reasons Not to Update</h2><br/>
Since Apple unveiled macOS Sonoma 14.4 earlier this month, the transition to the latest software update has not been entirely smooth for everyone, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/do-not-update-macos-sonoma-14-4/">number of issues have been reported by users</a> that significantly impact their daily workflow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Reasons-to-Not-Upgrade-to-macOS-Sonoma-14.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941874" /><br/>
If you anticipate that any of these problems could significantly impact your daily operations or productivity, it may be prudent to delay updating to the latest version of macOS Sonoma until Apple addresses these concerns with a subsequent fix. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: Apple's Four Upcoming AirPods Models</h2><br/>
On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/the-macrumors-show-four-new-airpods/">latest episode of <em>The MacRumors Show</em> podcast</a>, our hosts Hartley Charlton and Dan Barbera discussed circulating rumors on four upcoming models of AirPods, including two variants of fourth-generation AirPods, a very minor refresh of the AirPods Max, and next-generation AirPods Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/The-MacRumors-Show-FOUR-New-AirPods-Models-Coming-Soon-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942663" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/15/the-macrumors-show-new-ipad-air-upgrade/">Last week's episode</a> saw Dan and Harley discussing whether the next-generation iPad Air models will be a big enough upgrade for customers. Apple is expected to release a larger 12.9-inch iPad Air, but no major design changes are expected for the mid-range tablet. Key new features expected include the M2 chip and a landscape front camera.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/mar-21-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/23/top-stories-ios-18-ai-google-gemini/">Top Stories: iOS 18&#039;s Generative AI Features to Rely on Google?, Latest on New iPads, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-18s-generative-ai-features-to-rely-on-google-latest-on-new-ipads-and-more.2422617/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Two Weeks With the M3 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/m3-macbook-air-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-m3-macbook-air.2422577/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:16:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/m3-macbook-air-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The latest 13-inch and 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models have been available for two weeks now, and <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera has been using the 15-inch version since it launched. Over on our YouTube channel, Dan shared a review now that he's been able to spend some quality time with the machine.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="The Honest Truth About Apple's M3 MacBook Air" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YYAzLxLuMjg" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is a perfect all-around laptop, and the Air models are what we recommend for most people. In fact, the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is more machine than the average consumer likely even needs. For web browsing, sending emails, and other simple tasks, a more affordable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is more than enough, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/15/best-buy-macbook-air-all-time-low/">M1 MacBook Air is even available</a> at a super low &#36;650 price right now.<br/>
<br/>
For photo editing, video editing, and tasks that require a little more power, even the base model M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with 8GB Unified Memory is more than enough for many people. Upgrading the memory will give you a bit more leeway in terms of future proofing, and adding more storage is a good idea if you need space for file storage, games, and apps.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, the M3 has faster CPU and GPU speeds, hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading for 3D rendering and games, Wi-Fi 6E support, and support for two displays in clamshell mode. If you need these options, or don't mind shelling out a bit more money for a machine that will last longer, it's worth getting the M3, but we also think the more affordable &zwnj;M1&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are perfectly great for many people.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/m3-macbook-air-review/">Review: Two Weeks With the M3 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-m3-macbook-air.2422577/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Drops Plans to Develop MicroLED Displays for Apple Watch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-plans-to-develop-microled-displays-for-apple-watch.2422569/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:38:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has ended a project to develop microLED displays in-house, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-22/apple-scraps-plan-to-design-display-for-watch-in-house-cuts-jobs">according to <em>Bloomberg</a></em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></a> in a reversal of his prior reporting on the development of the technology. Apple invested billions in developing microLED displays, with plans to first add microLED to the Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-ultra-2-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939712" /><br/>
MicroLED was too expensive and too complex for Apple to design, so Apple is now reorganizing its display engineering teams and laying off employees in the U.S. and Asia. Some of the displaced employees may be able to find other roles in the company, and others will be provided with severance.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors that Apple had canceled plans for an Apple Watch with microLED <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">first surfaced in February</a> when supplier ams OSRAM said that a "cornerstone project" related to microLED had been canceled. Soon after, there were rumors that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/microled-apple-watch-potential-supplier-lost/">ended its relationship</a> with Kulicke &amp; Soffa, another company in the advanced display market.<br/>
<br/>
Both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/">analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> and <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/blog/apple-cancels-microled-project">Display Supply Chain Consultants</a> confirmed that Apple had canceled work on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a> after these rumors, but Gurman claimed that Apple was still working on the device. In <a href="http://webcache.googleusercontent.com/search?client=safari&rls=en&q=cache%3Ahttps%3A%2F%2Ftwitter.com%2Fmarkgurman%2Fstatus%2F1763297383046365515&ie=UTF-8&oe=UTF-8">a now-deleted tweet</a>, Gurman said that ams OSRAM was "one supplier" on the project, and that there were several other suppliers Apple was working with. "I doubt it was canceled," he wrote. <br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a></em> and <em>ETNews</em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-still-dedicated-microled-apple-watch-ultra/">also suggested</a> that ams OSRAM was replaced due to a performance drop and that Apple had another supplier lined up, but it appears that information was incorrect.<br/>
<br/>
MicroLED technology uses microscopic LEDs for individual pixels. It's more energy efficient than traditional LED, offers improved contrast, and has faster response times. Colors are brighter and better, and there's no risk of burn-in as there is with OLED. Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/">said to have abandoned the project</a> because it was not economically viable.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman claims that Apple will stick with OLED display technology for the Apple Watch "for now," but that the company is "eyeing microLED for other projects down the road." Apple is "identifying" potential new suppliers and processes for microLED, but it "won't likely happen anytime soon."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-ends-microled-apple-watch-development/">Apple Drops Plans to Develop MicroLED Displays for Apple Watch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-drops-plans-to-develop-microled-displays-for-apple-watch.2422569/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;95 Off Apple&#039;s New 15-Inch M3 MacBook Air, Available for &#36;1,204</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/low-price-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-95-off-apples-new-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-available-for-1-204.2422565/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 10:14:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/low-price-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon has further discounted Apple's brand new 15-inch M3 MacBook Air, now reaching &#36;95 off the original price. Only one model is on sale: the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air in Starlight is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX251F4X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,204.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/m3-macbook-air-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940237" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is the best price we've seen to date on the 15-inch M3 MacBook Air, and it beats the previous record low price seen on Amazon by about &#36;30. Amazon provides an estimated delivery date of Monday, March 25 for the fastest option and Wednesday, March 27 for free delivery.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX251F4X%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;95 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,204.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This version of the 15-inch MacBook Air just launched earlier in the month, alongside updated models of the 13-inch size as well. Both of the new MacBook Air machines include the M3 chip and focus on internal upgrades. Apple did not change the design of the MacBook Air with the 2024 update, using the same design that was first introduced in 2022. <br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/low-price-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-2/">Amazon Takes &#36;95 Off Apple&#039;s New 15-Inch M3 MacBook Air, Available for &#36;1,204</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-95-off-apples-new-15-inch-m3-macbook-air-available-for-1-204.2422565/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Steve Jobs Signed Business Card Fetches Over &#36;180,000 at Auction</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/steve-jobs-signed-business-card-auction/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steve-jobs-signed-business-card-fetches-over-180-000-at-auction.2422557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:23:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/steve-jobs-signed-business-card-auction/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Steve Jobs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A rare Apple Computer business card signed by Steve Jobs recently <a href="https://www.rrauction.com/auctions/lot-detail/348281006903082-steve-jobs-signed-apple-business-card-c-1983-psa-gem-mt-10/">sold for &#36;181,183 at auction</a>, according to Boston-based RR Auction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Steve-Jobs-Business-Card.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942677" /><br/>
The business card is from 1983, and it has been authenticated by well-known memorabilia grading service PSA, according to the auction listing. It features Apple's old six-color logo, and it lists the company's former address of 10495 Bandley Drive, in Cupertino, California. Jobs is listed as the Chairman of Apple's Board of Directors.<br/>
<br/>
RR Auction believes this sale has set a new record-high price for a signed business card.<br/>
<br/>
Jobs passed away in 2011 at the age of 56. Throughout his career, he was reluctant to sign autographs, so items with his signature on them often sell for large sums of money. Last year, for example, a check signed by Jobs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/11/steve-jobs-check-100k-auction/">sold for over &#36;100,000 at auction</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steve-jobs/">Steve Jobs</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/steve-jobs-signed-business-card-auction/">Steve Jobs Signed Business Card Fetches Over &#36;180,000 at Auction</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/steve-jobs-signed-business-card-fetches-over-180-000-at-auction.2422557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
