<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 04:04:11 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Introduces Tags, or Hashtags Without the Hash Symbol</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/threads-introduces-tags-or-hashtags/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-introduces-tags-or hashtags-without-the-hash-symbol.2413154/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 04:03:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/threads-introduces-tags-or-hashtags/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.threads.net/login">Threads</a> social network from Meta is <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mosseri/post/C0j585AvsJq">rolling out tags</a>, which work like hashtags on other platforms but include some unique additional functions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/tags-in-threads.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925647" /><br/>
The Threads compose window includes a new # button to add a tag to your post. Unlike hashtags, a tag can be a word or a phrase (with spaces) and does not include the hash symbol, so tags fit into sentences more naturally. Tags can also use special characters.<br/>
<br/>
Typing your tag performs a real-time search of existing tags that you can choose to use, or you can create your own tag. But users can tag only one topic per post to avoid tag spam. Users can click on a tag in a post to open all the posts in the search view.<br/>
<br/>
Tagging a post makes it more easily discoverable in searches of the topic, although all mentions of the used keywords show up in the same search screen, whether or not the posts they are included in have also been tagged. <br/>
<br/>
Currently there is no way to order searches chronologically, and Threads still lacks a trending section. Meta intends to launch Threads in the European Union <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/threads-to-launch-eu-in-december/">this month</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/threads-introduces-tags-or-hashtags/">Threads Introduces Tags, or Hashtags Without the Hash Symbol</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-introduces-tags-or hashtags-without-the-hash-symbol.2413154/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Max Announced Three Years Ago Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago-today.2413149/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 03:06:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> were announced three years ago today, marking the company's first push into the high-end over-ear headphones market under its own brand name. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/AirPods-Max-3-Years-Feature-1-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-925250" /><br/>
Rumors about Apple's work on a pair of high-end headphones, at the time believed to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/05/09/apple-over-ear-headphones-airpods-studio/">called the "AirPods Studio,</a>" heated up throughout 2020. They were announced abruptly via an unexpected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/airpods-max/">press release</a> on December 8, 2020 and went on sale the same day. Orders started arriving to customers one week later on Tuesday, December 15.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; offer many popular AirPods features such as the H1 chip, easy pairing, Active Noise Cancellation, Transparency, automatic switching, Spatial Audio with dynamic head tracking, but in a premium over-ear design for the first time. They also offer a headband made of a flexible mesh canopy, replaceable magnetic earcups, a Digital Crown for volume control, a button for switching between ANC and Transparency, and a Smart Case for storage and to put the headphones into a low power state.<br/>
<br/>
Demand for the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; was high immediately after launch, with shipping estimates that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/airpods-max-shipping-estimates/">stretched out several months</a>. Initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/10/airpods-max-unboxing-videos/">reviews of AirPods Max were favorable</a>, applauding the headphones for being "more than enough to compete with other high-end headphones." While the recommended retail price remains at &#36;549, the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are often <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#airpods">available with discounts</a> of over &#36;100.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; have also been subject to criticism since their launch, including for their price <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-max-vs-sony-wh-1000xm4-and-bose-nc-700/">relative to rival sets</a> of high-end over-ear headphones, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/28/third-party-airpods-max-solutions/">design of the Smart Case</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/07/airpods-max-owners-ear-cup-condensation/">condensation</a> inside the earcups, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/19/airpods-max-excessive-battery-drain/">poor battery life</a> (something that was later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/12/airpods-max-battery-drain-firmware-fix/">fixed via a software update</a>), and ANC strength being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/25/airpods-max-anc-performance-reduced/">reduced over time</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While the ‌&zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;‌ are now three years old, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/">next-generation</a> may only introduce a small number of upgrades consisting of a USB-C port, Bluetooth 5.3, and new color options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago/">AirPods Max Announced Three Years Ago Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago-today.2413149/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Podcasts App Arriving on Tesla Vehicles Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-podcasts-app-arriving-on-tesla/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-podcasts-app-arriving-on-tesla-vehicles-next-week.2413148/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:58:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-podcasts-app-arriving-on-tesla/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Tesla</category>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> app is set to arrive on Tesla vehicles with the company's 2023 Holiday Update that rolls out next week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Podcasts-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-798617" /><br/>
Tesla Model S, 3, X, Y, and Cybertruck owners in almost 50 countries and regions will receive the app via a free, over-the-air software update. A Premium Connectivity subscription is required to stream &zwnj;Apple Podcasts&zwnj; over a cellular connection.<br/>
<br/>
Following the update, users will see the &zwnj;Apple Podcasts&zwnj; app in the Tesla's App Launcher. It can be opened on top of the map or dragged to the My Apps dock at the bottom where it will remained pinned. When opening the &zwnj;Apple Podcasts&zwnj; app for the first time, users must use their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to scan an on-screen QR code to open a corresponding webpage and sign-in using their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Podcasts&zwnj; app for Tesla vehicles features the Listen Now tab, Up Next queue, Latest Episodes, Recently Played episodes, Browse tab, Top Shows, and Top Episodes, just like its counterparts on Apple devices. It also contains a user's entire podcasts library, enabling users to see the shows they follow, saved episodes, and the latest episodes from shows they follow.<br/>
<br/>
Playback is synced across devices so, when the driver arrives at their destination, they can continue listening from where they left off on another Apple device. &zwnj;Apple Podcasts&zwnj; is also directly integrated into Tesla's search experience, allowing users to search for specific shows, people, and topics and browse relevant results.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tesla/">Tesla</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-podcasts-app-arriving-on-tesla/">Apple Podcasts App Arriving on Tesla Vehicles Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-podcasts-app-arriving-on-tesla-vehicles-next-week.2413148/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Launch New Low-Cost iPad in Second Half of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-launch-low-cost-ipad-second-half-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-new-low-cost-ipad-in-second-half-of-2024.2413146/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 02:36:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-launch-low-cost-ipad-second-half-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will release a new entry-level <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in the second half of next year, according to a Taiwanese report on Apple's product development resource allocation plans. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ipad-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916839" /><br/>
<em><a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Spotlight/Supply-Chain/Apple-to-move-key-iPad-engineering-resources-to-Vietnam">Nikkei Asia</a></em> reports that Apple is working with China's BYD, a key &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; assembler, to move new product introduction (NPI) resources to Vietnam. NPI refers to when Apple works with suppliers on the design and development of new products to ensure they can be made properly in a new manufacturing plant. Apple has not moved NPI resources to Vietnam for such a core device before.<br/>
<br/>
Engineering verification for test production of the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; model will start around mid-February next year, according to the report's sources. The entry-level model, likely to be an 11th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, will then become available in the second half of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Starting at &#36;449, the "&zwnj;iPad&zwnj;" is Apple's low-priced mainstream &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, last updated in October 2022 with a complete redesign, larger display, USB-C port, A14 Bionic chip, 12-megapixel camera, and more. <br/>
<br/>
Apple was thought to be working on a new version of the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and the 11th-generation model is expected in 2024, but a more specific timeframe for its launch has not been rumored. There are no rumors about new features coming in the 11th generation model, but it is likely to get an updated processor and possibly camera upgrades.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's relocated &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; production to Vietnam follows a trend of Apple diversifying its supply chain and reducing its reliance on China as a major production hub with decades of experience in hardware manufacturing. Apple is also sending some NPI resources for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to India. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/apple-launch-low-cost-ipad-second-half-2024/">Apple to Launch New Low-Cost iPad in Second Half of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-launch-new-low-cost-ipad-in-second-half-of-2024.2413146/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 184 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-184/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-184-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2413117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 14:21:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-184/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 184 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, CSS, HTMK, JavaScript, Media, Web Animations, Web API, Web Assembly, Web Inspector, and WebGL.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Ventura and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of macOS that Apple released in September 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-184/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 184 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-184-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2413117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Former Apple Lawyer Gene Levoff Avoids Prison After Insider Trading Conviction</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/former-apple-lawyer-insider-trading-no-prison/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/former-apple-lawyer-gene-levoff-avoids-prison-after-insider-trading-conviction.2413116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 13:53:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/former-apple-lawyer-insider-trading-no-prison/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Former Apple director of corporate law Gene Levoff was today sentenced to a fine and four years of probation for insider trading, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-07/apple-s-ex-corporate-law-chief-avoids-prison-for-insider-trading">Bloomberg</a></em>. Levoff was facing up to two years in prison, but he will avoid time behind bars.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/apple-logo-cash-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1430" height="805" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-767473" /><br/>
Levoff's role at Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/02/13/apples-gene-levoff-charged-insider-trading/">was supposed to include</a> ensuring that Apple employees were compliant with the company's insider trading policies, including enforcement of "blackout periods" around Apple's earnings reports, but he ended up committing the crime he was meant to police.<br/>
<br/>
Due to his position, Levoff was given access to Apple's earnings results before they were made available to the public, and he used the information to buy Apple shares prior to better-than-expected results, and sell shares when there were weaker-than-expected earnings. Levoff earned around &#36;277,000, and avoided losses of around &#36;377,000 before he was fired by Apple in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Levoff last June <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/01/former-apple-lawyer-pleads-guilty-insider-trading/">pleaded guilty</a> to six counts of securities fraud for insider trading, and his sentencing took place today. In addition to four years probation, Levoff will pay approximately &#36;604,000.<br/>
<br/>
Federal prosecutors argued that Levoff should be sent to prison for insider trading to deter other corporate executives from committing a similar crime, but the judge overseeing the case said that he didn't feel it was necessary because Levoff lost his job and will no longer be able to practice law.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/former-apple-lawyer-insider-trading-no-prison/">Former Apple Lawyer Gene Levoff Avoids Prison After Insider Trading Conviction</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/former-apple-lawyer-gene-levoff-avoids-prison-after-insider-trading-conviction.2413116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Two Months With the iPhone 15 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/iphone-15-pro-max-two-month-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-months-with-the-iphone-15-pro-max.2413103/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 12:04:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/iphone-15-pro-max-two-month-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup came out in September, and while most reviews are done shortly after a new device launches, we like to follow up with a longer term review that gives us an opportunity to provide a deeper dive into what it's like using these phones on a day to day basis for months.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height=315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/drJNofd3gtk" title="iPhone 15 Pro Max Long Term Review: Still Worth It 2 Months Later?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera has been using his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max without a case to test durability, and the titanium frame has been holding up much better than stainless steel. Even after some minor drops, there are no scratches or scuffs to speak of.<br/>
<br/>
There were reports of overheating early on with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, but Apple has addressed this in software updates. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; stays cool to the touch for the most part, even when playing games. It can heat up when charging at random times, but it's not a consistent issue.<br/>
<br/>
Battery life is about on par with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro Max battery life, and there doesn't seem to be much of an improvement.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, Apple added an Action Button, and , well, it's not getting much use. It's hard to get in the habit of using a new button for things that we've done for years using other workflows.<br/>
<br/>
As for the camera, the best feature by far is the automatic portrait mode that lets you adjust focus after an image is captured without having to turn on Portrait mode. It's fun to use, and you can tap on each subject in the photo to change the focus from the foreground to the background. The 5x Telephoto lens is also a useful addition.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch our full video for more thoughts on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, and let us know how it's performed for you over the last two months if you have one.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/iphone-15-pro-max-two-month-review/">Review: Two Months With the iPhone 15 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-months-with-the-iphone-15-pro-max.2413103/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Developers Will Soon Get 25 Monthly Hours of Xcode Cloud With Apple Developer Program</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-developer-program-xcode-cloud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-will-soon-get-25-monthly-hours-of-xcode-cloud-with-apple-developer-program.2413101/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:41:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-developer-program-xcode-cloud/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Xcode</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=ik9z4ll6">today announced</a> that starting in January 2024, all Apple Developer Program memberships will include 25 compute hours of Xcode Cloud at no additional cost on top of the Developer membership fee.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Xcode-Cloud-icon.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848670" /><br/>
<a href="https://developer.apple.com/xcode-cloud/get-started/">Xcode Cloud</a> is designed to provide cloud-based tools to developers for building apps, running automated tests, providing apps to testers, and managing user feedback. It was introduced in 2021, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/07/xcode-cloud-now-available-to-all-apple-developers/">made available to all developers</a> in June 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Since launch, Apple has given developers access to 25 hours of Xcode Cloud per month at no cost, but that was scheduled to end this month. Apple has now decided to continue offering the free compute hours as part of its Developer Program membership.<br/>
<blockquote>We're pleased to announce that as of January 2024, all Apple Developer Program memberships will include 25 compute hours per month on Xcode Cloud as a standard, with no additional cost. If you're already subscribed to Xcode Cloud for free, no additional action is required on your part. And if you haven't tried Xcode Cloud yet, now is the perfect time to start building your app for free in just a few minutes.</blockquote><br/>
Apple initially planned to charge &#36;15 per month for 25 hours, but that tier will be free. 100 compute hours is priced at &#36;50 per month, 250 hours is priced at &#36;100 per month, and 1,000 hours is priced at &#36;400 per month.<br/>
<br/>
Each compute hour is an hour of time used to execute a task in the cloud, such as building an app or running tests. Compute hour usage is tracked through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> connect and the Apple Developer app.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/xcode/">Xcode</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-developer-program-xcode-cloud/">Developers Will Soon Get 25 Monthly Hours of Xcode Cloud With Apple Developer Program</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-will-soon-get-25-monthly-hours-of-xcode-cloud-with-apple-developer-program.2413101/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Outage Affecting Some Users [Update: Resolved]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-pay-outage-affecting-some-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-outage-affecting-some-users-update-resolved.2413099/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 11:34:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-pay-outage-affecting-some-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> and Wallet outage that is causing some users to experience issues with &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; web payments and in-app payments using &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/01/apple-pay-mac-website.jpg" alt="Mac Apple Pay" width="1694" height="1022" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-726024" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's System Status page</a>, the outage began at 5:04 a.m. Eastern Time, and it is ongoing. Apple says that only "some users" are having problems, but there are multiple tweets about the payment issues.<br/>
<br/>
Note that this is not affecting payments that are made using &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; in retail stores, with those &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; purchases working fine. Apple does say that some users could experience issues managing, purchasing, or topping-up transit cards. <br/>
<br/>
There is no word yet on when the &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; outage might be resolved, but we'll update this article when Apple says that the &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; issues have been addressed.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update</b>: Apple's status page has been updated to indicate the issue has been resolved.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-pay-outage-affecting-some-users/">Apple Pay Outage Affecting Some Users [Update: Resolved]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-outage-affecting-some-users-update-resolved.2413099/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Adds NameDrop-Like Feature for Sharing Boarding Passes, Movie Tickets, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/ios-17-namedrop-like-wallet-passes-sharing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-adds-namedrop-like-feature-for-sharing-boarding-passes-movie-tickets-and-more.2413092/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:30:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/ios-17-namedrop-like-wallet-passes-sharing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with the upcoming iOS 17.2 software update, there is a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-share-contact-details-with-namedrop/">NameDrop</a>-like feature that allows an iPhone user to quickly share boarding passes, movie tickets, and other Wallet app passes with another iPhone user.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/AirDrop-1Pass-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925564" /><br/>
To use the feature, open the Wallet app and tap on the pass that you want to share. Then, hold your iPhone near the top of another iPhone, and a "Share" button will appear below the pass on your iPhone. Finally, tap on the "Share" button to send the pass to the other iPhone via AirDrop. Both iPhones must be updated to iOS 17.2.<br/>
<br/>
While it is already possible to share many Wallet app passes via AirDrop, Messages, Mail, and more through the iOS sharing menu, this new feature aims to provide a quicker and more convenient method. It works similarly to NameDrop, an iOS 17 feature that lets users quickly share contact information by bringing two iPhones together.<br/>
<br/>
The feature is mentioned in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/ios-17-2-release-notes/">iOS 17.2 release notes</a>: "AirDrop improvements including expanded contact sharing options and the ability to share boarding passes, movie tickets, and other eligible passes by bringing two iPhones together." The software update is in the final stage of beta testing and should be released next week.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">many other new features and changes</a>, including a Journal app, spatial video recording on iPhone 15 Pro models, several improvements to the Messages and Weather apps, a Favorite Songs playlist in Apple Music, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/ios-17-namedrop-like-wallet-passes-sharing/">iOS 17.2 Adds NameDrop-Like Feature for Sharing Boarding Passes, Movie Tickets, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-adds-namedrop-like-feature-for-sharing-boarding-passes-movie-tickets-and-more.2413092/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second macOS Sonoma 14.2 Release Candidate to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-rc-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sonoma-14-2-release-candidate-to-developers.2413090/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 10:10:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-rc-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a second release candidate (RC) version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming few days after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-rc-to-developers/">first RC</a>. The second RC has a build number of 23C64, up from 23C63 for the first RC.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the Sonoma Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The release candidate version of &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 represents the finalized version of the softwae that will be released to the public should no major issues be found.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds support for enhanced AutoFill for PDFs, along with Contact Key Verification for Messages, a sticker tapback option, new Weather widgets, and more. Apple's release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote>This update introduces enhanced Autofill for PDFs and improvements to Messages and Weather. This release also includes other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
PDFs<br/>
- Enhanced AutoFill identifies fields in PDFs and other forms enabling you to populate them with information such as names and addresses from your contacts<br/>
<br/>
Messages<br/>
- Catch-up arrow lets you easily jump to your first unread message in a conversation by clicking the arrow visible in the top-right corner<br/>
- Add sticker option in the context menu lets you add a sticker directly to a bubble<br/>
- Contact Key Verification provides automatic alerts and Contact Verification Codes to help verify people facing extraordinary digital threats are messaging only with the people they intend<br/>
<br/>
Weather<br/>
- Precipitation amounts help you stay on top of rain and snow conditions for a given day over the next 10 days<br/>
- New widgets let you choose from next-hour precipitation, daily forecast, sunrise and sunset times, and current conditions such as Air Quality, Feels Like, and wind speed<br/>
- Wind map snapshot helps you quickly assess wind patterns and access the animated wind map overlay to prepare for forecasted wind conditions for the next 24 hours<br/>
<br/>
Clock<br/>
- Multiple timers let you run several timers simultaneously and create a name for each timer<br/>
- Timer presets help you quickly start a timer with a range of preset options<br/>
- Recents makes it easy to restart your recently used timers<br/>
<br/>
This update also includes the following new features:<br/>
- Favorite Songs Playlist in Apple Music lets you quickly get back to the songs you mark as favorites<br/>
- Use Listening History in Apple Music can be disabled in a Focus so music you listen to does not appear in Recently Played or influence your recommendations<br/>
- Shazam Music Recognition allows you to quickly identify songs playing online or around you, even when wearing AirPods<br/>
- New keyboard layouts provide support for 7 additional Sámi languages<br/>
- Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote><br/>
Apple is expected to release &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-rc-2/">Apple Seeds Second macOS Sonoma 14.2 Release Candidate to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sonoma-14-2-release-candidate-to-developers.2413090/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes iCloud&#039;s Advanced End-to-End Encryption Feature as Data Breaches Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-promotes-advanced-data-protection/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-iclouds-advanced-end-to-end-encryption-feature-as-data-breaches-increase.2413079/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-promotes-advanced-data-protection/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Advanced Data Protection</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/12/report-2-point-6-billion-records-compromised-by-data-breaches-in-past-two-years/">shared a study</a> conducted by MIT professor Dr. Stuart Madnick that found 2.6 billion personal records were compromised by data breaches in the past two years. The study was commissioned by Apple, but the cover page says that the "conclusions and opinions expressed are exclusively those of the author."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-Advanced-Data-Protection_screen-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876840" /><br/>
Apple provided an overview of the study in its press release:<blockquote>The report illustrates that the historic threats to user data that saw the number of data breaches nearly triple between 2013 and 2022, compromising 2.6 billion records over the course of two years, are only getting worse in 2023. In the U.S. alone, there were nearly 20 percent more breaches in just the first nine months of 2023 than in any prior year. The target for cybercriminals was very clear, with a 2023 survey finding that over 80 percent of breaches involved data stored in the cloud. This is after attacks targeting cloud infrastructure nearly doubled from 2021 to 2022.</blockquote>Additional details can be found in the study: "<a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/pdfs/The-Continued-Threat-to-Personal-Data-Key-Factors-Behind-the-2023-Increase.pdf">The Continued Threat to Personal Data: Key Factors Behind the 2023 Increase.</a>"<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the study's findings emphasize the need for end-to-end encryption, which iCloud already provides for 14 data categories by default. For users looking for additional protection, Apple offers an optional feature called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/ios-16-3-advanced-data-protection-global/">Advanced Data Protection</a>, which increases the number of iCloud data categories covered by end-to-end encryption to 23, including iCloud Backup, Notes, Photos, Voice Memos, and more.<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud/">How to Enable End-to-End Encryption for iCloud Backups</a></li></ul>"Bad actors continue to pour enormous amounts of time and resources into finding more creative and effective ways to steal consumer data, and we won't rest in our efforts to stop them," said Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/advanced-data-protection/">Advanced Data Protection</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-promotes-advanced-data-protection/">Apple Promotes iCloud&#039;s Advanced End-to-End Encryption Feature as Data Breaches Increase</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-iclouds-advanced-end-to-end-encryption-feature-as-data-breaches-increase.2413079/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Begins Countdown to Christmas Sale With Up to 50% Off Popular Charging Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/anker-countdown-to-christmas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-begins-countdown-to-christmas-sale-with-up-to-50-off-popular-charging-accessories.2413078/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 07:55:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/anker-countdown-to-christmas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker has launched its <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fchristmas-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1">newest holiday sale</a>, this one offering a special deal every day in the lead-up to Christmas. These sales offer up to 50 percent off select products, and include discounts on USB-C chargers, portable batteries, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-new-gold.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922736" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Today's exclusive offer is a free gift on orders worth &#36;99 or more. This one will expire later tonight and be replaced by an unknown sale tomorrow, so be sure to shop soon if you want a free gift added to your order. Additionally, Anker is offering exclusive holiday packaging on the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fcelebrate-the-holidays-with-anker-737-power-bank-powercore-24k%3Fvariant%3D42923622531222%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> and the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fanker-622-magnetic-battery-maggo-perfect-for-the-holiday-season%3Fvariant%3D42923622957206%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">MagGo Portable Battery</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the deals on Anker.com, we're also tracking a few <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F2A25B7A1-3EFE-419E-B3A6-3BD8FF119DAD%3Fingress%3D2%26visitId%3D0c5bd76b-6428-4b95-b3fa-6509a0cd9c50%26ref_%3Dast_bln">discounts for Anker accessories on Amazon</a>. These include wall chargers, cables, and the new <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Foldable-Connector-Portable-Charger%2Fdp%2FB0C6XLMQNZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Connector</a> for iPhone 15 devices at &#36;20.99, down from &#36;29.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fchristmas-sale%3Fref%3DmasterBanner1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 50% OFF</div>Anker's Countdown to Christmas Sale</div></a></div><h2>Portable Batteries</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Foldable-Connector-Portable-Charger%2Fdp%2FB0C6XLMQNZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;20.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1259-built-in-cable-power-bank-10000mah%3Fvariant%3D42733233766550%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;40.00, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa1335-130w-power-bank%3Fvariant%3D42691850797206%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">Prime 12,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;72.00, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1336-20000mah-power-bank?variant=42691854925974&amp;ref=christmas-sale">Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;104.00, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Portable-Generator-UltraFast-Optional%2Fdp%2FB0C5C89QKZ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;649.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Wireless Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fy1811%3Fvariant%3D42206465327254%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">3-in-1 Cube with MagSafe</a> - &#36;142.46, down from &#36;149.95</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Wall Chargers</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2637%3Fvariant%3D42621670490262%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">Nano Pro USB-C Wall Charger</a> - &#36;11.90, down from &#36;13.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2669-3-port-wall-charger%3Fvariant%3D42691852435606%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">67W 3-Port GaN Wall Charger</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2343-100w-usb-c-charger%3Fvariant%3D42691851911318%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">100W 3-Port GaN Wall Charger</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;84.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Docks</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa2342-240w-gan-charger%3Fvariant%3D42691851550870%26ref%3Dchristmas-sale">240W 4-Port GaN Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;159.99</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/anker-countdown-to-christmas/">Anker Begins Countdown to Christmas Sale With Up to 50% Off Popular Charging Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-begins-countdown-to-christmas-sale-with-up-to-50-off-popular-charging-accessories.2413078/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Executive Behind Breakthrough Hardware Technologies Retires</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/executive-behind-hardware-technologies-retires/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-executive-behind-breakthrough-hardware-technologies-retires.2413066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 06:30:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/executive-behind-hardware-technologies-retires/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple executive responsible for the company's multitouch technology, health sensors, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> is set to retire from the company, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-06/apple-aapl-executive-who-invented-iphone-multitouch-and-touch-id-leaving"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/ipad-air-touch-id-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1900" height="1069" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-762557" /><br/>
Steve Hotelling currently works as a vice president reporting to senior vice president of hardware technologies Johny Srouji. During his tenure, Hotelling significantly contributed to the development of some of Apple's most innovative and complex technologies used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple Watch, and Vision Pro headset. Hotelling's name appears on hundreds of patents, including filings related to multitouch displays and &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
Hotelling led the company's camera engineering team and was involved in the development of custom sensors. His work oversaw the development of the depth-sensing technologies crucial for augmented reality experiences and components fundamental to haptic feedback and ProMotion displays.<br/>
<br/>
Hotelling has also been a prominent representative for Apple in numerous legal trials throughout his two decades with the company. He was a key figure in a patent case against Samsung in the last decade and recently served as a crucial witness in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">trial involving Masimo</a>, which sued Apple over patents <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/09/29/masimo-apple-delaying-lawsuit-apple-watch/">related to health sensors</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the significance of his departure, Apple has not yet shared an official statement regarding Hotelling's retirement. His responsibilities are apparently being distributed among several of Srouji's direct reports, with Alan Gilchrist taking over the management of the camera and depth sensor teams, and Wei Chen taking over display technologies. Apple's hardware technologies group continues work on a custom 5G cellular modem, new wireless chips, microLED displays, and a non-invasive blood sugar sensor.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/executive-behind-hardware-technologies-retires/">Apple Executive Behind Breakthrough Hardware Technologies Retires</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-executive-behind-breakthrough-hardware-technologies-retires.2413066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify on iOS to Bring Back In-App Purchases, Beta Code Suggests [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/spotify-on-ios-in-app-purchases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-on-ios-to-bring-back-in-app-purchases-beta-code-suggests-updated.2413063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 05:48:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/spotify-on-ios-in-app-purchases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify appears to be bringing in-app payments back to its iOS app, based on code strings unearthed in the latest beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris discovered the new code references to an in-app payment system, including an IAP checkout screen and purchase retry panels for failed purchases.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear what the IAP references relate to, but the fact that they are included is curious in itself. Spotify has not allowed customers to sign up for a Spotify Premium subscription through the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>‌ for the last seven years.<br/>
<br/>
There is no mechanism for subscribing to Spotify through the Spotify app, as Spotify has restricted signups to its website in order to avoid paying Apple's fees. "You can't upgrade to Premium in the app," reads Spotify's "Premium" section in its iOS app. "We know, it's not ideal." <br/>
<br/>
Over the years, Apple and Spotify have had a long running dispute over Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; policies, with multiple public conflicts over app and subscription fees and app rejections due to Spotify's attempts to skirt the up to 30 percent cut that Apple takes from purchases.<br/>
<br/>
In comments made in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/30/facebook-spotify-app-store-criticism/">November 2022</a>, Spotify CEO Daniel Ek accused Apple of giving developers "the illusion of control," and said that the ‌&zwnj;App Store&zwnj;‌ is a "threat to the future of the internet" that denies consumers choice.<br/>
<br/>
Ek also clashed with Apple over Spotify's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/25/spotify-audio-book-app-update-rejected-apple/">audiobooks feature</a>. Apple in 2022 rejected Spotify's audiobook update several times and ultimately did not allow Spotify to direct users to purchase audiobooks through an in-app email signup button.<br/>
<br/>
Things are different over on Android devices. Since November 2020, Spotify has been be able to bill Android users directly in the Google Play version of Spotify without needing to go through the Google Play billing system. <br/>
<br/>
This is because Spotify uses Google's "<a href="https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/answer/12570971">User Choice Billing</a>," a feature that allows Android users to make purchases using the payment option they prefer. User Choice Billing is essentially an alternative billing option for in-app purchases, and it comes with a reduced fee.<br/>
<br/>
Apple offers no alternative billing from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. There are two exceptions, however, including South Korea and the Netherlands. Regulators in these countries have forced Apple to allow some apps to use third-party payment providers.<br/>
<br/>
With Google adopting options for alternative billing and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/11/apple-faces-further-charges-in-eu-antitrust-case/">continued regulatory pressure</a>, it is possible that Apple will also fold and expand the Dutch and South Korea processes to other countries and app types. However, whether the IAP references in Spotify's code relate to such a plan is unknown. Another possibility is that Spotify is preparing to increase the price of its subscriptions to account for Apple's commission on in-app purchases. <br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Spotify announced it will lay off about 1,500 employees, or 17% of its workforce, as the company seeks to downsize after a period of aggressive spending on podcasts and audiobooks. The latest round of cuts is the third in a year, with Spotify still facing annual financial losses amounting to hundreds of millions of dollars.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update</b>: Spotify <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/7/23992162/spotify-denies-its-bringing-in-app-payments-back-to-ios">tells <em>The Verge</em></a> it has "no plans to switch IAP [in-app payments] on at the moment."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/spotify-on-ios-in-app-purchases/">Spotify on iOS to Bring Back In-App Purchases, Beta Code Suggests [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-on-ios-to-bring-back-in-app-purchases-beta-code-suggests-updated.2413063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Facebook Messenger Rolls Out End-to-End Encryption by Default</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/facebook-messenger-end-to-end-encryption/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/facebook-messenger-rolls-out-end-to-end-encryption-by-default.2413057/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 04:03:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/facebook-messenger-end-to-end-encryption/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Facebook Messenger</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta is rolling out end-to-end encryption for personal messages and calls on Messenger and Facebook, finally delivering on a pledge it committed to some time ago.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/encrypted-messenger.jpg" alt="" width="1536" height="864" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925500" /><br/>
Messenger encryption originally arrived in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/10/05/facebook-encrypion-messenger/">2016</a> in the form of "secret conversations," and plans to extend the platform's cryptographic features have been floated ever since. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/12/default-end-to-end-encryption-on-messenger/">According to Loredana Crisan</a>, Head of Messenger, Meta is only now turning on end-to-end encryption for all messages and calls between two people after years spent "rebuilding Messenger features from the ground up."<br/>
<blockquote>Since 2016, Messenger has had the option for people to turn on end-to-end encryption, but we're now changing private chats and calls across Messenger to be end-to-end encrypted by default. This has taken years to deliver because we've taken our time to get this right. Our engineers, cryptographers, designers, policy experts and product managers have worked tirelessly to rebuild Messenger features from the ground up. We've introduced new privacy, safety and control features along the way like delivery controls that let people choose who can message them, as well as app lock, alongside existing safety features like report, block and message requests. We worked closely with outside experts, academics, advocates and governments to identify risks and build mitigations to ensure that privacy and safety go hand-in-hand.</blockquote>The extra layer of security provided by end-to-end encryption means that the content of messages and calls are protected from the moment they leave the sender's device to the moment they reach the receiver's device. In other words, nobody, including Meta, can see what is sent or said, unless the message is reported.<br/>
<br/>
End-to-end encrypted conversations also offer additional functionality including the ability to edit messages, higher media quality, and disappearing messages.<br/>
<br/>
Meta notes that end-to-end encryption won't prevent users from using features like themes and custom reactions, but "it may take some time for Messenger chats to be updated with default end-to-end encryption."<br/>
<br/>
As things stand, end-to-end encryption for group Messenger chats remains opt-in, and Meta previously said that Instagram messages will be encrypted "shortly after" the rollout of default encryption for Messenger chats.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facebook-messenger/">Facebook Messenger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/privacy/">Privacy</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/facebook-messenger-end-to-end-encryption/">Facebook Messenger Rolls Out End-to-End Encryption by Default</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/facebook-messenger-rolls-out-end-to-end-encryption-by-default.2413057/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Adds Push Notification Data to Law Enforcement Guidelines</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-updates-law-enforcement-guidelines/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-push-notification-data-to-law-enforcement-guidelines.2413049/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 02:32:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-updates-law-enforcement-guidelines/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has updated its <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/law-enforcement-guidelines-us.pdf">Legal Process Guidelines</a> to reflect the company's legal obligation to comply with law enforcement requests for Apple ID information associated with its push notification service. The change follows yesterday's revelation that governments are actively using smartphone notification data as a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/apple-governments-surveil-push-notifications/">user surveillance tool</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/appleprivacyad-cleaned.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="872" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833885" /><br/>
In the section titled "Information Available from Apple," Apple has appended an alphabetical list with the subsection "AA. Apple Push Notification Service (APNs)," which reads:<br/>
<blockquote>When users allow an application they have installed to receive push notifications, an Apple Push Notification Service (APNs) token is generated and registered to that developer and device. Some apps may have multiple APNs tokens for one account on one device to differentiate between messages and multi-media.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple ID associated with a registered APNs token may be obtained with a subpoena or greater legal process.</blockquote>Apple and Google have been forced by governments at home and abroad to provide users' data from notifications they get on their devices, US Senator Ron Wyden revealed on Wednesday in a letter to the Justice Department, drawing attention to a new smartphone privacy concern.<br/>
<br/>
The Justice Department declined to comment on the letter, but Apple and Google confirmed that they have been subject to the requests. The companies explained that they had been prohibited from sharing information about how governments monitored push notifications until Wyden's letter had been made public and given them the legal opening they needed.<br/>
<br/>
With push notifications enabled, Apple and Google create a small bit of data, known as a token, that links the user's device to the account information they've given the companies, such as their name and email address.<br/>
<br/>
A <em>Reuters</em> source familiar with the matter confirmed that both foreign and U.S. government agencies have been asking Apple and Google for user information related to push notifications. The data is said to have been used to attempt to tie anonymous users of messaging apps to specific Apple or Google accounts.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2023/12/06/push-notifications-surveillance-apple-google/"><em>The Washington Post</em></a> said on Wednesday it had found more than two dozen search warrant applications and other documents in court records related to federal requests for push notification data. Though many were redacted, nine of the documents pertained to the federal hunt for U.S. Capitol rioters on January 6, 2021.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-updates-law-enforcement-guidelines/">Apple Adds Push Notification Data to Law Enforcement Guidelines</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-push-notification-data-to-law-enforcement-guidelines.2413049/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Upgrading iPhone 16 Microphone to Boost Siri AI Experience</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-upgrading-iphone-16-microphone-to-boost-siri-ai-experience.2413044/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 01:07:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans a significant upgrade to the iPhone 16 microphone to improve the new AI-enhanced Siri experience, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/瑞聲科技與歌爾股份為ai-iphone的領先受益者-aac-and-goertek-are-ai-iphones-leading-beneficiaries-1ec29ee45e42">latest Medium post</a>, Kuo says that "strengthening Siri's hardware and software features and specifications is the key to promoting AI-generated content," adding that Apple's generative AI ambitions and integration of large-language models (LLMs) into Siri will heavily rely on improved voice input processing. <br/>
<br/>
To that end, Apple is preparing a major microphone upgrade for the iPhone 16, with better signal-to-noise ratio a key specification that will "improve the Siri experience significantly," says Kuo. The new microphone will also have better water resistance. <br/>
<br/>
The upgrade corroborates other reports suggesting Apple plans to make enhanced Siri features a key selling point of the iPhone 16. New Siri features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">powered by LLMs</a> are expected in iOS 18, and Kuo's report notes that Apple reorganized its Siri team in the third quarter of this year to integrate generative AI and LLMs. However, Kuo's predictions also add weight to rumors that additional on-device AI features could remain <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">exclusive to the iPhone 16 models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to the analyst's latest survey, AAC and Goertek are the microphone suppliers for the iPhone 16, and will benefit equally from the specification upgrade. "The ASP of microphones for each iPhone 16 will be at least 100–150% higher than that of the iPhone 15," says Kuo. "As a result, AAC's and Goertek's revenues and earnings are expected to benefit significantly from this upgrade."<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/">Kuo: Apple Upgrading iPhone 16 Microphone to Boost Siri AI Experience</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-upgrading-iphone-16-microphone-to-boost-siri-ai-experience.2413044/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Will Charge iPhones at 15W</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-qi2-chargers-will-charge-iphones-at-15w.2413020/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 16:53:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Anker</category>
		<category>Qi2</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next-generation Qi2 chargers from Anker will charge the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> at faster 15W speeds, Anker told <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/12/6/23990215/anker-qi2-15w-wireless-charging-iphone-13-14-15">The Verge</a></em>. Current Qi-based chargers from companies like Anker are limited to 7.5W when used with Apple's iPhones, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> chargers support 15W charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911511" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/magsafe-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
While Qi2 has the same magnetic alignment that &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; offers, Apple has not provided details on the Qi2 charging speeds that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> will support. During the introduction of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, Apple said they support Qi2, but the technical specifications page for the devices says that Qi wireless charging is limited to 7.5W.<br/>
<blockquote>Anker spokesperson Mary Woodbury confirmed in an email to The Verge that, unlike older Qi products that were limited to half-speed 7.5W charging with iPhones, the new MagGo products can support 15W charging, the same maximum rate you get with Apple's MagSafe-branded gear.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has not confirmed 15W charging speeds with Qi2, nor have other manufacturers working on Qi2 provided specific charging speeds, but if Anker's upcoming Qi2 chargers work at 15W, other wireless chargers will likely have the same maximum speed.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have had Qi2 support since they launched, and with the iOS 17.2 that's coming soon, Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/ios-17-2-qi-iphone-13-14-models/">adding Qi2 support</a> to the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
If Qi2 does support actual 15W charging speeds on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; similar to &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, the certification could help clear up some confusing with existing magnetic wireless chargers. Current Qi-based chargers that have magnets are still limited to 7.5W charging, but manufacturers often like to say that they support up to 15W because other non-iPhone smartphones are able to charge at those speeds.<br/>
<br/>
The first Qi2 chargers are expected in late 2023, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/31/belkin-qi2-wireless-chargers/">brands like Belkin</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/mophie-unveils-qi2-accessories/">Mophie</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/31/anker-usb-c-nano-accessories/">Anker</a> have already announced new Qi2 products.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anker/">Anker</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qi2/">Qi2</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/anker-qi2-15w-charging/">Anker&#039;s Qi2 Chargers Will Charge iPhones at 15W</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ankers-qi2-chargers-will-charge-iphones-at-15w.2413020/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hulu on Disney+ Beta Launches for Bundle Subscribers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hulu-on-disney-beta-launches-for-bundle-subscribers.2413014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 14:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Disney</category>
		<category>Hulu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Disney <a href="https://thewaltdisneycompany.com/hulu-on-disney-beta-launch/">today announced</a> that customers who subscribe to its Hulu and Disney+ bundle can access Hulu content through a new "Hulu on Disney+" beta that aims to combine the two apps into a single app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Hulu on Disney+ Beta Now Streaming" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AgHZ7EeNaSg" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
The beta is available to bundle subscribers as of now, with Disney planning to test the combined service before it rolls out in the spring. Bundle subscribers will see a Hulu title appear alongside Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars, and National Geographic tiles in the Disney+ interface.<br/>
<br/>
Clicking on the Hulu tile brings Bundle subscribers to the new Hulu Hub that has all of the Hulu content without the need to switch over to the Hulu app. The two-step launch process is meant to keep Hulu content separate from Disney+ content for parents who do not want the more adult content from Hulu accessible to children.<br/>
<br/>
Disney said that it wants to better understand consumer needs and wants for Hulu on Disney+ before it launches in March 2024. Disney does not plan to replace either the standalone Hulu or Disney+ subscriptions, both will continue be available.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/disney/">Disney</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/hulu/">Hulu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/hulu-disney-plus-merged-beta/">Hulu on Disney+ Beta Launches for Bundle Subscribers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hulu-on-disney-beta-launches-for-bundle-subscribers.2413014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
