<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Oct 2023 01:03:12 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warning: BMW Wireless Charging May Break iPhone 15&#039;s Apple Pay Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/01/bmw-charging-may-break-iphone-15-nfc-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-bmw-wireless-charging-may-break-iphone-15s-apple-pay-chip.2405806/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 06:14:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/01/bmw-charging-may-break-iphone-15-nfc-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>BMW</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you have an iPhone 15 and drive a BMW, it might be best to avoid charging the device with the vehicle's wireless charging pad for now.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/BMW-Logo-iPhone-15-Pro.jpg" alt="" width="1489" height="744" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914891" /><br/>
Over the past week, some BMW owners have complained that their iPhone 15's NFC chip no longer works after charging the device with their vehicle's wireless charging pad, according to comments shared <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-apple-pay-issue-bmw-related.2404307/">on the MacRumors Forums</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/DeeSoS3xy/status/1707882090107465845">X</a>, formerly known as Twitter. Affected customers say the iPhone goes into a data recovery mode with a white screen, and the NFC chip is no longer functional after the device reboots.<br/>
<br/>
In an iPhone, the NFC chip powers features like Apple Pay and digital car keys. Affected users receive a "Could Not Set Up Apple Pay" error message in the Wallet app, and there does not appear to be a way to fix the problem. Some customers say Apple replaced their iPhone after confirming the NFC chip failed, but the replacement iPhone is then vulnerable to the same issue, so there is currently no permanent solution.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pay-Error.jpg" alt="" width="1179" height="658" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914890" /><br/>
While complaints so far have come from iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max users, it is possible the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are also affected, so owners of any iPhone 15 model should proceed with caution until this issue is sorted.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear what the specific cause of the issue is, how many customers are affected, and which BMW models are affected. We've reached out to an Apple spokesperson for comment, and we'll update this story if we receive a response.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bmw/">BMW</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/01/bmw-charging-may-break-iphone-15-nfc-chip/">Warning: BMW Wireless Charging May Break iPhone 15&#039;s Apple Pay Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warning-bmw-wireless-charging-may-break-iphone-15s-apple-pay-chip.2405806/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Titanium Frame Does Not Contribute to Overheating Issue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-iphone-15-pro-overheating-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphone-15-pros-titanium-frame-does-not-contribute-to-overheating-issue.2405695/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 11:10:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-iphone-15-pro-overheating-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today said it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-responds-to-iphone-15-pro-overheating/">plans to release an iOS 17 software update</a> with a bug fix for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max overheating issue</a>, and the company has since shared additional details about the matter with <em>MacRumors</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
Importantly, Apple said the issue is not related to the titanium frame. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/">Contrary to a report</a> this week, Apple said the iPhone 15 Pro's design does not contribute to overheating. In fact, Apple said the titanium frame and aluminum substructure provide better heat dissipation than any previous-generation Pro models with stainless steel frames.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said some third-party apps have overloaded the A17 Pro chip for unknown reasons, including Instagram, Uber, and racing game Asphalt 9: Legends, and it is working with the developers of these apps to address the matter. Apple said its bug fix will not involve reducing the chip's performance in order to address the temperature-related issue, and it ensured that long-term performance will not be impacted.<br/>
<br/>
To reiterate Apple's statement:<blockquote>We have identified a few conditions which can cause iPhone to run warmer than expected. The device may feel warmer during the first few days after setting up or restoring the device because of increased background activity. We have also found a bug in iOS 17 that is impacting some users and will be addressed in a software update. Another issue involves some recent updates to third-party apps that are causing them to overload the system. We're working with these app developers on fixes that are in the process of rolling out.</blockquote>More details are available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-responds-to-iphone-15-pro-overheating/">initial coverage of Apple's statement</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-iphone-15-pro-overheating-details/">Apple Says iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Titanium Frame Does Not Contribute to Overheating Issue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphone-15-pros-titanium-frame-does-not-contribute-to-overheating-issue.2405695/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Address iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Issue With iOS 17 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-responds-to-iphone-15-pro-overheating/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-address-iphone-15-pro-overheating-issue-with-ios-17-update.2405682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 09:28:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-responds-to-iphone-15-pro-overheating/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release an iOS 17 update to address a bug that may contribute to the reported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max overheating issue</a>, according to a statement the company shared today with <em>MacRumors</em> and <a href="http://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2023/09/30/apple-iphone-15-iphone-15-overheating-exclusive-apple-comments-iphone-15-overheating-solution-coming"><em>Forbes</em> reporter David Phelan</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Apple also says some recent updates to third-party apps have overloaded the system and contributed to the overheating issue. The report notes that some of these apps include Instagram, Uber, and the racing game Asphalt 9: Legends, and Apple is working with the developers of these apps to address the issue. The report adds that Instagram already introduced a fix as part of an update to the app released on Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says iPhone 15 Pro models may run warmer than expected during the first few days after setting up or restoring the device due to increased background activity. This is standard behavior for new iPhones and only a temporary condition.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's statement:<blockquote>We have identified a few conditions which can cause iPhone to run warmer than expected. The device may feel warmer during the first few days after setting up or restoring the device because of increased background activity. We have also found a bug in iOS 17 that is impacting some users and will be addressed in a software update. Another issue involves some recent updates to third-party apps that are causing them to overload the system. We're working with these app developers on fixes that are in the process of rolling out.</blockquote>The bug should be fixed with iOS 17.1, which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-public-beta-1/">currently in beta</a> and is expected to be released in late October. It's quite possible that Apple might also make a bug fix available sooner with a smaller software update, such as iOS 17.0.3.<br/>
<br/>
According to the report, Apple will not be reducing the performance of the A17 Pro chip as part of the temperature-related bug fix. Apple also said the issue is not a safety risk and will not impact the long-term performance of affected iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the iPhone 15 Pro's titanium frame and aluminum substructure <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-iphone-15-pro-overheating-details/">do not contribute to the overheating issue</a>, ruling out a hardware problem.<br/>
<br/>
Not all iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max users have experienced overheating, and it's unclear how many customers are affected by the issue overall, but it should be resolved soon.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/apple-responds-to-iphone-15-pro-overheating/">Apple to Address iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Issue With iOS 17 Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-address-iphone-15-pro-overheating-issue-with-ios-17-update.2405682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: macOS Sonoma Released, iOS 17.1 Beta, and iPhone 16 Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/top-stories-macos-sonoma-released/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-macos-sonoma-released-ios-17-1-beta-and-iphone-16-rumors.2405652/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/top-stories-macos-sonoma-released/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mac fans, rejoice! You can now enjoy the upgrades that come with macOS Sonoma, which was released to the public this week just a bit later than the major updates for the rest of Apple's platforms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/top-stories-30sep2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914635" /><br/>
Apple isn't stopping there, of course, and it's already begun seeding iOS 17.1, macOS Sonoma 14.1, and other upcoming updates to developers and public beta testers. This week also saw some fresh rumors about the iPhone 16 (yes, already!), while discussion continues over thermal issues with the iPhone 15 Pro and Apple's controversial FineWoven accessories, so read on for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma With Desktop Widgets, Game Mode, and More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma was released to the public this week</a> following over three months of beta testing. The free software update includes many new features and changes for the Mac, including interactive desktop widgets, a Game Mode, the ability to add websites to the Dock as web apps, several Safari improvements, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
We've shared a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macos-sonoma-features/">list of macOS Sonoma features worth checking out</a>, and additional details about the software update can be found in our in-depth <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything New in iOS 17.1 Beta 1</h2><br/>
Less than two weeks after Apple released iOS 17, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-public-beta-1/">first beta of iOS 17.1</a> is already available. As usual, there are a handful of new features and changes coming to the iPhone with this software update for Apple Music, AirDrop, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912331" /><br/>
We've put together <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">a list of everything new in the first beta of iOS 17.1</a> with more details. The beta is now available for both developers and public beta testers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 to Include an Additional Capacitive 'Capture' Button</h2><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">plans to add a new capacitive button to iPhone 16 models</a> that is internally known as the "Capture Button," according to <em>MacRumors</em> sources.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
It's unclear what this button will be used for, but given that it is expected to be positioned below the power button on the right side of the iPhone, it could be a more conveniently placed shutter button for the camera when shooting in landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>22 New Features You May Have Missed in watchOS 10</h2><br/>
watchOS 10 is now available for the Apple Watch Series 4 and newer, and the software update includes several new features and changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/22-Hidden-Features-in-watchOS-10-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2248" height="1264" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913396" /><br/>
This week, we shared a list of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/22-hidden-features-watchos-10-apple-watch/">22 watchOS features and changes that you might not know about</a>. If you are looking for some new tips and tricks on how to use your Apple Watch to its fullest, be sure to check out the list for some helpful recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Concerns Highlighted in Two More Reports</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/iphone-15-pro-overheating-reports/">iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max overheating concerns</a> continue to make headlines this week, with the topic highlighted by <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> and <em>Bloomberg</em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said the titanium frame on iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/">negatively impacts thermal efficiency</a>. Kuo believes that Apple will likely address the issue through future software updates, but he said improvements might be limited.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple's FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 Continue to Be Heavily Criticized</h2><br/>
Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">FineWoven cases for iPhone 15 models have been heavily criticized</a> since they were released earlier this month, with some customers and media outlets complaining about the fabric exterior being prone to scratches and stains.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">recapped some of the negative feedback</a> last week, and the complaints have continued to surface. Apple has not commented on the matter so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/sep-28-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/top-stories-macos-sonoma-released/">Top Stories: macOS Sonoma Released, iOS 17.1 Beta, and iPhone 16 Rumors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-macos-sonoma-released-ios-17-1-beta-and-iphone-16-rumors.2405652/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Counter-Strike 2 Lacks Mac Support, Update Breaks CS:GO for macOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/counter-strike-2-no-mac-version-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/counter-strike-2-lacks-mac-support-update-breaks-cs-go-for-macos.2405627/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 01:54:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/counter-strike-2-no-mac-version-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Valve</category>
		<category>Steam</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Valve this week released <em>Counter-Strike 2</em>, the highly anticipated free upgrade for owners of <em>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive</em>, but Mac owners were left in the lurch on launch day, with the upgrade breaking the game and seemingly no macOS version forthcoming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/counter-srike-21.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="450" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914773" /><br/>
The title's release on Wednesday forced a 26GB update for everyone with <em>CS:GO</em>, including Mac users, but after installation those on macOS soon discovered that the update essentially makes the game unplayable because Steam subsequently attempts to launch an executable file for Windows. Some users have had to employ a <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/app/730/discussions/0/3881596897258134490/">workaround</a> to reverse the change and access <em>CS:GO</em>, but it's less than ideal.<br/>
<br/>
Valve quietly removed the macOS symbol on <a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/730/CounterStrike_2/">Steam's <em>Counter-Strike</em> product page</a>, while the only reference to this omission for <em>Counter-Strike 2</em> appears in <a href="https://steamcommunity.com/faqs/steam-help/view/5ED2-ED8E-81F4-0C18#macos">Valve's official FAQ</a>. A question about Mac support is met with the response: "No. CS2 is not available for Mac at this time," but provides no additional information.<br/>
<br/>
Regardless, Valve apparently failed to adequately warn Mac users, many of whom have racked up thousands of hours on <em>CS:GO</em> and spent hundreds of dollars on inventory purchases. One Mac gamer on <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/macgaming/comments/16u35zu/cs2_on_mac_i_feel_so_deflated_right_now/">Reddit</a> wrote:<br/>
<blockquote>I have around 6,000 hours in CS:GO, about 500&#36; worth of inventory. Am I supposed to leave all that behind now? Just cherish them as memories of the past never to be experienced again? I really believed Valve would have released a macOS version CS2 too. They have publicly denounced Windows' gaming monopoly in the past. With MacOS Sonoma, powerful Apple silicon chips, and Apple making strides to make gaming possible on Mac (and Valve's commitment to making their games available to everyone) I guess we didn't see this coming. Or maybe we did, but we were stubborn. I guess with Valve's darling Steam Deck, macOS became redundant to them as a way to challenge windows gaming monopoly. I am sorry you guys had to hear this, but I feel so disappointed right now, in myself and in Valve. I'm sure most of you CS:GO players were as excited and hopeful as I was for the game's launch.</blockquote><em>Counter-Strike: Global Offensive</em> is one of the most popular and long-running games on macOS, with a large community following, so the lack of support and transparancy from Valve for Mac users upgrading to <em>Counter-Strike 2</em> is all the more bewildering.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/counter-strike-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914774" /><br/>
Based on recent updates to the <em>CS2</em> macOS depot, some users believe a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/macgaming/comments/16vtc8h/cs2_changes_on_steamdb_dont_mean_anything/">Mac version is in development</a>, but it would likely relate to Rosetta 2 rather than a version that natively supports Apple silicon. With no word on the subject from Valve, this remains purely speculation.<br/>
<br/>
The long-rumored game, officially announced in March, updates many much-loved maps, and uses Valve's in-house Source 2 engine, featuring sharper textures, more realistic lighting, and new geometry. We've reached out to Valve for comment on this story and will update readers if we hear back.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Scott!)</em><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/valve/">Valve</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steam/">Steam</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/30/counter-strike-2-no-mac-version-available/">Counter-Strike 2 Lacks Mac Support, Update Breaks CS:GO for macOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/counter-strike-2-lacks-mac-support-update-breaks-cs-go-for-macos.2405627/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Wallet&#039;s New Bank Account Feature Likely to Expand to U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallets-new-bank-account-feature-likely-to-expand-to-u-s.2405603/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 20:11:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/ios-17-1-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.1 beta</a> released this week, iPhone users in the U.K. can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-uk-bank-account-balance-apple-wallet/">add debit and credit cards from select banks</a> in the country to the Wallet app and view their available balances and latest transactions for those accounts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/uk-bank-account-apple-wallet-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914320" /><br/>
Apple calls this feature Connected Cards, and it's currently available in the U.K. only, but there is now evidence to suggest it will expand to the U.S. in the future.<br/>
<br/>
As discovered by software researcher <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1707956080628687258">Aaron</a> (<a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1707956080628687258">@aaronp613</a>), the following fine print is shown in the Wallet app when setting up the feature in the U.K.:<blockquote>You permit Apple (Apple Payments Services Ltd (UK) or Apple Processing LLC (US)) to consolidate your account information and provide it to you. We do not store or share this information.</blockquote>Based on this fine print, <em>MacRumors</em> discovered a <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/connected-cards/">legal document on Apple's website</a> explicitly mentioning that the Connected Cards feature will eventually be available to U.S. residents, with personal data to be processed by Apple Processing LLC:<blockquote>If you are in the United States, Connected Cards is provided by Apple Processing LLC; if you are in the United Kingdom, Connected Cards is provided by Apple Payment Services Ltd (together, "Apple").</blockquote>It's unclear when Connected Cards will launch in the U.S., or which banks will participate in the country. In the U.K., the feature relies on the country's open banking framework, but it's unclear how it would work stateside. Earlier this year, the U.S. Consumer Financial Protection Bureau said it expected to <a href="https://www.consumerfinance.gov/about-us/blog/laying-the-foundation-for-open-banking-in-the-united-states/">finalize an open banking rule in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple is working on expanding the new &quot;Connected Cards&quot; feature in iOS 17.1 to the US via &quot;Apple Processing LLC&quot;<br><br>As found in the code: You permit Apple (Apple Payments Services Ltd (UK) or Apple Processing LLC (US)) to consolidate your account information and provide it to you. <a href="https://t.co/t8QxSWa3dL">pic.twitter.com/t8QxSWa3dL</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1707956080628687258?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 30, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-wallet-connected-cards-feature-in-us/">Apple Wallet&#039;s New Bank Account Feature Likely to Expand to U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-wallets-new-bank-account-feature-likely-to-expand-to-u-s.2405603/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma: 50 New Features and Changes Worth Checking Out</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/50-new-macos-sonoma-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-50-new-features-and-changes-worth-checking-out.2405581/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 15:55:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/50-new-macos-sonoma-features&#038;post_date=1696038904/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Tuesday released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of the company's Mac operating system. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; introduces interactive desktop widgets, web apps, new videoconferencing features, and updated capabilities across the platform.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/50-New-Features-and-Changes-Worth-Checking-Out-in-macOS-Sonoma.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913938" /><br/>
In this article, we've selected 50 new features and lesser-known changes that are worth checking out if you're upgrading. What do you think of &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; so far? Let us know in the comments.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="1._set_widget_color_options">1. Set Widget Color Options</h2><br/>
When not in use, interactive desktop widgets fade into the background by taking on a monochrome style, allowing you to concentrate on the active app or window. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/monochrome-desktop-widgets.jpg" alt="settings" width="2214" height="916" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914508" /><br/>
If you prefer this look, you can make it permanent by going to System Settings -> Desktop & Dock. In the "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a>" section, set Widget Style to Monochrome.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2._system_settings_navigation">2. System Settings Navigation</h2><br/>
In macOS Ventura, Apple replaced System Preferences with System Settings to align it with iOS and iPadOS, but the way controls were organized left many users wanting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits2.jpg" alt="" width="1048" height="534" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899401" /><br/>
The same System Settings interface remains in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, but it is now easier to navigate through different menu screens you have visited without continually scrolling through the sidebar, thanks to the addition of backward and forward buttons.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="3._facetime_reactions">3. FaceTime Reactions</h2><br/>
Apple has changed the way <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> integrates with the menu bar. The video effects options no longer appear in the Control Center, and instead have a new home in a dedicated green &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; menu bar item, which also includes a mini webcam view and buttons to trigger Reactions. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits1.jpg" alt="" width="1359" height="964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899402" /><br/>
Reactions include Love, Like, Dislike, Balloons, Rain, Confetti, Lasers, and Fireworks. Some reactions are even triggered automatically by the user's physical actions: One thumb up triggers a Like, and two thumbs up are attended by Fireworks. Similarly, one thumb down counts as a dislike, and two thumbs down initiates a rain shower.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="4._safari_profiles">4. Safari Profiles</h2><br/>
Safari has gained a new feature called Profiles, which is designed to help keep your browsing separate for different use cases like Work, School, or Personal. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits3.jpg" alt="" width="846" height="436" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899403" /><br/>
Go to the Profiles section in Safari -> Settings..., and you can create custom profiles, choose a symbol and color for each one, and select a Favorites folder. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/safari-profile-settings.jpg" alt="settings" width="836" height="452" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914509" /><br/>
Profiles silo your history, Tab Groups, and cookies, and you can also assign specific extensions to different profiles to optimize your browsing experience based on the task at hand.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="5._seamless_keyboard_input_and_dictation">5. Seamless Keyboard Input and Dictation</h2><br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; supports simultaneous use of keyboard input and Dictation, without any disruption in your flow of thought.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits4.jpg" alt="" width="2339" height="1146" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899405" /><br/>
In other words, you can keep typing after hitting the Dictation shortcut (assignable in System Settings -> Keyboard). So whenever your fingers need a rest, you can complete the sentence you were just typing by saying it out loud.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="6._presenter_overlay">6. Presenter Overlay</h2><br/>
When you're in a &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; or Zoom call, click-hold the green traffic light in the corner of an open app window and you'll see a screen sharing option, while a new Presenter Overlay feature can be used to keep you on screen and better able to point to details.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits7.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899410" /><br/>
When on a video call, you can either place yourself inside a movable bubble in the corner of the window or desktop that you're sharing, or you can bring on-screen content into the background of your own environment so that it looks as if you're standing just in front of it. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="7._dock_web_apps">7. Dock Web Apps</h2><br/>
Thanks to a new option in Safari, you can now create standalone web apps and add them to your Dock, alongside your regular apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-tidbits6.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899411" /><br/>
All you have to do is visit a website in Safari and select File -> Add to Dock.... You can then give the web app a name and even change its icon. When you open a docked web app, it will open in its own separate window that includes back and forward buttons for simple navigation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="8._caps_lock_is_on">8. Caps Lock Is On</h2><br/>
If the Caps Lock key on your keyboard is enabled in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, a handy indicator appears right near the cursor, so you're less likely to TYPE LIKE THIS BY ACCIDENT and get your passwords wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/CAPS-LOCK-symbol.jpg" alt="" width="854" height="364" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914524" /><br/>
Apple has also made the text cursor a little thicker, and its color now changes relative to the active application, so you'll have a better idea of which window your text is going to appear in when you start typing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="9._open_notes_in_pages">9. Open Notes in Pages</h2><br/>
You can now send notes from the Notes app directly to Pages. Simply open the note, click the Share button, then choose Open in Pages from the share sheet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/open-notes-pages.jpg" alt="notes" width="2548" height="1108" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914525" /><br/>
From there you can continue to edit the note in Pages, then save it or export it as a PDF, Word file, EPUB, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="10._iphone_widgets_on_your_mac">10. iPhone Widgets on Your Mac</h2> <br/>
Thanks to Apple's Continuity feature and its ability to sync with your devices, the widget library includes widgets from your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in all available sizes. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/widgets-macos.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901433" /><br/>
So even if you don't have the corresponding Mac app, you can still use the iOS widget right on your desktop. Simply drag it from the gallery into an available space.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-widgets-on-mac.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914526" /><br/>
If you have more than one &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, you can also choose which widgets show up in your Mac's widgets library. Go to System Settings -> Desktop & Dock, and in the "&zwnj;Widgets&zwnj;" section, click the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; dropdown to select the device that you want to sync to. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="_11._showhide_desktop_"> 11. Show/Hide Desktop </h2><br/>
By default, &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; hides all windows when you click on your wallpaper. This is handy if you tend to have a bunch of files on the screen that you need access to. But if you find this behavior maddening, you can limit it to happen only when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> is enabled.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/click-wallpaper-reveal-desktop.jpg" alt="" width="1638" height="656" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914527" /><br/>
Go to System Settings -> Desktop & Dock. In the Desktop & &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj; section, look for the option Click wallpaper to reveal desktop, then click Always and choose Only in &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj; instead. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="12._text_prediction">12. Text Prediction</h2><br/>
Thanks to improved machine learning technology, Apple has made macOS a lot more helpful, because it can better predict what you're going to type next. Apple says it has adopted a "transformer language model" that can even personalize prediction for individual users, learning your personal preferences and word choices to be more useful when typing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macos-text-prediction.jpg" alt="" width="870" height="438" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914528" /><br/>
As you type, the predicted text appears ahead of the cursor. If it has accurately predicted what you want to type, press the spacebar and macOS will fill it in for you. After using ‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌‌ for a few weeks, you should notice that the suggestions are much better at predicting what you want to say and presenting words for you to autofill. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/predictive-text-off.jpg" alt="settings" width="1380" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914529" /><br/>
If you find all of this distracting, you can turn it off. Go to System Settings -> Keyboard. Next to Input Sources, click Edit…. In the next window, toggle off the switch next to Show inline predictive text. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="13._managing_pdfs_in_notes">13. Managing PDFs in Notes</h2><br/>
When you drag PDFs into Notes, they are now presented full-width in the note, making it easier to view and interact with them. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/notes-pdf-viewing.jpg" alt="" width="2284" height="1108" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914530" /><br/>
Notes is no longer restricted to rendering the first page of a PDF. You can now view the individual pages of a document you're reviewing right inside the note, which is really handy for previewing multiple PDFs in the same note. You also get a row of thumbnails across the top of the PDF that you can click to navigate to a specific page more quickly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="14._link_notes_together">14. Link Notes Together</h2><br/>
Apple has made its stock Notes app significantly more useful by adding the simple yet powerful ability to link notes and connect related notes together. With just a few clicks, you can create links between notes in ‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, making it easy to jump from one idea to another. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/linked-notes-macos.jpg" alt="" width="1538" height="966" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914531" /><br/>
One way of adding a new link is by right-clicking on a space, word or phrase in any note and selecting Add Link from the contextual menu. You can also use the Command-K shortcut. This will let you link to another note by typing in its title. Using the "Name" field, you can create an optional alternative title for the link, or just stick with the original title for clarity. Once you're done, the link appears as hyperlink-style underlined text in your note, and clicking it snaps you straight into the note you linked to.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="15._link_from_a_list_of_notes">15. Link From a List of Notes</h2><br/>
The Notes app also offers an additional, quicker way to add links: Typing two greater-than symbols (>>) into a note invokes a list containing your six most recently modified notes, and tapping one instantly adds a link to that note.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/link-notes-recent-list.jpg" alt="" width="966" height="506" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914532" /><br/>
The same feature can be found in iOS, meaning you can now create wiki-style collections of interlinked notes, allowing you to organize your thoughts or discover new connections and associations between ideas.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="16._studio_light_and_background_blur">16. Studio Light and Background Blur</h2><br/>
Studio Light is now available in macOS when using video conferencing apps, on Studio Display and Mac models with Apple silicon, without the need for Continuity Camera. In the &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; menu bar UI, you can darken the background and illuminate your face using the Studio Light intensity slider.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/facetime-studio-light-portrait.jpg" alt="FaceTime" width="1780" height="956" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914535" /><br/>
With the Portrait slider, you can also control the amount of background blur, adding more or less blur to the depth-of-field effect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="17._choose_center_stage_camera">17. Choose Center Stage Camera</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, Continuity Camera automatically detects your face and frames you in the center, without you having to enable Center Stage. Still, turning on Center Stage keeps you centered in the camera frame as you move around. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/center-stage-continuity-camera.jpg" alt="center stage" width="1620" height="978" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914537" /><br/>
Choose Center Stage from the Video menu in the menu bar. To switch between the rear cameras on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, click the arrow next to Center Stage, then choose Main or Ultra Wide. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="18._find_messages_faster_">18. Find Messages Faster </h2><br/>
Previously in macOS, you could type a word or phrase in the search field of Apple's Messages app and it would return matching results, but there was no way to filter messages to more easily find what you were looking for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/messages-search.jpg" alt="" width="1030" height="606" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914534" /><br/>
That's changed in ‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌, and now you can combine multiple filters. If you're looking for images from a certain person, for example, you can type in "photos" and then the person's name, clicking each search filter to narrow down your search results.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="19._remove_all_url_tracking">19. Remove All URL Tracking</h2><br/>
Safari can remove tracking parameters from URLs in order to prevent cross-website tracking. When a tracking parameter is detected while browsing or copying a link, Safari strips the identifying components of the URL, while leaving the rest intact. The links still work as expected, but no longer have unique identifiers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/safari-advanced-tracking-protection-mac.jpg" alt="settings" width="2418" height="1354" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905304" /><br/>
To enable the feature for all browsing, open Safari -> Settings..., click the Advanced tab, make sure the box is checked next to Use advanced tracking and fingerprint protection, then choose "in all browsing" in the dropdown.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="20._safari_favicons">20. Safari Favicons</h2><br/>
In Safari 17, if you have the Favorites Bar enabled (View -> Show Favorites Bar in Safari's menu bar) the favicon for each site will appear beside its title, allowing you to more easily spot it in the bar.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/hide-safari-favicons.jpg" alt="" width="738" height="436" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905937" /><br/>
Favicons can certainly be handy, but they can make your browser interface look too busy and cluttered. Another possible issue with the space they take up is that if you have a full row of websites in your Favorites Bar, some of them will be lopped off the viewable area, and you may have to click the double chevron icon at the far right to reveal them.<br/>
<br/>
If this happens in your case, don't worry. It's not obvious, but you can easily prevent favicons from appearing in the Favorites Bar. Simply right-click anywhere on the bar and uncheck Show Icons in the pop-up menu.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="21._automatically_close_safari_tabs">21. Automatically Close Safari Tabs</h2><br/>
macOS can now close Safari's browser tabs on your behalf, based on when you last viewed them. Select Safari -> Settings... in the menu bar, then click the Tabs section. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/auto-close-tabs-safari.jpg" alt="safari" width="1672" height="878" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914539" /><br/>
Next to "Automatically close tabs" you'll find options to make the browser auto-close tabs that have not been viewed After One Day, After One Week, or After One Month.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="22._share_passwords_with_family">22. Share Passwords With Family</h2><br/>
Staying in Safari Settings, the Passwords menu now has a Share Passwords with Family option. This allows you to create a group of trusted contacts that you can share passwords and passkeys with across devices. (Passkeys let users sign in to apps and sites the same way they unlock their devices: With a fingerprint, a face scan, or a screen lock PIN.)<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/family-passwords.jpg" alt="safari" width="1462" height="890" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914540" /><br/>
Using the new feature, passwords and passkeys for shared media accounts, utilities, bills, and more can be provided to multiple people, and each person in the group can access, add to, and change passwords that are shared.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="23._clean_up_verification_codes">23. Clean Up Verification Codes</h2><br/>
These days, many websites and services use one-time passcodes sent via SMS or over email for verification purposes, but these one-time codes can soon clog up your Mail inbox and Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/cleanup-verification-codes.jpg" alt="safari" width="1404" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914541" /><br/>
In &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, there's a new option to have those messages auto-delete after the code is autofilled and used to authenticate a login. Go to Safari -> Settings... and click the Password section. Under "Verification Codes," you can toggle the switch next to Clean Up Automatically.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="24._set_private_browsing_search_engine">24. Set Private Browsing Search Engine</h2><br/>
In Safari, you can set different search engines for normal and Private Browsing modes. For example, you may want to set Google as the default search engine in regular browsing mode and a different search engine such as DuckDuckGo in Private Browsing mode for privacy reasons.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/private-browsing-search.jpg" alt="safari" width="1672" height="596" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914543" /><br/>
Go to Safari -> Settings..., click the Search section, then select a browser from the Private Browsing search engine dropdown.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="25._private_browsing_authentication">25. Private Browsing Authentication</h2><br/>
If you have any Private Browsing tabs open in Safari and then leave your computer, Apple's browser now requires <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication or your Mac password to access them again.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/private-browsing-authenticate.jpg" alt="safari" width="1672" height="740" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914542" /><br/>
If you don't tend to leave your Mac unlocked or find the authentication requirement annoying, you can turn it off pretty easily: Go to Safari -> Settings..., click the Privacy section, then uncheck the box next to Require &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; to view locked tabs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="26._per-website_app_extension_settings">26. Per-Website App Extension Settings</h2><br/>
In Safari, third-party app extensions have gained per-website privacy settings where relevant, allowing you to control access for all extensions with access to user data.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/per-website-app-extension-settings.jpg" alt="safari" width="1672" height="1184" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914769" /><br/>
You can find the "Edit websites..." for each app extension in the Extensions section of Safari's Settings window.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="27._disable_pointer_acceleration">27. Disable Pointer Acceleration</h2><br/>
Gamers rejoice – you can now disable pointer acceleration in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;. By default in macOS, the pointer moves more quickly for fast mouse movements and more precisely for slow mouse movements. Previously there was no way to prevent this natively, but that's changed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/disable-pointer-acceleration.jpg" alt="" width="1484" height="814" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914547" /><br/>
Go to System Settings -> Mouse -> Advanced..., then toggle off the switch next to Pointer acceleration.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="28._audio_message_improvements">28. Audio Message Improvements</h2><br/>
When recording an audio message, you're now able to pause and then continue recording the same message before sending. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/audio-messages-transcribed.jpg" alt="messages" width="764" height="420" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914549" /><br/>
Additionally, when listening to audio messages you received, a long click on the play button lets you opt to play back at up to 2x speed. Received audio messages are automatically transcribed, too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="29._notes_formatting_additions">29. Notes Formatting Additions</h2><br/>
Block Quote formatting makes it easy to visually offset a section of writing with a quote bar, while Monospaced formatting has been updated to Monostyled, for inset text with a distinct background.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/notes-formatting.jpg" alt="notes" width="1140" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914551" /><br/>
You can find these in the Notes menu bar under Format, or by clicking the text style icon when a note is open.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="30._easier_autocorrect_editing_">30. Easier Autocorrect Editing </h2><br/>
Autocorrection now briefly underlines autocorrected words, and you can right-click an underlined word to reveal and choose the original word that you typed. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/autocorrect-improved.jpg" alt="autocorrect" width="680" height="196" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914555" /><br/>
macOS will also learn your typing habits over time for each app, and avoid corrections that you revert. This also applies to explicit language, which will be added to your personal vocabulary list. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="31._activate_game_mode">31. Activate Game Mode</h2><br/>
Game Mode gives games the highest priority access to your CPU and GPU, lowering usage for background tasks. It turns on automatically when you fullscreen any game via the green button in the top-left corner of the game's window. When you enter full screen in this way, a Game Mode menu appears in the menu bar. You can use this menu to confirm that Game Mode is turned on for your game.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macos-sonoma-2021-imac-game-mode-menu-bar-turn-game-mode-off.jpg" alt="" width="1560" height="540" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913973" /><br/>
Game Mode also turns off automatically when you stop viewing your game in full screen. You can also turn it off while your game is still in full screen mode: From the Game Mode menu in the menu bar, choose Turn Game Mode Off.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="32._high_performance_screen_sharing">32. High Performance Screen Sharing</h2><br/>
Screen Sharing is its own app in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;. It's located in Applications/Utilities, and includes a list of all computers you've connected to in the past, the ability to see all computers on your local network with screen sharing enabled, and the option to create groups of computers. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/high-performance-screen-sharing.jpg" alt="screen sharing" width="860" height="606" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914397" /><br/>
It also features a high performance mode when a screen sharing connection has been established. Click the info (i) button next to a connection, and change the Screen Sharing Type from Standard to High Performance. High performance mode allows you to use the native resolution of the host computer's display, reduces latency, improves image quality, and features HDR and multi-monitor support. The feature is available on Macs with Apple silicon running &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; or later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="33._communication_safety">33. Communication Safety</h2><br/>
Communication Safety is an opt-in feature that warns children when sending or receiving photos that contain nudity. It's enabled by default for children under the age of 13 who are signed in with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> and part of a Family Sharing group, but parents can also enable it for older teens as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/communication-safety-mac.jpg" alt="settings" width="1484" height="762" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914394" /><br/>
When the feature is enabled in System Settings -> Screen Time -> Communication Safety, photos and videos containing nudity are automatically blurred in supported apps including Messages and &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;, and the child will be warned about viewing sensitive content. The warning also provides children with ways to get help. It uses on-device processing to detect photos and videos containing nudity, ensuring that Apple and third parties cannot access the content, and that end-to-end encryption is preserved in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="34._live_speech">34. Live Speech</h2><br/>
Using the new Live Speech accessibility feature, you can type on your Mac and have your words spoken aloud, or directly into apps like ‌&zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;‌ audio. Live Speech can be set up in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; by going to Settings -> Accessibility -> Live Speech, where you can choose a voice to use, and save commonly used phrases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/live-speech-mac.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="907" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914405" /><br/>
Alternatively, you can record yourself reading and make a Personal Voice for use with Live Speech. Go to System Settings -> Accessibility -> Personal Voice, then tap Create a Personal Voice.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="35._copy_icloud_link">35. Copy iCloud Link</h2><br/>
You can now share photos and videos stored in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-photo-library/">iCloud Photos</a> by generating an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> link.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/copy-icloud-link.jpg" alt="photos" width="1514" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914432" /><br/>
Simply select a photo or drag a selection box over several photos, click the Share button, then select Copy &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Link, and it will be copied to your clipboard ready for pasting in an email or message.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="36._wallpaper_to_screen_saver_">36. Wallpaper to Screen Saver </h2><br/>
Sonoma brings all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> screensavers to your Mac - they download on demand to save on storage, and they look great. The way to get the best out of them though, is to use the same video for your wallpaper and screensaver. You can do this using the Show as screen saver / wallpaper toggle in System Settings -> Wallpaper, and Screen Saver.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/sonoma-screensavers.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="1240" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914505" /><br/>
With the toggle enabled, your icons and app windows fade out and the desktop wallpaper starts to move when the screen saver comes on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="37._system_settings_in_spotlight">37. System Settings in Spotlight</h2><br/>
Sonoma lets you toggle system settings like Bluetooth, Wi-Fi, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>, Focus Modes, and more directly in Spotlight search.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/bluetooth-spotlight-setting.jpg" alt="spotlight" width="1249" height="343" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914629" /><br/>
You can still access these settings in Control Center and the System Settings app, but some users will find this method a little quicker. It's the same small yet welcome quality of life improvement that users have seen in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="38._icloud_passwords_extension">38. iCloud Passwords Extension</h2><br/>
Apple's &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; password manager can now be used in Chrome for Mac, Microsoft Edge, and other Chromium-based browsers, thanks to an updated &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Passwords extension that works in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/icloud-passwords-extension.jpg" alt="" width="1074" height="504" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914626" /><br/>
In other words, you don't need to open Safari or migrate your &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; passwords to another password manager. The Chrome extension can also AutoFill passwords and one-time codes, save new passwords, and lets you right-click QR codes to set up code generators. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="39._people__pets">39. People & Pets</h2><br/>
Regular users of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app will be undoubtedly familiar with the People album, which tries to identify faces in your pictures so that you can label people with their proper names and use that label as an organizing element in your library or as a discoverable tag.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/people-and-pets-photos.jpg" alt="photos" width="1288" height="572" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914431" /><br/>
In addition to people, the ‌&zwnj;Photos&zwnj;‌ app in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; can recognize cats and dogs, so you can have your pets automatically sorted into albums. Accordingly, the People album has been renamed the "People & Pets" album. To manually assign your furry friends, type "pets" into the search field in your library, and you can go about identifying any unnamed pets.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="40._auto-hide_menu_bar_options">40. Auto-Hide Menu Bar Options</h2><br/>
In System Settings -> Control Center, there are new options to control when the menu bar automatically hides. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/hide-show-menu-bar.jpg" alt="" width="1496" height="428" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914407" /><br/>
Scroll down to the "Menu Bar Only" section and click the dropdown next to Automatically hide and show the menu bar, and you'll be able to choose from Always, On Desktop Only, On Full Screen Only, and Never.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="41._weather_units">41. Weather Units</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, the Weather app has received an overhaul, and now includes new features like the ability to view the previous day's weather, and a new moon module that tells you the phases of the moon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/weather-settings.jpg" alt="weather" width="2434" height="1486" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914441" /><br/>
In addition to the ability to view temperature in Celsius and Fahrenheit, you can also now change the unit measurements for wind speed, precipitation, pressure, and distance: You can find these options in Weather -> Settings, under the Units section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="42._reminder_grocery_lists">42. Reminder Grocery Lists</h2><br/>
Apple has added a handy little list function to the Reminders app to help you when you're out to pick up some groceries. When you create a list with the new "Groceries" list type (named "Shopping" outside the U.S), you can input various foods and sundries and have them organized automatically by category. The organization makes it easier to find what you need when you're at the grocery store, or out shopping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/groceries-reminder-list.jpg" alt="" width="1300" height="966" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914640" /><br/>
The available category types in Reminders include Produce, Breads & Cereals, Frozen Foods, Snacks & Candy, Meat, Dairy, Eggs & Cheese, Bakery, Baking Items, Household Items, Personal Care & Health, and Wine, Beer & Spirits.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="43._reminder_list_column_view">43. Reminder List Column View</h2><br/>
The Reminders app also features a new scrollable Column view, making it easy to visualize your tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/groceries-list-column.jpg" alt="" width="2312" height="1506" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914639" /><br/>
You can find it in the Reminders menu bar, under View -> as Columns.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="44._hey_siri">44. <del datetime="2023-09-28T14:08:26+00:00">Hey</del> Siri</h2><br/>
In macOS on machines with Apple silicon, you can just say "‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>‌" to activate ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌, dropping the "Hey" that's been used as a wake word for years. ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ will activate when you say the ‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ word, so you can speak more naturally.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/listen-for-hey-siri.jpg" alt="settings" width="1484" height="566" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914426" /><br/>
If the change is causing you to unintentionally wake &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, you can revert it by going to System Settings -> &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; & Spotlight, then select Listen for -> Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="45._share_an_airtag">45. Share an AirTag</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> app now includes the ability to share &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; accessories with multiple people. Up to five other people can share an AirTag or &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network accessory. Simply select the AirTag, then click Add Person under "Share This AirTag" to get started.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/share-airtag.jpg" alt="" width="968" height="713" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914651" /><br/>
Everyone in the sharing group is able to see the item's location, get directions to the item, and play a sound to help pinpoint a shared item's location when nearby.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="46._customize_text_size_per_app">46. Customize Text Size Per App</h2><br/>
You can now set your preferred text size on a per-app basis, thanks to Sonoma's expanded Accessibility settings.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/text-size-per-app.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914664" /><br/>
Go to System Settings -> Accessibility -> Display, then simply choose the app you want to customize text size for and make your point selection. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="47._identify_mail_attachment_downloads">47. Identify Mail Attachment Downloads</h2><br/>
When you download an email attachment from Mail and view it in Finder, the file includes a new mail symbol next to it to let you know it's an email attachment.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/reply-to-email-attachment.jpg" alt="" width="844" height="560" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914669" /><br/>
If you right-click the attachment, there's even a "Reply to [name of sender]" option in the contextual menu that when selected will open the Mail compose window, ready for you to type up your reply message.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="48._visual_look_up_enhancements">48. Visual Look Up Enhancements</h2><br/>
Visual Look Up in &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; has been vastly improved, so you can now find similar recipes from photos of food, map routes to stores identified in photos, and identify the meaning of signs and symbols on things like laundry tags. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/visual-lookup-video.jpg" alt="" width="1658" height="1300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914675" /><br/>
You can also find out information about things that appear in paused video frames.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="49._add-only_calendar_access">49. Add-Only Calendar Access</h2><br/>
In System Settings, a new Privacy & Security -> Calendar setting allows you to give third-party apps write-only access to your calendars.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/add-only-calendar-access.jpg" alt="settings" width="1430" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914679" /><br/>
Selecting this means apps are limited to writing new events to your calendars, without being able to see your information.<br/>
 <br/>
<h2 id="50._sensitive_content_warnings">50. Sensitive Content Warnings</h2><br/>
With Sensitive Content Warnings enabled in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, incoming files, videos, and images are scanned on-device and blocked if they contain nudity. The opt-in blurring can be applied to images in Messages, AirDrop, Contact Posters for the Phone app, &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; messages, and third-party apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/sensitive-content-warning.jpg" alt="settings" width="1498" height="636" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914427" /><br/>
Note that this is separate from the Communication Safety features the Apple has implemented for children, and is designed for people of all ages. You can enable Sensitive Content Warnings by going to System Settings -> Privacy & Security -> Sensitive Content Warning and turning on the requisite toggle.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/50-new-macos-sonoma-features/">macOS Sonoma: 50 New Features and Changes Worth Checking Out</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-50-new-features-and-changes-worth-checking-out.2405581/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CarPlay Not Working for Some iPhone 15 Users, Possibly Because of USB-C Cables</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-carplay-issues/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/carplay-not-working-for-some-iphone-15-users-possibly-because-of-usb-c-cables.2405572/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:27:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-carplay-issues/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> is not working as expected for some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> users, an issue that is likely linked to the transition to USB-C. There are multiple complaints <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-not-working-with-wired-carplay.2404203/">from <em>MacRumors</em> readers</a> and Reddit users who are unable to get &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; to work with their new devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/CarPlay-SharePlay.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899259" /><br/>
Cable type and available port options are a common theme in the &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; reports, with many of the functionality problems linked to USB-A to USB-C cables. Many cars, even some that are more recent, have only USB-A ports and not USB-C ports, so a USB-A to USB-C cable is required.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, it appears that not all USB-A to USB-C cables on the market will work, and some that work in certain vehicles will not work in others. A Reddit user explains:<blockquote>I got in my car this morning and plugged my phone in with a USB-A to USB-C cord in order to use Carplay, and found it does not connect. It charges, but no Carplay. In my Carplay settings on my phone, it says the name of my car as if it were connected, but nothing shows up on the screen.<br/>
<br/>
I work at a dealership so I tried it in a bunch of different cars and nothing worked. My car doesn't have any USB-C ports, so I tried the Apple-supplied C to C cable in a 2023 model and it worked no problem. So it seems that either USB-A to USB-C does not allow Carplay, or it simply does not work anymore with non-Apple chargers.</blockquote>Other &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users chimed in and mentioned having the same problems, though some were able to get &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; to work with USB-A to USB-C cables like those from Belkin. Several people had success getting &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; working with a USB-A port using <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBelkin-Charge-Type-C-Note10-Nintendo%2Fdp%2FB08557ZVLV">Belkin's BoostCharge USB-A to USB-C cable</a>, but others had no luck.<blockquote>Having tried 2 good quality cables I called Apple Support about this. They proceeded through various potential remedies which didn't work. The call ended with me agreeing to try the cable supplied with the phone, after getting a suitable adaptor. When I got home I tried 4 more cables. 3 of them worked, these being ones from Sony, Samsung and Nintendo (I think). Today I tried the Apple cable + adaptor and that works as well. The good quality cables (3 of) all previously gave me no problems, mainly charging but also a high speed PC to VR headset connection. iPhone to Windows PC connection worked fine with one of them (I could connect to my phone in iTunes). I suspect that there is a specification point that the 3 "good quality" cables have missed. If so, I don't know if it is the car or the iPhone that is particular about this spec. point!</blockquote>Trying a variety of cables, specifically those from known brands and with data transfer support, seems to be the best way to get &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; to work, but it is worth noting that some people have not been able to get &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; to work <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CarPlay/comments/16qk5hr/iphone_15_carplay_not_working/">even with</a> Apple's adapters and cables. From Reddit:<blockquote>I have the exact same problem. Have tried (and bought) several different high quality cables, nothing works. Been through all the troubleshooting scripts and AppleCare+. Seems like either an iPhone 15 or an iOS 17 problem.</blockquote>One <em>MacRumors</em> reader that contacted us said that the issue had been reported to Apple and that Apple is working on a fix for the problem. Apple could perhaps implement a software update that improves compatibility with some cables, or the company could better explain which USB-C cables will work with the new iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
While most of the complaints have been from car owners who are limited to USB-A connection ports, there <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-not-working-with-wired-carplay.2404203/?post=32553705#post-32553705">are also reports</a> from some who have vehicles with USB-C ports and even some complaints about wireless &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;. One <em>MacRumors</em> thread suggests that VPNs <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-not-working-with-wired-carplay.2404203/post-32556747">may be responsible</a> for some recent connection issues, though turning off a VPN did not work for all users.<blockquote>Oy, I just went to my car to check and am having the same issue. If a VPN is activated when the car starts, the car will not pick up CarPlay at all. If the VPN is disabled, CarPlay starts, then if I turn the VPN back on CarPlay crashes.</blockquote>With the wide range of reports, there appear to be multiple &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; issues at the current time. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users may need to transition to different cables, but Apple may need to release a software update to solve some of the &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; problems.<br/>
<br/>
If you've had issues with &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-carplay-issues/">CarPlay Not Working for Some iPhone 15 Users, Possibly Because of USB-C Cables</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/carplay-not-working-for-some-iphone-15-users-possibly-because-of-usb-c-cables.2405572/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook on Using Vision Pro: &#039;It&#039;s an Aha Moment&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/tim-cook-on-using-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-on-using-vision-pro-its-an-aha-moment.2405568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 14:00:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/tim-cook-on-using-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said in an interview with <em><a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/tim-cook-interview-apple-vision-pro-b2420852.html">The Independent</a></em> that the upcoming Vision Pro is part of his nightly routine, and that it has convinced him that spatial computing is the future. He described using the Vision Pro as an industry-defining "aha" moment.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898552" /><br/>
"There are huge differences in how people look at it, depending on if they've read about it or actually tried it," said Cook. "I believe even more about how profound spatial computing is. When you've tried it, it's an aha moment, and you only have a few of those in a lifetime."<br/>
<br/>
While analysts don't expect the Vision Pro headset to sell well during its first year of availability, and have expressed skepticism about Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/">ability to bring costs down</a>, Cook remains positive about the headset's future impact.<br/>
<br/>
Cook has been in Europe to meet with app developers, and he said that so far, Apple is seeing "some incredible work." He went on to explain that there's "so much [developer] excitement out there" over the headset, which is set to come out in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
The headset will have a gaming focus, and Apple is solidifying its reputation for gaming with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models. There's an A17 Pro in the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and Pro Max that allows for console-quality gaming, and Apple is working with developers to bring console games to the device. Cook said that Apple is "very serious" about gaming and that it is "not a hobby" for the company. "We're putting all of ourselves out there," he said.<br/>
<br/>
Cook's full interview, which also includes some tidbits about apps being created for Vision Pro, can be read at <em><a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/tim-cook-interview-apple-vision-pro-b2420852.html">The Independent</a></em>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/tim-cook-on-using-vision-pro/">Apple CEO Tim Cook on Using Vision Pro: &#039;It&#039;s an Aha Moment&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-on-using-vision-pro-its-an-aha-moment.2405568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Uses Tiny QR Codes to Track Display Manufacturing Failures and Cut Costs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-displays-tiny-qr-codes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-uses-tiny-qr-codes-to-track-display-manufacturing-failures-and-cut-costs.2405567/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 13:45:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-displays-tiny-qr-codes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple etches <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> displays with small QR codes that let it precisely track the number of defective screens that are thrown out by suppliers, according to a new report from <em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/how-a-hidden-bar-code-in-iphone-screens-saved-apple-hundreds-of-millions-of-dollars">The Information</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-sizes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912524" /><br/>
One barcode is the size of a grain of sand and can be viewed only with special equipment, while the other is on the inside of the display along the bezel. Apple spent millions of dollars developing the barcode process and installing laser scanning equipment at Lens Technology and Biel Crystal, two manufacturers that make the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s cover glass.<br/>
<br/>
With this system, Apple has a precise count of every piece of glass produced by Lens and Biel, and an exact read on how much material is wasted due to defects. A source that spoke to <em>The Information</em> said that when the barcodes were first implemented, Apple found that as many as three out of 10 pieces of cover glass were thrown away due to manufacturing errors, and with pressure from Apple, the suppliers have been able to cut that down to one in 10. Because Apple pays for production, lowering error rates has saved it hundreds of millions of dollars.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has used the display barcodes to streamline manufacturing since 2020, and the company is able to see which company made the glass and the date it was manufactured for tracking production level and yield rate. Other &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; components have had small barcodes to trace defects or find the source of leaks for many years, but prior to the display system, barcodes were primarily used for metal parts.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/how-a-hidden-bar-code-in-iphone-screens-saved-apple-hundreds-of-millions-of-dollars"><em>The Information</em>'s full report</a> goes into more detail on the barcode, including the complex, multi-step process that Apple uses to get the barcodes onto the displays.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-displays-tiny-qr-codes/">Apple Uses Tiny QR Codes to Track Display Manufacturing Failures and Cut Costs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-uses-tiny-qr-codes-to-track-display-manufacturing-failures-and-cut-costs.2405567/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 and 16 Pro: Preliminary Weights and Dimensions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-16-pro-preliminary-weights-and-dimensions.2405558/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:34:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>MacRumors</em> has obtained preliminary information on the weights and dimensions planned for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro, and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max. The information corroborates <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">previous reports</a> suggesting that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and 16 Pro Max will feature larger displays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 and 16 Plus</h2><br/>
Current information suggests that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus will maintain the same dimensions as the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, with the only difference being an increase in weight of around 2 grams for both models – 173g for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, and 203g for &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will be available in the same 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch display sizes as their predecessors.<br/>
<br/>
Regardless of the dimensions, however, the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus are expected to feature a redesigned camera bump, with a vertical camera arrangement similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12. They are also likely to include a capacitive Action button and potentially even an all-new capacitive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">"Capture Button."</a><br/>
<br/>
In terms of materials, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus should use the same type of aluminum found on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; chassis, and will also feature matte back glass. The choice of materials is unlikely to have any significant impact on the weight of the devices, with the increase being a consequence of minor design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Pro and 16 Pro Max</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max will feature an increase in display size compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, measuring roughly 6.3 inches and 6.9 inches, respectively. To be more precise, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro will have a 6.27-inch display (159.31 mm), while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max will feature a 6.85-inch (174.06 mm) panel. <br/>
<br/>
This represents a noticeable increase of 0.2 inches for both models. As a result, the dimensions of the device as a whole will increase. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and 16 Pro Max will be slightly taller than their predecessors, while also being somewhat wider. Interestingly, the width of both devices appears to align with their respective &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14-series counterparts, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro and 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPhone 16 Pro</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Thickness</th><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>149.6 mm</td><br/>
 <td>146.6 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>71.45 mm</td><br/>
 <td>70.60 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Display</th><br/>
 <td>6.3" (159.31 mm)</td><br/>
 <td>6.1" (155.38 mm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>194 grams</td><br/>
 <td>187 grams</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPhone 16 Pro Max</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Thickness</th><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 <td>8.25 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>163.0 mm</td><br/>
 <td>159.9 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>77.58 mm</td><br/>
 <td>76.70 mm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Display</th><br/>
 <td>6.9" (174.06 mm)</td><br/>
 <td>6.7" (169.98 mm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>225 grams</td><br/>
 <td>221 grams</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
As far as materials are concerned, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max are expected to maintain the same Grade 5 Titanium used on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, with the same brushed finish and curved design. Similar to the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro is also expected to feature a slightly larger Action Button, and an entirely new capacitive "Capture Button."<br/>
<br/>
It's worth emphasizing that the information presented here is remarkably early. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is almost a whole year away, and the design is far from being finalized. While changes throughout development are always possible, significant deviations from the dimensions and weights we've listed are unlikely, and the information we've provided represents our best insight into the overall size of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
For additional details on what to expect, check out our dedicated rumor roundup page for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-16-preliminary-weights-dimensions/">iPhone 16 and 16 Pro: Preliminary Weights and Dimensions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-and-16-pro-preliminary-weights-and-dimensions.2405558/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will the iPhone 15 Launch in (PRODUCT)RED Next Year?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-productred-possibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-iphone-15-launch-in-product-red-next-year.2405527/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:18:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-productred-possibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>(PRODUCT)RED</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are available in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/new-iphone-15-iphone-15-plus-color-options/">variety of colors</a>, there is currently no (PRODUCT)RED option for the devices. However, there is a decent possibility that the color will make a reappearance early next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/PRODUCT-RED-Apple.jpg" alt="" width="980" height="551" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914633" /><br/>
Apple has released at least one new iPhone in (PRODUCT)RED <a href="https://twitter.com/TailosiveTech/status/1707450569747791956">every year since 2017</a>, so it seems probable that the color could be introduced for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus in March or April of 2024, in order to boost sales of the devices midway through their product cycle. This is exactly what happened <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/03/21/apple-announces-iphone-7-productred-special-edition/">with the iPhone 7</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/04/09/productred-iphone-8-iphone-8-plus/">iPhone 8 series</a>, which both gained a (PRODUCT)RED option about six to seven months after their initial release.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear if the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max would also be made available in (PRODUCT)RED early next year. Earlier this year, <em>9to5Mac</em> reported that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/23/iphone-15-color-options/">tested a dark red color option</a> for the iPhone 15 Pro models, but leaker @URedditor <a href="https://twitter.com/URedditor/status/1695510448504795253">disputed this claim</a>. Regardless of whether or not the color was tested, there is always a first time for everything, so we shall see what transpires.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone models released in (PRODUCT)RED over the years:<ul><li><strong>2022:</strong> iPhone 14, iPhone 14 Plus, and the third-generation iPhone SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>2021:</strong> iPhone 13 and iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li><strong>2020:</strong> iPhone 12, iPhone 12 mini, and the second-generation iPhone SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>2019:</strong> iPhone 11</li><br/>
<li><strong>2018:</strong> iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, and iPhone XR</li><br/>
<li><strong>2017:</strong> iPhone 7 and iPhone 7 Plus</li></ul>Other mid-cycle color additions have included yellow for the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus in March 2023, green for the entire iPhone 13 lineup in March 2022, and purple for the iPhone 12 and iPhone 12 mini in April 2021.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/productred/">(PRODUCT)RED</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/iphone-15-productred-possibility/">Will the iPhone 15 Launch in (PRODUCT)RED Next Year?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-iphone-15-launch-in-product-red-next-year.2405527/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;199.99 and Up to 90% Off Apple Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-29-23/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-199-99-and-up-to-90-off-apple-accessories.2405519/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 08:57:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-29-23/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're still tracking steep discounts on first party Apple accessories at Woot as we head into the weekend, alongside Anker's best USB-C devices getting marked down on Amazon. In terms of Apple hardware, you'll find some of the best deals ever seen on Apple Watch Ultra and Ultra 2 below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0003.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847993" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C)</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/airpods-pro-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914627" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;49 off the USB-C AirPods Pro 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/new-airpods-pro-2-usb-c/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C/MagSafe Case) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The price on the AirPods Pro 2 has fluctuated over the past few days at Amazon, so if they aren't at &#36;199.99 when you click, be sure to check back again later.<br/>
<br/>
One of the biggest deals of the week came from Amazon, which already has &#36;49 off the all-new AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case. It's available for &#36;199.99, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Woot Apple Accessory Sale</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-watch-charger-yellow-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914568" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to 90% off Apple accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-woot-apple-accessory/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 90% OFF</div>Woot Apple Accessory Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot's Apple accessory sale from earlier this week has changed some of its products on offer, now including the Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for just &#36;34.99, down from &#36;79.00. Other record low prices have hit the MagSafe Duo Charger, various Leather Cases for iPhone 14, and more.<br/>
<br/>
All products in this sale are in new condition and include a one year Apple limited warranty, except for the Beats headphones which include a 90 day Woot limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_14">Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;79.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4">MagSafe Duo Charger</a> - &#36;94.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">iPhone 14 Pro Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro-max-leather-case-with-magsafe%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">iPhone 14 Pro Max Leather Case</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fnew-beats-powerbeats-pro-wireless-earbuds-4%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_8">Powerbeats Pro</a> - &#36;129.95, down from &#36;249.95</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 1 & 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ultra-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914570" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;100 off Apple Watch Ultra (gen 1) and &#36;19 off Apple Watch Ultra 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/deals-apple-watch-ultra-698/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra for &#36;698.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;779.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With the launch of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 last week, we're tracking notable discounts on the original model at Amazon. You can get the Apple Watch ultra for as low as &#36;698.99, down from &#36;799.00. If you want the latest model, Amazon has it for &#36;779.99, down from &#36;799.00. Although this isn't a particularly steep markdown, if you had your eye on an Ultra 2 at launch this is the best cash discount you'll find around online.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/anker-yellow-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914571" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on USB-C accessories from Anker</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392060864">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/deals-anker-usb-c-batteries-chargers/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
We tracked quite a few Anker discounts this week, mainly focusing on USB-C accessories for your new iPhone 15. You'll find all of the best Anker discounts listed below, including deals on portable batteries, MagSafe chargers, and more. A highlight of the sale is the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695391997901">Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> at &#36;99.99 for Amazon Prime members, down from &#36;149.99.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK6DDL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1695997078084">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392060864">3-Port Compact USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;47.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C5QY4BL2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21QB6T2P2WP1O_1695997144955">Nano Charging Station USB-C Power Strip</a> - &#36;52.79 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BSGH355C%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392107984">6-in-1 USB-C Compact Power Strip</a> - &#36;93.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695391997901">Power Bank 24,000 mAh with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BYNZXFM2%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1695392166960">Power Bank 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;110.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;129.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macbook-air-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914573" /><ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;249 off M1 and M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/kw/APMLY33LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612">B&H Photo</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-5/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/kw/APMLY33LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Two MacBook Air discounts remain available as we head into October, including the M1 13-inch model at &#36;749.99 (&#36;249 off) and the M2 13-inch model at &#36;899.00 (&#36;200 off). Both of these represent best-ever prices on the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-29-23/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Get AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C for &#36;199.99 and Up to 90% Off Apple Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-get-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-for-199-99-and-up-to-90-off-apple-accessories.2405519/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Should You Buy the Apple Watch Series 9?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-watch-series-9/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-should-you-buy-the-apple-watch-series-9.2405504/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 07:58:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-watch-series-9/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/should-you-buy-the-new-apple-watch-series-9/id1602394741?i=1000629651715">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the latest Apple Watch models, who should upgrade, and consider whether it is worth waiting for the rumored "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SFss7eAWEmo?si=Wd4BU_ulHw9USaCe" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
After spending several days with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, we discuss our initial experiences with the new devices, their design, and some of their standout features such as the Action button and USB-C port. We also return to the matter of Apple's FineWoven accessories, which appear to have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">received relatively poorly</a> by customers.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> feature brighter displays, a Double Tap gesture for touch-free control, the S9 chip, locally processed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> for faster responses and access to health data, the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip for Precision Finding and deeper <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> integration, and 64GB of storage. We talk through some of our favorite features of the new devices and weigh up who should consider upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
On a related matter, we take a look at the "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">Apple Watch X</a>," a complete overhaul of the device expected to launch next year. It is rumored to feature thinner casings, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">larger displays</a>, microLED technology, larger batteries, blood pressure monitoring, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">new mechanism</a> for connecting bands.<br/>
<br/>
Listen to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> in <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cub21ueWNvbnRlbnQuY29tL2QvcGxheWxpc3QvNjk1NTlmZTgtMzMxOC00ZDI5LTkyMmYtYWJlMTAwNjhjYTYzLzg1OTRmODNjLTBkN2QtNDhkOS04OTcxLWFkZmEwMTAzOWEzMS9kODA4NmM5Ni1iNmQ4LTRkNWMtYTZiMy1hZGZhMDEwM2M4NmQvcG9kY2FzdC5yc3M%3d">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player. Watch a video version of the show <a href="https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLD8VmuL7qc7ii5uyjzSRk3UM7KI_c4qC5">on the <em>MacRumors</em> YouTube channel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; background: transparent;" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741" height="450" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-storage-access-by-user-activation allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-features/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's new FineWoven accessories, some of our favorite <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> features, and who should consider upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for more episodes, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/20/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-talks-iphone-14/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/09/iphone-14-event-reactions-with-luke-miani/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the show, and let us know what subjects you would like the podcast to cover in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/the-macrumors-show-apple-watch-series-9/">The MacRumors Show: Should You Buy the Apple Watch Series 9?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-should-you-buy-the-apple-watch-series-9.2405504/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Get the 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air for All-Time Low Price of &#36;899 (&#36;200 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-get-the-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-for-all-time-low-price-of-899-200-off.2405481/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 06:24:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air has dropped to <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/kw/APMLY33LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> today on B&H Photo, down from &#36;1,099.00. B&H Photo offers free two-day shipping in the contiguous United States, and has all four colors of Space Gray, Silver, Midnight, and Starlight at this price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/macbook-air-spacegray-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1428" height="802" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-887878" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is an all-time low price on the 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air, and B&H Photo's deal on it will last through 5:30 p.m. Central Time today. B&H Photo also has the <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710306-REG/apple_mly43ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/kw/APMLY43LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612">512GB model at &#36;200 off</a>, which is a solid second-best price on that notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/kw/APMLY33LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for an even steeper discount, and don't mind an older model MacBook Air, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/deals-apples-m1-macbook-air-5/">Amazon has the M1 MacBook Air for &#36;749.99</a> this week. Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/deals-13-inch-m2-macbook-air/">Deals: Get the 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air for All-Time Low Price of &#36;899 (&#36;200 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-get-the-13-inch-m2-macbook-air-for-all-time-low-price-of-899-200-off.2405481/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Ramp Up Generative AI Research With New Hires and Investment</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-to-ramp-up-ai-research/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-ramp-up-generative-ai-research-with-new-hires-and-investment.2405471/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 05:22:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-to-ramp-up-ai-research/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>AppleGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple wants to hire more staff to work on artificial intelligence in the United Kingdom, CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today said (via <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-66954267"><em>BBC News</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Cook reaffirmed that Apple is actively researching generative AI technology, and said that he expects Apple's investment in the UK and AI to increase. He also highlighted how AI is already behind several features on Apple devices, such as Fall Detection, Crash Detection, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>'s predictive autocorrect.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is believed to now be spending <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/apple-conversational-ai-spending/">millions of dollars a day</a> on conversational AI research. The company is reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/15/apple-engineers-working-on-chatgpt-like-ai/">working on</a> a chatbot tool that some engineers have dubbed "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/19/apple-experimenting-with-chatgpt-tool/">Apple GPT</a>" to rival OpenAI's ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
Cook is currently visiting the UK following trips to several other countries in Europe. Yesterday, he visited St. Mary's Primary School and Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/15/apple-battersea-opens-today/">new store in Battersea Power Station</a>. Earlier today, he met the Prince and Princess of Wales.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It was a true honor to meet with the Prince and Princess of Wales. We had a wonderful and wide-ranging discussion about the environment, mental health, and other issues that mean a great deal to all of us. <a href="https://t.co/QGVmxo9Qa5">pic.twitter.com/QGVmxo9Qa5</a></p>&mdash; Tim Cook (@tim_cook) <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook/status/1707687882037645717?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 29, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The move to hire more staff appears to come in contrast to widespread redundancies at big tech companies. Yesterday, it emerged that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/epic-games-layoffs/">laying off over 800 employees</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applegpt/">AppleGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-to-ramp-up-ai-research/">Apple to Ramp Up Generative AI Research With New Hires and Investment</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-ramp-up-generative-ai-research-with-new-hires-and-investment.2405471/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple iOS Update to Fix iPhone 12 Radiation Levels Approved by French Regulators</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-software-update-approved-iphone-12-france/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ios-update-to-fix-iphone-12-radiation-levels-approved-by-french-regulators.2405456/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 03:23:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-software-update-approved-iphone-12-france/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>France</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has had its software update for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 devices in France approved by regulators, after the company threatened to suspend sales of the phones earlier this month due to radiation levels (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/french-authorities-approve-apples-software-update-its-iphone-12-2023-09-29/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/purple-iphone-12-and-12-mini.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-805183" /><br/>
In early September, France <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/france-orders-end-to-iphone-12-sales-radiation/">ordered</a> Apple to halt ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12 sales and "fix" existing devices to bring them into electromagnetic radiation compliance with European standards. The increase in emitted electromagnetic radiation observed over time by regulators appears to have been the result of successive software updates issued by Apple, and was not present when the ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12 was launched in 2020.<br/>
<br/>
The ANFR ordered Apple to "remove the ‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12‌ from the French market from September 12 due to the model exceeding the limit" for electromagnetic absorption by the body. The agency also told Apple to recall every ‌‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 12‌ it has ever sold in the country. Ministers later said that though the radiation level was above the accepted standard, it was not dangerous and people were safe to continue using the phones, local media reported.<br/>
<br/>
Apple later said it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-12-software-update-france-radiation/">issue a software update</a> for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 users in France to address the radiation concerns. The French regulator ANFR responded by saying it would test the software update. If it made a difference to the electromagnetic waves the device emitted, ANFR said it would bring the model into compliance with European standards applied in France, and the marketing withdrawal order would be lifted.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-software-update-approved-iphone-12-france/">Apple iOS Update to Fix iPhone 12 Radiation Levels Approved by French Regulators</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ios-update-to-fix-iphone-12-radiation-levels-approved-by-french-regulators.2405456/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 Buyer&#039;s Guide: How Incremental Upgrades Stack Up Over the Years</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-generations-compared/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-buyers-guide-how-incremental-upgrades-stack-up-over-the-years.2405453/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:57:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-generations-compared&#038;post_date=1695992243/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch has received some incremental updates in recent years, with significant upgrades becoming fewer and farther between as the device has progressed. Since the Apple Watch's generation-over-generation enhancements are relatively small, it is all the more important to consider when an upgrade is justified and whether an older model could suffice for your needs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-914497" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>'s headline upgrade is the S9 chip, bringing improved performance to the Apple Watch for the first time in four years and facilitating features like Double Tap. It is priced starting at &#36;399. Last year's Series 8 introduced body temperature sensing and Crash Detection, but the last moderately significant update for the device was 2021's Series 7, which introduced larger display sizes and fast-charging capability. All previous Apple Watch models from before the Series 9 have been discontinued, but older models may still be found for even lower prices from third-party retailers or second-hand.<br/>
<br/>
Read on to see the breakdown below for each new feature, change, and improvement that was added with each Apple Watch model compared to its direct predecessor. Viewing each generation's changes in this way helps weigh up the accumulative upgrades one receives by skipping multiple generations when buying a new device, as well as get a sense of which generations offered the biggest overall upgrades.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_9_2023">Apple Watch Series 9 (2023)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Retina display with up to 2,000 nits of brightness</li><br/>
<li>Display can get dimmer in dark rooms and at night (down to 1 nit of brightness)</li><br/>
<li>Double Tap gesture</li><br/>
<li>S9 chip (based on A15 Bionic)</li><br/>
<li>4-core Neural Engine (x2 faster than Series 8)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>‌ processed on-device for requests that do not need information from the internet</li><br/>
<li>‌&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;‌ can access health and fitness data</li><br/>
<li>25% more accurate dictation</li><br/>
<li>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip</li><br/>
<li>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> proximity integration</li><br/>
<li>64GB storage</li><br/>
<li>Pink aluminum casing introduced</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_8_2022">Apple Watch Series 8 (2022)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>S8 chip (same CPU as S6)</li><br/>
<li>More powerful gyroscope and high dynamic range accelerometer</li><br/>
<li>‌Crash Detection</li><br/>
<li>Body temperature sensor</li><br/>
<li>Wrist temperature sensing during sleep</li><br/>
<li>Cycle tracking with retrospective ovulation estimates</li><br/>
<li>Blue and Green aluminum casings discontinued, Silver aluminum reintroduced</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Edition discontinued</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_7_2021">Apple Watch Series 7 (2021)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>41mm and 45mm case sizes</li><br/>
<li>1.7mm display borders for almost 20% more screen area than Series 6</li><br/>
<li>QWERTY keyboard</li><br/>
<li>Up to 70% brighter display than Series 6 indoors when wrist is down</li><br/>
<li>S7 chip (Same CPU as S6)</li><br/>
<li>Crack-resistant front crystal (50% thicker)</li><br/>
<li>IP6X dust resistance</li><br/>
<li>Fast charging for up to 80% charge in about 45 minutes (33% faster than Series 6)</li><br/>
<li>Silver and Space Gray aluminum casings discontinued, Midnight, Starlight, and Green introduced</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_6_2020">Apple Watch Series 6 (2020)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Up to 2.5x brighter always-on display</li><br/>
<li>Access Notification Center, Control Center, and Complications when display is asleep</li><br/>
<li>S6 chip (based on A13 Bionic, 20% faster than S5)</li><br/>
<li>Always-on altimeter</li><br/>
<li>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</li><br/>
<li>2.4GHz and 5GHz Wi-Fi</li><br/>
<li>Blood oxygen sensor</li><br/>
<li>Faster charging for a full charge in under 1.5 hours</li><br/>
<li>Improved battery life for tracking certain workouts, such as indoor and outdoor runs</li><br/>
<li>Blue and (PRODUCT)RED aluminum casing options introduced</li><br/>
<li>Space Black stainless steel casing available with Apple Watch Hermès only, Graphite option introduced</li><br/>
<li>Ceramic Apple Watch Edition discontinued</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_5_2019">Apple Watch Series 5 (2019)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Always-on Retina display</li><br/>
<li>Force Touch removed</li><br/>
<li>S5 chip</li><br/>
<li>Compass</li><br/>
<li>32GB storage</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Edition reintroduced with White Ceramic, Natural Titanium, and Space Black Titanium casing options</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_4_2018">Apple Watch Series 4 (2018)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>40mm and 44mm case sizes</li><br/>
<li>Over 30% larger display with curved corners</li><br/>
<li>3.0mm display borders</li><br/>
<li>S4 chip (2x faster than S3)</li><br/>
<li>Gyroscope and accelerometer</li><br/>
<li>Barometric altimeter</li><br/>
<li>Fall detection</li><br/>
<li>2.4GHz Wi-Fi</li><br/>
<li>Optical heart sensor and electrical heart sensor for ECG</li><br/>
<li>16GB storage</li><br/>
<li>Digital Crown with haptic feedback</li><br/>
<li>50% louder speaker</li><br/>
<li>Relocated microphone for reduced echo and better sound quality</li><br/>
<li>Faster charging for a full charge in 1.5 hours</li><br/>
<li>Gold stainless steel casing introduced</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Edition discontinued</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_3_2017">Apple Watch Series 3 (2017)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>S3 chip (70% faster than S2)</li><br/>
<li>Barometric altimeter</li><br/>
<li>Bluetooth 4.2</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; able to speak through the onboard speaker</li><br/>
<li>LTE cellular model available with red Digital Crown</li><br/>
<li>Rose Gold aluminum casing discontinued</li><br/>
<li>Gray Ceramic Apple Watch Edition model introduced</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_2_2016">Apple Watch Series 2 (2016)</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Retina display with up to 1,000 nits of brightness (2x brighter than previous generation)</li><br/>
<li>S2 chip (dual‑core)</li><br/>
<li>GPS and GLONASS receiver </li><br/>
<li>Water resistant up to 50 meters</li><br/>
<li>Gold and Rose Gold aluminum casing options added</li><br/>
<li>18K Gold and Rose Gold Apple Watch Edition discontinued, Ceramic model introduced in White</li><br/>
<li>Apple Watch Nike+ variant introduced</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; does not seem to provide a meaningful upgrade for most Series 7 and Series 8 users. If you have an Apple Watch Series 6 or older, upgrading to the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; will generally be worthwhile, with plenty of new features across the board. Discounted Apple Watch Series 7 and Series 8 models are also a good option for those coming from a Series 6 or older if you are looking to save money.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">considered moving</a> the Apple Watch away from an annual upgrade cycle to offer more substantial updates less frequently. Next year's Apple Watch "Series X" is rumored to be a significant update to mark the tenth anniversary of the device, featuring thinner casings, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">larger displays</a>, microLED technology, larger batteries, blood pressure monitoring, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/gurman-apple-watch-x-redesign-planned/">new mechanism</a> for connecting bands.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-generations-compared/">Apple Watch Series 9 Buyer&#039;s Guide: How Incremental Upgrades Stack Up Over the Years</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-buyers-guide-how-incremental-upgrades-stack-up-over-the-years.2405453/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple &#039;Concerned&#039; About China&#039;s New App Store Rules Banning Unregistered Foreign Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-china-discuss-rules-banning-western-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-concerned-about-chinas-new-app-store-rules-banning-unregistered-foreign-apps.2405451/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 02:46:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-china-discuss-rules-banning-western-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple staff met with Chinese officials in recent months to discuss concerns over new rules that will restrict Apple from offering many foreign apps currently available in its China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, according to a new paywalled <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/apple-china-met-to-discuss-beijings-crackdown-on-western-apps-2219afcb">Wall Street Journal</a></em> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Desaturated.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833991" /><br/>
China already blocks the websites of many popular Western social media apps like Instagram, X (formerly Twitter), Facebook, YouTube, and WhatsApp, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in China can still download the apps from Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; if they use an unauthorized VPN that connects them to an internet server outside the country. China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/07/31/russia-bans-vpns-apple-pulls-apps-china/">banned VPN services</a> from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
The five social media apps named above have been downloaded from Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; more than 170 million times in China over the last decade, according to estimates by Sensor Tower.<br/>
<br/>
According to the report, Chinese officials told Apple staff that it must strictly implement rules banning unregistered foreign apps, thereby closing a loophole allowing Chinese &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to download them.<br/>
<br/>
Under new rules issued in July by China's Ministry of Industry and Information Technology, Apple will no longer be able to offer such apps in its China &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; from next July unless the app operators are registered with the government. The new rules affect both foreign and domestic app distributors, and aren't specifically targeting Apple.<br/>
<br/>
However, the operators are unlikely to register with the Chinese government, since doing so would force them to comply with data transfer and censorship requirements. Such a scenario would leave Apple with no choice but to remove them or face legal sanctions.<br/>
<br/>
Investors are said to be concerned about how the new rules will affect Apple's services bottom line, which includes &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; transactions. Apple is also said to be concerned about issues the company could face in implementing the rules, such as whether users in China who access foreign apps through its overseas app stores would be able to continue to do so.<br/>
<br/>
According to the report, Apple was told during the recent discussions that the new rules are needed to crack down on online scams, pornography, and the circulation of information that violates China's censorship rules.<br/>
<br/>
China has recently banned government officials from using iPhones and other foreign smartphones for work or from bringing such devices to their government offices, and earlier this month the ban was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/07/china-expanding-government-iphone-ban/">expanded</a> to multiple state agencies and state companies, highlighting China's renewed attempts to block foreign technology.<br/>
<br/>
China is an important market for Apple, with the region accounting for about a fifth of its sales. Most of Apple's manufacturing base remains in the country, despite the company's efforts in recent years to diversify its supply chain to places like Vietnam and India.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/29/apple-china-discuss-rules-banning-western-apps/">Apple &#039;Concerned&#039; About China&#039;s New App Store Rules Banning Unregistered Foreign Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-concerned-about-chinas-new-app-store-rules-banning-unregistered-foreign-apps.2405451/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will There Be An Apple Event in October?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-october-event-possibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-there-be-an-apple-event-in-october.2405390/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 16:34:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-october-event-possibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It is typical for Apple to hold up to four events per year: one in the spring, WWDC in June, the fall <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> event, and a fourth fall event that's Mac and/or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> focused. Unfortunately, there are few additional product announcements planned for the final months of 2023, and it's looking like there won't be another fall event this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/ipad-air-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904045" /><br/>
Earlier this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> told <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> hosts that he <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/gurman-october-apple-event-unlikely/">does not expect</a> Apple to hold an October event because the company does not have enough new products and features to justify it. Major new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac launches are not expected until 2024, suggesting it will be a slow holiday season for Apple outside of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
During Apple's August earnings call, CFO Luca Maestri said that Mac and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; revenue is expected to drop double digits. Last October, Apple introduced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models and a 10th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, plus it was still seeing sales of the redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> during the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's warning about the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac revenue drop suggests that it does not expect to have products to entice customers during the holiday quarter, and that is in line with rumors.<br/>
<br/>
There is a possibility that we will see <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/09/gurman-october-apple-event-unlikely/">at least one iPad</a> unveiled in October, perhaps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/apple-ipad-mini-7-release-late-2023/">an iPad mini</a>, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, or an 11th-generation low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, but these will be minor refreshes. &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models with OLED displays and M3 chips won't be coming until 2024.<br/>
<br/>
We could also see at least one Mac with a new M3 chip, and this could be a &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, 13-inch MacBook Pro, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, or a 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>. Gurman said that if these products do come out in 2023, Apple is likely to unveil them via press release rather than with an event.<br/>
<br/>
While Gurman believes M3 Macs could come out in 2023, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said recently that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/kuo-first-m3-macbooks-unlikely-2023/">will not launch</a> new MacBook models with M3 processors before the end of the year, which may narrow down any M3 Mac releases to desktop models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did not hold an October event last year, but there were October events in 2013, 2014, 2016, 2018, 2020, and 2021.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-october-event-possibility/">Will There Be An Apple Event in October?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-there-be-an-apple-event-in-october.2405390/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
