<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2024 02:03:53 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.2.1 for iPhone Now Confirmed as iOS 18.3 Beta Testing Continues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/ios-18-2-1-confirmed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-1-for-iphone-now-confirmed-as-ios-18-3-beta-testing-continues.2446063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 13:38:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/ios-18-2-1-confirmed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following our report that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/21/apple-preparing-ios-18-2-1/">internally testing iOS 18.2.1 for the iPhone</a>, an anonymous social media account with a proven track record of sharing iOS-related information has revealed the upcoming software update's build number: 22C161.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
With the build number now known, the update is now confirmed. <br/>
<br/>
When the anonymous account shares a build number for an upcoming iOS version, the update is usually released no more than a week later. However, given it is currently the holiday season, it could take longer for the update to be released. We continue to respect the account's request that we not link to their social media posts.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.2.1 should be a minor update that fixes bugs and/or addresses security vulnerabilities, but it is unclear which specific issues might be resolved. There are not any critical, widespread bugs that we know about at this particular time, but Apple has obviously identified various bugs and/or security vulnerabilities that it wants to patch ahead of iOS 18.3.<br/>
<br/>
Apple began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/16/apple-releases-ios-18-3-beta-1/">testing iOS 18.3</a> with developers and public beta testers earlier this month. That update is likely to be released to all users in January or early February, and only minor changes have been discovered in it so far.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/ios-18-2-1-confirmed/">iOS 18.2.1 for iPhone Now Confirmed as iOS 18.3 Beta Testing Continues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-1-for-iphone-now-confirmed-as-ios-18-3-beta-testing-continues.2446063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains Why It Doesn&#039;t Plan to Create a Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-explains-why-it-wont-make-search-engine/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-it-doesnt-plan-to-create-a-search-engine.2446055/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 11:50:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-explains-why-it-wont-make-search-engine/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's senior vice president of services Eddy Cue has explained why the iPhone maker does not plan to create a search engine like Google.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/applegoogle.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-736930" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://fingfx.thomsonreuters.com/gfx/legaldocs/zgvoalybovd/apple%20declaration.pdf">declaration</a> filed with a U.S. federal court in Washington, D.C. last week, Cue said Apple is against the idea for the following reasons:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>The development of a search engine would cost Apple "billions of dollars" and "take many years," and this would divert investment money and employees away from "other growth areas" that the company is focused on.</li><br/>
<li>The search business is "rapidly evolving" due to artificial intelligence, so it would be "economically risky" for Apple to create a search engine.</li><br/>
<li>In order to create a "viable" search engine business, Apple would be required to "sell targeted advertising," which is "not a core business" for the company and would go against its "longstanding privacy commitments."</li><br/>
<li>Apple does not have enough "specialized professionals" and "operational infrastructure" needed to build and run a successful search engine business.</li></ul>Earlier this year, as part of the U.S. Department of Justice's antitrust trial against Google, the court declared that the deal that sees Google set as the default search engine in Apple's web browser Safari <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/google-search-antitrust-monopoly/">is illegal</a>. In his declaration, Cue asked the court to allow Apple to defend the deal by having its own witnesses testify during the trial.<br/>
<br/>
"Only Apple can speak to what kinds of future collaborations can best serve its users," wrote Cue. "Apple is relentlessly focused on creating the best user experience possible and explores potential partnerships and arrangements with other companies to make that happen."<br/>
<br/>
As part of the deal, Cue revealed that Google paid Apple roughly &#36;20 billion in 2022 alone.<br/>
<br/>
If the agreement can no longer continue, Cue said "it would hamstring Apple's ability to continue delivering products that best serve its users' needs."<br/>
<br/>
The declaration was earlier <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-seeks-defend-googles-billion-dollar-payments-search-case-2024-12-24/">reported <em>by Reuters</em></a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-explains-why-it-wont-make-search-engine/">Apple Explains Why It Doesn&#039;t Plan to Create a Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-it-doesnt-plan-to-create-a-search-engine.2446055/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are the Three Apple Products You&#039;re Most Likely to Unwrap This Christmas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/three-apple-products-likely-to-unwrap-this-christmas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-three-apple-products-youre-most-likely-to-unwrap-this-christmas.2446053/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/three-apple-products-likely-to-unwrap-this-christmas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		<category>Piper Jaffray</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With such a wide array of products now available, Apple devices will be under the Christmas trees of many families this season. However, there are three that are most likely to be there.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/m4-ipad-pro-snowflakes.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-979386" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.statista.com/chart/20055/items-brands-most-often-mentioned-as-a-top-item-on-teens-holiday-wishlist/">Piper Jaffray</a> surveys, Apple is constantly among the most desired brands among teens, appearing in 10% of all holiday wish lists, far ahead of competitors like Nike and Louis Vuitton.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>AirPods</h3><br/>
AirPods are one of the most popular tech gifts during the holidays. In a <a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/1350738/top-tech-gifts-by-number-of-buyers-us/">2022 Statista survey</a>, headphones and earbuds were ranked as the most sought-after tech gift, with 61 million U.S. adults planning to buy them during the season.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/airpods-4-holiday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-981158" /><br/>
Given Apple's popularity and AirPods' market dominance, it's likely they make up a significant portion of these purchases. Their relatively affordable price point compared to other Apple products, combined with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#airpods">frequent discounts</a>, cements their place as a top holiday gift.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently released the fourth-generation AirPods in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4-vs-airpods-4-with-anc-buyers-guide-which-should-you-choose/">two variants</a>: one entry-level model for &#36;129 and one higher-end model with active noise cancellation and wireless charging for &#36;179, which is also likely to drive gifting around this time of year.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Watch</h3><br/>
The Apple Watch has become a go-to gift for all ages, and its popularity as a holiday gift continues to grow. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-watch-bands.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-980992" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/holiday-iphones-ipads-and-macs-maybe">recent data</a> from Consumer Intelligence Research Partners (CIRP), 9% of Apple Watch owners reported receiving their watch as a gift during the holiday season, compared to just 2% the rest of the year. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has expanded the Apple Watch lineup since 2020, adding the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> and the premium Apple Watch Ultra, offering three distinctly different models that cater to a wide range of users and budgets. Somewhat similar to AirPods, Apple Watches <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#apple_watch">frequently see discounts</a> and the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; starts at just &#36;249, making it an ideal gift.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iPad</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> remains a popular holiday gift, particularly for families and students, thanks to its versatility and range of models catering to different needs. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/ipad-air-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-975372" /><br/>
CIRP data shows that 6% of &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; buyers received their device as a gift during the holiday season, compared to just 2% in other quarters.<br/>
<br/>
The 10th generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, starting at &#36;349, offers a highly accessible excellent entry point into Apple's tablet lineup. With its 10.9-inch display, A14 Bionic chip, and support for accessories like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> and Magic Keyboard Folio, it's a good choice for anyone seeking a low-cost, all-purpose device for entertainment or light productivity. For those looking to spend more, Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> provide additional options.<br/>
<br/>
Like the AirPods and Apple Watch, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; often sees <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#ipad">discounts</a> in the lead up to the holiday period, ensuring that it remains one of the most popular holiday gifts.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>What About iPhones and Macs?</h3><br/>
Despite their popularity, Apple's other flagship products—the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Mac—are rarely given as gifts. CIRP data indicates that close to 0% of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; buyers and just 1% of Mac buyers received their devices as gifts during the holiday season. The reasons for this are relatively straightforward: both products are expensive, and gifting them often involves somewhat more complex buying decisions, such as signing up for carrier plans or selecting memory configurations.<br/>
<br/>
What Apple devices are you gifting this holiday season? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/piper-jaffray/">Piper Jaffray</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/three-apple-products-likely-to-unwrap-this-christmas/">Here Are the Three Apple Products You&#039;re Most Likely to Unwrap This Christmas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-the-three-apple-products-youre-most-likely-to-unwrap-this-christmas.2446053/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#36;99 Apple TV Might Make a Comeback Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/99-dollar-apple-tv-is-a-possibility-next-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/99-apple-tv-might-make-a-comeback-next-year.2446051/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 09:00:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/99-dollar-apple-tv-is-a-possibility-next-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new Apple TV streaming box is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/12/apple-tv-homepod-mini-2025-launch/">rumored to launch next year</a>, and there is a possibility that the device's U.S. pricing will start at just &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-4k-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953895" /><br/>
Shortly after the current Apple TV 4K model launched in October 2022, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo predicted that the next Apple TV would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">"more affordable" than the current model</a>. He said a "sub-&#36;100 price" would be the "sweet spot" for the Apple TV, but exact pricing for the next model remains to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
Both the 2010 and 2012 versions of the Apple TV were priced at &#36;99 in the U.S. at launch, and Apple eventually lowered the price of the 2012 model to &#36;69, so there is precedent for a sub-&#36;100 Apple TV that would better compete with lower-priced streaming devices like the Google TV Streamer, which costs &#36;99.99. Amazon and Roku have even cheaper streaming stick options starting as low as &#36;24.99 on sale.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., the current Apple TV starts at &#36;129 with 64GB of storage, and a 128GB model with an added Ethernet port is available for &#36;149.<br/>
<br/>
Rumored features for the next Apple TV include a faster A-series chip and Wi-Fi 6E support.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">built-in camera has also been rumored</a> for a future Apple TV model. tvOS 17 added a FaceTime app to the Apple TV, allowing for users to have video calls by using the rear camera on a connected iPhone or iPad. If the Apple TV gained a built-in camera, users would no longer need to rely on an external device for video calls on the TV.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear exactly when in 2025 the new Apple TV will be released.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/99-dollar-apple-tv-is-a-possibility-next-year/">&#36;99 Apple TV Might Make a Comeback Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/99-apple-tv-might-make-a-comeback-next-year.2446051/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirTag 2 Launching Next Year With These New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/what-to-expect-from-airtag-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airtag-2-launching-next-year-with-these-new-features.2446048/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 08:35:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/what-to-expect-from-airtag-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to release an AirTag 2 next year, and a few new features and changes have already been rumored for the item tracker.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/AirTag-and-Lavender-iPhone.jpg" alt="" width="1001" height="563" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796089" /><br/>
Below, we recap what to expect from the AirTag 2:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>The new AirTag is expected to be equipped with Apple's second-generation Ultra Wideband chip for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/15/airtag-2-longer-range-rumor/"><strong>longer range</strong></a>. The chip debuted last year in the iPhone 15 and the Apple Watch Ultra 2, and Apple said it offers up to three times the range as its first-generation Ultra Wideband chip in the current AirTag. On the iPhone 15 and iPhone 16 models, there is a Precision Finding feature that can help you to find your friends in busy places, and it offers up to approximately 60 meters (around 200 feet) range. The new AirTag could offer similar range.</li><br/>
<li>The new AirTag's <strong>built-in speaker is expected to be more difficult to remove</strong>, as a stalking-related safety measure.</li><br/>
<li>The new AirTag is rumored to have <strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/02/kuo-new-airtag-production-late-2024/">improved integration with the Apple Vision Pro</a></strong>, but there are no specific details about this.</li><br/>
<li>No major design changes are expected.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The new AirTag is rumored to launch in mid-2025. The current AirTag debuted in April 2021.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/what-to-expect-from-airtag-2/">AirTag 2 Launching Next Year With These New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airtag-2-launching-next-year-with-these-new-features.2446048/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/5-holiday-camera-features-to-try-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2446036/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 08:10:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/5-holiday-camera-features-to-try-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the holiday season, capturing photos and videos of the festivities with family and friends is an important activity for many. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> has a suite of camera features that can significantly elevate the quality and creativity of your holiday photos and videos. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Five-iPhone-Camera-Features-to-Try-This-Holiday-Season-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-927844" /><br/>
It's easy to forget about many of the individual camera features the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has to offer, and many capabilities go unused by most users, so the holidays is the perfect time to revisit them and try something new. For users of Apple's latest models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> takes things even further with several enhanced camera features and the all-new Camera Control.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Spatial Video Capture</h3><br/>
For users of more recent &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, the holiday season presents an ideal opportunity to experiment with Spatial Video capture feature. Available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro Max, and all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, the feature allows users to record videos in a three-dimensional format, bringing a new level of depth and realism to holiday memories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
While Apple's Vision Pro or a device like the Meta Quest 3 is required for the best experience when playing back Spatial Video, this should not deter users from exploring the feature. Spatial Video capture is available to help users begin creating a library of immersive videos right away, regardless of whether they have a headset device yet. Spatial Videos can also be played back as normal 2D content on other devices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/record-spatial-video-iphone/">How to Record Spatial Video</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The technology behind Spatial Video Capture involves using the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s Main and Ultra Wide cameras. When recording, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; seamlessly combines inputs from these cameras to create a single video file that encapsulates a three-dimensional perspective. This is achieved through sophisticated computational videography techniques, which intelligently scale the field of view from the Ultra Wide camera to match that of the Main camera.<br/>
<br/>
The result is a video that, while technically 2D in format, contains depth information that can be utilized by compatible devices to produce a 3D viewing experience. The spatial dimension added to these videos creates a sense of immersion and presence that far surpasses traditional video, supposedly making the viewer feel as if they are actually part of the captured moment. However, it's worth noting that Spatial Video capture works best in good lighting. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ultra Wide-Angle Lens for Group Shots</h3><br/>
The holiday season presents the perfect opportunity to utilize the often under-utilized Ultra Wide camera lens. This lens, available on most &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models starting from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, offers unique advantages that are particularly useful during the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/iphone-11-pro-ultra-wide.jpg" alt="" width="2264" height="1186" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-722975" /><br/>
The Ultra Wide lens is particularly adept at photography in confined spaces that would be difficult to capture fully with the standard Wide lens. One of the most significant advantages of the Ultra Wide lens is its ability to fit more into the frame without needing to move back, and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; displays the Ultra Wide camera's feed outside the frame of the Wide camera by default in the camera app. This is especially helpful during family gatherings where you might want to capture a large group of people in one photo.<br/>
<br/>
The Ultra Wide camera got a considerable upgrade with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, jumping to 48-megapixels to match the Main camera, resulting in considerably sharper, higher-resolution output and better low-light performance.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Cinematic Mode</h3><br/>
The holiday season is a good time for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 and newer model users to try out Cinematic mode, a feature that adds a depth-of-field effect to videos. Cinematic mode uses advanced computational algorithms to automatically focus on subjects and creatively blur the background, akin to what you would see in high-end cinematography. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Cinematic-Mode-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-900525" /><br/>
Cinematic mode allows users to focus on details in a creative way, by shifting focus smoothly from one subject to another. Cinematic mode also simplifies capturing these moments by automatically adjusting focus when people enter or leave the frame, or when the subject of the video looks in a different direction. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/shoot-video-in-cinematic-mode-iphone-13-iphone-14/">How to Shoot Video in Cinematic Mode</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Photographic Styles</h3><br/>
Photographic Styles, a feature introduced in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 series, offers a personalized photography experience that can help enhance holiday photos. The feature allows users to choose and customize a photographic style that automatically applies to their photos, ensuring that every shot reflects their preferred aesthetic. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/photographic-styles-iphone-13.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-817882" /><br/>
Photographic Styles are not one-size-fits-all filters. Instead, they are smart adjustments that apply selectively to different parts of the photo, such as skin tones and sky. Photographic Styles intelligently adapt to the lighting conditions in each shot, adjusting to preserve natural-looking skin tones and textures.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16-photographic-styles/">Customizing Your iPhone 16 Images With Photographic Styles</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-16-edit-photographic-styles-after-shooting/">iPhone 16: Edit Photographic Styles After Shooting</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-photographic-styles-iphone-13-pro/">How to Use Photographic Styles in the Camera App (iPhone 13, 14, and 15)</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Users can choose from preset styles like Rich Contrast, Vibrant, Warm, and Cool, each offering a unique look. During the holidays, this means you can select a style that best suits the festive mood and give your images a distinctive look.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, Apple overhauled Photographic Styles from the ground up. These newer Photographic Styles adjust specific colors in select parts of your photos to adjust the overall appearance, for a more specialized, richer look compared to the previous version.<br/>
<br/>
The first five Photographic Styles are tuned for skin undertones, including Cool Rose, Neutral, Amber, Rose Gold, and Gold. Cool Rose accentuates cool pinkish undertones, while neutral neutralizes warm undertones. Amber, Rose Gold, and Gold accentuate those specific tones. These can be fairly subtle, depending on the settings you choose.<br/>
<br/>
Other Styles are closer to what you get with a filter, adding more dramatic effects that impact the mood of the image. On the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, Photographic Styles can also be added and edited retrospectively. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Enhanced Portrait Mode</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup introduced some substantial improvements to Portrait mode. Now, users can adjust the focus of an image or add background blur after its capture, even if Portrait mode isn't initially selected. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-portrait-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2503" height="1401" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-912809" /><br/>
Post-shot editing capability allows you to experiment with different focal points, ensuring that each portrait captures the subject in the most flattering and interesting way. This improvement is especially useful for snapping quick, candid shots of family members and pets over the holiday period. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s Portrait mode has also been refined to perform better in low-light conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-how-to-take-portrait-mode-photos/">iPhone 15: How to Take Portrait Mode Photos</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/5-holiday-camera-features-to-try-out/">5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2446036/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Popular iPhone Camera App &#039;Halide&#039; Gaining Three New Features in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/halide-three-new-features-in-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-iphone-camera-app-halide-gaining-three-new-features-in-2025.2446046/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 08:04:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/halide-three-new-features-in-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Halide</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lux, the developers behind Halide and Kino, have <a href="https://www.lux.camera/the-road-to-halide-mark-3/">announced</a> their plans for Halide 3.0, a major update slated for release in 2025 with a series of new features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/halide-camera-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-968869" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.lux.camera/the-road-to-halide-mark-3/">Halide "Mark III"</a> is set to gain one-tap color grading. Color grading has been a highly requested addition since the launch of Process Zero, Halide's proprietary image processing system, which debuted in 2024. The feature is expected to allow users to apply professional-grade film looks instantly, similar to the capabilities offered in Lux's Kino app. Lux envisions this feature going beyond presets, potentially enabling users to import custom looks created by others.<br/>
<br/>
While iPhones have long supported HDR through Apple's native algorithms, Halide has refrained from adopting the technology due to concerns over aesthetic preferences and technical compatibility. Lux aims to address these concerns by introducing a nuanced, tasteful HDR implementation that avoids the garish appearance often associated with poorly executed HDR. The timing coincides with advancements in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, particularly the introduction of Adaptive HDR, which extends HDR compatibility to legacy file formats like JPEG. Lux believes this development marks a tipping point for HDR’s broader adoption and plans to integrate the feature alongside its color grading tools.<br/>
<br/>
Lux is also planning to debut a complete redesign of Halide's user interface. With Halide Mark II turning five years old in 2025, Lux has decided it is time for a visual and functional overhaul. The company has hinted that the changes will integrate tightly with the new features, such as making the color grading interface central to the app’s operation. <br/>
<br/>
Lux has launched an <a href="https://discord.gg/cGjhm26X">official Discord server</a>, allowing Halide subscribers to access early builds, share ideas, and participate in discussions to help shape the new version of the app. The server will also host a year-long photography challenge, offering weekly prompts and resources to inspire photographers and encourage engagement within the community.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/halide/">Halide</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/halide-three-new-features-in-2025/">Popular iPhone Camera App &#039;Halide&#039; Gaining Three New Features in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-iphone-camera-app-halide-gaining-three-new-features-in-2025.2446046/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Historically &#039;Bumpy Relationship&#039; With Nvidia Detailed in Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-nvidia-relationship-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-historically-bumpy-relationship-with-nvidia-detailed-in-report.2446044/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 07:31:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-nvidia-relationship-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Nvidia</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nvidia has become one of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/05/aapl-vs-nvidia-3-trillion-dollar-companies/">world's most valuable companies</a> thanks to strong demand for its artificial intelligence (AI) server chips from big tech companies like Amazon, Microsoft, and Google. However, one tech giant that is not a major Nvidia customer is Apple, and a new report attempts to explain why this might be.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-vs-Nvidia.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953774" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/how-apple-developed-an-nvidia-allergy"><em>The Information</em>'s Wayne Ma today outlined</a> Apple's historically "bumpy relationship" with Nvidia, but much of the bad blood dates to the 2000s and early 2010s, when Steve Jobs was still CEO and Macs used Nvidia graphics. It is unclear how much these past issues matter today, if at all, and the report acknowledges that Apple's current relationship with Nvidia "isn't entirely acrimonious." Two examples of the companies getting along include Apple's recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/20/apple-nvidia-speed-up-ai-language-models/">collaboration with Nvidia on machine learning research</a>, and Nvidia <a href="https://resources.nvidia.com/en-us-awe-2024/omniverse-apple-vision-pro">showcasing the Apple Vision Pro</a> when it announced a new software framework earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has mostly rented access to Nvidia GPUs through the cloud from companies like Amazon and Microsoft, and it is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/apple-intelligence-servers-new-chip-report/">reportedly developing its own AI server chip</a> as a longer-term solution, but neither of those things prove that Apple still has an "allergy" to Nvidia as the report states. As has been the case for more than a decade, and even more so in recent years, Apple simply wants to develop as many in-house chips and technologies as possible for many reasons, including lower production costs, improved integration between hardware and software, and reduced reliance on external suppliers. So, this seems less about Apple avoiding Nvidia in particular, and more about Apple owning the whole widget in general.<br/>
<br/>
This trend has been playing out for many years now. In addition to Apple long designing its own iPhone chips, the company started releasing its own Mac chips in 2020, in a transition away from Intel. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apple-5g-modem-plans-report/">long-rumored 5G modem</a> is expected to begin rolling out in iPhones next year, in a move away from its current supplier Qualcomm. Apple is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/12/apple-custom-bluetooth-wifi-chip/">reportedly developing its own Wi-Fi and Bluetooth chip</a>, a move that will impact Broadcom.<br/>
<br/>
So while Steve Jobs may have once pretended an Nvidia executive was no longer in the room during a meeting, as the report states, it seems most likely that Apple simply has no need to directly purchase GPUs from Nvidia. Apple is clearly fine with renting access to the GPUs from cloud providers until its in-house chip is ready.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/how-apple-developed-an-nvidia-allergy">The report</a> is nevertheless an interesting read, and it reinforces how Jobs was very good at holding a grudge when he was unhappy with a situation.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nvidia/">Nvidia</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apple-nvidia-relationship-report/">Apple&#039;s Historically &#039;Bumpy Relationship&#039; With Nvidia Detailed in Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-historically-bumpy-relationship-with-nvidia-detailed-in-report.2446044/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s First Bezel-Free iPhone Unlikely to Be Ready for 2026 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apples-zero-bezel-iphone-delayed-beyond-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-bezel-free-iphone-unlikely-to-be-ready-for-2026-launch.2446032/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 04:03:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apples-zero-bezel-iphone-delayed-beyond-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's plans to create an iPhone with a completely bezel-free display are reportedly facing significant technical challenges, with a new report suggesting that the technology may not be ready by 2026 as previously hoped. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/xiaomi_quad_curved_waterfall_display_concept_phone_angled_press_image.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983395" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Xiaomi's 2021 Quad-Curved Waterfall Display concept phone</em></div><br/>
Apple has seemingly been on a years-long quest to slim down the bezels on its iPhone models until they vanish out of sight, but it looks like the first "zero-bezel" iPhone is still a few years away yet. According to Korean-language outlet <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=31956">The Elec</a></em>, Apple has been working with Samsung Display and LG Display to develop the revolutionary screen technology, but the work has hit snags.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's vision reportedly differs significantly from existing curved display implementations, such as those previously used in Samsung smartphones or Xiaomi's "quad-curved waterfall display" concept. The iPhone maker is specifically working to avoid the "magnifying glass effect" that typically occurs on curved display edges like those already seen on some smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast to typical curved-edge phones, Apple is said to envision a unique design that maintains the iPhone's signature flat display and angular sides while extending the screen seamlessly over the edges, similar to the current Apple Watch design. Some industry insiders have reportedly described the intended aesthetic as "pebble-like."<br/>
<br/>
However, the technical challenges apparently remain substantial. Both Samsung Display and LG Display need to adapt two existing technologies, including Thin Film Encapsulation (TFE) for protecting OLED displays from environmental damage, and Optical Clear Adhesive (OCA) for bonding transparent adhesive films around curved edges. The suppliers also need to ensure there's adequate space for components like the iPhone antenna.<br/>
<br/>
The development of OCA technology in particular has reportedly proven troublesome, as the current solutions suffer from side-view distortion issues, and engineers have still to address impact damage concerns for the edge-wrapped display design.<br/>
<br/>
Apple had planned to begin mass production in time for the displays to feature on an iPhone 18 in 2026, but for that to happen, discussions with display manufacturers should have already been finalized by now. However, industry insiders report that these talks are still ongoing, suggesting the timeline for introducing the "zero-bezel" technology on an iPhone will likely slip further into the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/apples-zero-bezel-iphone-delayed-beyond-2026/">Apple&#039;s First Bezel-Free iPhone Unlikely to Be Ready for 2026 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-first-bezel-free-iphone-unlikely-to-be-ready-for-2026-launch.2446032/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2446022/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you been good this year? If so, you may be interested to know that Google has launched its annual <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">Santa tracking feature</a>, allowing Santa to be tracked in real time on his journey to the North Pole as he prepares to deliver presents to children around the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/santa-tracker-1.jpg" alt="" width="2096" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-830800" /><br/>
Google's Santa Tracker continues a two-decade tradition for the company, allowing excited children (and grown-ups!) to keep up with the jolly gift-giver's travels throughout December 24. On this day, Santa's Village transforms into a tracking experience where children can follow Santa and his reindeer as they merrily go about their important work.<br/>
<br/>
Santa can be tracked using a web browser on iPhone, iPad, or Mac by visiting Google's <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">official Santa Tracking website</a>. The site features a live map of Santa's current location, his next stop, a live video feed of his journey, and the estimated time that he will arrive in each specific location.<br/>
<br/>
The Santa site provides pictures of locations that Santa has already visited, a live count of gifts that have been delivered, and Santa's current distance from your location. There are also a selection of games to play, creative things to do, and videos to watch.<br/>
<br/>
Other Santa tracking services are also available, such as the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/norad-tracks-santa-claus/id1181633163">NORAD Tracks Santa Claus app</a> and website, but Google's site is often the most interactive and detailed. Happy holidays!<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole/">Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2446022/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Air Models With M4 Chip Expected to Launch &#039;Earlier&#039; Than iPhone SE 4 and iPad 11</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-models-with-m4-chip-expected-to-launch-earlier-than-iphone-se-4-and-ipad-11.2446002/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 13:06:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/21/apple-products-rumored-for-early-2025/">many product announcements planned</a> for the first half of next year, including updated MacBook Air models, an iPad 11, an iPhone SE 4, the AirTag 2, updated iPad Air models, and potentially more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m3-macbook-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952247" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1871298143494795319">social media post</a> today, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reiterated that the iPad 11, iPhone SE 4, and updated iPad Air models will be coming in the "spring" next year. Notably, he said the updated 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models with the M4 chip will be announced "earlier" than those other devices, but he did not provide a specific timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
This likely means that the updated MacBook Air models will be announced in a press release on the Apple Newsroom website at some point from January through March, whereas the other devices might be announced at Apple's usual spring event in March or April. Apple would be getting the minor MacBook Air update out of the way early.<br/>
<br/>
Apple earlier this month released macOS 15.2, and in doing so it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/macos-sequoia-15-2-m4-macbook-air-leak/">accidentally confirmed new MacBook Air models</a> coming next year. <br/>
<br/>
No major design changes have been rumored for the next MacBook Air, with only the M4 chip and other minor upgrades expected. Plausible new features could include a Center Stage camera, and an upgrade from Thunderbolt 3 to Thunderbolt 4 ports.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already updated the MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini with M4 chip options a few months ago. Geekbench results showed that the M4 chip is up to around <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-chip-benchmarks/">25% faster than the M3 chip</a> in terms of multi-core CPU performance.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/macbook-air-with-m4-chip-launch-timing/">New MacBook Air Models With M4 Chip Expected to Launch &#039;Earlier&#039; Than iPhone SE 4 and iPad 11</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-models-with-m4-chip-expected-to-launch-earlier-than-iphone-se-4-and-ipad-11.2446002/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How to Make the iOS 18 Photos App Suck Less</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/how-to-make-the-ios-18-photos-app-suck-less/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-make-the-ios-18-photos-app-suck-less.2445992/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 09:49:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/how-to-make-the-ios-18-photos-app-suck-less/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Photos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple overhauled the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, introducing a new, unified design that did away with the navigation bar and merged everything into a single screen. It marked the single biggest change to image management since the launch of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, and it's been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/21/apples-photos-app-overhaul-controversial/">controversial with some users</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/6vXFNxz01Us?si=yj2KYI9c0m2KPoWz" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
There's no returning to what the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app used to be unless Apple decides to roll back the changes, but there are a few tweaks that can be made to make it easier to get used to the new layout.<br/>
<br/>
First, if you haven't done so already, scroll down to the bottom of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app and tap on Edit. From there, make sure all your most used &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; features are at the top of the app. In this section, you'll find Recent Days, Albums, People and Pets, Memories, and Pinned Collections.<br/>
<br/>
Pinned Collections is a little confusing because it's a second customizable interface that has many of the same options as the main app, but think of it as a folder in a folder. It can be useful to put up top and add your most accessed utilities to, such as screenshots or specific albums.<br/>
<br/>
You can rearrange the sections of your &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app by dragging and dropping to reorder, plus you can hide any of the collections. If you don't want to see Featured &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, Wallpaper Suggestions, or Trips, for example, you can uncheck those so they won't be listed in the app. If you don't like that redundant Pinned Collections section, you can hide that too.<br/>
<br/>
If you haven't spent a lot of time fussing with the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, you might not know about the filters. In the full Library view, which you get to by swiping down, tapping on the arrows will show you the filters option. You can filter for photos, videos, edited images, screenshots, and favorites, or sort by recently added or date captured. There are also options to weed out screenshots and Shared With You images from your main photo library.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app isn't all bad. Search has improved quite a bit, and you can search for really specific parameters like "plants in Florida" or "Eric in a blue shirt."<br/>
<br/>
What do you think of the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app? Are you getting used to it? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/how-to-make-the-ios-18-photos-app-suck-less/">How to Make the iOS 18 Photos App Suck Less</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-to-make-the-ios-18-photos-app-suck-less.2445992/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Donation Campaign for World AIDS Day Raised &#36;3 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/apple-pay-donation-campaign-raised-3-million/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-donation-campaign-for-world-aids-day-raised-3-million.2445996/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 09:45:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/apple-pay-donation-campaign-raised-3-million/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		<category>(PRODUCT)RED</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[(RED) today <a href="https://x.com/RED/status/1871211971913429063">announced</a> that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-pay-world-aids-day-donation-campaign/">annual Apple Pay donation campaign</a> raised a total of &#36;3 million this year for <a href="https://www.theglobalfund.org/">The Global Fund to Fight AIDS, Tuberculosis and Malaria</a>. Apple's donation was capped at &#36;3 million, so it reached that cap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-Pay-RED.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="608" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983368" /><br/>
"Thank you, Apple and Apple customers for hitting this incredible milestone and helping provide life-saving healthcare in vulnerable communities," said (RED).<br/>
<br/>
Last month, Apple announced that it would again donate &#36;5 to The Global Fund for every purchase made using Apple Pay on Apple.com, through the Apple Store app, or at an Apple Store from November 29 through December 8.<br/>
<br/>
The Global Fund aims to combat diseases such as HIV/AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria throughout the developing world. Apple said its donation to the organization will continue to "help fund critical health programs that save lives."<br/>
<br/>
Apple runs this donation campaign ahead of World AIDS Day on December 1 each year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has supported The Global Fund for 18 years through its partnership with the (RED) brand, co-founded by U2 singer Bono. Apple offers some products in a <a href="https://www.apple.com/product-red/">(PRODUCT)RED</a> color, and a portion of the proceeds from every one of these products sold by Apple goes to The Global Fund. Apple said it has raised more than &#36;250 million to date.<br/>
<br/>
The number of Apple products available in (PRODUCT)RED has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/26/apple-has-scaled-back-productred/">dwindled in recent years</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/productred/">(PRODUCT)RED</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/apple-pay-donation-campaign-raised-3-million/">Apple Pay Donation Campaign for World AIDS Day Raised &#36;3 Million</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-donation-campaign-for-world-aids-day-raised-3-million.2445996/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From iOS 19: All the Rumors So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/what-to-expect-from-ios-19-so-far/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-ios-19-all-the-rumors-so-far.2445989/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 08:38:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/what-to-expect-from-ios-19-so-far/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a> is not expected to be announced until June 2025, but information about the software update is already starting to surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Generic-iOS-19-Feature-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978988" /><br/>
Below, we recap the biggest iOS 19 rumors so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More ChatGPT-Like Siri</h2><br/>
iOS 19 will introduce a "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/21/apple-llm-siri-2026/">more conversational Siri</a>" powered by "more advanced large language models," according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. He said this upgrade will make Siri more like OpenAI's ChatGPT, allowing the assistant to "handle more sophisticated requests."<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely unveil the revamped Siri when it unveils iOS 19 at WWDC 2025 next June, but Gurman said it will not be available until as early as spring 2026. That suggests the feature will be released as part of an iOS 19.4 update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
In the meantime, iOS 18.2 added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/apple-releases-ios-18-2-update/">ChatGPT integration to Siri</a>, and Gurman expects an integration with Google's Gemini to follow in a later update. And <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/22/apple-intelligence-features-timing/">with iOS 18.4</a>, Siri will gain on-screen awareness, deeper per-app controls, and a few other enhancements, but it will still not offer fully-fledged ChatGPT-like conversational abilities directly.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Delayed Features</h2><br/>
Gurman revealed that some other features have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/24/ios-19-rumors/">"postponed" until iOS 19.4</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"I'm told that a larger-than-usual number of features scheduled for iOS 19 (beyond the new Siri) are already postponed until spring 2026 (when iOS 19.4 debuts)," he said.<br/>
<br/>
He did not provide any specific details about the features that are pushed back.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/12/ios-18-updates-cause-ios-19-delays/">attributed the delay to the gradual rollout of Apple Intelligence features</a> between iOS 18.1 and iOS 18.4, which is preventing some Apple software engineers from moving on to iOS 19 development. In line with this information, an unnamed source within Apple told French website iPhoneSoft.fr that they are still working on iOS 18 development.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatible iPhones</h2><br/>
According to French website iPhoneSoft.fr, iOS 19 will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/22/ios-19-compatible-iphones-rumor/">compatible with any iPhone that is capable of running iOS 18</a>, which would mean the following models:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XS</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XS Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XR</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone SE (2nd generation or later)</li><br/>
</ul>The oldest devices in that list are the iPhone XS, iPhone XS, and iPhone XR, all of which were released in September 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, some iOS 19 features will be unavailable on older iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
If this report is accurate, it would be the second year in a row in which Apple did not drop support for any iPhone models with its major annual iOS release. iOS 18 is compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17 is.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17 dropped support for the iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, and iPhone X.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
The first iOS 19 and iPadOS 19 betas should be released during WWDC 2025 next June, and the updates are likely to be released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/what-to-expect-from-ios-19-so-far/">What to Expect From iOS 19: All the Rumors So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-ios-19-all-the-rumors-so-far.2445989/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Macs With M5 Chips Expected to Launch in This Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/m5-macs-launch-timing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macs-with-m5-chips-expected-to-launch-in-this-order.2445988/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 08:27:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/m5-macs-launch-timing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac Pro</category>
		<category>M5</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo today <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/be-semiconductor-poised-to-benefit-from-iphone-18-pro-variable-aperture-apple-pcc-high-end-m5-03e0810e52f2">outlined mass production timing</a> for the M5 series of chips, which he expects to be used in both future Macs and Apple Intelligence servers. The rollout will likely begin next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-2024-feature-purple-m5.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983351" /><br/>
Kuo expects the standard M5 chip to enter mass production in the first half of 2025, followed by the M5 Pro and M5 Max chips in the second half of the year. Then, he expects the M5 Ultra chip to enter mass production in 2026.<br/>
<br/>
So, nothing too surprising.<br/>
<br/>
The timeframes suggest that M5 Macs will launch in a similar order as M4 Macs. Apple will likely update the MacBook Pro lineup with M5 series chips in October next year, and the MacBook Air should receive the M5 chip in the first half of 2026. Apple is likely to update the Mac Studio and Mac Pro later in 2026, or in 2027. It is unclear if the iMac and Mac mini will be updated next year, as those models are not always updated annually.<br/>
<br/>
M4 Macs have rolled out in a similar manner so far. Apple updated the MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini with the M4 series of chips in October, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/11/macos-sequoia-15-2-m4-macbook-air-leak/">MacBook Air is expected to be updated</a> by the end of March next year. Mac Studio and Mac Pro models with M4 Max and/or M4 Ultra chips are expected to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-studio-m4-mac-pro-2025/">in mid-to-late 2025</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As previously rumored, Kuo said M5 series chips will be manufactured with TSMC's third-generation 3nm process, known as N3P. That will result in the usual year-over-year performance and power efficiency improvements over the M4 series of chips.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence servers are currently powered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/apple-building-m2-ultra-and-m4-servers/">by the M2 Ultra chip</a>, and they are expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/06/apple-intelligence-servers-with-m4-chips-report/">start using M4 series chips next year</a>. Beyond that, Kuo said Apple will eventually switch to high-end, server-grade M5 chips that are better suited for artificial intelligence inferencing. He said these chips will also be manufactured with the N3P process, offer improved thermal performance, and have a separated CPU and GPU design. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m5/">M5</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Pro">Mac Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-pro.1">Mac Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/m5-macs-launch-timing/">Macs With M5 Chips Expected to Launch in This Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macs-with-m5-chips-expected-to-launch-in-this-order.2445988/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sizes Change Next Year: What to Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-sizes-change-next-year-what-to-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sizes-change-next-year-what-to-know.2445987/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 07:40:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-sizes-change-next-year-what-to-know/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year, Apple tweaked iPhone 16 Pro screen sizes to make them bigger than 2023's iPhone 15 Pro models, and next year we are also expecting a change in the size of the displays in the iPhone 17 lineup. Here's what we know.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-16-Apple-Store.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976828" /><br/>
<h2>Standard iPhone 17</h2><br/>
Apple could introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/">new display size</a> for the standard iPhone 17 model in 2025. The iPhone 17 could measure in at 6.3 inches, up from 6.1 inches, which would make it the same size as the current iPhone 16 Pro. At 6.3 inches, it would be in between the size of the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 and the 6.7-inch iPhone 15 Plus. However, next year there may be only one non-Pro model in Apple's lineup (see below).<br/>
<br/>
<h2><del datetime="2024-12-23T12:20:49+00:00">iPhone 17 Plus</del> – iPhone 17 Air</h2><br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple plans to eliminate the Plus model in 2025 due to subpar sales and replace it with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">slimmed down iPhone 17</a> that could come with an "iPhone Air" moniker. While the iPhone 16 Plus has a 6.7-inch display, the iPhone 17 Air is expected to fall somewhere between the iPhone 17 Pro and 17 Pro Max in size. Separate rumors have targeted <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">6.55 inches</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">6.6 inches</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/22/iphone-17-lineup-specs-detail-upgrades/">6.65 inches</a> as the display size that Apple has settled on, which would make it smaller than the iPhone 17 Pro Max, but larger than the 17 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Pro & Pro Max</h2><br/>
Apple is currently not expected to change the size of its Pro models next year, having already tweaked them this year in the iPhone 16 series. That means the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max should measure roughly 6.3 inches and 6.9 inches, respectively. However, according to <em>The Information</em>, the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max will have "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/first-iphone-17-pro-design-leak/">significant design changes</a>" that go beyond display size. These changes are said to include the use of aluminum for the frame instead of titanium, a half-aluminum, half-glass backing rather than an all-glass back, and a rectangular camera bump.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
  <th>iPhone 16 Models (2024)</th><br/>
  <th>iPhone 17 Models (2025)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 6.1 inches</td><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 17</strong>: 6.3 inches</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 6.7 inches</td><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 17 Air</strong>: 6.5-6.6 inches</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 6.3 inches</td><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 17 Pro</strong>: 6.3 inches</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 6.9 inches</td><br/>
  <td><strong>iPhone 17 Pro Max</strong>: 6.9 inches</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><div class="clear"></div><p></p><br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Display Technology</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/iPhone-14-Pro-Display-Two-Times-Brighter-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2504" height="1408" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862901" /><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">120Hz ProMotion Across the Lineup</span><br><br/>
Apple intends to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/promotion-standard-iphones-2025/">expand</a> ProMotion to all iPhone models in 2025, allowing all models to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/ltpo-for-all-iphone-17-models-report/">ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate</a> for smoother scrolling and video content when necessary. Previously, only "Pro" models in Apple's iPhone lineup have had the feature. Notably, ProMotion would also enable the display on the iPhone 17 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-and-17-air-120hz-promotion-rumor/">iPhone 17 "Air"</a> to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate as low as 1Hz, allowing for an always-on display that can show the Lock Screen's clock, widgets, notifications, and wallpaper even when the device is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">More Power-Efficient Screens</span><br><br/>
A recent <a href="https://x.com/Jukanlosreve/status/1863866205045727481">unconfirmed rumor</a> suggests that Apple's upcoming iPhone 17 Pro models may feature a new display technology known as Low-Dielectric TEE (Transmission Electrically Enhanced). The term likely refers to the use of materials with a low dielectric constant in the display's thin-film encapsulation (TFE). While it's not yet clear what this specific innovation offers, incorporating low-dielectric materials can in general reduce signal interference and energy loss, leading to more efficient power usage and potentially longer battery life. <br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Scratch Resistant Anti-Reflective Display</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 17 will feature an anti-reflective display that is more scratch-resistant than Apple's Ceramic Shield found on iPhone 15 models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">according to one rumor</a>. The outer glass on the iPhone 17 is said to have a "super-hard anti-reflective layer" that is "more scratch-resistant." It's not clear whether Apple is planning to adopt the Gorilla Glass Armor that Samsung uses in its Galaxy S24 Ultra, but the description of Corning's latest technology matches the rumor. That said, it's worth keeping in mind that the new iPhone 16 Pro models have the latest-generation Ceramic Shield, which has an advanced formulation that is 2x tougher than glass on any other smartphone, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Smaller Dynamic Island</span><br><br/>
Apple's iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature a significantly narrower Dynamic Island, thanks to the device's adoption of a smaller "metalens" for the Face ID system, claims <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-rumor/">Haitong's Jeff Pu</a>. While a traditional iPhone camera has curved lenses that redirect light towards the image sensor, a metalens is a thin and flat lens with microscopic patterns etched onto it that can focus light more precisely. Assuming this results in a narrowed Dynamic Island, it would be the first time that Apple has changed the feature since it debuted on the iPhone 14 Pro in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Models Past: Notable Size Changes</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/iphone-12-vs-iphone-12-mini.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="812" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-763912" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>The Original iPhone to iPhone 4S (2007-2011):</strong> The first iPhone, launched in 2007, featured a 3.5-inch screen, a size that Apple maintained up to the iPhone 4S. This screen size was considered quite large at the time compared to many contemporary phones.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone 5 to iPhone 5S/SE (2012-2016):</strong> With the iPhone 5, Apple increased the screen size to 4 inches. This change addressed the growing consumer trend towards larger screens, allowing for an improved viewing experience while maintaining a comfortable grip.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone 6 and 6 Plus (2014):</strong> A significant change came with the iPhone 6 and 6 Plus, featuring screen sizes of 4.7 inches and 5.5 inches respectively. This move was a response to the burgeoning market of larger smartphones or "phablets." It marked Apple's foray into a segment that competitors like Samsung had been capitalizing on.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>iPhone X (2017):</strong> With the introduction of the iPhone X in 2017, Apple shifted to a new design paradigm, reducing bezels and introducing notch-based displays. The iPhone X had a 5.8-inch screen, which was a middle ground between the two previous sizes. </li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone XR (2018):</strong> The iPhone XR retained the new design profile as the iPhone X but upped the display size to 6.1 inches. </li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone XS Max (2018):</strong> The iPhone XS Max was the first "Max" model Apple released, featuring a 6.5-inch display, making it larger than any previous iPhone model.<br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 12 Pro Max (2020):</strong> The iPhone 12 Pro Max featured a 6.7-inch Super Retina XDR display, making it once again the largest iPhone ever at the time of its release.</li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 12 mini & iPhone 13 mini (2020-2021):</strong> The iPhone 12 mini was introduced in 2020, and marked the first time since the original iPhone SE that Apple released a new model specifically designed to be smaller and more compact. Featuring a 5.4-inch screen, it catered to users who preferred smaller, more manageable phones that could be easily used with one hand. The iPhone 13 mini continued the trend, however reports and market analysis indicated that the overall demand for such a device was relatively low compared to Apple's larger models, and Apple has not replicated the option in iPhone lineups since. </li><br/>
<li><strong>iPhone 15 Pro to iPhone 16 Pro (2023-2024)</strong>: Apple this year introduced the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max, featuring larger displays of 6.3 inches and 6.9 inches, respectively. Up from the 6.1 and 6.7-inch respective sizes of the previous iPhone Pro and iPhone Pro Max models, the current devices also boast thinner bezels, enhancing the viewing experience without significantly increasing the device's overall size. </li><br/>
</ul>What do you think about Apple's expected iPhone 17 size changes? Share your thoughts in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-sizes-change-next-year-what-to-know/">iPhone Sizes Change Next Year: What to Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sizes-change-next-year-what-to-know.2445987/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 18 Pro Rumored to Be More Like DSLR Camera With This Upgrade</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-18-pro-rumored-camera-upgrade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-pro-rumored-to-be-more-like-dslr-camera-with-this-upgrade.2445981/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 06:24:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-18-pro-rumored-camera-upgrade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 18</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 18 Pro and iPhone 18 Pro Max are still nearly two years away from launching, a new feature has already been rumored for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-design-cameras.jpg" alt="" width="923" height="517" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966096" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/be-semiconductor-poised-to-benefit-from-iphone-18-pro-variable-aperture-apple-pcc-high-end-m5-03e0810e52f2">blog post</a> today, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo reiterated that the main rear camera on both iPhone 18 Pro models will offer variable aperture, which would be a first for the iPhone. The main camera refers to the 48-megapixel Fusion camera, which was also known as the Main or Wide camera on older iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
With variable aperture, users would be able to control the amount of light that passes through the camera's lens and reaches the sensor. The main camera on iPhone 14 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro models have a fixed aperture of ƒ/1.78, and the lens is always fully open and shooting with this widest aperture. With the iPhone 18 Pro models, users would be able to manually change the aperture, according to this rumor.<br/>
<br/>
Variable aperture is typically a capability seen on professional DSLR/mirrorless cameras from the likes of Sony and Canon.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/08/variable-aperture-rumored-for-iphone-18-pro/">first made this claim</a> last month. Today, he added that Dutch manufacturer BE Semiconductor will supply assembly equipment for the aperture blades, which is the mechanical part that would control how much light passes through the lens.<br/>
<br/>
A variable aperture on iPhone 18 Pro models should provide users with greater control over depth of field, which refers to how sharp a subject appears in the foreground compared to the background. However, given that smartphones have smaller image sensors due to physical size restraints, it is unclear exactly how meaningful this improvement would be.<br/>
<br/>
This rumor will likely evolve over time. Kuo did not say if iPhone 18 Pro models will be getting a larger sensor, but such an upgrade would pave the way for meaningful improvements to depth of field. Apple already offers Portrait mode, which artificially makes the background look more blurry behind a person or other subject in a photo. A larger image sensor would enable that "bokeh" effect more naturally on iPhone 18 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Variable aperture was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/23/iphone-17-mechanical-aperture-rumor/">previously rumored for at least one iPhone 17 model</a>, but Kuo believes the feature is slated for iPhone 18 Pro models instead.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 18 Pro models are expected to launch in September 2026.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-18/">iPhone 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/iphone-18-pro-rumored-camera-upgrade/">iPhone 18 Pro Rumored to Be More Like DSLR Camera With This Upgrade</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-pro-rumored-to-be-more-like-dslr-camera-with-this-upgrade.2445981/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>X Announces Major Price Increases for Ad-Free Premium Plus Tier</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/x-raises-premium-plus-subscription-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-announces-major-price-increases-for-ad-free-premium-plus-tier.2445970/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 03:50:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/x-raises-premium-plus-subscription-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[X (Twitter) has <a href="https://help.x.com/en/premium-plus-price-update">announced</a> a big jump in pricing for its Premium Plus subscription tier, with monthly rates in the US jumping from &#36;16 to &#36;22, representing a 37.5% increase. The annual subscription cost will also rise from &#36;168 to &#36;229.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
The price changes took effect on December 21, 2024, with new subscribers paying the higher rates immediately. Existing Premium Plus subscribers will maintain their current pricing until January 20, 2025, after which the new rates will apply on their next billing cycle.<br/>
<br/>
The price hikes vary significantly by region, with some markets seeing particularly steep increases. In Nigeria, the monthly subscription cost has surged by over 365%, while Turkish users face a 156% increase. European subscribers will see their monthly rates rise from €16 to €21, and Australian users will need to pay &#36;35 AUD, up from &#36;26 AUD. A full list of new pricing by country is <a href="https://help.x.com/en/using-x/x-premium#tbpricing-bycountry">available here</a>.<br/>
<br/>
X justified the price increase by highlighting several Premium Plus features, including a completely ad-free experience and enhanced access to the platform's Grok AI capabilities. The company also emphasized that the higher subscription fees will support its creator revenue sharing program, which now focuses on rewarding content quality and engagement rather than ad views.<br/>
<br/>
The basic X subscription tier remains unchanged at &#36;3 per month. It's the largest price increase for US subscribers on Premium Plus since Elon Musk acquired the platform in 2022.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/x-raises-premium-plus-subscription-prices/">X Announces Major Price Increases for Ad-Free Premium Plus Tier</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-announces-major-price-increases-for-ad-free-premium-plus-tier.2445970/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Expected to Ship With iPadOS 18.3 in Spring 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/ipad-expected-to-ship-ipados-18-3-spring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-expected-to-ship-with-ipados-18-3-in-spring-2025.2445968/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 03:31:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/ipad-expected-to-ship-ipados-18-3-spring/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release an entry-level iPad 11 in the spring and iPadOS 18.3 will be pre-installed on the shipped devices, according to a source with a proven track record for upcoming Apple software updates. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-iPad-10th-gen-Magic-Keyboard-Folio-Apple-Pencil-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2056" height="1156" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870269" /><br/>
Several reports in the last few months have suggested Apple is developing an 11th-generation iPad that is scheduled to be released around the same time as a new iPhone SE 4 and iPad Air <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/new-entry-level-ipad-coming-spring-2025/">in the spring</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Today's source adds weight to the evidence. Apple is expected to release iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3 in late January or early February, which would be time enough for the company to get the latest software on new devices for shipping around March.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors of new features are thin on the ground, but today's source says his information does not support rumors that the low-cost iPad will include Apple's upcoming custom 5G modem, which is also expected to be introduced in the iPhone SE and iPhone 17 Air in 2025. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apple-5g-modem-plans-report/">modem chip will be capable</a> of theoretical 5G download speeds of up to 4Gb/s, which is slower than Qualcomm's modems in current phones. The chip will not support the fastest mmWave 5G, and will instead be limited to sub-6GHz 5G.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has said that the device will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/entry-level-ipad-apple-intelligence-late-2025/">likely support Apple Intelligence</a>, which suggests the iPad 11 will have a newer A-series chip compared to the iPad 10, and at least 8GB of RAM. Apple released the iPad 10 in October 2022 with the A14 Bionic chip. Gurman has also said Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/apple-working-on-redesigned-ipad-magic-keyboard/">new Magic Keyboard accessory</a> for the low-cost ‌iPad‌ and/or the iPad Air which is expected to come out by the middle of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/16/apple-releases-ios-18-3-beta-1/">seeded</a> the first betas of iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3, but there's no word yet on what's included. What we do know is that Apple is still working to roll out Apple Intelligence features. iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2 include Image Playground, Genmoji, and Siri ChatGPT integration, but there are still new ‌Siri‌ functions that are slated for release next year.<br/>
<br/>
We could see updates to ‌Siri‌ with iOS 18.3, and the features Apple has in development include personal context, on-screen awareness, and the ability to do more in and between apps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/23/ipad-expected-to-ship-ipados-18-3-spring/">New iPad Expected to Ship With iPadOS 18.3 in Spring 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-expected-to-ship-with-ipados-18-3-in-spring-2025.2445968/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 19 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/22/ios-19-compatible-iphones-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphones.2445930/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 08:09:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/22/ios-19-compatible-iphones-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 19</category>
		<category>iPhoneSoft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 19 will not drop support for any iPhone models, according to <a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2024/12/20/ios-19-liste-iphone-compatibles-ipad-moins">French website iPhoneSoft.fr</a>. The report cites a source within Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Generic-iOS-19-Feature-Mock-Light.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978991" /><br/>
The report said that iOS 19 will be compatible with any iPhone that is capable of running iOS 18, which would mean the following models:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 16 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XS</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XS Max</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone XR</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone SE (2nd generation or later)</li><br/>
</ul>The oldest devices in that list are the iPhone XS, iPhone XS Max, and iPhone XR, all of which were released in September 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, some iOS 19 features will be unavailable on older iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
If this report is accurate, it would be the second year in a row in which Apple did not drop support for any iPhone models with its major annual iOS release. iOS 18 is compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17 is.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17 dropped support for the iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, and iPhone X.<br/>
<br/>
There is slightly worse news for iPadOS 19, as the report said that update will drop support for the iPad 7 from 2019. Fortunately, the report said all other iPad models that can run iPadOS 18 will be compatible with iPadOS 19 next year.<br/>
<br/>
The first iOS 19 and iPadOS 19 betas should be released during WWDC 2025 next June, and the updates are likely to be released in September. Not many iOS 19 features have been rumored yet, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/22/first-ios-19-feature-leaked/">Siri is expected to become more conversational</a> like ChatGPT in a later iOS 19.4 update, which is likely to be released around March 2026.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-19/">iOS 19</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphonesoft/">iPhoneSoft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/22/ios-19-compatible-iphones-rumor/">iOS 19 Rumored to Be Compatible With These iPhones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-19-rumored-to-be-compatible-with-these-iphones.2445930/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
