<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 13:03:17 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.0.2 for Apple Watch Ultra 2 and Series 9</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-2-for-apple-watch-ultra-2-and-series-9.2404873/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 12:54:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.0.2, a minor update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that came out earlier this month. watchOS 10.0.2 comes five days after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-1/">release of watchOS 10.0.1</a>, another minor update.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" /><br/>
According to Apple's release notes for the update, watchOS 10.0.2 includes bug fixes and important security updates for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌.0.2 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> by opening it up and going to General &gt; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update appears to be limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-9/">watchOS 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-2/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.0.2 for Apple Watch Ultra 2 and Series 9</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-0-2-for-apple-watch-ultra-2-and-series-9.2404873/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.0.2 and iPadOS 17.0.2 for All iPhones and iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-ios-17-0-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-0-2-and-ipados-17-0-2-for-all-iphones-and-ipads.2404870/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 12:47:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-ios-17-0-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.0.2 and iPadOS 17.0.2 updates, with the software coming five days after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apple-releases-ios-17-0-1/">releases of iOS 17.0.1</a> and iPadOS 17.0.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.0.2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913923" /><br/>
Today's iOS 17.0.2 and iPadOS 17.0.2 updates arrive as build 21A351 and can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
Note that iOS 17.0.2 was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/warning-update-your-iphone-15-to-ios-17-0-2/">previously made available</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> owners, and those who purchased an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; were prompted to install the update during the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> setup process.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has now made iOS 17.0.2 available for all iPhones compatible with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> instead of limiting it to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, but &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; users already have the software and will not see the update.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, iOS 17.0.2 fixes an issue that could prevent transferring data directly from another &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; during setup, an issue that affected the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> release notes are the same, but mention transferring from another &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-ios-17-0-2/">Apple Releases iOS 17.0.2 and iPadOS 17.0.2 for All iPhones and iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-0-2-and-ipados-17-0-2-for-all-iphones-and-ipads.2404870/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Eddy Cue Explains Why Google is iPhone&#039;s Default Search Engine</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-on-why-google-is-default-on-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eddy-cue-explains-why-google-is-iphones-default-search-engine.2404859/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 12:04:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-on-why-google-is-default-on-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Eddy Cue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's services chief Eddy Cue today testified in the antitrust trial between the U.S. Department of Justice and Google, answering questions about a deal that sees Google set as the default search engine on the iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/applegoogle.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-736930" /><br/>
According to a <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23891037/apple-eddy-cue-testimony-us-google">report from <em>The Verge</em></a> today, Google pays Apple billions of dollars per year in order for Google to be set as the default search engine on Apple platforms. The exact amount that Google pays Apple has not been publicly disclosed during the trial, as a lot of the testimony in the case has taken place behind closed doors.<br/>
<br/>
Cue reportedly last negotiated the deal between Apple and Google in 2016. When asked why Apple chose Google as its default search engine, Cue said "there wasn't a valid alternative to Google at the time," and he said there still isn't one.<br/>
<br/>
"We make Google be the default search engine because we've always thought it was the best," added Cue. "We pick the best one and let users easily change it."<br/>
<br/>
Cue acknowledged that Apple feels it is more committed to privacy than Google, but argued that the deal between the two companies requires Google to allow users to search without logging in, and said that Apple has built several privacy protections into its Safari web browser in order to ensure that users are safeguarded.<br/>
<br/>
Cue also admitted that Apple does not allow users to change the default search engine during the iPhone's setup process, but he said this decision supports Apple's goal of getting users "up and running as fast as possible."<br/>
<br/>
To change the iPhone's default search engine at any point after setup, users can simply open the Settings app, tap Safari, tap Search Engine, and select one of the available options: Google, Yahoo, Bing, DuckDuckGo, or Ecosia.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/26/23891037/apple-eddy-cue-testimony-us-google"><em>The Verge</em></a> and <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/09/26/technology/google-antitrust-trial-secrecy.html"><em>The New York Times</em></a> have additional coverage of Cue's testimony.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eddy-cue/">Eddy Cue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-on-why-google-is-default-on-iphone/">Apple&#039;s Eddy Cue Explains Why Google is iPhone&#039;s Default Search Engine</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-eddy-cue-explains-why-google-is-iphones-default-search-engine.2404859/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari 17 With Profiles, Locked Private Browsing Windows and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-safari-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-17-with-profiles-locked-private-browsing-windows-and-more.2404852/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:46:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-safari-17/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Monterey</category>
		<category>macOS Ventura</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released Safari 17, the newest version of the Safari browser. Safari 17 can be downloaded on macOS Monterey and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-13/">macOS Ventura</a>, and it brings some of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> features to older operating systems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/safari-icon-blue-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833485" /><br/>
Safari 17 introduces support for Profiles, so browsing can be separated into topics like work and personal, plus it adds enhanced private browsing functionality that locks the private browser when it is not in use.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that search has been improved to provide more relevant results, and multiple tabs can be selected to add them to the tab bar or a Tab Group. Apple's full release notes for the update are below:<blockquote>Safari 17 introduces new features, even faster performance, and improved security.<br/>
<br/>
- Profiles keep your browsing separate for topics like work and personal, separating your history, cookies, extensions, Tab Groups, and Favorites<br/>
- Enhanced Private Browsing locks your private browsing windows when you're not using them, blocks known trackers from loading, and removes identifying tracking from URLs<br/>
- Streamlined search offers more relevant, faster, and easier-to-read results<br/>
- Multiple tab selection allows you to select multiple tabs at once and move them around the tab bar or create a Tab Group<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.</blockquote>Safari can be downloaded from the System Settings menu on &zwnj;macOS Ventura&zwnj; or in System Preferences on macOS Monterey.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-13/">macOS Ventura</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-monterey.234">macOS Monterey</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-ventura.239">macOS Ventura</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-safari-17/">Apple Releases Safari 17 With Profiles, Locked Private Browsing Windows and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-17-with-profiles-locked-private-browsing-windows-and-more.2404852/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Studio Display Firmware 17 With Improvements to Built-In Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-studio-display-firmware-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-studio-display-firmware-17-with-improvements-to-built-in-camera.2404841/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 11:10:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-studio-display-firmware-17/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Displays</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, Apple today released a Studio Display 17 firmware update after several months of beta testing. The update includes improvements to the camera, and it is available after updating to &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839183" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/apple-studio-display-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" /><br/>
The Studio Display firmware can be updated by connecting the display to a Mac. Studio Display owners can go to System Preferences &gt; Software Update to install the firmware.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the update adds support for zoom, recenter, and manual framing for the built-in camera in the Studio Display, plus it includes minor stability improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been improving the Studio Display camera since the device first launched and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/apple-studio-display/">was criticized</a> for poor camera quality. Back in April of 2022, Apple released firmware to improve the functionality of the built-in camera, improving the contrast, colors, and overall look.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/displays/">Apple Pro Display XDR</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Apple Studio Display</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-accessories.77">Mac Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-studio-display-firmware-17/">Apple Releases Studio Display Firmware 17 With Improvements to Built-In Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-studio-display-firmware-17-with-improvements-to-built-in-camera.2404841/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Low-Cost Apple Vision Pro Might Be Canceled</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-low-cost-apple-vision-pro-might-be-canceled.2404831/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:13:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-vision-pro-shipment-growth-may-be-below-market-expectations-apple-vision-pro出貨成長可能低於市場預期-7a5eeb613ab0">may have canceled plans</a> to produce a lower-cost version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset, according to Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. There were multiple rumors of a lower-cost model coming out sometime around 2025, but that may not happen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Kuo does not give a reason for why the lower-cost headset may have been nixed, but he says that unless Apple significantly cuts down on cost, significant shipment growth in Vision Pro shipments may not happen in 2025. Kuo expects Apple to ship approximately 400,000 to 600,000 headsets in 2024, and he says that while it will provide an "excellent experience," it may take "longer than the market expects" to become Apple's next star product. <br/>
<br/>
A second-generation version of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; is expected to go into mass production by the first half of 2027 "at the latest," and Kuo says that it is possible there will be no hardware updates for the Vision Pro until then.<br/>
<br/>
Both <em>The Information</em> and <em>Bloomberg</em> have suggested that Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/apple-cheaper-ar-vr-headset/">working on a more affordable version</a> of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; headset. The initial version will be priced at &#36;3,500, which will put it out of reach of many Apple customers. <br/>
<br/>
The rumors have said that Apple is developing a budget-friendly model that could be closer in price to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but given the high price of the current model, it is unclear how rapidly Apple could bring component costs down. If Apple does indeed continue work on a more affordable model, it could feature lower resolution internal displays and cheaper build materials. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/low-cost-vision-pro-canceled/">Kuo: Low-Cost Apple Vision Pro Might Be Canceled</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-low-cost-apple-vision-pro-might-be-canceled.2404831/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma With New Widget Features, Safari Updates, Screen Sharing Improvements and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-macos-sonoma/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-with-new-widget-features-safari-updates-screen-sharing-improvements-and-more.2404826/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 10:01:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-macos-sonoma/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/09/macos-sonoma-is-available-today/">today released macOS 14 Sonoma</a>, the newest version of the operating system that runs on the Mac. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> has been in beta testing for several months, and it is compatible with the 2019 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro, the 2018 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, the 2018 and later MacBook Pro, the 2019 and later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
The ‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; adds interactive widgets to the desktop, bringing them out of the Today view and making them more prominent and useful. With Continuity, you can even see and interact with your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> widgets on your Mac.<br/>
<br/>
There are a range of new Apple TV-like screensavers that feature slow-motion videos of worldwide locations, along with matching desktop wallpapers. Apple added a new Game Mode for Macs with Apple silicon chips, and this option prioritizes games on the CPU and GPU for smoother performance.<br/>
<br/>
Video conferencing gets a boost with a Presenter Overlay effect for sharing content, plus there's a high performance mode for Screen Sharing that offers higher frame rates and low-latency audio so pros can access their content creation workflows from anywhere.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tgeqM3RqhF4" title="macOS Sonoma: Best Features You Need to Know!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Safari's Private Browsing mode is locked behind <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, Profiles can be used to separate work and personal browsing, and there are improved tracking and fingerprinting protections to preserve your privacy. You can save your favorite websites as web apps on the desktop or the dock, and they will work as regular apps with a simplified toolbar.<br/>
<br/>
Many of the features that are in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> are also in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;. The Messages app supports a new stickers experience that turns all emoji into stickers, the People album can recognize pets, and Visual Lookup works with videos and can recognize food and identify symbols on labels and signs.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a> can be shared with other people using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain passwords can be shared with friends and family members, the Notes app supports inline PDFs, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> can now be activated without saying "Hey." Apple's full release notes for the update are below.<blockquote>macOS Sonoma brings all‑new capabilities that elevate your productivity and creativity. Discover even more ways to personalize your Mac with stunning screensavers and widgets that you can add to your desktop. Elevate your presence on video calls with a new way to present your work that keeps you a part of the presentation. Safari profiles and web apps help you organize your browsing in all-new ways. Game Mode boosts your gaming performance. Sonoma also brings big updates to Messages, Keyboard, and Accessibility. And when you upgrade, you get the latest security and privacy protections available for Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Screen Savers</strong><br/>
Stunning screen savers of locations from around the world seamlessly become your desktop wallpaper when you log-in<br/>
- Shuffle settings for rotating through screensavers by theme including Landscape, Cityscape, Underwater, and Earth<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Widgets</strong><br/>
- Widgets can be placed anywhere on the desktop and adapt to the color of your wallpaper while working in apps<br/>
- iPhone widgets can be added to your Mac when your iPhone is nearby or on the same Wi-Fi network<br/>
- Interactive widgets let you take actions directly from the widget such as running a shortcut, pausing media, and more<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Video Conferencing</strong><br/>
- Presenter Overlay keeps you front and center while sharing your screen in FaceTime or third-party video conferencing apps (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Reactions layer 3D effects like hearts, balloons, confetti, and more around you in video calls and can be triggered with gestures (Mac with Apple silicon, Continuity Camera with iPhone 12 and later)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Safari and Passwords</strong><br/>
- Profiles keep your browsing separate for topics like work and personal, separating your history, cookies, extensions, Tab Groups, and favorites<br/>
- Web apps let you use any website like an app, complete with an icon in the Dock for faster access and a simplified toolbar for easier browsing<br/>
- Enhanced Private Browsing locks your private browsing windows when you're not using them, blocks known trackers from loading, and removes tracking that identifies you from URLs<br/>
- Password and passkey sharing allows you to easily share accounts with trusted contacts<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Live Stickers sync from iOS and iPadOS to macOS, giving you access to the Live Stickers you create on your iPhone and iPad<br/>
- Search filters for people, keywords, and content types like photos or links help you more easily find what you are looking for<br/>
- Swipe to reply inline on any iMessage bubble<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Gaming</strong><br/>
- Game Mode gives games the highest priority on the CPU and GPU, delivering more consistent frame rates and lower latency to wireless controllers and AirPods (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Keyboard</strong><br/>
- Improved autocorrect accuracy makes typing even easier by leveraging a more powerful transformer-based language model<br/>
- Inline predictive text shows single- and multi-word predictions that you can add by pressing the Space bar<br/>
- Improved Dictation experience supports using your voice and keyboard together to enter and edit text<br/>
<br/>
<strong>AirPods</strong><br/>
- Adaptive Audio delivers a new listening mode that dynamically blends Active Noise Cancellation and Transparency to tailor the noise control experience based on the conditions of your environment (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Personalized Volume adjusts the volume of your media in response to your environment and listening preferences over time (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Conversation Awareness lowers your media volume and enhances the voices of the people in front of the user, all while reducing background noise (AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Press to mute and unmute your microphone by pressing the AirPods stem or the Digital Crown on AirPods Max when on a call (AirPods (3rd generation), AirPods Pro (1st and 2nd generation), or AirPods Max with the latest firmware)<br/>
- Improved AirPods automatic switching now detects Mac up to 2X faster (AirPods (2nd and 3rd generation), AirPods Pro (1st and 2nd generation), AirPods Max with the latest firmware)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Privacy</strong><br/>
- Sensitive Content Warnings can be enabled to help prevent users from unexpectedly viewing sensitive images in Messages<br/>
- Expanded Communication Safety protections for children now detect videos containing nudity in addition to photos shared through Messages and the system Photos picker<br/>
- Improved sharing permissions let you choose which photos to share and add calendar events without providing access to your entire photo library or calendar<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Live Speech lets you type what you want to say and reads it aloud in FaceTime calls or in-person conversations<br/>
- Personal Voice helps users at risk of speech loss create a voice that sounds like them in a private and secure way using on-device machine learning<br/>
- Made for iPhone compatible hearing devices can be paired and used with Mac (MacBook Pro (2021), Mac Studio (2022), and Mac computers with M2 chip)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This release also includes other features and improvements:</strong><br/>
- One-Time verification code AutoFill from Mail helps you quickly sign into sites in Safari, without leaving the browser<br/>
- Inline PDFs and document scans in Notes are presented full-width making them easy to view<br/>
- Grocery Lists in Reminders automatically group related items into sections as you add them<br/>
- Visual Look Up for recipes helps you find similar dishes from photo<br/>
- Visual Look Up in video helps you learn about objects that appear in paused video frames<br/>
- Pets in the People album in Photos surfaces individual pets just like friends or family members<br/>
- Option to say "Siri" in addition to "Hey Siri" for a more natural way to activate Siri (Mac with Apple silicon, AirPods Pro (2nd generation))<br/>
- High performance mode in Screen Sharing supports color workflows and improves responsiveness while remotely accessing a Mac (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Item sharing in Find My allows you to share an AirTag with up to five other people<br/>
- Activity History in Home displays a recent history of events for door locks, garage doors, security systems, and contact sensors<br/>
- Battery health management updated on 13-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip to better optimize long term battery health<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices.</blockquote><h2>Read More</h2><br/>
For a deeper look at all of the new features in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;, we have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">dedicated macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-releases-macos-sonoma/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma With New Widget Features, Safari Updates, Screen Sharing Improvements and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-with-new-widget-features-safari-updates-screen-sharing-improvements-and-more.2404826/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Issues Likely Due to Thermal Compromises, Not 3nm Node</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-overheating-issues-likely-due-to-thermal-compromises-not-3nm-node.2404820/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 09:12:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Complaints about heat issues with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models are not related to TSMC's 3-nanometer node that was used for the A17 Pro chip, according to well-respected <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/the-iphone-15-pro-series-overheating-issues-are-unrelated-to-tsmcs-advanced-3nm-node-iphone-15-5f354b1ab155">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
Kuo says that overheating could be caused by "compromises made in the thermal system design" that allowed Apple to cut down on the weight of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models. Kuo says that the reduced heat dissipation area and titanium frame have negatively impacted the thermal efficiency of the devices. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to address the thermal issues through software updates, but improvements will be limited unless Apple plans to lower processor performance. Kuo believes that if Apple is unable to "properly address this issue," shipments could be impacted over the life cycle of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15pros-overheating-during-gaming-severe-throttling.2403584/">have been reports</a> about the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models becoming hot to the touch, and some tests have suggested that when this happens, the processor is throttled in order to cool the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> down. These tests have been benchmarks and extreme use cases that may not impact users in day-to-day life, but it remains to be seen how the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models will run console-quality games like Resident Evil Village and Death Stranding.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/iphone-15-pro-overheating/">Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Overheating Issues Likely Due to Thermal Compromises, Not 3nm Node</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-overheating-issues-likely-due-to-thermal-compromises-not-3nm-node.2404820/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma Optimizes Latest 13-Inch MacBook Air&#039;s Battery Health</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/macos-sonoma-13-macbook-air-m2-battery-health/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-optimizes-latest-13-inch-macbook-airs-battery-health.2404806/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/macos-sonoma-13-macbook-air-m2-battery-health/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[macOS Sonoma better optimizes the long-term battery health of the 13-inch MacBook Air with the M2 chip, according to Apple's release notes for the software update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/macbook-air-spacegray-purple-battery.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913843" /><br/>
"Battery health management updated on 13-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip to better optimize long term battery health," the release notes state.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not provide any additional details about the exact optimizations that it made, nor have there been any widespread battery health complaints from customers who own this 13-inch MacBook Air model, released in July 2022. Battery health information can be found by opening the System Settings app and clicking on Battery.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT211832">support document</a>, Apple explains how the battery health management feature works:<blockquote>Battery health management is designed to improve your battery's lifespan by reducing the rate at which it chemically ages. The feature does this by monitoring your battery's temperature history and its charging patterns.<br/>
<br/>
Based on the measurements that it collects, battery health management may temporarily reduce your battery's maximum charge. This happens as needed to ensure that your battery charges to a level that's optimized for your usage—reducing wear on the battery, and slowing its chemical aging.</blockquote>macOS Sonoma is set to be released today following over three months of beta testing, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/24/macos-sonoma-launch-date-and-features/">key new features</a> including interactive desktop widgets, a Game Mode, the ability to add websites to the Dock as web apps, several Safari improvements, and more. We previously shared a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/will-my-mac-run-macos-sonoma/">list of Macs compatible with the update</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/macos-sonoma-13-macbook-air-m2-battery-health/">macOS Sonoma Optimizes Latest 13-Inch MacBook Air&#039;s Battery Health</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-optimizes-latest-13-inch-macbook-airs-battery-health.2404806/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Chief Calls on Apple CEO Tim Cook to Open Hardware and Software Ecosystem</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/eu-calls-on-apple-to-open-ecosystem/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-chief-calls-on-apple-ceo-tim-cook-to-open-hardware-and-software-ecosystem.2404803/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 08:01:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/eu-calls-on-apple-to-open-ecosystem/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[EU industry chief Thierry Breton today publicly called on Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> to open the company's ecosystem of hardware and software to rivals (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eus-breton-tells-apple-ceo-open-its-ecosystem-rivals-2023-09-26/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
Following an in-person meeting with Cook earlier today in Brussels, Belgium, Breton told <em>Reuters</em>:<blockquote>The next job for Apple and other Big Tech, under the DMA (Digital Markets Act) is to open up its gates to competitors. Be it the electronic wallet, browsers or app stores, consumers using an Apple iPhone should be able to benefit from competitive services by a range of providers.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The EU's Digital Markets Act seeks to curtail the power of major tech companies. Designated "gatekeeper" platforms will now face prohibition against favoring their own services over those of rivals. Earlier this month, Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, Safari, and iOS were officially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">classified as gatekeepers</a>. Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/app-sideloading-support-coming-ios-17/">expected to add support</a> for sideloading apps from outside the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; on iPhones and iPads in Europe via an update to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> due to the DMA's requirements.<br/>
<br/>
Breton went on to be critical of Apple's argument that security and privacy are the reasons it protects its closed ecosystem. "EU regulation fosters innovation, without compromising on security and privacy," Breton added. After the discussion, Cook today visited a local Apple retail store in Brussels:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Great to connect with team members and customers at Apple Brussels! <a href="https://t.co/RYW2NOGiM9">pic.twitter.com/RYW2NOGiM9</a></p>&mdash; Tim Cook (@tim_cook) <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook/status/1706609678522658865?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 26, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple apparently declined to respond to Breton's latest remarks.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/eu-calls-on-apple-to-open-ecosystem/">EU Chief Calls on Apple CEO Tim Cook to Open Hardware and Software Ecosystem</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-chief-calls-on-apple-ceo-tim-cook-to-open-hardware-and-software-ecosystem.2404803/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>22 New Features You May Have Missed in watchOS 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/22-hidden-features-watchos-10-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/22-new-features-you-may-have-missed-in-watchos-10.2404798/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 07:33:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/22-hidden-features-watchos-10-apple-watch&#038;post_date=1695749597/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last week launched <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, the latest major software update for compatible Apple Watch models, as well as the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and second-generation Apple Watch Ultra, both of which come with &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; pre-installed. Headline &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; features include a new Smart Stack interface with widgets, new watch faces, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/22-Hidden-Features-in-watchOS-10-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2248" height="1264" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913396" /><br/>
In this article, we've listed 22 other features and enhancements in Apple's new smartwatch software, many of which may have gone under your radar. Bear in mind that ‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; requires Apple Watch Series 4 or later and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> XS or later running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="1._automate_night_mode">1. Automate Night Mode</h2><br/>
On Apple Watch Ultra models, &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; brings a new Modular Ultra watch face that, like the Wayfinder face, supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/night-mode/">Night Mode</a>. &zwnj;Night Mode&zwnj; puts a red filter on the display, and previously could only be manually activated by turning the Digital Crown. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/1-auto-night-mode.jpg" alt="" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912577" /><br/>
In &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;, however, there's a &zwnj;Night Mode&zwnj; setting in the watch face edit screen for these two watch faces that lets you set it to Auto or On/Off. On the Auto setting, &zwnj;Night Mode&zwnj; will automatically activate in poor lighting conditions, such as when your sleeve is covering your watch or when you look at it in a dark room. Note that turning the Digital Crown no longer works, as this action now brings up the new Widget Stack. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2._check_control_center_status">2. Check Control Center Status</h2><br/>
Small icons at the top of Control Center indicate the status of certain settings — for example, that your Apple Watch is connected to cellular, your location is being used by an app, and features like Airplane Mode and Do Not Disturb are on.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/2-control-center-status.jpg" alt="" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912587" /><br/>
If you're not sure what a displayed status icon means, you can now tap the icons to get details.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="3._set_multiple_timers">3. Set Multiple Timers</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-label-multiple-timers-ios/">Like iPhones running iOS 17</a>, you can now set multiple concurrent timers on Apple Watch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/3-multiple-timers-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912582" /><br/>
Open the Timer app, create and start a timer, then tap the + button in the upper right corner to return to the Timers screen, where you can create and start another timer.<br/>
<br/>
With multiple timers counting down, you can use the Digital Crown to switch between timer displays, or alternatively you can keep track of them in the timer list. Tip: to assign a label such as "cupcakes" to a timer, use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>. Raise your Apple Watch, then say something like "Set a 12 minute cupcakes timer."<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="4._access_the_app_switcher">4. Access the App Switcher</h2><br/>
In previous versions of watchOS, you could access the Dock by pressing the Side button, but in &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; this action has been reassigned to the Control Center. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/4-access-app-switcher.jpg" alt="" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912580" /><br/>
You can, in fact, still access the Dock (now called the App Switcher) with a double press of the Digital Crown. Turning the Digital Crown scrolls through apps, and the most recently used app appears at the front of the Dock with other apps behind it, in the order they were last opened. Apps that are currently running a session — a Maps navigation session or a Workout session, for example — appear at the front.<br/>
<br/>
You can also remove apps from the App Switcher: turn the Digital Crown to the app you want to remove, swipe left on the app, then tap X.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="_5._adjust_the_flashlight"> 5. Adjust the Flashlight</h2><br/>
When the flashlight it activated, you can now adjust the brightness intensity by turning the Digital Crown up and down.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/5-adjust-flashlight.jpg" alt="" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912583" /><br/>
To turn on the flashlight, press the Side button to open Control Center, then tap the Flashlight button. Don't forget, you can also swipe left to choose a mode — steady white light, flashing white light, or steady red light.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="6._set_a_target_elevation_alert">6. Set a Target Elevation Alert</h2><br/>
In the compass app, you can set a target elevation and receive an alert after going beyond it. The new alert option is designed to help you stay safe and remind you to rest and acclimate as you move.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/set-target-elevation.jpg" alt="compass" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913731" /><br/>
Open the Compass app, tap the info (i) button, then tap Set Target Alert. Turn the Digital Crown to set the target elevation, then tap the check button, and you'll receive the alert when the elevation is exceeded.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="7._get_relative_waypoint_elevation">7. Get Relative Waypoint Elevation</h2><br/>
Each screen that shows the compass dial in the Compass app has a new Elevation button at the bottom of the display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/compass-3d-view.jpg" alt="compass" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913732" /><br/>
Tap it, and you'll get a 3D-like view of your waypoint elevations relative to your current elevation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="8._browse_waypoints">8. Browse Waypoints</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;, you can browse waypoints, including those you’ve created in the Compass app as well as waypoints from guides in the Maps app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/browse-waypoints.jpg" alt="compass" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913777" /><br/>
In the Compass app, tap the info (i) button, then tap Waypoints. Tap Compass Waypoints, and you'll see any waypoints you’ve created as well as automatically generated waypoints such as the location of your parked car and the last estimated locations where cellular connectivity and Emergency SOS were available.<br/>
<br/>
You can also tap a guide, such as My Places or a guide you created in the Maps app, to view those waypoints on the compass. Note that waypoints that are more than 50 miles from you won’t appear on the compass dial. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="9._find_your_iphone_with_directions">9. Find Your iPhone With Directions</h2> <br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> share the same updated Ultra Wideband chip as can be found in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> series, so if you have one of the latest Apple Watch models you can use Precision Finding to ping your nearby &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and get accurate directions to it. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/find-iphone-watch.jpeg" alt="find" width="2448" height="1632" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913780" /><br/>
On your Apple Watch, press the Side button to bring up the Control Center, then tap the Ping &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; button. Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will play a sound and, if your &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; or Ultra 2 is within range, the screen will display a general heading and distance to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the size of the circle increases to guide movement in the correct direction. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="10._find_hiking_trails">10. Find Hiking Trails</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;, you can use the Maps app to find hiking trails and learn more about them, including details like their name, length, highest and lowest elevations, and the distance from your current location to the nearest access point.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/maps-trails.jpg" alt="maps" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913734" /><br/>
In the Maps app, scroll to the area you want to search, tap the search button, then enter "trails" into the input field. Nearby trailheads will appear as green dots that you can tap, and the name of a trail appears near the bottom of the display. You can also turn the Digital Crown to browse through nearby trail results.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="11._view_offline_maps">11. View Offline Maps</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, Apple has added the ability to download Maps for use offline, providing access to turn-by-turn directions and information for a chosen area even if you do not have a cellular or Wi-Fi connection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/downloaded-apple-maps.jpg" alt="maps" width="4320" height="2700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909329" /><br/>
Offline maps are automatically available on Apple Watch when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is on and within Bluetooth range (about 33 feet or 10 meters). To learn how to download offline maps on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/download-offline-maps-ios-apple-maps/">see our dedicated how-to</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="12._view_maps_walking_radius">12. View Maps Walking Radius</h2><br/>
The Maps app now includes a new Walking Radius feature that shows you how long it will take to walk to points of interest around you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/maps-walking-radius.jpg" alt="maps" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913735" /><br/>
To change the radius, turn the Digital Crown. You can increase it to a walking time of up to 60 minutes. To change the radius unit to distance, touch and hold the map, scroll down, then tap Distance below Radius Unit.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="13._share_your_location">13. Share Your Location</h2><br/>
Like in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, you can now let others know where you are by sharing your location in Messages, and it will be updated in real time right in the conversation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/share-location.jpg" alt="messages" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913736" /><br/>
Start a new message or open a conversation, tap the A button, then tap the Share Location button. You can then choose to show your live location (Share), which updates in real time, or share your static location (tap the pin icon, then tap Send Pin). <br/>
<br/>
If you share your live location, you can do so For One Hour, Until End of Day, or Indefinitely. To stop sharing your location, simply tap the shared location, then tap Stop Sharing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="14._start_a_group_facetime_call">14. Start a Group FaceTime Call</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;, you can now start group <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> audio calls right on your Apple Watch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/group-facetime.jpg" alt="phone" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913738" /><br/>
Open the Phone app on your Apple Watch, start a &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; audio call, then tap the ellipsis button and tap Add People to choose a contact. When someone joins the call, tap 2 People Active, tap the + button, then choose another contact.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="15._log_your_state_of_mind">15. Log Your State of Mind</h2><br/>
Using the Mindfulness app on Apple Watch, you can log your mood at different times throughout the day and input an overall mood for the day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/log-state-of-mind.jpg" alt="mental" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913741" /><br/>
Tap State of Mind, then tap either "Log how you're feeling right now," or "Log how you've felt overall today." Turn the Digital Crown to indicate how you're feeling then tap the checkmark button. You'll then be asked to choose words that describe how you're feeling and what's having the biggest impact on you.<br/>
<br/>
After you've logged your state of mind, you can check it against other lifestyle factors in the Health app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, under Mental Wellbeing -> State of Mind.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="16._record_video">16. Record Video</h2><br/>
For the first time on Apple Watch, in &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; you can use the Camera Remote app to record video from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/record-video.jpg" alt="camera" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913750" /><br/>
Simply open the Camera Remote app, position your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to frame the shot using your Apple Watch as a viewfinder, turn the Digital Crown to zoom, then touch and hold the Shutter button to start recording video. Release the button to stop.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="17._plan_home_energy_usage">17. Plan Home Energy Usage</h2><br/>
In the Home app on Apple Watch, Apple has added a new "Grid Forecast" section like the one found on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;. The feature is designed to use your location to tell you when "clean" energy is available to use, so you can be mindful of when you're using energy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ios-17-grid-forecast.jpg" alt="" width="3189" height="1794" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910962" /><br/>
Open the Home app, then tap the Energy category to show the Grid Forecast. Green bars in the widget indicate when cleaner energy is available in your area. If there are no bars, cleaner energy isn't forecast for the near future.<br/>
<br/>
If you're traveling, Grid Forecast shows energy information for both your home location, and the location of your paired &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Note that Grid Forecast is available only in the contiguous United States.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="18._add_another_airplay_device">18. Add Another AirPlay Device</h2><br/>
While controlling audio on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> device such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, you can switch to or add additional &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; devices using the Now Playing app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/now-playing.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913770" /><br/>
On the Now Playing screen, tap the ellipsis (three dots) button. Tap &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj;, then add devices by tapping them. You can also stop playback on any device simply by tapping it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="19._type_to_speak">19. Type to Speak</h2><br/>
Using the Live Speech accessibility feature, you can type on Apple Watch and have your words spoken aloud, both in person and on phone and &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; audio calls. Live Speech can be set up on Apple Watch by going to Settings -> Accessibility -> Live Speech, where you can choose a voice to use. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/live-speech.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913772" /><br/>
After setting up the Accessibility Shortcut (Settings -> Accessibility -> Accessibility Shortcut -> Live Speech) you can triple-click the Digital Crown and type what you'd like to have spoken out loud.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="20._change_your_email_signature">20. Change Your Email Signature</h2><br/>
By default, messages you send from your Apple Watch are signed with "Sent from my Apple Watch." Prior to &zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;, you couldn't customize your email watch signature, but now you can.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/mail-signature.jpg" alt="mail" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913773" /><br/>
Open the Watch app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, tap My Watch, tap Mail, then tap Custom. Tap Signature, then create your new signature.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="21._share_a_news_story">21. Share a News Story</h2><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; introduces an option to share news stories in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a> from your Apple Watch. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/share-news.jpg" alt="news" width="1260" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913774" /><br/>
Open the News app on your watch, scroll to a story, then tap it. Scroll down, tap the Share button, then choose a sharing option.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="22._ping_your_apple_watch">22. Ping Your Apple Watch</h2><br/>
For some time now, it's been possible to ping your misplaced &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with your Apple Watch. In &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, you can now do the reverse and ping your Apple Watch with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; if you forgot where you put it down.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/ping-watch-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903766" /><br/>
Apple doesn't include the new Ping My Watch button in the default Control Center set, but you can add it manually: Go to Settings -> Control Center, then under "More Controls," tap the + button next to Ping My Watch. (Okay, technically not a "&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj; feature," but still worth knowing!)<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/22-hidden-features-watchos-10-apple-watch/">22 New Features You May Have Missed in watchOS 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/22-new-features-you-may-have-missed-in-watchos-10.2404798/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Looking to Save Space in Future iPhones With Thinner Circuit Boards</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-looking-to-save-space-with-thinner-pcbs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-save-space-in-future-iphones-with-thinner-circuit-boards.2404787/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 06:42:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-looking-to-save-space-with-thinner-pcbs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will begin using a new material to make its printed circuit boards thinner starting next year, according to a source with a good track record.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Apple-Silicon-Teal-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-767478" /><br/>
Apple will reportedly switch to using resin coated copper (RCC) foil as a new printed circuit board (PCB) material in 2024. The change will apparently allow Apple to make its PCBs even thinner. Current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> PCBs are made from a flexible copper substrate material. A thinner PCB could free up valuable space inside compact devices like the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch to provide more room for larger batteries or other components.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> Pro models are expected to grow in size from 6.1- and 6.7-inches to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">6.3- and 6.9-inches</a>, respectively. The increase in size is believed to be partly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/28/gurman-corroborates-iphone-16-pro-size-increase/">due to a need for more internal space</a> for additional components such as a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/periscope-lens-exclusive-iphone-15-pro-max/">tetraprism telephoto camera</a> with 5x optical zoom and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">capacitive "Capture" button</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The information comes from an <a href="https://weibo.com/u/1833340431">integrated circuit expert</a> on Weibo, who was first to report that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> would retain the A15 Bionic chip, with the A16 being exclusive to the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ Pro models. Most recently, the user said that the A17 chip designed for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌ Plus will be made using a fundamentally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/">different manufacturing process to the A17 Pro</a> in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> to cut costs.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-looking-to-save-space-with-thinner-pcbs/">Apple Looking to Save Space in Future iPhones With Thinner Circuit Boards</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-looking-to-save-space-in-future-iphones-with-thinner-circuit-boards.2404787/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Get the 10th Gen iPad for New Record Low Price of &#36;379 (&#36;70 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/deals-10th-gen-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-get-the-10th-gen-ipad-for-new-record-low-price-of-379-70-off.2404780/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 06:18:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/deals-10th-gen-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 64GB Wi-Fi 10.9-inch iPad has hit a new all-time low price today on B&H Photo, available for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1731146-REG/apple_mpq13ll_a_10_9_ipad_10th_gen.html/kw/APMPQ13LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. This deal is available for the Blue and Silver color options and B&H Photo offers free two-day shipping in the contiguous United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Deals.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893589" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with B&H Photo. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We typically track this version of the 10th generation iPad at around a discounted price of &#36;399.00, so today's deal beats the previous record low by &#36;20. As of now, only B&H Photo has this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1731146-REG/apple_mpq13ll_a_10_9_ipad_10th_gen.html/kw/APMPQ13LLA/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This iPad launched in October 2022 with a complete redesign, larger display, USB-C port, the A14 Bionic chip, a 12-megapixel camera, and more. There's Touch ID support on the tablet, located on the top button of the iPad.<br/>
<br/>
For even more iPad deals, head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-deals/">Best Deals guide for iPad</a>. In that guide we track the best discounts online for iPad, iPad mini, iPad Air, and iPad Pro. You can also keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/deals-10th-gen-ipad/">Deals: Get the 10th Gen iPad for New Record Low Price of &#36;379 (&#36;70 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-get-the-10th-gen-ipad-for-new-record-low-price-of-379-70-off.2404780/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Back to School Promotion Ends Soon: Here&#039;s What You Can Get</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apples-back-to-school-2023-promotion-ends-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-promotion-ends-soon-heres-what-you-can-get.2404775/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 05:38:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apples-back-to-school-2023-promotion-ends-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Back to School Promotion</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In June, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/06/apple-launches-2023-back-to-school-promotion/">launched its annual Back to School promotion</a> in the U.S. for college students. This year's promotion offers students a free Apple gift card with the purchase of an eligible Mac or iPad from Apple, along with 20% off AppleCare+ plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/2022-back-to-school-apple-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2178" height="1224" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851334" /><br/>
In the U.S. and Canada, the promotion <a href="https://www.apple.com/us/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">ends on October 2</a>, so time is running out to take advantage of the offer if you are a student. In the U.K. and select other European countries, the promotion ends a few weeks later, on October 23.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple is offering the following:<ul><li><strong>&#36;150 Apple gift card</strong> with any new MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, or iMac</li><br/>
<li><strong>&#36;100 Apple gift card</strong> with any new iPad Pro, iPad Air, or Mac mini</li></ul>The gift card can be used towards purchases of Apple products and accessories, App Store apps, subscriptions to services like Apple Music, iCloud+ storage, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The offer is available through Apple's online education store and at Apple Store locations for students attending or accepted to a higher-education institution, faculty and staff of higher-education institutions, parents purchasing on behalf of an eligible student, employees of a K-12 institution, and select others.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/back-to-school-promotion/">Back to School Promotion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apples-back-to-school-2023-promotion-ends-soon/">Apple&#039;s Back to School Promotion Ends Soon: Here&#039;s What You Can Get</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-back-to-school-promotion-ends-soon-heres-what-you-can-get.2404775/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 50+ Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro-buyers-guide-50-differences-compared.2404752/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 03:40:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro&#038;post_date=1695735634/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 13 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> brings over 50 new features and improvements to Apple's high-end smartphones compared to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> Pro, which was released two years prior. This buyer's guide breaks down every major difference you should be aware of between the two generations and helps you to decide whether it's worth upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-13-Pro-vs-15-Pro-Feature-1.5-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913695" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro debuted in 2021, introducing a brighter display with ProMotion technology for refresh rates up to 120Hz, the A15 Bionic chip, a telephoto camera with 3x optical zoom, Macro photography and photographic styles, Cinematic mode for recording videos with shallow depth of field, ProRes video recording, a 1TB storage option, and five hours of additional battery life. The &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro was discontinued upon the announcement of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> Pro in 2022, but it is still possible to get hold of it second-hand.<br/>
<br/>
Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models is best for you and serves as a way to clearly see the all of the differences that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; brings to the table. This article focuses on the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, but to understand the differences between the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, see our other buyer's guide:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer's Guide: 30+ Upgrades Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Although the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; share most of their basic features, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; offers a large number of notable upgrades, such as a titanium design, 48-megapixel main camera, always-on display, Action button, USB-C port, and A17 Bionic chip.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Surgical-grade stainless steel chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aerospace-grade titanium chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More repairable design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7.65mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>8.25mm depth (0.6mm thicker)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>204g or 240g weight</td><br/>
 <td>187g or 221g weight (17g or 19g lighter)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td>TrueDepth camera array with ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>‌</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thinner borders around the display for slightly smaller overall footprint</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1,200 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 <td>1,600 nits peak brightness (HDR) and 2,000 nits peak brightness (outdoor)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Always-On display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip (5nm)</td><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a>)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>6-core GPU with with hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated AV1 decoder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.5 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.78 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra-wide camera with ƒ/1.8 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra-wide camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel telephoto camera with ƒ/2.8 aperture and sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel telephoto camera with ƒ/2.8 aperture and larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module (Pro Max only)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/2.2 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel front-facing camera with ƒ/1.9 aperture and autofocus</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating on camera lenses</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>True Tone flash</td><br/>
 <td>Adaptive True Tone flash</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, and 3x optical zoom</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom (5x instead of 3x on Pro Max)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>13mm, 24mm, 28mm, 35mm, and 77mm focal length picker (120mm instead of 77mm on Pro Max)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Photonic Engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Shoot and instantly transfer 48-megapixel ProRAW images to Mac via USB 3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record video directly to an external drive</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 60 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode for recording videos with shallow depth of field (1080p at 30 fps)</td><br/>
 <td>Cinematic mode for recording videos with shallow depth of field (4K HDR up to 30 fps)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Action mode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Log video recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Academy Color Encoding System</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record spatial video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Bluetooth 5.0</td><br/>
 <td>Bluetooth 5.3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Emergency SOS</td><br/>
 <td>Emergency SOS via satellite</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>eSIM optional</td><br/>
 <td>eSIM only (in the U.S.)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>USB 2 transfer speeds (up to 480Mb/s)</td><br/>
 <td>USB 3 transfer speeds (up to 10Gb/s, 20x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>DisplayPort support for up to 4K HDR video output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for Qi wireless charging</td><br/>
 <td>Support for Qi 2 wireless charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>22- or 28-hour battery life</td><br/>
 <td>23- or 29-hour battery life</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB storage options</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB storage options (no 128GB tier on Pro Max)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Silver, Gold, Graphite, Sierra Blue, and Alpine Green color options</td><br/>
 <td>Natural Titanium, Blue Titanium, White Titanium, and Black Titanium color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is a significant upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro, introducing meaningful quality-of-life features like the USB-C port and Action button that change the methods of interaction with the device. The new, considerably more lightweight titanium design, slimmer borders around the display, and contoured edges result in a noticeably different aesthetic and feel in the hand.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; also brings major advancements to photography and videography, adding an Adaptive True Tone flash, a 48-megapixel main camera for high-resolution images and, on the larger model, a telephoto camera with 5x optical zoom. Software features such as Photonic Engine, Smart HDR 5, Next-generation portraits, Action mode, and a host of professional videography features like external recording and Log also take the photography and videography capabilities of the device to the next level.<br/>
<br/>
This is not to mention fast data transfer via USB 3, satellite connectivity, new color options, the second-generation ultra wideband chip, and the A17 Pro chip – Apple's first chip made with a &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; fabrication process, which radically improves the gaming capabilities of the device.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the scale and breadth of these improvements, most &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro will be able to justify upgrading to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, especially if they value the new design, USB-C port, Action button, and camera improvements. It is only worth sticking with the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro if you are holding off for an even more substantial upgrade in the future, but many users will see tangible benefits by upgrading now.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 50+ Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro-buyers-guide-50-differences-compared.2404752/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Radio Shows and More Now Available in Apple Podcasts App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-music-radio-shows-podcasts-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-radio-shows-and-more-now-available-in-apple-podcasts-app.2404744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 02:52:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-music-radio-shows-podcasts-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers can now stream shows from Apple's original radio catalog via the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> app, fulfilling a new services pledge made by the company earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-music-channel-podcasts.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913710" /><br/>
The new Podcasts app integration means eligible subscribers can delve into &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; original radio shows from the likes of &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; 1, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Hits, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Country – as if they were made to be listened as podcasts. <br/>
<br/>
The feature went live for eligible subscribers early on Tuesday, as per Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/06/apple-previews-new-features-coming-to-apple-services-this-fall/">announcement</a> in June: <br/>
<blockquote>"Subscribers will be able to listen to the entire catalog of award-winning, commercial-free Apple Music radio shows in Apple Podcasts, where they can follow individual shows to automatically download and be notified of new episodes as soon as they're released."</blockquote>The &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; content can be accessed from the Podcast app's Listen Now screen, as well as from the Channels section in the Library tab.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-podcasts-radio-shows.jpg" alt="" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913712" /><br/>
In addition to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; radio shows, users with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+ subscription should also soon be able to find News-related content in the Podcasts app.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> Apple has shared the following related <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/09/over-100-new-podcasts-from-top-apps-and-services-launch-on-apple-podcasts/">announcement</a>:<blockquote>Starting today, subscribers to Apple Music, Apple News+, Calm, and Lingokids can access over 60 original podcasts, including more than 2,500 musically rich episodes from Apple Music Radio. New shows from top apps and services will launch every week this fall.</blockquote><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-music-radio-shows-podcasts-app/">Apple Music Radio Shows and More Now Available in Apple Podcasts App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-radio-shows-and-more-now-available-in-apple-podcasts-app.2404744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Initially Explored Using GPS to Control AirPods Pro Adaptive Audio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-explored-gps-for-airpods-pro-adaptive-audio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-initially-explored-using-gps-to-control-airpods-pro-adaptive-audio.2404738/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 01:32:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-explored-gps-for-airpods-pro-adaptive-audio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>TechCrunch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Apple introduced second-generation ‌‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>‌, the Adaptive Transparency feature offered a new way to reduce loud environmental noise for more comfortable everyday listening. Adaptive Audio is designed to build on that approach by dynamically blending the existing Transparency and Active Noise Cancellation modes together to deliver the best audio experience in the moment, tailoring the noise control as the user between different environments and interactions. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/airpods-pro-2-ios-17.jpg" alt="" width="2407" height="1354" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900421" /><br/>
In this way, Adaptive Audio aims to automatically reduce loud or distracting noises in your surroundings, such as the sound of a leaf blower or a passing plane overhead, while other noises, like the sudden beep of a car horn, remain audible.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/new-airpods-pro-features-ios-17-how-to-use/">How to Use All the New AirPods Pro Features in iOS 17</a></li></ul><br/>
In a new interview with <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2023/09/25/apple-executives-break-down-airpods-new-features/">TechCrunch</a></em>, Apple's VP of sensing and connectivity Ron Huang revealed that Apple originally considered using GPS location to inform &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; of the user's whereabouts and adapt the audio experience accordingly. In real-world testing, however, the method proved inefficient. From the interview:<br/>
<blockquote>"During early exploration for Adaptive Audio, we basically put you in ANC versus transparency, based on where you are," says Huang. "You can imagine the phone can give a hint to the AirPods and say, "hey, you're in the house" and so forth. That is a way to do that, but after all our learnings, we don't think that is the right way to do it, and that is not what we did. Of course, your house is not always quiet and the streets are not always loud. We decided that, instead of relying on a location hint from the phone, the AirPods monitor your environment in real time and make those decisions intelligently on their own."</blockquote>Huang in the interview also returned to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/22/apple-on-airpods-pro-vision-pro-lossless-audio/">reason why</a> USB-C &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; can support Lossless Audio with Vision Pro thanks to the updated H2 chip's support for the 5GHz wireless band (second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with a Lightning port only support 2.4GHz):<br/>
<blockquote>"Bluetooth typically runs on 2.4 gigahertz, and that airspace is very, very noisy," says Huang. "Everybody's running on 2.4. That's why routers Wi-Fi routers, for example, are typically dual-band if not tri-band, because the 5Ghz spectrum is that much cleaner. To get to really, really low latency audio, and to get to really high fidelity, lossless audio — it's all about a very, very clean and real-time channel between two. The combination of 5Ghz and the fact that they are very proximal allowed us to do that. We're able to basically redesign a brand new audio protocol over the 5Ghz for AirPods."</blockquote>Elsewhere in the interview, Huang touches on other features that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> brought to &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, including Conversation Awareness, Personalized Audio, and faster device switching. Priced at &#36;249 in the U.S., the updated second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; began arriving to customers late last week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/techcrunch-com/">TechCrunch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/apple-explored-gps-for-airpods-pro-adaptive-audio/">Apple Initially Explored Using GPS to Control AirPods Pro Adaptive Audio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-initially-explored-using-gps-to-control-airpods-pro-adaptive-audio.2404738/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Users Report Weather Complication Issues in watchOS 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/watchos-10-weather-complication-issues/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-users-report-weather-complication-issues-in-watchos-10.2404733/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 00:21:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/watchos-10-weather-complication-issues/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some Apple Watch users on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> have reported experiencing issues with Weather complications failing to display data on the watch face, despite the Weather app itself presenting no such issues. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/weather-complications.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913698" /><br/>
Apple Watch users have taken to the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-10-and-weather-rain-complication-problem.2403847/"><em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>, <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255145549">Apple's Support Community</a>, and other platforms to share their experiences. <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/09/25/watchos-10-weather-bug/?extended-comments=1#comments">9to5Mac</a></em> has highlighted the problem, and some <em>MacRumors</em> staff have seen its occurrence on their own watches. <br/>
<br/>
Affected complications appear blank where weather data should be showing, and yet tapping the complication reveals the expected information in the Weather app. The issue appears to be happening on various models whether they are on watchOS 10.0 or have been updated to the latest watchOS 10.0.1 update.<br/>
<br/>
Until Apple issues an update to correct the problem, one temporary workaround that users have had the most success with is to open the Watch app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and toggle the 24-Hour Time switch in the Clock app settings, wait a few seconds, then toggle it back to its original position. The paired Watch should update, and the affected complications should display weather data again (until they don't again – your mileage may vary).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/clock-app-24-hour-setting.jpg" alt="" width="2737" height="1426" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913699" /><br/>
Has your Apple Watch been affected by the Weather complications issue? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/26/watchos-10-weather-complication-issues/">Apple Watch Users Report Weather Complication Issues in watchOS 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-users-report-weather-complication-issues-in-watchos-10.2404733/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 to Include an Additional Capacitive &#039;Capture&#039; Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-an-additional-capacitive-capture-button.2404661/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:50:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series is expected to gain an additional capacitive button, known internally as the "Capture Button." Codenamed "Project Nova," the button is likely to be one of the main selling points of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, assuming it gets past the initial testing phase. The Capture Button is located on the same side as the Power button, only positioned slightly lower - where the mmWave cutout can be found on more recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models. The mmWave cutout has been moved to the opposite side, located under the volume buttons. It is currently unknown what the new capacitive button will be used for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
The Capture Button is expected to be a capacitive button rather than a standard mechanical one. Capacitive buttons, unlike mechanical buttons, do not move when pressed down. Instead, the button detects pressure and touch, providing haptic feedback through the use of haptic engines. The buttons are expected to work similarly to the Home Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, which mimics the press of a physical button through the built-in Taptic Engine. According to our sources, the capacitive buttons will feature force sensor functionality. Force sensors detect applied force, and convert the magnitude of force into electrical signals.<br/>
<br/>
Early in the development of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, Apple experimented with capacitive buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the form of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/#:~:text=Project%20Bongo%2C%20as%20it%20was,do%20not%20move%20when%20pressed.">the since-canceled Bongo project</a>. The Bongo module, unlike the Capture Button, consisted of capacitive Power and Volume buttons, and didn’t bring any additional buttons into the mix. Based on what we’ve heard from our sources, the Bongo module was canceled during the EVT stage of development, after unsatisfactory test results and a significant number of hardware issues. The cancelation left Apple engineers with ample room to reimagine the capacitive buttons for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; series, with an entirely new twist this time around.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike the Bongo project, the Capture Button is set to make its debut across the entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, including the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus. It is worth noting, though, that Apple also created a hardware configuration without the Capture Button button, possibly as a fallback variant in the event of continued hardware failure rates. The Capture Button has appeared on both eSIM-only units and devices with support for physical SIM card slots.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913688" /><br/>
Along with the new Capture Button, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to gain a capacitive Action Button. Known as "Project Atlas," the haptic Action Button uses a design similar to the Capture Button, using strain gauges and reluctance motor to provide the necessary haptic feedback.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the Capture Button and upgraded Action Button, the base model &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is expected to feature a redesigned camera bump, with vertical camera arrangement akin to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12. The Pro models are also set to feature an increase in screen size, from 6.1" and 6.7" to 6.3" and 6.9", respectively.<br/>
<br/>
It is important to consider that the information presented here is pre-production information. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is still in the early stages of development, and the design has not been finalized. Because of this, there is always a chance that we may not see the Capture Button on the final product.<br/>
<br/>
For more details on what to expect, check out our rumor roundup page for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">iPhone 16 to Include an Additional Capacitive &#039;Capture&#039; Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-to-include-an-additional-capacitive-capture-button.2404661/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 Continue to Be Heavily Criticized</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-finewoven-cases-for-iphone-15-continue-to-be-heavily-criticized.2404651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 12:05:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new FineWoven cases for iPhone 15 models have been heavily criticized since they were released earlier this month, with some customers and media outlets complaining about the fabric exterior being prone to <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2023/9/20/23882255/apple-iphone-15-finewoven-case-wallet-bad">scratches</a> and <a href="https://mastodon.macstories.net/@viticci/111119387802099507">stains</a>. We <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">recapped some of the negative feedback</a> last week, and complaints have continued to surface.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://512pixels.net/2023/09/finewoven-case-letdown/"><em>512 Pixels</em> blog post</a> on Sunday, Relay FM co-founder Stephen Hackett shared a photo of his FineWoven case with a misaligned USB-C port cutout, resulting in the pentalobe screw on the right side of the USB-C port being partially exposed.<br/>
<br/>
"It's one thing for these cases to be a letdown in terms of material, but this is a level of sloppiness that genuinely surprises me from Apple," he wrote. "I know not every example out there is as bad as mine, but the vibes around this case aren't good."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/FineWoven-USB-C-Cutout.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913672" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Photo: Stephen Hackett</em></div><br/>
On social media, some users claimed that the USB-C cutout only appears to be misaligned because of the angle that the photo was taken at, but other users responded with <a href="https://twitter.com/OprahsGift/status/1706087754847666583">straight-on photos</a> of the FineWoven case with the same issue. Not all of the cases have this issue, but multiple customers appear to be affected.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, <a href="https://twitter.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1705377239850951047">Parker Ortolani</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/HartleyCharlton/status/1706025920648114222"><em>MacRumors</em> editor Hartley Charlton</a> shared photos of FineWoven cases with visible damage on display at Apple Stores. An anonymous, alleged Apple Store employee <a href="https://twitter.com/LindaLominger/status/1706349826093273269">mentioned likewise</a> in a post on X, formerly Twitter.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Here you can see FineWoven cases after less than a day on retail shelves. Not great. <a href="https://t.co/9RwCAax7sG">pic.twitter.com/9RwCAax7sG</a></p>&mdash; Parker Ortolani (@ParkerOrtolani) <a href="https://twitter.com/ParkerOrtolani/status/1705377239850951047?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 23, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple describes FineWoven as a "durable micro-twill" material made from 68% post-consumer recycled polyester, and said the material has a significantly lower carbon footprint than leather. Earlier this month, Apple announced that it would no longer use leather in any new products or accessories, as part of its environmental responsibility efforts.<br/>
<br/>
It's hard to measure exactly how much negative feedback there is for the new FineWoven cases, but the material certainly appears to be proving quite unpopular so far. We've reached out to Apple for comment, and we'll update this story if we hear back.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">Apple&#039;s FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 Continue to Be Heavily Criticized</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-finewoven-cases-for-iphone-15-continue-to-be-heavily-criticized.2404651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
