<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 20:02:31 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Planning 20-Inch MacBook With Foldable Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-planning-20-inch-macbook-with-foldable-screen.2421253/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 19:12:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Foldable MacBook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to release a 20-inch MacBook with a foldable screen in around three years, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
"Apple's only foldable product with a clear development schedule is the 20.3-inch MacBook, expected to enter mass production in 2027," said Kuo, <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1765563986089783322">in a post on X today</a>. He did not provide any additional details about the device.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo is the third source to mention the possibility of a 20-inch MacBook, alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/31/apple-foldable-notebook-2025/">display industry analyst Ross Young</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-20-inch-display-future-macbook-pro/">Korean website <em>The Elec</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
The largest laptop that Apple currently sells is the 16-inch MacBook Pro. The company also once offered a 17-inch MacBook Pro, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2012/06/11/apple-quietly-discontinues-macbook-pro-17/">discontinued in 2012</a>. The new foldable MacBook would have a screen that measures around 20 inches diagonally when fully expanded, but Kuo did not provide any details about the device's exact design.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said the 20-inch MacBook is Apple's only foldable product with a clear development schedule, suggesting that a foldable iPhone or iPad are not coming any time soon.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-macbook/">Foldable MacBook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/20-inch-macbook-kuo/">Kuo: Apple Planning 20-Inch MacBook With Foldable Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-planning-20-inch-macbook-with-foldable-screen.2421253/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Car&#039;s Decade of Development and &#039;Failure&#039; Detailed in New Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cars-decade-of-development-and-failure-detailed-in-new-report.2421232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:15:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman and Drake Bennett today published an <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-03-06/apple-car-s-crash-design-details-tim-cook-s-indecision-failed-tesla-deal">in-depth report</a> examining Apple's decade-long attempt at creating an electric vehicle. The project was reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">canceled last week</a> after many challenges and setbacks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/Apple-car-wheel-icon-Kevin-Lynch-feature-blue-revamp.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839900" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple vice president Kevin Lynch, who oversaw the electric vehicle project in its later years</em></div><br/>
The report described a 2020 prototype of Apple's electric vehicle:<blockquote>The prototype, a white minivan with rounded sides, an all-glass roof, sliding doors and whitewall tires, was designed to comfortably seat four people and inspired by the classic flower-power Volkswagen microbus. The design was referred to within Apple, not always affectionately, as the Bread Loaf. The plan was for the vehicle to hit the market some five years later with a giant TV screen, a powerful audio system and windows that adjusted their own tint. The cabin would have club seating like a private plane, and passengers would be able to turn some of the seats into recliners and footrests.</blockquote>Apple once considered acquiring Tesla to bolster its efforts, the report said:<blockquote>But before sketching out its own designs, Apple considered acquiring Tesla. At that point the electric-car maker's success was far from assured, and its value was less than &#36;30 billion, or a 20th of what it is today. Adrian Perica, Apple's head of corporate development, held a series of meetings with Elon Musk. But Cook, who'd succeeded Jobs three years earlier, shut the deal down while negotiations were still at an early stage.</blockquote>Apple also considered partnering with or acquiring Mercedes-Benz, BMW, Ford, Volkswagen, McLaren, and other automakers, according to the report:<blockquote>Talks with Mercedes-Benz progressed further. For a few months, Apple and the German automaker actively worked on a partnership similar to the Tesla idea, but with a twist. Mercedes would manufacture Apple's vehicle, while it would also sell its own cars with Apple's self-driving platform and user interface. Apple eventually pulled out, in part because the early work gave its executives confidence they could build a car on their own, people involved in the failed deal say.</blockquote>The project was ultimately a "failure" due to indecision, the report said:<blockquote>But Apple never got close to realizing its original vision, or any of its subsequent ones. It didn't get as far as testing a full-scale prototype on public roads. That it didn't is partly thanks to the enormous technical difficulty of its self-driving goals, as well as the punishing economics of the automaking business. The project was also a failure, at the highest levels of the company, to settle on one thing and do it.</blockquote>The report detailed how Apple's COO Jeff Williams and Apple Car chief Kevin Lynch broke the  news of the project's cancellation to employees:<blockquote>The meeting lasted about 12 minutes. Both men thanked the staffers for their work and got straight to the reorg and layoffs. Some employees would immediately get shifted to Apple's AI division, and some would move over to software engineering. A chunk of the team, though, was immediately without a job. Hardware engineers would have the opportunity to apply for roles in other groups, but there aren't spots for everyone. Other employees, such as the hundreds of car-specific engineers, test track technicians, self-driving car testers and automotive safety experts, received emails with their severance packages. As for the Arizona track, Apple is already working to sell it.</blockquote>Other notable details mentioned in the report include that Steve Jobs was apparently first to raise the idea of Apple building a vehicle, and that some Apple employees received a tour of Jay Leno's garage and his car collection early on.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2024-03-06/apple-car-s-crash-design-details-tim-cook-s-indecision-failed-tesla-deal"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s full report</a> is a worthwhile read for those interested in learning more about Apple's vehicle project, and we also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">shared our own recap last week</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-car-history-bloomberg-report/">Apple Car&#039;s Decade of Development and &#039;Failure&#039; Detailed in New Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cars-decade-of-development-and-failure-detailed-in-new-report.2421232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 190 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2421238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 190 includes fixes and updates for CSS, History, HTML, JavaScript, Media, Networking, SVG, URLs, Web API, and Web Inspector.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Ventura and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of macOS that Apple released in September 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 190 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-190-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2421238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing FaceTime on Apple TV With Belkin&#039;s New MagSafe iPhone Mount</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-facetime-on-apple-tv-with-belkins-new-magsafe-iphone-mount.2421225/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 11:34:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Belkin</category>
		<category>FaceTime</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Belkin this week released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/belkin-iphone-magsafe-mount-for-apple-tv/">new iPhone Mount with MagSafe</a>, which is designed to attach to a television for use with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> 4K. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Mount lets you use your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as a camera for your &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Belkin iPhone MagSafe Stand" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MdByMW-lVX0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Apple actually showed off this mount when it introduced &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; on &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, but it hasn't been available for purchase until now, and there hasn't been an official solution for mounting an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a television set.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1V2ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-apple-tv-4k">Priced at &#36;49.95</a>, the Belkin &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mount has a bracket that is able to attach to a TV or a display that's up to four inches thick, or it can be used with a pedestal as a standalone mount next to a TV.<br/>
<br/>
It's super simple to use the mount, and you just need to pop it on the TV and then stick your MagSafe-enabled &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the mount. You can adjust the tilt from -20 to +30 degrees for the perfect filming angle, and it works in either portrait or landscape mode.<br/>
<br/>
We tested the mount with &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;, but it is also compatible with any Continuity Camera-supported apps. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; activates automatically as the camera in &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; or another supported app, and all you need to do is be signed in with the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> on both devices.<br/>
<br/>
Note that using an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a camera for an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; requires the second-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K or later with tvOS 17, and an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; (or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>) running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later.<br/>
<br/>
Using a TV for &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; is great if you're FaceTiming with multiple people or for SharePlay sessions, and there are options to set up a split-screen layout when using &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;. The mount and the Continuity Camera feature work with Center Stage, and reactions like fireworks are supported.<br/>
<br/>
Large-screen &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; is definitely an experience that's worth trying out if you tend to do a lot of video calling. <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1V2ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-apple-tv-4k"> Apple is selling the Belkin Mount</a> for &#36;49.95, and it's shipping out almost immediately.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/belkin/">Belkin</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/facetime-apple-tv-belkin-magsafe-iphone-mount/">Testing FaceTime on Apple TV With Belkin&#039;s New MagSafe iPhone Mount</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-facetime-on-apple-tv-with-belkins-new-magsafe-iphone-mount.2421225/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains Why It Terminated Epic&#039;s Latest Developer Account</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-explains-terminating-epic-games-account/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-it-terminated-epics-latest-developer-account.2421220/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 09:40:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-explains-terminating-epic-games-account/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today said it has <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/site/en-US/news/apple-terminated-epic-s-developer-account">terminated Epic Games Sweden's developer account</a> worldwide due to the game developer's pattern of untrustworthy behavior.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
Apple shared the following statement with <em>MacRumors</em>:<blockquote>Epic's egregious breach of its contractual obligations to Apple led courts to determine that Apple has the right to terminate "any or all of Epic Games' wholly owned subsidiaries, affiliates, and/or other entities under Epic Games' control at any time and at Apple's sole discretion." In light of Epic's past and ongoing behavior, Apple chose to exercise that right.</blockquote>In a letter sent to Epic, lawyers representing Apple said that Epic has proven to be "verifiably untrustworthy." Apple said it cannot be assured that Epic will follow the Apple Developer Program's terms and conditions in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Epic said that it had intended to use the Swedish account to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">launch an Epic Games Store on iOS</a> in the EU, and this would have brought the Fortnite app back to the iPhone. Starting with iOS 17.4, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">allows alternative app marketplaces</a> on the iPhone in the EU, as part of its compliance with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
In a press release, Epic said that Apple terminating the Swedish developer account is a "serious violation" of the Digital Markets Act, and "shows Apple has no intention of allowing true competition on iOS devices." <br/>
<br/>
More from Epic's response:<blockquote>In terminating Epic's developer account, Apple is taking out one of the largest potential competitors to the Apple App Store. They are undermining our ability to be a viable competitor and they are showing other developers what happens when you try to compete with Apple or are critical of their unfair practices.</blockquote>Epic believes that Apple suspended its Swedish developer account in part due to Epic CEO Tim Sweeney's public criticism of Apple's proposed Digital Markets Act compliance plans. Epic shared a letter it received from the App Store's chief Phil Schiller, who indeed said that Sweeney's "colorful criticism" of Apple's plans, but also Epic's history of "intentionally violating contractual provisions with which it disagrees," strongly suggest that Epic does not intend to follow the Apple Developer Program rules if reinstated.<br/>
<br/>
The legal battle between the two companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">began in 2020</a>, after Apple removed Fortnite from the App Store on the iPhone due to Epic introducing a direct payment option in the app for the in-game currency V-Bucks, in defiance of the App Store rules. In what appears to have been an orchestrated move, Epic promptly filed a lawsuit against Apple, accusing the company of anti-competitive behavior.<br/>
<br/>
Apple had already terminated one of Epic's other developer accounts in 2020 after the company violated the App Store's rules with its Fortnite stunt.<br/>
<br/>
Epic continues to litigate against Apple in both the U.S. and Australia, and it appears that the highly-publicized legal battle is far from over.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-explains-terminating-epic-games-account/">Apple Explains Why It Terminated Epic&#039;s Latest Developer Account</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-why-it-terminated-epics-latest-developer-account.2421220/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Air vs. MacBook Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 30+ Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide-30-differences-compared.2378980/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 09:29:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro&#038;post_date=1709756940/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">recently updated</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> by adding the M3 chip, so how do the new machines compare to its latest MacBook Pro models?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/M2-MBA-vs-M2-MacBook-Pro-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2507" height="1410" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-883243" /><br/>
Despite now being similar in appearance, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and the MacBook Pro are very different devices, so should you consider purchasing the 13- or 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, which start at &#36;999, to save money, or do you need one of the higher-end 14- or 16-inch MacBook Pro models, which cost at least &#36;600 more? Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two popular Apple silicon machines is best for you.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>MacBook Pro</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: 13.6-inch display<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: 13.6- or 15.3-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>14.2- or 16.2-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>LCD Liquid Retina display</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mini-led/">Mini-LED</a> Liquid Retina XDR display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>60hz refresh rate</td><br/>
 <td>ProMotion for refresh rates up to 120Hz</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>500 nits brightness</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 1,000 nits sustained (full-screen) brightness and 1,600 nits peak brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> or M3 chip</td><br/>
 <td>Apple M3, M3 Pro, or M3 Max chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: Enhanced 5nm node (N5P) based on A15 Bionic chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> (2021)<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> node (N3B) based on A17 Pro chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> (2023)</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;3nm&zwnj; node (N3B) based on A17 Pro chip from &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; (2023)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: 3.49 GHz CPU clock speed<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: 4.05 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 <td>4.05 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>8-core CPU with 4 performance cores and 4 efficiency cores</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: 8-core CPU with 4 performance cores and 4 efficiency cores<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong>: Up to 12-core CPU with 6 performance cores and 6 efficiency cores<br/>
<strong>M3 Max</strong>: Up to 16-core CPU with 12 performance cores and 4 efficiency cores</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 10-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: 10-core GPU<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong>: Up to 18-core GPU<br/>
<strong>M3 Max</strong>: Up to 40-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>100GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: 100GB/s memory bandwidth<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong>: 150GB/s memory bandwidth<br/>
<strong>M3 Max</strong>: 300GB/s or 400GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>8GB, 16GB, or 24GB unified memory</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: 8GB, 16GB, or 24GB unified memory<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong>: 18GB or 36GB unified memory<br/>
<strong>M3 Max</strong>: 36GB, 48GB, 64GB, 96GB, 128GB unified memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M3 models only</strong>:<br/>
New GPU architecture<br/>
Dynamic Caching<br/>
Hardware-accelerated ray tracing<br/>
Hardware-accelerated mesh shading<br/>
Support for AV1 decode</td><br/>
 <td>New GPU architecture<br/>
Dynamic Caching<br/>
Hardware-accelerated ray tracing<br/>
Hardware-accelerated mesh shading<br/>
Support for AV1 decode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: Neural Engine<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: 15% faster Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>15% faster Neural Engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>256GB, 512GB, 1TB, or 2TB of storage</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: 512GB, 1TB, or 2TB storage<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong> or <strong>M3 Max</strong>: 512GB, 1TB, 2TB, 4TB, or 8TB storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Passive cooling</td><br/>
 <td>Active cooling</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: Wi-Fi 6<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: Wi-Fi 6E</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Two Thunderbolt / USB 4 ports</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: Two Thunderbolt / USB 4 (USB-C) ports<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong> or <strong>M3 Max</strong>: Three Thunderbolt 4 (USB-C) ports</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>HDMI 2.1 port with support for multichannel audio output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>SDXC card slot</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>13-Inch</strong>: Four-speaker sound system<br/>
<strong>15-Inch</strong>: Six-speaker sound system with force-canceling woofers</td><br/>
 <td>High-fidelity six-speaker sound system with force-cancelling woofers</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Three-mic array with directional beamforming</td><br/>
 <td>Studio-quality three-mic array with high signal-to-noise ratio and directional beamforming</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2</strong>: Support for one external display<br/>
<strong>M3</strong>: Support for up to two external displays when the lid is closed</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3</strong>: Support for up to two external displays when the lid is closed<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong>: Support for up to two external displays<br/>
<strong>M3 Max</strong>: Support for up to four external displays</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>13-Inch</strong>: 52.6-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery<br/>
<strong>15-Inch</strong>: 66.5-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3 14-Inch</strong>: 70-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong> or <strong>M3 Max 14-Inch</strong>: 72.4-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery<br/>
<strong>16-Inch</strong>: 100-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>18-hour battery life</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3 14-Inch</strong>: 22-hour battery life<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong> or <strong>M3 Max 14-Inch</strong>: 18-hour battery life<br/>
<strong>16-Inch</strong>: 22-hour battery life</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>30W, 35W, or 67W USB-C Power Adapter</td><br/>
 <td>67W, 96W, or 140W USB-C Power Adapter</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Silver, Space Gray, Starlight, or Midnight color options</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3:</strong> Silver or Space Gray color options<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro</strong> or <strong>M3 Max</strong>: Silver or Space Black color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>M2 13-Inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;999<br/>
<strong>M3 13-Inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;1,099<br/>
<strong>M3 15-Inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;1,299</td><br/>
 <td><strong>M3 14-Inch:</strong> Starts at &#36;1,599<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro 14-Inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;1,999<br/>
<strong>M3 Pro 16-Inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;2,499</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
Both the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and MacBook Pro share the same basic design with a flat top and rounded edges on the bottom, but they do have several minor details that differ. For example, while both MacBooks have displays with a "notch" at the top to facilitate the built-in webcam, the MacBook Pro's bezels are noticeably slimmer. The keyboard area of the high-end MacBook Pro is also all-black.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/macbook-air-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="912" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-850089" /><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and M3 version of the MacBook Pro are available in Silver and Space Gray, but the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is also offered in Starlight and Midnight color options, so if you are looking for a particular aesthetic with one of these finishes, you will need to get the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. Space Black is exclusive to the MacBook Pro with the M3 Pro and M3 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (13-Inch)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (15-Inch)</th><br/>
 <th>MacBook Pro (14-Inch)</th><br/>
 <th>MacBook Pro (16-Inch)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>0.44 inches (1.13 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>0.45 inch (1.15 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>0.61 inches (1.55 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>0.66 inch (1.68 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>11.97 inches (30.41 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>13.40 inches (34.04 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>12.31 inches (31.26 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>14.01 inches (35.57 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Depth</th><br/>
 <td>8.46 inches (21.5 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>9.35 inches (23.76 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>8.71 inches (22.12 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>9.77 inches (24.81 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>2.7 pounds (1.24 kg)</td><br/>
 <td>3.3 pounds (1.51 kg)</td><br/>
 <td>3.5 pounds (1.61 kg)</td><br/>
 <td>4.8 pounds (2.15 kg)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Dimensions are also a key area of difference between the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and MacBook Pro. The 16-inch MacBook Pro is considerably larger and heavier than the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, but it is important to not understate the difference between the 14-inch MacBook Pro and the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. While the 14-inch MacBook Pro offers a larger display than the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, its marginally larger footprint, added thickness, and an additional 0.8 pounds of weight do make for a noticeably less portable machine if you prefer to travel light.<br/>
<br/>
Even so, the 14-inch MacBook Pro offers a very good balance of portability and performance, so if you need its added capabilities, its size and weight should not hold you back. The 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; also provides a good balance of portability and display area, but users wary of its size should opt for the 13-inch model.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="ports_and_connectivity">Ports and Connectivity</h3><br/>
The selection of ports is an area of major difference between the two machines. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; features just two Thunderbolt ports, while the M3 version of the MacBook Pro adds an HDMI 2.1 port and SDXC card slot. When configured with the M3 Pro or M3 Max, the MacBook Pro has a total of three Thunderbolt 4 ports, in addition to its HDMI 2.1 port and SDXC card slot. Both machines feature a 3.5mm headphone jack with support for high-impedance headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/2021-macbook-pro-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1952" height="1156" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821474" /><br/>
All in all, the MacBook Pro is much more versatile in terms of physical connectivity, offering useful features for professionals who use SDXC cards from digital cameras or even simply more USB peripherals.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="display_size">Display Size</h3><br/>
The smaller &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;'s display is 13.6 inches in size, which is a little smaller than the 14.2-inch MacBook Pro, and markedly smaller than the 16.2-inch MacBook Pro. 13.6 inches is still bigger than the largest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> model, which comes in at 12.9 inches, and even all of the previous &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and smaller MacBook Pro models, meaning that it should be adequate for most users. The 14.2-inch MacBook Pro simply offers a little bit more screen real estate to those who need high-end capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
The 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and 16.2-inch MacBook Pro's displays will be better replacements for a desktop machine and provide much more screen space to arrange multiple windows and use professional applications that benefit from additional display area.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="display_technology">Display Technology</h3><br/>
The display technologies of both machines are significantly different. Like most MacBooks in recent years, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has an LCD panel, but owing to its slim bezels and rounded corners, Apple calls it a Liquid Retina display. The 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models feature Apple's more advanced mini-LED Liquid Retina XDR technology for deeper blacks, better dynamic range, and improved color accuracy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/macbook-pro-display.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1274" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821240" /><br/>
The XDR display can get much brighter, reaching as high as 1,600 nits of brightness at its peak when showing HDR content. The 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models also have ProMotion displays, allowing them to vary their refresh rate up to 120Hz. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; does not have a display with a variable refresh rate.<br/>
<br/>
It will be worth getting the high-end MacBook Pro models for viewing and editing HDR content, as well as watching high-framerate video such as sports. The display of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is sufficient for most users and some may not even notice a drastic difference. The MacBook Pro's deeper blacks and smoother on-screen motion simply offer a slightly better experience.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chips">Chips</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; contains the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; or M3 chip, while MacBook Pro customers can choose between the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips. The M3 Pro and M3 Max are scaled-up versions of the M3 chip that offer additional CPU and GPU cores. See the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max's Geekbench 5 Benchmark scores below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <th>M3 Pro</th><br/>
 <th>M3 Max</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Single-Core</th><br/>
 <td>2,570–2,630</td><br/>
 <td>3,010</td><br/>
 <td>3,120</td><br/>
 <td>3,120</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Multi-Core</th><br/>
 <td>9,630–9,650</td><br/>
 <td>11,763</td><br/>
 <td>14,010–14,410</td><br/>
 <td>19,160–21,215</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Metal (Graphics)</th><br/>
 <td>41,300–45,550</td><br/>
 <td>47,430</td><br/>
 <td>68,330–77,070</td><br/>
 <td>124,060–157,120</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The M3 Pro and M3 Max provide CPUs with up to eight additional cores and GPUs with up to 30 additional cores. The entry-level &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;'s &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip is only slightly less powerful than the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max in single-core tasks, but the M3 chips, and particularly the Pro and Max versions, are considerably better in multi-core and graphics tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Apple-M3-chip-series-architecture.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920045" /><br/>
With significantly more transistors, performance CPU cores, and GPU cores, the M3 Pro and M3 Max are powerful chips designed for professionals with demanding workflows. The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3, on the other hand, are more consumer-oriented chips focused on delivering surprisingly impressive performance and excellent efficiency to keep temperatures down and prolong battery life.<br/>
<br/>
It is also worth noting that the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is passively cooled and contains no fan, which can slightly constrain peak performance compared to the MacBook Pro, since the high-end machines have large fans to actively cool the system and push the chips harder.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; only supports a single external display. The limitations of the M3 also mean that &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and MacBook Pro devices configured with this chip support up to two external displays when the lid is closed, whereas M3 Pro and M3 Max machines support up to two and four external displays, respectively. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="memory_and_storage">Memory and Storage</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; can be configured with up to 24GB of unified memory and up to 2TB of storage, which should be more than enough for the vast majority of users. For those who need even more memory and storage, the MacBook Pro can be configured with significantly more memory and storage than the top-spec &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 Pro and M3 Max chips in the MacBook Pro also provide up to 150GB/s and 400GB/s memory bandwidth respectively – an enormous increase over the 100GB/s memory bandwidth with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3 models.<br/>
<br/>
Buyers should also be aware that the 256GB &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; base models have up to 50 percent slower SSDs than configurations with more storage. This is because the base models only have a single SSD module inside, whereas models with larger amounts of storage have two SSD chips, significantly increasing the overall speed of the machine's storage.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="speakers_and_microphones">Speakers and Microphones</h3><br/>
The 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has a four-speaker sound system that is surprisingly full and balanced for such a small, slim device. The 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and all of the MacBook Pro models take things to the next level with a six-speaker sound system with force-cancelling woofers for dramatically bigger and deeper audio. Apple also describes the MacBook Pro's speaker system as "high-fidelity," which may be invaluable to users who work in professional audio production or simply listen to a lot of music out-loud.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/macbook-pro-speakers.jpg" alt="" width="1128" height="684" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821784" /><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has a three-mic array with directional beamforming that is perfect for activities like video calls and voice notes. The MacBook Pro has what Apple calls a "studio-quality" three-mic array with high signal-to-noise ratio and directional beamforming. While they are not as good as a dedicated microphone, the MacBook Pro's microphones are impressive and, at a push, are suitable for production purposes like podcasting.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="battery_life">Battery Life</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has an 18-hour battery life, offering the same battery life as the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 Pro or M3 Max chips, and four hours less than the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 chip and the 16-inch MacBook Pro. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="final_thoughts">Final Thoughts</h2><br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is the best option for casual users, offering an excellent balance of features and performance in a highly portable design. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;'s &#36;999 starting price is much more affordable compared to the MacBook Pro, and with an education discount or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#macbook_air">offer from our Apple Deals Roundup</a>, it is possible to get that price down by at least &#36;100. The additional &#36;600 to get the MacBook Pro likely is not worth it for most ordinary users, and on the contrary, many will prefer the slimmer, lighter design of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and perhaps even its additional color options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/macbook-pro-sizes-space-gray.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="693" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821783" /><br/>
Professionals who require larger and more accurate displays, additional ports, more memory and storage, and a very high level of performance should look to the 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 Pro and M3 Max chips, and the higher price points of these machines reflects this. The high-end MacBook Pro models are not targeted at everyday consumers, being clearly tailored to creatives and professionals who rely heavily on the capabilities of their machines. As such, these high-end models should only be a go-to option if you are a power-user or professional who can make use of its advanced features. The 16-inch MacBook Pro, in particular, is also potentially a good desktop replacement machine due to its large display.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide: All Differences Compared</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/">13-Inch vs. 15-Inch MacBook Air Buyer's Guide</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/14-inch-macbook-pro-vs-16-inch-macbook-pro/">Late 2023 MacBook Pro Buyer's Guide: 14-Inch and 16-Inch Models Compared</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Alternatively, if you are considering the &#36;1,299 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, it may be worth paying more to get the M3 MacBook Pro. For just &#36;200 more, the M3 MacBook Pro offers a considerably better Liquid Retina XDR display with ProMotion, a more powerful chip with active cooling, four extra hours of battery life, better speakers and microphones, an HDMI port and SDXC card slot, and more. In fact, if you configure the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with 512GB of storage to match the M3 MacBook Pro, there is only a &#36;100 between the two machines, so in this instance it is almost always worth getting the more powerful machine, unless maximizing screen size is your only priority.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/">MacBook Air vs. MacBook Pro Buyer&#039;s Guide: 30+ Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide-30-differences-compared.2378980/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Changes Trade-In Values for iPhones, iPads, and Apple Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-march-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-changes-trade-in-values-for-iphones-ipads-and-apple-watches.2421214/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 08:42:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-march-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Trade-In</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today adjusted its estimated <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">trade-in values</a> for select iPhone, iPad, and Apple Watch models in the U.S., with the changes reflected on its website.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iPhone-Trade-In-Box.jpg" alt="" width="1472" height="828" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902097" /><br/>
Apple slightly increased trade-in values for the iPhone 14 Pro Max, second-generation iPhone SE, Apple Watch Series 4, and first-generation Apple Watch SE, while trade-in values slightly decreased for the entry-level iPad, Apple Watch Ultra, Apple Watch Series 7, and second-generation Apple Watch SE.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's trade-in changes are outlined below:<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Device</th><br/>
 <th>New Values</th><br/>
 <th>Old Values</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPhone 14 Pro Max</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;630</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;620</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPhone SE 2</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;90</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;70</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">iPad</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;250</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;260</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;365</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;390</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 7</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;145</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;155</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 4</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;70</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;60</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch SE 2</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;120</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;125</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch SE 1</div></strong></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;95</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Up to &#36;90</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div>Apple also adjusted trade-in values for select Android smartphones today, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/">for select Macs earlier this week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Trade-ins can be completed on Apple's website or at an Apple Store, and the credit can be applied towards the purchase of a new Apple product, or placed on an Apple gift card for later use. <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">Apple's trade-in page</a> offers a complete list of values for devices.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-trade-in/">Apple Trade-In</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-adjusts-trade-in-values-march-2024/">Apple Changes Trade-In Values for iPhones, iPads, and Apple Watches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-changes-trade-in-values-for-iphones-ipads-and-apple-watches.2421214/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock Drops to &#36;99.99 (&#36;180 Off) Among Other Mac Accessory Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-drops-to-99-99-180-off-among-other-mac-accessory-deals.2421208/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 07:34:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC is back today with a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">new Mac accessory sale</a> that includes notable discounts on Thunderbolt docks, USB-C hubs, external drives and enclosures, internal memory upgrade kits for Mac, and more. Most products are in stock and ready to ship out today, and OWC offers free shipping on orders &#36;149.00 and over.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/owc-dock-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939882" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of the sale include a collection of Thunderbolt docks for up to &#36;180 off. These docks allow you to easily connect a wide array of peripherals to your Mac, including two 4K displays or one 5K display with the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock</a>, which is down to a new record low price of &#36;99.99. This beats the previous sale price by about &#36;80 and it will last until Friday at 12:00 a.m. PT.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;180 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
All of the devices listed below are in new condition at OWC, although the retailer does provide various item condition options for anyone who might want to save money by purchasing open box items. Be sure to visit <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">OWC's sale landing page</a> to browse the full sale, which also features deals on cables, Mac accessories, keyboards, and headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDSDRDR%2F">Atlas Dual SD Card Reader</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T04C%2F">4TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T12C%2F">12TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;219.99, down from &#36;369.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T16C%2F">16TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T08C%2F">8TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;269.99, down from &#36;394.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T24C%2F">24TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;78.99, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;154.99, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;3.98, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fshop%2Ffirewire%2Fon-the-go">OWC Mercury On-The-Go Pro Portable Storage</a> - Up to 25% off</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-deals/">OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock Drops to &#36;99.99 (&#36;180 Off) Among Other Mac Accessory Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-drops-to-99-99-180-off-among-other-mac-accessory-deals.2421208/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores Now Stock 14-Inch M3 MacBook Pro With 16GB of RAM</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-stores-now-stock-16gb-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-now-stock-14-inch-m3-macbook-pro-with-16gb-of-ram.2421197/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 06:30:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-stores-now-stock-16gb-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple retail stores now stock a configuration of the entry-level, M3 MacBook Pro with 16GB of unified memory.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/new-16-gb-macbook-pro-configuration.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939861" /><br/>
The configuration, spotted by French website <a href="https://consomac.fr/news-18831-une-nouvelle-reference-de-macbook-pro-14.4-avec-puce-m3-et-16-go-de-ram.html"><em>Consomac</em></a>, is now highlighted as a standard option <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-mac/macbook-pro/14-inch">on Apple's website</a> for &#36;1,999. While the configuration itself is not new, since customers can upgrade from 8GB to 16GB of memory with a &#36;200 build-to-order upgrade, the presence of a new default option offering this configuration allows customers to purchase an M3 MacBook Pro with 16GB of memory without any hardware upgrades. Most notably, it also means that the 16GB machine will be stocked by Apple retail stores and third-party retailers for the first time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/apple-stores-now-stock-16gb-macbook-pro/">Apple Stores Now Stock 14-Inch M3 MacBook Pro With 16GB of RAM</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-now-stock-14-inch-m3-macbook-pro-with-16gb-of-ram.2421197/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Alternative iOS App Stores Only Work for &#039;Grace Period&#039; When Traveling Outside of EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/alternative-ios-app-stores-eu-grace-period/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alternative-ios-app-stores-only-work-for-grace-period-when-traveling-outside-of-eu.2421188/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 04:22:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/alternative-ios-app-stores-eu-grace-period/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/">release of iOS 17.4</a>, iPhone users in the European Union can access third-party app stores, but Apple warns that EU users traveling outside of the bloc will only have a "grace period" before some features stop working altogether when they're away.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
From Apple's <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-gb/118110">support document</a> detailing alternative app marketplaces:<br/>
<blockquote>If you leave the European Union for short-term travel, you'll continue to have access to alternative app marketplaces for a grace period. If you're gone for too long, you'll lose access to some features, including installing new alternative app marketplaces. Apps you installed from alternative app marketplaces will continue to function, but they can't be updated by the marketplace you downloaded them from. </blockquote>We've contacted Apple for clarification on the duration of this "grace period" and are waiting to hear back.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is allowing iPhone users in the EU access to alternative app stores in order to comply with the regulatory framework of the Digital Markets Act, which comes into effect for all 27 countries included in the bloc on March 7. The change means users can download apps from marketplaces outside of Apple's own App Store for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
In iOS 17.4, EU users concerned with the potential privacy, safety, and security risks of alternative app marketplaces can set their preferred alternative app store as the default App Store on their device via Settings. A Screen Time setting also allows parents to decide whether their children's devices are able to install apps from alternative app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
To gain access to alternative app marketplaces, the country or region of a user's Apple ID must be set to one of the countries or regions of the EU, and they must be physically located in the EU. Apple says device eligibility for access to alternative app marketplaces is determined by using on-device processing, with only an indicator of eligibility sent to Apple. To preserve user privacy, Apple does not collect a device's location.<br/>
<br/>
The first alternative app marketplace will launch in the EU this week. German IT service provider <a href="https://mobivention.com/presse-en-2/mobivention-revolutionises-the-distribution-of-ios-apps-in-the-eu-with-an-authorised-alternative-app-marketplace/?lang=en">Mobivention</a> will launch its corporate-focused Mobivention App Marketplace on Thursday. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/">MacPaw</a> has also announced it will offer an alternative app marketplace sometime in April, while <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">Epic Games</a> also has plans to launch one. <br/>
<br/>
For additional details about changes to the App Store and more in the EU, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">read our previous coverage</a>. The changes do not apply outside of the EU, nor do they apply to iPadOS in any country.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/06/alternative-ios-app-stores-eu-grace-period/">Alternative iOS App Stores Only Work for &#039;Grace Period&#039; When Traveling Outside of EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alternative-ios-app-stores-only-work-for-grace-period-when-traveling-outside-of-eu.2421188/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-4.2421157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:28:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features&#038;post_date=1709688516/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the iOS 17.4 update that brings some major changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> (and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>) in Europe. Many of the biggest changes in iOS 17.4 are limited to people in the European Union, but there new additions in the update that are available worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932462" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
In this article, we've rounded up everything new in iOS 17.4.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="eu_changes">EU Changes</h2><br/>
Apple is changing the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act. These changes are included in iOS 17.4, but are limited to countries that are in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833990" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Black.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="alternative_app_stores_and_new_app_store_terms_eu">Alternative App Stores and New App Store Terms (EU)</h3><br/>
App developers in the EU can opt to offer alternative app stores or install their apps through alternative stores, and Apple has a whole new fee structure that goes along with this change. There's a new business structure that developers can opt in to, which applies to both apps distributed in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and apps that are distributed through alternative means.<br/>
<br/>
App developers using the new system will need to pay a standard fee of 0.50 euros per user per year, with the first million installs offered for free. Apps distributed through alternative app stores will have no commission. Apps distributed through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; will pay a reduced 17 percent commission, or 10 percent for those in the small business program or for user subscriptions older than a year.<br/>
<br/>
Developers can choose not to opt in to the new system and can use the existing system with the same 15/30 percent commission that's available elsewhere in the world. Apple has a fee calculator to help developers determine what they'll pay with the existing setup, with the new setup, with the new setup using alternative app stores, and with the new setup using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Users are able to set their preferred alternative app store as the default app store on their device if desired. EU users will see an option for this in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
There are a huge number of behind-the-scene changes that are enabling this feature in the EU, with updates to all kinds of system messaging. Users in the EU will, for example, get a pop up warning when an app from an alternative app store contains malware, and there are new screens for verifying the information from an alternative app.<br/>
<br/>
A Screen Time setting will allow parents to decide whether their children's devices are able to install apps from alternative app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="alternative_payment_options_eu">Alternative Payment Options (EU)</h3><br/>
Apple is also allowing apps to use alternative payment options in their apps, and there is no longer a requirement to use in-app purchase. Developers who distribute apps through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and use an alternative payment option will see a three percent discount in their &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; fees.<br/>
<br/>
Developers who distribute through alternative apps and also use an alternative payment option will pay Apple no fees beyond the set 0.50 euro fee per user.<br/>
<br/>
With alternative payments, purchases for digital goods and services can be made directly in an app or a developer can choose to link to their website to have a user make a payment. Apple is requiring developers to use a known, secure payment provider.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="third-party_browser_updates_eu">Third-Party Browser Updates (EU)</h3><br/>
After updating to iOS 17.4, EU users that open Safari will see a pop up that allows them to choose a new default browser option from a list of the most popular browsers on iOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also allowing alternative browser engines, and will not limit browsers like Chrome to the WebKit engine.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="nfc_access_eea">NFC Access (EEA)</h3><br/>
Third-party payment apps and banks have access to the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in iOS 17.4, and can offer contactless payments directly on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; without using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> or the Wallet app in the European Economic Area. Users can set a default contactless payment provider that activates at tap-to-pay terminals or when the Side button on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is pressed twice.<br/>
<br/>
The option for setting a default contactless payment provider is available in the Settings app in the European Economic Area, and this section will also provide details on all apps that have requested and been granted contactless payment access.<br/>
<br/>
EEA users can also change the default Wallet app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="web_apps_eu">Web Apps (EU)</h3><br/>
Apple initially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/ios-17-4-nerfs-web-apps-in-the-eu/">restricted the functionality</a> of Progressive Web Apps (PWAs) in the European Union in iOS 17.4, but after a negative response from EU users, Apple walked the decision back.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> Web Apps will no longer be disabled, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-walks-back-decision-to-disable-eu-web-apps/">but WebKit is required</a>. Web apps added to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from a browser that does not support WebKit will not work.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="gaming_app_changes_worldwide">Gaming App Changes (Worldwide)</h2><br/>
Streaming game apps are now allowed on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; worldwide, which means services like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW can be offered as standalone &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously only allowed cloud gaming services to be offered via the web, but dedicated apps that let users stream games from servers are now permitted.<br/>
<br/>
Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_emoji">New Emoji</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 introduces new emoji characters that include lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932812" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-New-Emoji-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1077" /><br/>
There are also 18 people and body emojis that now have the option to face in either direction.<br/>
<br/>
These emoji are part of the Unicode 15.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ios-17-future-emoji/">approved in September 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messaging_with_siri">Messaging with Siri</h2><br/>
The Automatically Send Messages setting under <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> &amp; Search has been renamed "Messaging with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;," and there is an option to set &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to read incoming messages in a specific language like Spanish, French, German, Chinese, and many more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932819" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-messaging-with-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The change does not update the primary language that &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; listens in and responds to, but is limited to message playback.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcasts_and_music">Podcasts and Music</h2><br/>
The "Listen Now" tabs in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and Podcasts apps have been renamed to "Home."<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932818" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-music-home.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Podcasts also uses the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Now Playing bar when collapsed.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcast_transcripts">Podcast Transcripts</h2><br/>
The Podcasts app now offers transcripts, similar to how lyrics work in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app. You can follow along with an episode as the text is highlighted in sync with the audio.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932875" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/podcast-app-transcript.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Podcast transcripts are available in English, Spanish, French and German, and the transcripts support searching for a specific word or phrase.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="music_recognition">Music Recognition</h2><br/>
Songs that have been identified with music recognition can be added to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Playlists, the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Library, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_imessage_security_protocol">New iMessage Security Protocol</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Apple is introducing a "state-of-the-art" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-announces-imessage-security-upgrade/">post-quantum cryptographic protocol</a> for iMessage called PQ3.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" /><br/>
PQ3 protects against "Harvest Now, Decrypt Later" attacks where a malicious actor collects encrypted data with the hope of decrypting it with a quantum computer at some point in the future. Quantum computers are expected to eventually be able to make large-scale calculations that would allow them to decrypt content secured with traditional encryption methods, but that won't be possible with PQ3.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_15_battery_health">iPhone 15 Battery Health</h2><br/>
Apple in iOS 17.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/ios-17-4-iphone-15-battery/">changed the Battery interface</a> in the Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models. These devices now show Battery Health with a readout such as "Normal," for a quick at-a-glance way to see the status of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937223" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ios-17-4-battery-health-optimization-iphone-15.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Tapping into the battery health readout shows the battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use will be listed. This information was previously hidden in the General &gt; About section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also updated the support information for the battery, as the company retested and found that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; battery can maintain 80 percent of its original capacity <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-raises-iphone-15-advertised-battery-lifespan/">at 1,000 complete charge cycles</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stolen_device_protection">Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
In the Stolen Device Protection section of the Settings app, there is now an option to require a security delay always or only when away from familiar locations.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932874" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple says that this feature is designed to give users the option for increased security in all locations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stopwatch_live_activity">Stopwatch Live Activity</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 adds a Live Activity function for the Stopwatch feature on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. When activated through the Clock app, the Stopwatch now shows up in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> and on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933379" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stopwatch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
There are controls for pausing the Stopwatch, clearing it, and starting a new lap.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="call_identification">Call Identification</h2><br/>
Call identification in iOS 17.4 displays Apple-verified business names, logos, and department names when the information is available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_for_business">Messages for Business</h2><br/>
With Messages for Business, businesses can provide opt-in information for order statuses, flight notifications, fraud alerts, and other transactions.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_tv_app">Apple TV App</h2><br/>
The "How to Watch" section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app that shows where a movie or TV show can be viewed now has a list interface rather than a card interface.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933405" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-how-to-watch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<h2 id="app_store">App Store</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;'s Purchase feature now shows account-wide purchase history for an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>. It includes TV and movie purchases, music purchases, subscriptions, and app purchases, and it is the same interface that is available when accessing the purchase information for any &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933406" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/app-store-purchase-history-ios-17-4.jpg" alt="" width="5289" height="2975" /><br/>
Apps are still listed, but under a new "Apps" section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="clock_widget">Clock Widget</h2><br/>
There's a new City Digital Clock widget that can be added to the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; or Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935544" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ios-17-4-city-digital.jpg" alt="" width="5344" height="3006" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_cash_virtual_card_numbers">Apple Cash Virtual Card Numbers</h2><br/>
In the Wallet app, Apple Cash users can generate a virtual card number to make purchases when &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; is not an option.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935966" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-cash-virtual-card-number.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="real-time_apple_card_apple_savings_and_apple_cash_budget_app_integration">Real-Time Apple Card, Apple Savings, and Apple Cash Budget App Integration</h2><br/>
Apple in iOS 17.4 is giving third-party budget apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/">real-time information</a> on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, Apple Cash, and Apple Savings accounts transactions for up-to-the-minute budget reporting.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hand_gesture_reactions_in_video_apps">Hand Gesture Reactions in Video Apps</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4, there's a new API for developers that can be used to turn off hand gesture reactions in video calls. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> added a gesture reactions that are enabled by default in all video calling apps, leading to awkwardness when moving the hands in certain ways during serious calls.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900390" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/ios-17-facetime-effects.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1070" /><br/>
Online therapists and other professionals have had to add disclaimers about the feature, as there was no way to turn it off on the provider's end. Following iOS 17.4 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, developers can turn off the fireworks, confetti, and other options in their apps. Users were already able to turn off reactions on their iPhones, iPads, and Macs in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hey_siri">Hey Siri</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.4, the option to say &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; instead of Hey &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is now available for French, German, and Spanish speakers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="carplay_instrument_cluster_update">CarPlay Instrument Cluster Update</h2><br/>
In supported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> vehicles, there's now an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> option to show information about upcoming turn-by-turn maneuvers in the instrument cluster. &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; users will be able to swap the display type between the main and instrument cluster by tapping on the map configuration button located in the upper right of the main Maps screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908367" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/volvo-s60-drivers-apple-maps.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The option is available in vehicles that support the dual-screen &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; experience.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="next-generation_carplay_support">Next-Generation CarPlay Support</h2><br/>
Next-generation &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; is set to launch in the U.S. later in 2024, and code in iOS 17.4 references eight new &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Car Camera:</strong> This app will display the vehicle's rear-view camera feed.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Charge:</strong> For electric vehicles, this app will display battery level, charging status, time remaining until the battery is fully charged, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Climate:</strong> This app will provide access to a vehicle's climate controls within &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heating system, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Closures:</strong> This app will display if any of the vehicle's doors are opened, and it might also display vehicle warning symbols.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Media:</strong> This app will provide access to FM and AM radio station controls within &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj;, along with other media options like SiriusXM. It is unclear if SiriusXM will offer satellite connectivity, or remain limited to internet streaming. Users will be able to select from a list of music genres, such as Top 40 and Rock.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Tire Pressure:</strong> This app will display air pressure for each of the vehicle's tires, and provide low pressure, high pressure, and flat tire warnings.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Trips:</strong> This app will provide a variety of driving-related data, including the vehicle's average speed, fuel efficiency or energy efficiency, the total time elapsed and distance traveled on a trip, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
An image in iOS 17.4 beta suggests that &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; will also likely display a "Goodbye" screen after the driver shuts off the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932992" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Goodbye.jpg" alt="" width="1374" height="484" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="bug_fixes">Bug Fixes</h2><br/>
There are two bug fixes in iOS 17.4. The update addresses an issue that could cause contact images in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> to be blank, and it fixes a Dual SIM problem that could cause the number used in a group message to change from primary to secondary.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="security_updates">Security Updates</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 fix several vulnerabilities, including two that may have been actively exploited to gain access to user devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple patched an RTKit vulnerability and a WebKit vulnerability that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/">says may have been exploited</a>, so it is a good idea to update right away.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For details on all of the features that are included in the &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; update, we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">have a dedicated roundup</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">iOS 17.4 Features: What&#039;s New in iOS 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-features-whats-new-in-ios-17-4.2421157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;500 Off Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Pro and &#36;100 Off 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-pro-and-100-off-13-inch-m2-macbook-air.2421155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:04:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a pair of MacBook Air and MacBook Pro deals today at B&H Photo and Best Buy, respectively. You'll find the <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF">13-inch M2 MacBook Air for &#36;100 off</a> at B&H Photo and the <a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV">13-inch M2 MacBook Pro for up to &#36;500 off</a> (with a membership) at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/macbook-pro-school.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905459" /><em><small>Note: Macrumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the Best Buy deals, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Pro for <a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> with a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is at <a href="https://howl.me/clLUq2Iesoa"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> with this extra discount, down from &#36;1,499.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Only My Best Buy Plus/Total members can see these final deal prices.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLUqqn8QaV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;400 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Pro (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLUq2Iesoa"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Pro (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Both of these represent all-time low prices on the 2022 MacBook Pro, which has the Touch Bar. Even without the exclusive My Best Buy Plus/Total discounts these remain solid deals if not quite record low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-m2-13-inch.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939833" /><br/>
Secondly, B&H Photo has the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, which is down from &#36;999.00. Apple dropped the price of this model down to &#36;999.00 this week with the introduction of the new M3 MacBook Airs, and this is the first notable discount on that price that we've tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1710305-REG/apple_mly33ll_a_13_6_macbook_air_m2.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1364298/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m2-macbook-pro-macbook-air-deal/">Get Up to &#36;500 Off Apple&#039;s 13-Inch M2 MacBook Pro and &#36;100 Off 13-Inch M2 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-500-off-apples-13-inch-m2-macbook-pro-and-100-off-13-inch-m2-macbook-air.2421155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Lets Budget Apps Read Real-Time Apple Card Transaction Info</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-budget-apps-read-real-time-apple-card-transaction-info.2421142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:25:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After updating to iOS 17.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> users who want to track their real-time spending with budgeting apps will have more opportunities to do so. iOS 17.4 opens up real-time &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions to third-party apps budgeting apps beyond Mint for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/apple-card-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="1144" height="644" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-735877" /><br/>
Mint added support for the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; back in 2022, but Apple did not provide the same integration to other third-party apps. Intuit folded Mint into Credit Karma at the beginning of the year, though, leaving former users not interested in Credit Karma without a way to track their &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; transactions. &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;, Apple Savings, and Apple Cash accounts can now be added to select budget apps.<br/>
<br/>
With Mint accounts set to shut down on March 23, Apple has expanded &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; support to other third-party apps just in time for people to adopt a new service. So far, budgeting apps <a href="https://www.monarchmoney.com/">Monarch</a>, <a href="https://www.ynab.com">YNAB</a>, and <a href="https://copilot.money">Copilot</a> have added &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; support.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-card-ios-17-4-budget-apps/">iOS 17.4 Lets Budget Apps Read Real-Time Apple Card Transaction Info</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-lets-budget-apps-read-real-time-apple-card-transaction-info.2421142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Gives Developers More Insight Into App Performance With Over 50 New Analytics Reports</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-developers-more-insight-into-app-performance-with-over-50-new-analytics-reports.2421140/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:45:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the app ecosystem changes that Apple is making in the European Union to comply with the Digital Markets Act, Apple has introduced new analytics information that's available to developers around the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757303" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-developer-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="572" /><br/>
There are more than 50 reports that are available through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> Connect API, with these reports aimed at giving developers more insight into their app performance. Apple added &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, iOS, and CloudKit data analytics that provide hundreds of new metrics.<br/>
<br/>
Some of the new reports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-developer-analytics-expansion/">were shared</a> back when Apple's app changes were first announced in January.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Store Engagement</strong> - Apple is offering additional insight into the number of users on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; that interact with a developer's app or share it with other people.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Store Commerce</strong> - Developers can get more information on downloads, sales and proceeds, pre-orders, and transactions made with the In-App Purchase system.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>App Usage</strong> - Apple now provides more information on crashes, active devices, installs, app deletions, and more.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Frameworks Usage</strong> - Developers can get info on their app's interaction with iOS features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Widgets</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>, and PhotoPicker.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Performance</strong> - Apple offers insights into how apps perform and how users are interacting with specific app features.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The CloudKit console is also being updated with data about Apple Push Notifications and File Provider.<br/>
<br/>
Apple anonymizes the data that is used in the new report options, and developers can also now grant third-party access to their performance reports.<br/>
<br/>
More information on the new analytics reports will be provided by Apple later today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-new-developer-analytics-reports/">Apple Gives Developers More Insight Into App Performance With Over 50 New Analytics Reports</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-gives-developers-more-insight-into-app-performance-with-over-50-new-analytics-reports.2421140/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Make Sure to Update: iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Fix Two Major Security Vulnerabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-fix-two-major-security-vulnerabilities.2421136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 11:02:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> owners may want to update to iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 in the near future, as the updates address two security vulnerabilities that may have been exploited to gain access to user devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
In the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214081">security support document</a> for the updates, Apple says that it "is aware of a report" that RTKit and kernel vulnerabilities may have been exploited by bad actors.<blockquote>Impact: An attacker with arbitrary kernel read and write capability may be able to bypass kernel memory protections. Apple is aware of a report that this issue may have been exploited.</blockquote>Apple fixed the memory corruption issue with improved validation to patch the security hole.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 also address an Accessibility vulnerability and an issue with Safari Private Browsing that could allow locked tabs to be briefly visible while switching tab groups.<br/>
<br/>
The software updates were released this morning and are available on eligible iPhones and iPads by going to Settings > General > Software Update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/ios-17-4-vulnerability-fix/">Make Sure to Update: iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 Fix Two Major Security Vulnerabilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-fix-two-major-security-vulnerabilities.2421136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Tweaks New EU App Store Business Terms After Developer Feedback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-new-eu-app-store-business-terms-after-developer-feedback.2421134/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 10:41:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 17.4, Apple's app ecosystem changes in the European Union have gone into effect. Apple today said that it made some last minute updates to its terms of service after receiving feedback from developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
To distribute apps through an app marketplace, with a reduced fee to Apple, or with an alternative payment option, developers have to opt in to new business terms that accept the Core Technology Fee and other new pricing mandates. Apple did not initially provide a way for developers to try the new system and then opt back out if it does not work out, but now there is a one-time term swap option available in some circumstances.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that developers have a one-time option to terminate the new rule addendum [<a href="https://developer.apple.com/contact/request/download/alternate_eu_terms_addendum.pdf">PDF</a>] and swap back to Apple's standard business terms, though there is a catch. Developers who want to change back cannot have distributed an app through an alternative app marketplace or have used an alternative payment processing method.<blockquote>You may terminate this Addendum without also terminating the Developer Agreement one time, provided You have never had an Application be an Alternative App Marketplace (EU), be distributed through an Alternative App Marketplace (EU), use Linking Out, or use Alternative Payment Processing.</blockquote>Opt-out will be available for developers who decided to continue to distribute their apps through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> while adopting the Core Technology Fee and reduced commission option. The CTF is .50 euros per download after 1 million downloads, and the commission is 13 percent for small business owners and 20 percent for installs over 1 million (this includes the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; payment processing fee).<br/>
<br/>
Developers who want to create an alternative app marketplace <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/alternative-app-marketplace-in-the-eu/">can now do so</a> without a stand-by letter of credit for €1,000,000, which would restrict marketplace creation to large companies. Developers who have been a member of good standing in the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more and have an app that had more than one million first annual installs in iOS in the EU in the prior calendar year can create a marketplace without the proof of funds.<br/>
<br/>
There is also no longer a corporate entity requirement when signing up for new terms, so a large business can sign up at the developer account level rather than having to have each controlling membership approve the swap to the updated business terms.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.4 released, we should soon be seeing the first alternative app marketplaces launch. Developers are now free to adopt the new business terms, distribute their apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and use third-party payments in their apps. Note that all of these changes are limited to developers and users in the European Union.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-tweaks-eu-app-store-business-terms/">Apple Tweaks New EU App Store Business Terms After Developer Feedback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tweaks-new-eu-app-store-business-terms-after-developer-feedback.2421134/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 With EU App Changes, New Emoji, Podcast Transcripts and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-with-eu-app-changes-new-emoji-podcast-transcripts-and-more.2421124/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 10:01:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4, the fourth major updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system that came out in September 2023. The software updates come over a month after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/">released iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4D8Dy0kP-Cg" title="iOS 17.4 Out Now: New Features!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update. <br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.4, Apple introduces sweeping changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps function in the European Union, paving the way for alternative app marketplaces on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, alternative payment systems on iOS and iPadOS, third-party browser engine support, and NFC access for banks and third-party payment providers. These features are limited to the EU, and the changes are not applicable in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did, however, make worldwide changes to gaming apps. Apple is now allowing cloud gaming apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW. Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to these App Store-related updates, iOS 17.4 adds new emoji characters, <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apple-introduces-transcripts-for-apple-podcasts/">transcripts for podcasts</a> in the Podcasts app, Stopwatch Live Activities, improvements to battery health reporting on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, and more. Apple's full release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote><strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in the emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji add the option to face them in either direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Apple Podcasts</strong><br/>
- Transcripts let you follow an episode with text that highlights in sync with the audio in English, Spanish, French and German<br/>
- Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, tapped to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update includes the following enhancements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Music recognition lets you add songs you have identified to your Apple Music Playlists and Library, as well as Apple Music Classical<br/>
- Siri has a new option to announce messages you receive in any supported language<br/>
- Stolen Device Protection supports the option for increased security in all locations<br/>
- Battery Health in Settings shows battery cycle count, manufacture date, and first use on iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models<br/>
- Call Identification displays Apple-verified business name, logo, and department name when available<br/>
- Business updates in Messages for Business provide trusted information for order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions you opt into<br/>
- Apple Cash virtual card numbers enable you to pay with Apple Cash at merchants that don't yet accept Apple Pay by typing in your number from Wallet or using Safari AutoFill<br/>
- Fixes an issue where contact pictures are blank in Find My<br/>
- Fixes an issue for Dual SIM users where the phone number changes from primary to secondary and is visible to a group they have messaged<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222">https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</a></blockquote><br/>
Note that Apple's release notes in the United States do not highlight the changes in the European Union, but the update does now allow for alternative app marketplaces to be installed on iPhones in Europe. If you're in Europe and affected by the changes, you will see different release notes that include details on Apple's app ecosystem updates. <blockquote><strong>Apps in the EU</strong><br/>
Residents of the European Union will now have new options to:<br/>
<br/>
- Install apps from alternative app marketplaces<br/>
- Install web browser with alternative browser engines<br/>
- Manage your default web browser the first time you open Safari<br/>
- Use alternative payment options for apps in the App Store with the external purchases badge<br/>
- Some options require developer support</blockquote>More information on what's new in iOS 17.4 can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">our iOS 17.4 features guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/">Apple Releases iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 With EU App Changes, New Emoji, Podcast Transcripts and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-with-eu-app-changes-new-emoji-podcast-transcripts-and-more.2421124/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>13-Inch vs. 15-Inch MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-vs-15-inch-macbook-air-buyers-guide.2391905/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 08:47:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709668020/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> continues to be available in 13- and 15-inch sizes after Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">latest refresh</a> that added the M3 chip. The 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; offers almost all of the same hardware with a significantly larger display, yet there are still some key differences that are worth considering when purchasing one of the machines.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/MacBook-Air-Multiple-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-851176" /><br/>
The 13- and 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are almost exactly the same in terms of feature set and design, both sporting high-resolution Liquid Retina displays, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, two Thunderbolt ports, and much more. Both machines can be configured with the exact same amounts of memory and storage, and they are both available in the same color options. This simplifies purchasing decisions to just a few important aspects.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="key_differences">Key Differences</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>13.6-inch Liquid Retina display</td><br/>
 <td>15.3-inch Liquid Retina display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> or M3 chip</td><br/>
 <td>M3 chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts with 8-Core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>10-Core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Four-speaker sound system</td><br/>
 <td>Six-speaker sound system with force-cancelling woofers</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Integrated 52.6-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 <td>Integrated 66.5-watt-hour lithium-polymer battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>30W USB-C Power Adapter (with 8-core GPU chip) or 35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter</td><br/>
 <td>35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;999</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;1,299</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
It is important to note that while the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has a battery that is 13.9-watt-hours larger than the 13-inch model, both machines have the same 18-hour battery life. This is likely due to the increased power consumption of the larger display.<br/>
<br/>
If you plan to heavily use your laptop's built-in speakers, the 15-inch model offers a worthwhile reason to get the larger model, offering two extra speakers inside the larger chassis. The smaller &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; also misses out on the force-canceling woofers that are present in the 15-inch model, meaning that its audio isn't quite as good.<br/>
<br/>
Since size is the main difference between the two &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models, prospective customers may wish to drill into the specific dimensions and weight of the machines. The 15-inch model adds 0.6 pounds (0.27 kg) and may be more difficult to get into a bag or backpack due to its larger footprint.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Height</th><br/>
 <td>0.44 inch (1.13 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>0.45 inch (1.15 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Width</th><br/>
 <td>11.97 inches (30.41 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>13.40 inches (34.04 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Depth</th><br/>
 <td>8.46 inches (21.5 cm)</td><br/>
 <td>9.35 inches (23.76 cm)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Weight</th><br/>
 <td>2.7 pounds (1.24 kg)</td><br/>
 <td>3.3 pounds (1.51 kg)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
While the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with the M3 chip starts at &#36;1,099, making it &#36;200 cheaper than the 15-inch model, if you choose the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with a 10-core GPU, this price difference shrinks to &#36;100. If you add the 35W Dual Port Compact Power Adapter, the difference shrinks to just &#36;80. With this in mind, most users considering an M3 model should opt for the 15-inch model since it provides much more screen real-estate and better speakers.<br/>
<br/>
You should only buy the M3 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; if you specifically want a lighter, more portable device and are concerned about having to carry a device as large as the 15-inch model around. Likewise, the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is a better buy if you are price-conscious and don't need anything more than an 8-core GPU and the 30W USB-C Power Adapter. The &#36;1,099 13-inch model is still quite a bit more affordable than the 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, with virtually no compromises in terms of features. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer's Guide: All Differences Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is also available with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip for &#36;999. This is the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; Apple introduced in mid-2022 and it now represents an entry-level model. If affordability is your main concern, this 13-inch model is the best choice, coming in at &#36;300 less than the 15-inch M3 model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/13-vs-15-inch-macbook-air/">13-Inch vs. 15-Inch MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-vs-15-inch-macbook-air-buyers-guide.2391905/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New MacBook Air Launching on Friday With These 5 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-launching-on-friday-with-these-5-new-features.2421117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 08:26:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">updated the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air</a> with several new features and changes. The laptops can be ordered now, with in-store availability and deliveries to customers set to begin on Friday, March 8.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><br/>
Below, we outline key new features added to the MacBook Air, including the M3 chip, Wi-Fi 6E, expanded external display support, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 Chip</h2><br/>
Both the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air are now available with Apple's latest M3 chip for faster performance and improved power efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
As expected, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/first-benchmark-result-macbook-air-m3/">early benchmark result</a> has revealed that the M3 chip is up to 20% faster than the M2 chip in the previous MacBook Air models in terms of CPU performance. These results are consistent with the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
With the M3 chip, the MacBook Air has also gained hardware-accelerated ray tracing for improved graphics rendering in games, along with AV1 video decoding.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Two External Displays</h2><br/>
While previous MacBook Air models with Apple silicon officially support only one external display, the new models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-two-displays-lid-closed/">support two external displays</a>. However, a second display can only be used when the MacBook Air's lid is closed.<br/>
<br/>
When the lid is open, the new models support one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz. When the lid is closed, a second display with up to 5K resolution at 60Hz can be connected, according to Apple's tech specs.<br/>
<br/>
Even more displays can be connected to the MacBook Air with the use of DisplayLink adapters. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wi-Fi 6E</h2><br/>
The new MacBook Airs support Wi-Fi 6E for "up to twice as fast" wireless download speeds compared to the previous models with Wi-Fi 6, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 6E extends the capabilities of Wi-Fi 6 to the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference with a compatible device and router. The entire current-generation Mac lineup now supports Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Microphone Upgrades</h2><br/>
Apple says the microphones in the new MacBook Air models offer "enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls" compared to the previous models. The microphones also gained support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/block-background-noise-facetime-mac/">"Voice Isolation" and "Wide Spectrum" modes</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Fingerprint Seal for Midnight Color</h2><br/>
Just <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">like the Space Black MacBook Pro</a>, the Midnight MacBook Air now features an "anodization seal to reduce fingerprints," according to Apple.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/m3-macbook-air-features/">New MacBook Air Launching on Friday With These 5 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-macbook-air-launching-on-friday-with-these-5-new-features.2421117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Discover Samsung Spring Sale Has Massive &#36;700 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-discover-samsung-spring-sale-has-massive-700-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-and-more.2421110/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 07:47:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has kicked off a <a href="https://howl.me/clLNJuxoiqi">Discover Samsung Spring Sale</a>, which is set to run through the end of the week. During this event you'll find discounts on <a href="https://howl.me/clLNSBlHkaL">4K and 5K Samsung monitors</a>, including the popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and Smart Monitor M8, as well as storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/samsung-viewfinity-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939071" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;700 off this a new all-time low price on the 2023 display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNLtD8GuF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/clLNM6CvUKB"><strong>&#36;349.99</strong></a> in Sunset Pink, down from &#36;699.99. Other colors, like Warm White, are priced at <a href="https://howl.me/clLNPiqsTe3"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the new iMac line, and it's at another new record low price during Samsung's Spring Sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/samsung-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905732" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLNM6CvUKB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;350 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up a collection of other discounts you can find during the new Discover Samsung Spring Sale below. Shoppers should note that some of these deals are timed and will only last today, while others are slated to stick around all week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2hIAozaO">27-inch Odyssey HDR10 Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gYG78Q9">34-inch ViewFinity HDR10 Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2gbHK6cQ">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNROoH7so">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2e77z0lE">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs/Audio</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN0R87SoM">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNZ1m9EMM">55-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNX3ZnLNR">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNXcrr7pC">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000 on select models</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNYXDQ23m">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLNWfhuoAS">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,399.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Smartphones</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN3lYPzGg">Galaxy S24+</a> - Save up to &#36;1,050 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN39d8ucx">Galaxy S24 Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;1,220 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN4VDZt8i">Galaxy Z Fold5</a> - Save up to &#36;950 with participating carriers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clLN5FExalV">Galaxy Z Flip5</a> - Save up to &#36;660 with participating carriers</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/discover-samsung-massive-discount/">New Discover Samsung Spring Sale Has Massive &#36;700 Discount on ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-discover-samsung-spring-sale-has-massive-700-discount-on-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-and-more.2421110/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
