<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 08:02:39 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 iPhone Apps Apple Still Hasn&#039;t Brought to iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/apps-apple-still-hasnt-brought-to-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-apps-apple-still-hasnt-brought-to-ipad.2449010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/apps-apple-still-hasnt-brought-to-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		<category>Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple has made strides in bringing long-missing apps to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in recent years, there are still five <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> apps that remain noticeably absent.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Apple-iPad-Air-and-iPad-Pro-11-inch-and-13-inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-949646" /><br/>
After years of requests from users, Apple finally introduced the Health, Weather, and Calculator apps to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in iPadOS 16, 17, and 18, providing a tweaked experience for the bigger screen. However, this week's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">debut of Apple Invites</a>, an event-planning app exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, highlights that Apple is still not bringing all of its first-party applications to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. Here are five apps we're still waiting on to come to Apple's tablet:<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Invites</h3><br/>
Apple introduced the Invites app earlier this week, offering a streamlined way for users to create, manage, and send event invitations. The app allows users to design invitations with customized backgrounds, photos, and AI-generated imagery via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/General-Apple-Invites-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-988154" /><br/>
It integrates with Maps and Weather to provide location and climate details for attendees, and features RSVP tracking along with collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists and shared photo albums.<br/>
<br/>
Despite its clear utility, Apple Invites remains natively unavailable on &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, with the only options being running the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; version or using the browser version via icloud.com. Given that iPads are commonly used for light productivity tasks, planning, and creative work, the absence of Invites on the platform is a peculiar omission. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Wallet</h3><br/>
First introduced in 2012 as Passbook and later rebranded as Wallet, Apple's digital wallet app is best known for storing credit and debit cards for use with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. However, Wallet also houses event tickets, boarding passes, loyalty cards, and transit passes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Wallet-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-899453" /><br/>
While the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; lacks NFC hardware, making contactless &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; in stores impossible, there are still several Wallet features that could benefit &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users. The ability to view transaction history, receive &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; notifications, and manage delivery tracking from online purchases could all be useful on a larger display. For example, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> users might find Wallet beneficial for accessing event tickets or passes without needing to switch to their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Sports</h3><br/>
Apple Sports launched with iOS 17.2, providing users with real-time scores, standings, and statistics across a wide range of professional and college sports leagues. The app integrates with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Sports-Broadcast-Info.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-987351" /><br/>
Apple Sports similarly has not yet made the jump to &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. While &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users can obviously access live scores through Safari or third-party apps, the lack of a dedicated Sports app on iPadOS is an unusual limitation for such a simple app.<br/>
<br/>
Given the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s famous suitability for media consumption, including watching live sports through services like &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+, the absence of a native Sports app makes little sense. Users who might want to monitor games while working or browsing on their &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; are left without the convenience that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users enjoy. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Phone</h3><br/>
While iPads cannot function as standalone cell phones, they are capable of receiving calls via an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; using Continuity, yet there is no Phone app for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Phone-App-Icon-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-954687" /><br/>
This means &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users cannot initiate continuity phone calls without first opening <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> or a third-party VoIP app. There is also no call history, no favorites list, and no way to access voicemail directly from the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Journal</h3><br/>
Apple introduced the Journal app in iOS 17.2 as a new way for users to document their daily experiences, incorporating text, photos, locations, and audio recordings into structured journal entries. The app uses machine learning to offer prompts and suggestions based on a user's daily activities.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-journal-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-957061" /><br/>
Unlike many other iPhone-exclusive apps, Journal cannot even be downloaded and run on an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. Because it is a system app rather than an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> download, there is no workaround for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; users who might want to use it in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> or another multitasking mode.<br/>
<br/>
Given that journaling is often associated with extended writing and reflection, an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; version would seem particularly useful, allowing users to write longer entries with a paired Magic Keyboard or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>. The lack of an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; version is made even more conspicuous by the fact that many popular third-party journaling apps, such as Day One, offer excellent cross-platform compatibility. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wallet/">Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/apps-apple-still-hasnt-brought-to-ipad/">5 iPhone Apps Apple Still Hasn&#039;t Brought to iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-apps-apple-still-hasnt-brought-to-ipad.2449010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple &#039;Invites&#039; App, iPhone SE 4 Imminent, AppleCare Changes, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/top-stories-apple-invites-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-invites-app-iphone-se-4-imminent-applecare-changes-and-more.2448995/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/top-stories-apple-invites-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While we're still waiting for Apple's first major hardware releases of the year, we may not have much longer to wait, though Apple has also been tiding us over with this week's release of a new "Invites" app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/top-stories-2025-02-08.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988767" /><br/>
This week also saw some AppleCare changes, the debut of the first native pornography app for iPhone via an alternative app store in the European Union, and more, so read on below for all of this week's biggest news!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Launches New 'Invites' App</h2><br/>
Apple this week announced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">launch of a new app called "Invites,"</a> which is designed to allow users to plan events like birthday parties, graduations, vacations, baby showers, and more. While event creation is limited to iCloud+ subscribers, anyone can reply to an invitation they receive from the service. Be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-app-hands-on/">check out our hands-on video</a> to see how it works, while Dan and Hartley discussed Invites and related topics on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/the-macrumors-show-invites-app/">this week's episode of The MacRumors Show</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Invites-Thumb-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988174" /><br/>
Word of the app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/new-icloud-invite-service-report/">surfaced over the past several weeks</a>, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-invites-leaked-on-icloud-website/">Apple itself leaking a few details</a> just ahead of the official introduction.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone SE 4 Launching as Soon as Next Week</h2><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/iphone-se-4-launch-next-week/">next-generation iPhone SE could debut as soon as next week</a> with a launch to follow later in February, reports <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. Apple isn't expected to hold an event for the ‌iPhone SE‌ 4, and will instead unveil the device through a press release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-SE-4-Single-Camera-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978495" /><br/>
We had been expecting the MacBook Air to be the first major Apple hardware launch of 2025, but unless Apple has really big plans for next week, it appears the next-generation budget iPhone will be first out of the gate.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>EU's AltStore Gets First Native iOS Pornography App</h2><br/>
iOS users in the European Union this week gained access to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/03/eu-altstore-porn-app/">first dedicated native pornography app for the iPhone</a>, distributed through the AltStore PAL alternative app store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/hot-tub-app-eu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988025" /><br/>
While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/03/apple-doesnt-approve-eu-porn-app/">Apple expressed displeasure at the app's launch</a> and shared its concerns about user safety risks and undermined consumer trust, the company is required under the EU's Digital Markets Act to allow alternative marketplaces with their own content rules. Apple is only allowed to subject such apps to a notarization process that checks them for malware, fraud, and other egregious issues, with the company unable to limit apps based on content that has traditionally been barred under App Store rules.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>An Apple TV Refresh is Coming in 2025 - Here's What You Should Know</h2><br/>
Apple hasn't refreshed the Apple TV since 2022, but rumors suggest that we're finally going to get an update in 2025. We don't have a full picture of what to expect yet, though we have some hints on what's coming.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-TV-2025-Thumb-2.jpg" alt="" width="2909" height="1636" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988206" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/apple-tv-2025-whats-coming/">Check out our article and video highlighting what we're expecting to see</a> in terms of chips, design, pricing, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Raises Monthly AppleCare+ Subscription Price for All iPhones</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/applecare-iphone-price-increase/">increased the prices for its monthly AppleCare+ subscription prices for the iPhone</a>, raising the cost by 50 cents for all models in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/applecare-apple-care-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1896" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828594" /><br/>
The price increase comes as Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/applecare-plus-policy-change-at-apple-stores/">made some changes to the way it markets AppleCare+</a>, doing away with fixed 2-year plans in retail stores and in the Settings app on iPhones in favor of monthly and annual subscription options, and also emphasizing more expensive plans that include Theft & Loss coverage over the standard plans.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Expected to Announce Powerbeats Pro 2 on February 11</h2><br/>
Apple previously teased that Powerbeats Pro 2 would be released in 2025, and now an announcement date has leaked. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman this week said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/powerbeats-pro-2-announcement-date-leaked/">Apple plans to unveil the wireless earbuds on Tuesday, February 11</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/apple-power-beats-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985456" /><br/>
Powerbeats Pro are a sportier, fitness-focused alternative to AirPods Pro with built-in, adjustable ear hooks for a secure fit, and Gurman expects the new models to feature an H2 chip and retain the current &#36;250 price point, while our own code discovery last year indicated they will support heart rate monitoring during workouts.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/feb-6-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/08/top-stories-apple-invites-app/">Top Stories: Apple &#039;Invites&#039; App, iPhone SE 4 Imminent, AppleCare Changes, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-invites-app-iphone-se-4-imminent-applecare-changes-and-more.2448995/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Launch is Imminent - What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-se-4-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-launch-is-imminent-what-to-expect.2448969/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:42:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-se-4-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is almost here, with rumors suggesting we're going to see it introduced as soon as next Tuesday. With a release happening in the very near future, we thought we'd highlight everything we know about Apple's newest &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/pOfyMb7mktY" title="iPhone SE 4 Coming Next Week!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<h2>Design</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 4 will look like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, featuring a 6.1-inch OLED display. The device's launch will mark the end of smaller iPhones, as Apple will no longer sell anything smaller than 6.1 inches. The current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is 4.7 inches, so the updated size will be noticeable, but getting rid of the bezels means there's not a huge difference in overall device size despite the much larger display.<br/>
<br/>
Apple used to sell a 5.4-inch &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; "mini," but it was discontinued after the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 13 mini because the device simply wasn't selling well. In the future, Apple may appease those who want a small &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a clamshell device that folds in half, but rumors suggest that such a device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">at least a year off</a>.<br/>
<br/>
If you want to know what the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will look like, just go take a look at the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;. It'll have the same general design with an all-display design, aluminum and glass build, mute switch, volume buttons, notch, power button, and 5G antenna/SIM tray. There will be a change to the back of the device, though. The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is expected to have a single-lens rear camera, rather than the dual-lens setup of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
You might have seen rumors about an Action Button or Camera Control button for the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 during the rumor cycle, but it's looking more and more like those are not features that are coming to Apple's low-cost device. &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; dummy models have not included an Action button or a Camera Control button, nor have cases designed for the device.<br/>
<br/>
Both early &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; cases and dummy models are often crafted based on supply chain leaks, and they're usually accurate because there's a lot of money up for grabs having a case ready to go right when a new device launches.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Display</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; introduced Ceramic Shield, which is stronger than typical smartphone glass and better able to hold up to drops and scratches. The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 should be more durable than the current model.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is the last &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with an LCD display, so the launch of the new model with an OLED display will see the end of LCD display technology for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>No More Touch ID</h3><br/>
With an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14-style all-display design, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> is going away. Unless Apple keeps the existing &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; around as a super low-cost device, there will be no &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; in the lineup after the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 launches.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; is still used for Macs and some iPads, but Apple will transition fully to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> for its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models with the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4.<br/>
<br/>
There are people who prefer &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; to &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;, but Apple is all-in on facial recognition, and it's more secure than &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;. There's a less than <a href="https://support.apple.com/guide/security/optic-face-touch-passcodes-passwords-sec9479035f1/web">1 in 1,000,000 chance</a> that a random person could unlock your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;, but a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/105095">1 in 50,000 chance</a> for &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Getting rid of the &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; Home button allows for much more screen space, though it is worth noting there will still be a notch. We did hear some rumors suggesting Apple might use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> for the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, but that's another feature that looks like it'll be reserved for the more expensive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; options.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>No More Lightning</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; will have a USB-C port for charging, which also means the Lightning port will be eliminated from almost all Apple devices. Older-generation iPhones like the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus still have a Lightning port, but Apple has been phasing it out.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is one of the last Apple devices that continues to use Lightning, and when Apple discontinues the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, which could happen with the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; launch, Lightning will be eliminated from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MagSafe</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; added support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, and since the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is using an &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; design, it's very likely it will work with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories and will support &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wireless charging. &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; is not an option for the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>A18 Chip and 8GB RAM</h2><br/>
Apple is going to equip the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 with the same A18 chip that's in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, which means it's going to have flagship performance at a much more affordable price. The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will be a solid deal, and the A18 chip will allow it to last for years to come.<br/>
<br/>
With the A18 chip, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features, and it's going to be a huge improvement over the A15 chip in the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;. &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; requires 8GB RAM, so the new &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will also have double the RAM of the current model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Storage Space</h2><br/>
There's no rumor about this, but the rest of Apple's iPhones start with 128GB of storage, so it's likely we're going to see the end of the 64GB storage option this year. 64GB is simply not enough storage space, even for a low-cost &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Camera</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will have a single-lens camera with a Wide lens. Rumors suggest it'll get the same 48-megapixel Wide lens that's in the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, which will bring a major leap in photo quality compared to the 12-megapixel camera in the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 won't have a Telephoto lens or an Ultra Wide lens, but if it does indeed use the same Wide lens, it will support next-generation portraits with focus and depth control, the newest photographic styles, and an option to crop in to 2x optical zoom.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Connectivity</h2><br/>
Apple is going to debut its new in-house modem in the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, and it'll give us our first look at how Apple's modem technology compares to Qualcomm.<br/>
<br/>
The new modem chip won't support the fastest mmWave 5G speed, but it will connect to the more widespread 6GHz networks. Apple wants to cut down on its reliance on Qualcomm, and this new modem chip is the first step.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Emergency SOS via Satellite and Crash Detection</h3><br/>
This is speculation, but with the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, Apple added a Crash Detection feature that alerts emergency services if you're in a car accident. It's an important safety feature that's likely to be included in the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and later also support Emergency SOS via Satellite, and there's a good chance that'll be added to the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Battery Life</h2><br/>
Rumors suggest the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will have the same battery as the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, which means it'll offer up to 20 hours of video playback, up to 16 hours of streaming video, and up to 80 hours of audio playback.<br/>
<br/>
There's quite a bit more space in a 6.1-inch device for a battery than there is in a 4.7-inch device, so it should come as no surprise that there will be a major improvement in overall battery life.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; offers 15 hours of video playback and up to 10 hours of streaming video playback.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pricing</h2><br/>
With higher-end components, the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 could be more expensive than the current model, but Apple is still aiming for a price point under &#36;500. The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 3 is priced starting at &#36;429.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>No Event</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is an important new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in Apple's lineup, but it reuses components from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, so it's not the most exciting device. Apple isn't going to hold an event to unveil the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, instead introducing it through a press release and coverage on the Apple website.<br/>
<br/>
We're expecting the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 to be announced early next week, perhaps on Tuesday, February 11, which is the same day that Apple plans to unveil its new Powerbeats earbuds. It could also come the day before or the day after if Apple is aiming to space out its announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Launch Date</h2><br/>
After being introduced early next week, Apple will likely accept pre-orders for the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; before launching it later in February.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-se-4-what-to-expect/">iPhone SE 4 Launch is Imminent - What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-launch-is-imminent-what-to-expect.2448969/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dbrand&#039;s Always-On &#039;Aperture&#039; Case Protects Your Vision Pro Without Interfering With Sensors and Buttons</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/dbrand-aperture-vision-pro-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dbrands-always-on-aperture-case-protects-your-vision-pro-without-interfering-with-sensors-and-buttons.2448967/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:37:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/dbrand-aperture-vision-pro-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Dbrand today announced the launch of its new <a href="https://dbrand.com/shop/limited-edition/aperture">Aperture protective cover</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, which is designed to protect the large glass display of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/dbrand-aperture-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="634" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988828" /><br/>
Made in a Voronoi style with multiple cutouts in a polyurethane material, the cover fits onto the front of the Vision Pro. The cover does not block any of the sensors or buttons on the Vision Pro, so it can be left on the device at all times, which is useful for VR games and activities that might lead you into walls.<br/>
<br/>
Dbrand developed the case after seeing a 3D printed version from Kyle Goodrich, a former AR designer at Snap. Apple bundles the Vision Pro with a protective cover, but Apple's cover is designed to be in place only while the Vision Pro isn't being worn.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/dbrand-vision-pro-battery-case.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988829" /><br/>
The Aperture Faceplate is being sold alongside a separate Aperture Battery Holster that matches the design of the cover while also adding a clip to attach it to an item of clothing while the Vision Pro is in use. Both the Battery Holster and the Faceplate are available in black or orange.<br/>
<br/>
The Aperture Faceplate alone is priced at &#36;49, while the combo is &#36;69. The accessories can be <a href="https://dbrand.com/shop/limited-edition/aperture">purchased from the Dbrand website</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/dbrand-aperture-vision-pro-case/">Dbrand&#039;s Always-On &#039;Aperture&#039; Case Protects Your Vision Pro Without Interfering With Sensors and Buttons</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dbrands-always-on-aperture-case-protects-your-vision-pro-without-interfering-with-sensors-and-buttons.2448967/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Beta 1 Coming as Soon as Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ios-18-4-launching-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-1-coming-as-soon-as-next-week.2448963/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 11:32:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ios-18-4-launching-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first beta of Apple's upcoming iOS 18.4 update could be released as soon as the middle of next week, according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1887941492603502592"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" /><br/>
Next week may be busy with the launch of Apple's new Powerbeats that have a heart rate sensor and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 4, but we could still get the new beta on February 12 or February 13. If Apple waits until the week after that, the software could come on February 18, as February 17 is Presidents' Day, a U.S. a holiday.<br/>
<br/>
Apple often follows software releases with new betas, but there has been a delay between iOS 18.3 and the iOS 18.4 beta. Apple released iOS 18.3 11 days ago on Monday, January 27, and we'll be at the two week mark on February 10.<br/>
<br/>
It's not unheard of for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/29/ios-18-4-beta-timing/">Apple to take some time</a> between software updates and betas, especially when an update has a lot of new features. Rumors suggest that iOS 18.4 will bring major <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> changes, which Apple outlined earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is set to gain personal context, onscreen awareness, and the ability to do more in and between apps. With &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s history of performance issues and questionable responses compared to other personal assistants, Apple likely wants to ensure that it gets this new feature set right.<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; abilities are one of the major &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features that Apple has already been highlighting in advertising and information about AI, so there are a lot of expectations.<br/>
<br/>
The update will also likely bring new emoji characters, some changes to default app options in the European Union, and an expansion of &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; to new languages and countries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already said that &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will expand to additional countries in an April update, so we are expecting iOS 18.4 to be in beta testing through March ahead of an April launch.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ios-18-4-launching-soon/">iOS 18.4 Beta 1 Coming as Soon as Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-1-coming-as-soon-as-next-week.2448963/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Leaker Issues Apology: &#039;Profound and Expensive Mistake&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/apple-leaker-issues-apology/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leaker-issues-apology-profound-and-expensive-mistake.2448957/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:21:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/apple-leaker-issues-apology/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last year, we reported that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/apple-sues-former-employee-for-alleged-leaking/">Apple sued its former software engineer Andrew Aude</a> for providing journalists with confidential information about the company's future plans, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/21/apple-launching-journaling-app/">details about the Journal app</a>, Vision Pro headset, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-Leak-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-806007" /><br/>
As reported <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2025/02/07/former-leaker-sued-by-apple-has-now-apologized-as-the-lawsuit-is-dismissed/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>, the Superior Court of Santa Clara County on Thursday <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/825250528/Apple-Inc-v-Andrew-Aude-Stipulation-of-Dismissal">dismissed the lawsuit</a> after Apple and Aude reached an agreement to resolve this matter. The court document for the case's dismissal does not provide any specific details about the agreement, but Aude issued a public apology on the same day.  <br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/andyaude1/status/1887639465574998500">post</a> on social media platform X, formerly known as Twitter, Aude said leaking information was a "profound and expensive mistake."<br/>
<br/>
Aude's full apology:<blockquote>I spent nearly eight years as a software engineer at Apple. During that time, I was given access to sensitive internal Apple information, including what were then unreleased products and features. But instead of keeping this information secret, I made the mistake of sharing this information with journalists who covered the company. I did not realize it at the time, but this turned out to be a profound and expensive mistake. Hundreds of professional relationships I had spent years building were ruined. And my otherwise successful career as a software engineer was derailed, and it will likely be very difficult to rebuild it. Leaking was not worth it. I sincerely apologize to my former colleagues who not only worked tirelessly on projects for Apple, but work hard to keep them secret. They deserved better.</blockquote>Aude joined Apple in 2016, to work on optimizing battery performance, and the company fired him in 2023 after learning of his wrongful disclosures. For more details about the situation, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/apple-sues-former-employee-for-alleged-leaking/">previous coverage of the lawsuit</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/apple-leaker-issues-apology/">Apple Leaker Issues Apology: &#039;Profound and Expensive Mistake&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leaker-issues-apology-profound-and-expensive-mistake.2448957/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Could Apple Pull iCloud Services From the UK Market?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/could-apple-pull-icloud-services-from-uk/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/could-apple-pull-icloud-services-from-the-uk-market.2448955/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 09:04:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/could-apple-pull-icloud-services-from-uk/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Given today's bombshell report revealing the UK government's unprecedented demand for backdoor access to encrypted iCloud data, it's clear that Apple now faces a massive challenge. How it responds could have major implications for not only the company's privacy stance, but also its global operations as well as its reputation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iCloud-Versus-UK-Key-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988727" /><br/>
According to <em>The Washington Post</em>, the British government has secretly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/">demanded</a> that Apple give it blanket access to all encrypted user content uploaded to iCloud. The spying order reportedly came by way of a "technical capability notice," a document sent to Apple ordering it to provide access under the sweeping UK Investigatory Powers Act (IPA) of 2016.  <br/>
<br/>
According to sources that spoke to the publication, Apple is likely to stop offering encrypted storage in the UK as a result of the demand. Specifically, Apple could withdraw Advanced Data Protection, an opt-in feature that provides end-to-end encryption (E2EE) for iCloud backups, such as Photos, Notes, Voice Memos, Messages backups, and device backups. <br/>
<br/>
In this scenario, UK users would still have access to basic iCloud services, but their data would lack the additional layer of security that prevents even Apple from accessing it. In other words, UK users' iCloud data would revert to standard encryption, allowing Apple to potentially access the contents of said data if it is compelled to do so by UK authorities when a warrant is issued. Although no specific instance has been publicly confirmed, the IPA grants UK security agencies the legal framework to request data from companies when it is accessible.  <br/>
<br/>
Apple could always pursue legal challenges. However, according to the IPA, while the company can appeal the "technical capability notice," it must comply with the order during the appeals process. Apple would be forced to temporarily implement the backdoor while arguing against its legality. Not only that, the IPA makes it a criminal offense to reveal that the government even made the demand. <br/>
<br/>
Needless to say, such a gag order would prevent Apple from being up front with its customers about the security changes. When a backdoor is introduced — even if its purpose is to grant law enforcement access — it creates an alternative route into a secure channel. This not only increases the risk that bad actors might discover and exploit the vulnerability, but it also breaks the promise of complete confidentiality. Apple would essentially be lying to its customers about the watertightness of its E2EE security.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Nuclear Option</h2><br/>
A more dramatic response from Apple would involve completely removing iCloud services from the UK. While this would protect Apple's encryption standards, it would severely disrupt millions of UK users who rely on iCloud for photo storage, device backups, and document syncing. Users would need to find alternative cloud storage solutions and potentially lose access to years of accumulated data.<br/>
<br/>
Theoretically, Apple could attempt a technical workaround by restructuring iCloud to isolate UK user data. However, the IPA allows British authorities to compel tech companies to assist with data access regardless of where that company is based, so this solution might not satisfy the government's demand for worldwide access. It would also require costly engineering resources to implement, not to mention set a concerning precedent for other countries seeking similar arrangements.<br/>
<br/>
"I don't see how this is to be resolved, as Apple has made such a big point of privacy for users," said Alan Woodward, a professor of cybersecurity at Surrey University, speaking to <em><a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c20g288yldko">BBC News</a></em>. "If they accede to this technical notice their reputation will be in tatters. They're bound to challenge it."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Global Implications</h2><br/>
The UK's demand could also put the government's data-sharing agreement with the European Union at risk. The two regions currently have an agreement allowing the free flow of personal data between the EU and UK, but the arrangement faces review this year. The creation of an encryption backdoor could be viewed as violating the EU's strict data protection standards.<br/>
<br/>
The spy order has already raised concerns in Washington, placing Apple in a potential diplomatic crossfire. According to <em>The Post</em>, the Biden administration first began tracking this issue since the UK first indicated it might demand backdoor access. <br/>
<br/>
The timing is particularly awkward, given that US security agencies have recently been advocating for increased use of encryption to combat Chinese cyber threats. In December, the FBI, the National Security Agency, and the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency jointly recommended that companies "ensure that traffic is end-to-end encrypted to the maximum extent possible" to protect against state-sponsored hacking. Creating a backdoor for UK authorities would directly contradict this guidance and could weaken US cyber defenses, potentially forcing Apple to choose between complying with UK law or protecting US national security interests.<br/>
<br/>
It's worth noting that Apple has repeatedly and forcefully opposed creating backdoors in its products. In its March 2023 submission to UK Parliament, the company stated plainly: "We would never create a backdoor in our products." This echoes CEO Tim Cook's firm stance during the 2016 San Bernardino case, where he declared, "Apple has never built a backdoor into any of our products and never will." <br/>
<br/>
The company doubled down on this position in its 2024 submission to the UK Parliament regarding changes to the IPA, warning that the provisions "could be used to force a company like Apple, that would never build a back door into its products, to publicly withdraw critical security features from the UK market." <br/>
<br/>
Apple's core principle that "privacy is a fundamental human right" is a position it has consistently maintained through the years in the face of government demands for weakened encryption. Confronted by the UK government's latest encryption demands, the company must now prove whether its commitment to user privacy is truly unbreakable, or just a corporate slogan that crumbles under regulatory pressure.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/could-apple-pull-icloud-services-from-uk/">Could Apple Pull iCloud Services From the UK Market?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/could-apple-pull-icloud-services-from-the-uk-market.2448955/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Prices of the Year Hit AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2, Plus Apple Watch SE Discounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-7-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-prices-of-the-year-hit-airpods-4-and-airpods-pro-2-plus-apple-watch-se-discounts.2448952/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 08:09:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-7-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This was one of the biggest weeks for Apple deals so far in 2025, headlined by up to &#36;80 in savings across the AirPods lineup. You can still find these great deals online today, along with savings on Anker accessories, Apple Watch SE, Studio Display, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0010.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848000" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/airpods-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903332" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;80 off AirPods</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/airpods-4-hit-new-all-time-low/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best deals this week centered on AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2, both of which are seeing the year's best prices so far on Amazon. You can get the AirPods 4 from &#36;99.99 and the AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;169.00 on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Galaxy S25</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/samsung-galaxy-s25-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988701" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save up to &#36;1,250 when pre-ordering the new Samsung Galaxy S25 smartphones</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/ocq3lbgam37ey">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/pre-order-discounts-galaxy-s25-smartphones/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/60hr8e2476e4h"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,250 OFF</div>Samsung Galaxy S25 Smartphones</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung recently announced its new lineup of Galaxy S25 smartphones, and you can find multiple pre-order discounts and offers on Samsung's website. This includes up to &#36;1,250 in trade-in credits and Samsung credits when pre-ordering the Galaxy S25, Galaxy S25+, and Galaxy S25 Ultra. Students can save an extra 5 percent on the new smartphones as well.<br/>
<br/>
The high-end <a href="https://howl.link/60hr8e2476e4h">Galaxy S25 Ultra</a> is priced starting at &#36;1,299.99 for 256GB, and you can save up to &#36;1,250 on this model with trade-in credits and Samsung credits. If you trade in a Galaxy S24 Ultra, Z Fold6, or Z Fold5, you can get as much as &#36;900 off the new S25 Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, if you select the 256GB Galaxy S25 Ultra, you can get the Galaxy Buds3 Pro for free, and if you select the 512GB Galaxy S25 Ultra, you can get the Galaxy Buds3 Pro for only &#36;20. You'll find these offers if you scroll down on the Galaxy S25 Ultra page, under the "Start building healthy habits with Galaxy" section.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/anker-lantern-puprle-2.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988705" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Anker charging accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fvalentines-day-specials%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-PowerCore-Portable-Retractable-Emergency%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fth%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/anker-valentines-day-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fvalentines-day-specials%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Anker Valentine's Day Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-PowerCore-Portable-Retractable-Emergency%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Anker Power Station with Display and Lantern for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker began its Valentine's Day sale this week, and it has some notable discounts on wireless chargers, portable batteries, and more. You can also find a big discount on the popular Anker Power Station with Display and Lantern on Amazon, available for &#36;89.99 (&#36;50 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-watch-se-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988706" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;80 off Apple Watch SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/get-apple-watch-se-for-169/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ73CFS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHRBF1J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon began the week with the return of all-time low prices on the Apple Watch SE, with &#36;80 off both 40mm and 44mm GPS models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/sonos-ace-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964245" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to 25% off Sonos audio products</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/01/sonos-home-theater-super-bowl/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 25% OFF</div>Sonos Super Bowl Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sonos began its annual Super Bowl sale this week, offering up to 25 percent off select home theater audio equipment. This sale includes big discounts on popular products like the Sonos Arc and Sonos Ray soundbars, and it will end on February 9.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/studio-display-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988708" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;299 off Apple Studio Display</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/02/apple-studio-display-299-off/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3HP4KL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Nano-Texture Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we saw the Apple Studio Display get discounted for the first time in 2025, and these all-time low prices are still available right now. The best deal is on the Standard Glass model for &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-7-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Best Prices of the Year Hit AirPods 4 and AirPods Pro 2, Plus Apple Watch SE Discounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-best-prices-of-the-year-hit-airpods-4-and-airpods-pro-2-plus-apple-watch-se-discounts.2448952/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s All-New &#039;Invites&#039; App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/the-macrumors-show-invites-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-all-new-invites-app.2448944/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 07:42:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/the-macrumors-show-invites-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>Apple Invites</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's all-new "Invites" app for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h37I4mud_DE?si=ZNK8ACGojPErtCt1" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Earlier this week, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/apple-launches-new-invites-app/">announced "Invites,"</a> which is designed to help users plan group events like birthday parties, graduations, vacations, baby showers, and more. Users can choose a background image or generate one using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> and customize the look of the invite with different fonts. Apple automatically adds in data from the Maps and Weather apps so that invitees have all of the information they need for an event. People who receive invites can RSVP and the sender can track who has responded. There are options to create a dedicated shared <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> album and a collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlist for the event. <br/>
<br/>
Invites is <a href="https://www.apple.com/icloud/">an iCloud+ service</a>, which means that it is available to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscribers only. &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ is priced starting at &#36;0.99 per month, and it provides users with additional &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; storage over the free 5GB that comes with any device. While anyone is able to respond to an Invite that's sent out, creating invites is limited to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;+ subscribers. <br/>
<br/>
We discuss Apple's &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; website and accessing the company's services from non-Apple devices, since Invites is also available via icloud.com. In addition, we reflect on the other apps that Apple has introduced in recent years, including Clips, News, Journal, and Sports. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> also has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/31/the-macrumors-show-latest-iphone-se-4-rumors/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about all of the latest rumors about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 4 as it nears launch. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-invites/">Apple Invites</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/the-macrumors-show-invites-app/">The MacRumors Show: Apple&#039;s All-New &#039;Invites&#039; App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-apples-all-new-invites-app.2448944/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Work on Apple TV+&#039;s &#039;Severance&#039; Season 3 Now Underway</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/severance-season-3-work-now-underway/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/work-on-apple-tv-s-severance-season-3-now-underway.2448937/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 06:30:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/severance-season-3-work-now-underway/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Production on the third season of "Severance" is already underway, with its writers room currently active in Los Angeles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Severance-Apple-TV-Plus-Banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-877229" /><br/>
While Apple has not yet officially announced Severance's renewal, executive producer and director Ben Stiller told <a href="https://www.hollywoodreporter.com/tv/tv-features/ben-stiller-severance-apple-filmmaking-parents-documentary-1236126909/"><em>The Hollywood Reporter</em></a> that work on the next season has begun. Stiller said that he hopes to avoid the nearly three-year gap that separated the first and second seasons. <br/>
<br/>
The prolonged development of Severance's second season is attributed to multiple factors, including the 2023 Hollywood strikes, which virtually halted production industry-wide. The second season also underwent extensive rewrites and reshoots as Stiller and the production team sought to refine character arcs and expand on the show's world-building to ensure that its "mystery box" narrative delivers on its premise. <br/>
<br/>
Stiller also indicated that Apple remains invested in maintaining the show's production quality amid falling budgets in the industry. The cost per episode for season two is believed to have approached &#36;20 million, placing Severance among the most expensive series in Apple's streaming portfolio. According to Parrot Analytics, season one of Severance generated over &#36;200 million in new subscriptions for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+, particularly in international markets. Apple does not release detailed viewership metrics, but third-party rankings have consistently placed Severance among its top-performing originals.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/severance-season-3-work-now-underway/">Work on Apple TV+&#039;s &#039;Severance&#039; Season 3 Now Underway</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/work-on-apple-tv-s-severance-season-3-now-underway.2448937/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Did You Know iPhones Can Measure a Person&#039;s Height? Here&#039;s How</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-measure-persons-height/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/did-you-know-iphones-can-measure-a-persons-height-heres-how.2448936/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 06:27:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-measure-persons-height/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhones equipped with a LiDAR Scanner have a useful trick: they can be used to measure a person's height. In order to take advantage of this feature, you will need an iPhone Pro or Pro Max model released in 2020 or later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-Measure-Height-Contact-Shadow.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-988688" /><br/>
Below, we outline how to measure a person's height with an iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Measure</h2><br/>
The ability to measure a person's height is built into Apple's pre-installed Measure app.<br/>
<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Measure app on a compatible iPhone (see list below).</li><br/>
<li>Make sure the person is visible on your iPhone's screen from head to toe.</li><br/>
<li>Wait a moment, and a line should appear at the top of the person's head with their height measurement.</li><br/>
<li>To take a photo of the measurement, tap the shutter button (filled-in white circle) in the bottom-right corner of the app.</li><br/>
<li>To save the photo, tap the screenshot in the bottom-left corner of the screen, tap Done at the top, and tap Save to Photos.</li></ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tips</h2><br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>The app measures a person's height from the ground to the top of their head or hair. However, if the person is wearing a hat, the height measurement will be from the ground to the top of the hat.</li><br/>
<li>You can also measure a person's seated height.</li><br/>
<li>You can switch between imperial (feet and inches) and metric (centimeters) in the Settings app under Measure → Measure Units.</li></ul>Here are some additional tips <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102468">from Apple's website</a>:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>Make sure that you're in a place with good lighting.</li><br/>
<li>Avoid dark backgrounds and reflective surfaces.</li><br/>
<li>Check that the person you're measuring has nothing covering their face or head, like a face mask or sunglasses.</li><br/>
<li>Try to step back from the person you're measuring. You might be standing too close.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Compatible iPhones</h2><br/>
The feature requires an iPhone with a LiDAR Scanner next to the rear camera. This sensor is typically used for augmented reality purposes, but its ability to measure a person's height is a useful bonus that many people don't know about.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Pro Max</li></ul>The feature is not available on any other iPhone models.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/iphone-measure-persons-height/">Did You Know iPhones Can Measure a Person&#039;s Height? Here&#039;s How</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/did-you-know-iphones-can-measure-a-persons-height-heres-how.2448936/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Enable End-to-End Encryption for Your iCloud Backups</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/enable-end-to-end-encryption-for-your-icloud-backups.2448931/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 05:20:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud&#038;post_date=1738945200/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Advanced Data Protection for iCloud feature uses end-to-end encryption to provide the highest level of cloud data security that Apple offers. Here's everything you need to know about enabling it on your devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-Advanced-Data-Protection_screen-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876839" /><br/>
The encrypted security feature gives you the choice to further protect your important iCloud data, including iCloud Backup, Photos, Notes, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's use of end-to-end encryption means the vast majority of your most sensitive iCloud data can only be decrypted on your trusted Apple devices where you're signed in with your Apple ID account, ensuring that the data remains secure even in the case of a data breach in the cloud. In other words, no-one – not even Apple – can access your data except you.<br/>
<br/>
iCloud already protects 14 sensitive data categories using end-to-end encryption by default, including passwords in iCloud Keychain and Health data. For users who enable Advanced Data Protection, the total number of data categories protected using end-to-end encryption rises to 23, including iCloud Backup, Notes, and Photos. <br/>
<br/>
Advanced Data Protection provides end-to-end encryption for the following additional iCloud categories:<br/>
<ul><li>Device Backups and Messages Backups</li><br/>
		<li>iCloud Drive</li><br/>
		<li>Notes</li><br/>
		<li>Photos</li><br/>
		<li>Reminders</li><br/>
		<li>Voice Memos</li><br/>
		<li>Safari Bookmarks</li><br/>
		<li>Siri Shortcuts</li><br/>
		<li>Wallet Passes</li></ul>The only major iCloud data categories that are not covered are iCloud Mail, Contacts, and Calendar because of the need to interoperate with the global email, contacts, and calendar systems. <br/>
<br/>
Crucially, Advanced Data Protection for iCloud is an opt-in feature, so you must enable it yourself using the steps below. Note that if you lose access to your account, you can only recover your data using your device passcode or password, a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212513">recovery contact</a>, or a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT208072">recovery key</a>. (You will be guided to set up at least one recovery contact or recovery key before Advanced Data Protection is enabled.)<br/>
<br/>
It's also worth bearing in mind that when Advanced Data Protection is enabled, access to your data via iCloud.com is disabled by default, although you will have the option to turn on data access on iCloud.com, which allows the web browser to have temporary access to data-specific encryption keys.<br/>
<br/>
Before you enable Advanced Data Protection, you'll first have to update all your devices to the latest software versions, otherwise you'll have to remove these devices from your account as they won't support end-to-end encryption. Advanced Data Protection is available globally on the iPhone, iPad, and Mac, running iOS 16.3 or later, iPadOS 16.3 or later, and macOS 13.2 or later, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Enable Account Recovery on iPhone, iPad, and Mac</h2><br/>
Before turning on Advanced Data Protection, you'll need to set up Account Recovery. This ensures you can recover your data if you forget your password.<br/>
<ol><li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on your iPhone or iPad (or System Settings on Mac), and then select your Apple Account banner at the top of the menu.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>iCloud</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Advanced Data Protection</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/advanced-data-protection2.jpg" alt="settings" width="2760" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988641" /><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Account Recovery</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Add a <strong>Recovery Contact</strong>, and set a <strong>Recovery Key</strong> if desired.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/advanced-data-protection1.jpg" alt="settings" width="2760" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988642" /></ol><br/>
<br/>
A recovery contact should be a trusted person such as a family member or friend who also owns an Apple device. They will receive recovery codes if you ever forget your password. If you opt to set a 28-character recovery key, you'll need to print it out and keep it somewhere safe, or store it in a password manager. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Enable Advanced Data Protection on iPhone, iPad, and Mac</h2><br/>
Once Account Recovery is set up, you can enable Advanced Data Protection for iCloud Backups.<br/>
<ol><li>Open <strong>Settings</strong> on iPhone or iPad (System Settings on Mac) and then select your Apple Account banner at the top of the menu.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>iCloud</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Advanced Data Protection</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Toggle on the switch for Advanced Data Protection to turn it on.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/advanced-data-protection3.jpg" alt="settings" width="2760" height="2760" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988644" /><br/>
<br/>
That's it. Your iCloud backups are now protected with end-to-end encryption.<br/>
<br/>
You can turn off Advanced Data Protection at any time. Upon doing so, your device will securely upload the required encryption keys to Apple servers, and your account will revert to a standard level of protection.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud/">Enable End-to-End Encryption for Your iCloud Backups</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/enable-end-to-end-encryption-for-your-icloud-backups.2448931/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac App Store Stops Working on Older macOS Versions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/mac-app-store-not-working-older-macos-versions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-app-store-stops-working-on-older-macos-versions.2448930/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 05:02:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/mac-app-store-not-working-older-macos-versions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mac users running macOS Mojave (10.14) and earlier versions are reporting widespread issues accessing the Mac App Store, with many unable to sign in or download previously purchased apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Mac-App-Store-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800078" /><br/>
Based on reports compiled by <a href="https://mjtsai.com/blog/2025/02/06/mac-app-store-broken-on-macos-10-14-and-earlier/">Michael Tsai</a>, the problems appear to have emerged around January 24, 2025, coinciding with Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=rzloycgp">making changes to Mac App Store receipts</a>. Users attempting to access the store on affected systems are receiving various error messages, including "An unexpected error occurred while signing in" and "The data couldn't be read because it isn't in the correct format."<br/>
<br/>
Different behaviors have been reported across affected macOS versions. Catalina (10.15) and later versions continue to function normally, while users on Mojave (10.14) can browse the store but are unable to complete new purchases or download previous purchases once their current session expires. Meanwhile, High Sierra (10.13) users are reporting missing interface elements and failed sign-in attempts, and Sierra (10.12) users are encountering error messages preventing access.<br/>
<br/>
The timing suggests a possible connection to Apple's recent changes in Mac App Store receipt handling, but the exact cause remains unclear. For users affected by these issues, Apple provides alternative sources for <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-gb/102662">macOS installers</a>, and many third-party apps remain available outside Apple's App Store ecosystem via direct downloads from developers' websites.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/mac-app-store-not-working-older-macos-versions/">Mac App Store Stops Working on Older macOS Versions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-app-store-stops-working-on-older-macos-versions.2448930/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Air and MacBook Air Stocks Running Low at Apple Stores, With New Models Likely Coming Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ipad-air-macbook-air-stocks-running-low-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-and-macbook-air-stocks-running-low-at-apple-stores-with-new-models-likely-coming-soon.2448929/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 04:41:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ipad-air-macbook-air-stocks-running-low-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's inventory of iPad Air and MacBook Air models is running low at its retail stores, indicating that refreshes for the devices are likely just around the corner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/macbook-air-pink.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986821" /><br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-06/apple-s-long-awaited-overhaul-of-budget-iphone-nears-release">reports</a> that Apple's stock of both products is "dwindling," as the company gears up to launch new updates. Apple is expected to launch a MacBook Air with its faster M4 chip, along with updated iPad Air models during the first half of 2025. <br/>
<br/>
Some rumors have suggested the iPad Air will have the M3 chip that's a step behind the M4 in the iPad Pro, but Gurman said in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/12/ipad-11-rumored-specs/">January</a> that Apple could opt for the M4 instead. A leaker who has provided reliable information in the past also said in January that the iPad Air 7 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/ios-18-3-build-for-iphone-se-4-leak/">will use the M3 chip</a>, not the M4 chip. No other major hardware or design changes are expected.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also developing a new version of the Magic Keyboard for the iPad Air. It will not have an aluminum top case like the iPad Pro, but it could have a function row of keys and some other features from the iPad Pro Magic Keyboard. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is also believed to be working on a new 11th-generation entry-level iPad. Gurman has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/12/ipad-11-rumored-specs/">said</a> Apple will use the A17 Pro chip – the same one that's in the iPhone 15 Pro models and the iPad mini 7. The A17 Pro chip supports Apple Intelligence, so presumably that means the new iPad will come with at least 8GB of RAM, which is the minimum requirement for Apple's suite of AI features.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman's inventory stock check was mentioned in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/iphone-se-4-launch-next-week/">report</a> claiming that Apple could announce the new iPhone SE 4 as soon as next week via a press release, with a launch to follow later in February. Gurman suggests that Apple will unveil its new low-cost iPhone the same time as the new PowerBeats Pro 2 earbuds, which Apple plans to unveil as soon as February 11. However, he also said the new MacBook Air and iPads are "coming soon," suggesting they are likely to arrive later in the spring.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/ipad-air-macbook-air-stocks-running-low-apple/">iPad Air and MacBook Air Stocks Running Low at Apple Stores, With New Models Likely Coming Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-and-macbook-air-stocks-running-low-at-apple-stores-with-new-models-likely-coming-soon.2448929/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ordered by UK to Create Global iCloud Encryption Backdoor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ordered-by-uk-to-create-global-icloud-encryption-backdoor.2448927/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 02:37:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The British government has secretly demanded that Apple give it blanket access to all encrypted user content uploaded to the cloud, reports <em><a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/02/07/apple-encryption-backdoor-uk/">The Washington Post</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/iCloud-General-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-982796" /><br/>
The undisclosed order is said to have been issued last month, and requires that Apple creates a back door that allows UK security officials unencumbered access to encrypted user data worldwide – an unprecedented demand not before seen in any other democratic country.<br/>
<br/>
The spying order came by way of a "technical capability notice," a document sent to Apple by the Home Secretary, ordering it to provide access under the sweeping UK Investigatory Powers Act (IPA) of 2016. Critics have labeled the legislation the "Snooper's Charter," as it authorizes law enforcement to compel assistance from companies when needed to collect evidence.<br/>
<br/>
An Apple spokesperson declined to comment on the revelation, though the law actually makes it a criminal offense to reveal that the government even made such a demand. Likewise, the Home Office told the publication that its policy was not to discuss any technical demands. "We do not comment on operational matters, including for example confirming or denying the existence of any such notices," a spokesman said.<br/>
<blockquote>One of the people briefed on the situation, a consultant advising the United States on encryption matters, said Apple would be barred from warning its users that its most advanced encryption no longer provided full security. The person deemed it shocking that the UK government was demanding Apple's help to spy on non-British users without their governments' knowledge. A former White House security adviser confirmed the existence of the British order.</blockquote><h2>Apple May Drop UK iCloud Services Over Secret Encryption Access Order</h2><br/>
<br/>
Apple is likely to stop offering encrypted storage in the UK, rather than break the security promises it made to its users, people familiar with the matter told the publication. However, that would not affect the UK order for backdoor access to the service in other countries, including the United States. Apple has previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/">said</a> it would consider pulling services such as FaceTime and iMessage from the UK rather than compromise future security.<br/>
<br/>
The order would compromise Apple's Advanced Data Protection, which the company launched in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/apple-advanced-data-protection/">2022</a>. The feature gives users the option to end-to-end encrypt many additional iCloud data categories, including Photos, Notes, Voice Memos, Messages backups, device backups, and more, making their data inaccessible to anyone else – including Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Google has enforced default encryption for Android phone backups since 2018. When asked by <em>The Post</em> whether any government had requested a backdoor, Google spokesman Ed Fernandez did not provide a direct answer but suggested none exist: "Google cannot access Android end-to-end encrypted backup data, even with a legal order," he stated.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud/">How to Enable End-to-End Encryption for iCloud Backups</a></li></ul><br/>
The IPA was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/">updated</a> in 2023 to allow the Home Office to outlaw certain encrypted services using a technical capability notice. Apple at the time called the then proposed amendments "an unprecedented overreach by the government," saying that if the update was enacted, "the UK could attempt to secretly veto new user protections globally preventing us from ever offering them to customers."<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook has consistently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/12/21/60-minutes-inside-apple-special/">insisted</a> that providing back-door access past its encryption for authorities would open the door for "bad guys" to gain access to its users' data. Cyber security experts agree that it would only be a matter of time before bad actors discover such a point of entry. Apple's stance was enhanced in 2016 when it successfully fought a US order to unlock the iPhone of a shooter in San Bernardino, California.<br/>
<br/>
US law enforcement's longstanding objections to encryption have recently taken a backseat to concerns over large-scale cyber intrusions attributed to Chinese state-backed hackers. The attackers infiltrated major telecommunications providers, granting them unfettered access to private phone calls. During a December press conference alongside FBI officials, a Department of Homeland Security representative cautioned Americans against assuming traditional phone networks offer privacy, instead advising them to use encrypted communication whenever feasible.<br/>
<br/>
That same month, the FBI, National Security Agency, and Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency issued a joint advisory detailing numerous countermeasures against the Chinese cyber campaign. Among their recommendations: "Ensure that traffic is end-to-end encrypted to the maximum extent possible."<br/>
<br/>
In a statement, privacy campaigner Big Brother Watch said: "This misguided attempt at tackling crime and terrorism will not make the UK safer, but it will erode the fundamental rights and civil liberties of the entire population."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/">Apple Ordered by UK to Create Global iCloud Encryption Backdoor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ordered-by-uk-to-create-global-icloud-encryption-backdoor.2448927/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Considered a MagSafe Speaker for iPhone, But Scrapped It</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/sonos-iphone-magsafe-speaker-prototyped/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-considered-a-magsafe-speaker-for-iphone-but-scrapped-it.2448916/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 17:12:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/sonos-iphone-magsafe-speaker-prototyped/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos, known for its range of high-end speakers, considered developing a speaker that would connect to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/sonos/607657/sonos-iphone-magsafe-speaker">The Verge</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/magsafe-battery-pack-on-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808593" /><br/>
Engineers at the company prototyped a tiny, iPhone-compatible speaker that would attach directly to the device, with music that would play over a Bluetooth connection. According to <em>The Verge</em>, the prototype speaker had a square shape, and it was similar to the look of Apple's now-discontinued <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a>, but thicker.<br/>
<br/>
Some employees thought the speaker product would resonate with Gen Z, and expected it to deliver good sound regardless of the compact size. Sonos ended up scrapping the project, though, due to "technical limitations, questionable appeal, and a limited target market."<br/>
<br/>
Sonos has been working to expand its product lineup. Last year, Sonos introduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">the Sonos Ace headphones</a> that compete with high-end headphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, and later this year, it is rumored to be planning to introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/04/sonos-set-top-box/">set-top box similar to the Apple TV</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/sonos-iphone-magsafe-speaker-prototyped/">Sonos Considered a MagSafe Speaker for iPhone, But Scrapped It</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-considered-a-magsafe-speaker-for-iphone-but-scrapped-it.2448916/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iPad Continues to Dominate Tablet Market</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apples-ipad-continues-to-dominate-tablet-market/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipad-continues-to-dominate-tablet-market.2448914/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:44:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apples-ipad-continues-to-dominate-tablet-market/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Canalys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple continues to have no close competition in the tablet market, earning 42.3 percent of the global tablet market share in the fourth quarter of 2024, according to a <a href="https://www.canalys.com/newsroom/global-tablet-shipments-q4-2024">new report from Canalys</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ipad-pro-blue-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962219" /><br/>
Apple shipped an estimated 16.9 million iPads during the quarter, up from 14.8 million in Q4 2023. The company's closest competitor was Samsung, with 7 million tablets shipped in Q4 2024 for 17.8 percent of the market. Lenovo, Huawei, and Xiaomi were third, fourth, and fifth, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
For all of 2024, Apple shipped an estimated 57 million iPads for 38.6 percent of the market. Apple shipped over twice as many tablets as Samsung in 2024, with Samsung shipping just 27.8 million.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refreshed its high-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> with an M4 chip in 2024, plus it revamped the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> with an A17 Pro chip and added an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>. In 2025, Apple plans to refresh the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and update the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; yet again.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/canalys/">Canalys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apples-ipad-continues-to-dominate-tablet-market/">Apple&#039;s iPad Continues to Dominate Tablet Market</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipad-continues-to-dominate-tablet-market.2448914/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mistral AI&#039;s &#039;Le Chat&#039; Chatbot Now Available on iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/mistral-ais-le-chat-chatbot-now-available-on-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mistral-ais-le-chat-chatbot-now-available-on-iphone.2448913/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/mistral-ais-le-chat-chatbot-now-available-on-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you haven't had enough of AI apps, there's yet another to download and try out as of today. European company Mistral's <a href="https://chat.mistral.ai/chat">Le Chat</a> chatbot can now be used through a dedicated iOS app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/le-chat-mistral.jpg" alt="" width="4275" height="2405" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988598" /><br/>
Mistral is a French AI company founded by engineers from Google and Meta. It creates its own open-weight large language models, and is aiming to compete with OpenAI. Le Chat has been <a href="https://chat.mistral.ai/chat">available on the web</a>, but the app will make it better able to compete with ChatGPT, DeepSeek, Gemini, and other options.<br/>
<br/>
Like many competing chatbots, Le Chat supports natural language conversations, real-time web search, document analysis, and image generation.<br/>
<br/>
LeChat is free to use, but access to the highest performing models is limited. A &#36;14.99 per month fee unlocks a Pro tier with unlimited web browsing, extended access to news, and unlimited messaging.<br/>
<br/>
Le Chat can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for free. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/le-chat-by-mistral-ai/id6740410176">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/mistral-ais-le-chat-chatbot-now-available-on-iphone/">Mistral AI&#039;s &#039;Le Chat&#039; Chatbot Now Available on iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mistral-ais-le-chat-chatbot-now-available-on-iphone.2448913/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Launching as Soon as Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/iphone-se-4-launch-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-launching-as-soon-as-next-week.2448911/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:30:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/iphone-se-4-launch-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> could debut as soon as next week with a launch to follow later in February, reports <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-06/apple-s-long-awaited-overhaul-of-budget-iphone-nears-release"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Apple isn't expected to hold an event for the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, and will instead unveil the device through a press release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-SE-4-Single-Camera-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978495" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is expected to have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14-style design, with Apple eliminating the thick bezels and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> Home button of the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;. When the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 launches, it will mark the end of &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to unveil its custom in-house modem in the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4, and it will be the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to get the new modem chip. While Apple's modem chip won't be as advanced as Qualcomm's modem chips, it will be Apple's first step toward cutting down on its reliance on Qualcomm.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 will support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, and it will be equipped with the same A18 chip that's in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and 8GB RAM. It will also have a USB-C port, allowing it to be sold in Europe again, and it is expected to feature a single-lens 48-megapixel rear camera. <br/>
<br/>
While the current &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is priced at &#36;429, Apple could increase the price of the new model due to the inclusion of the faster chip, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, and other features. Pricing is expected to remain below &#36;500 though, so that the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 is competitive with lower-end smartphones from Samsung and Google. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman suggests that Apple will unveil the &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; 4 around the same time as the new PowerBeats Pro 2 earbuds, which Apple plans to unveil as soon as February 11. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/iphone-se-4-launch-next-week/">iPhone SE 4 Launching as Soon as Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-launching-as-soon-as-next-week.2448911/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Removed Apps Infested With Screen Reading Malware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apple-removed-screen-reading-malware-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-removed-apps-infested-with-screen-reading-malware.2448910/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:19:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apple-removed-screen-reading-malware-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Information on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/05/ocr-malware-app-store/">new "SparkCat" malware</a> infesting a small number of iOS apps was shared yesterday by Kaspersky, and shortly after the report came out, Apple pulled the apps from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-JoeBlue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833073" /><br/>
Some of the apps that had hidden malware included ComeCome, WeTink, and AnyGPT. 11 apps were removed in total, but when removing the apps, Apple found another 89 with the same code that had been previously rejected or removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; for violating Apple's fraud policies. When an app is removed for fraud, Apple terminates the associated developer account.<br/>
<br/>
As outlined by Kaspersky, the apps used a malicious framework with OCR capabilities designed to suss out sensitive information in images and screenshots stored on iPhones. Recovery phrases for crypto wallets were a specific target, with attackers aiming to steal bitcoin and other cryptocurrency, but the malware could target other phrases like passwords.<br/>
<br/>
By default, Apple blocks access to a user's photos, so the apps would have needed express user consent to operate. If given permission to access a Photo Library, the apps could scan through the images to look for key phrases outlined by the attackers. If an image with a relevant phrase was found, it was uploaded to a remote server. Kaspersky found that the malware was likely targeting iOS users in Europe and Asia.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that Apple added granular control over the images that an app is able to access back in iOS 14, and there is an option to provide access to a limited number of images rather than an entire library. It is a good idea to avoid apps that seem sketchy, and to refrain from giving an app access to all of your images.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also provides an App Privacy Report that outlines all of the instances when an app accesses sensitive data like location, images, camera, and microphone. The App Private Report can be found in the Privacy section of the Settings app.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/06/apple-removed-screen-reading-malware-apps/">Apple Removed Apps Infested With Screen Reading Malware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-removed-apps-infested-with-screen-reading-malware.2448910/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
