<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 08:02:58 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iPhone 16e Announced, iOS 18.4 Beta, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/top-stories-iphone-16e-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-iphone-16e-announced-ios-18-4-beta-and-more.2449953/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/top-stories-iphone-16e-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week saw Apple introduce the newest member of the iPhone 16 family, the iPhone 16e, as a new low-cost option to replace the iPhone SE. The iPhone 16e delivers a number of key improvements as well as Apple's first custom cellular modem.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/top-stories-2025-02-22.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991355" /><br/>
Apple also began seeding the first beta versions of its next round of operating systems, and there are a number of tweaks and improvements in iOS 18.4 while visionOS 2.4 will bring Apple Intelligence to the Vision Pro headset, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iPhone 16e With A18 Chip and Apple Intelligence, Pricing Starts at &#36;599</h2><br/>
As expected, Apple this week introduced a successor to the third-generation iPhone SE, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-announces-iphone-16e/">arrived with a name change: iPhone 16e</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-iPhone-16e-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990884" /><br/>
The iPhone 16e features a larger 6.1-inch OLED display, up from a 4.7-inch LCD on the iPhone SE. The display has a notch for Face ID, completing Apple's move away from the Touch ID fingerprint button on its iPhone lineup.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 16e is powered by an A18 chip, enabling support for Apple Intelligence features, such as notification summaries and Genmoji for creating custom emoji. In the iPhone 16e, the A18 chip has a 6-core CPU and a 16-core Neural Engine, but a binned 4-core GPU. The A18 chip in the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus has a 5-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Unveils 'C1' as First Custom Cellular Modem</h2><br/>
One notable feature of the iPhone 16e is the inclusion of Apple's first custom cellular modem, dubbed C1. Apple says it's the most power-efficient modem ever in an iPhone, helping the iPhone 16e to achieve the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/iphone-16e-battery-life/">longest battery life ever in a 6.1-inch iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-c1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990815" /><br/>
While the C1 is the culmination of seven years of work for Apple, it's also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-says-c1-modem-is-just-the-start/">just the first in a family of chips</a> that will see Apple iterate and improve upon the C1. In fact, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-already-testing-a-c2-modem/">C2 modem chip</a> is reportedly already in testing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16e vs. iPhone 16 Buyer's Guide: 25+ Differences Compared</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16e starting at &#36;599 is considerably more expensive than the iPhone SE it's replacing, it's still &#36;200 cheaper than the iPhone 16.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-16e-vs-16-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990861" /><br/>
For those weighing whether to purchase an iPhone 16e or an iPhone 16, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-16e-vs-iphone-16/">we've put together a buyer's guide</a> highlighting the over 25 differences between the models to help you decide.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything New in iOS 18.4 Beta 1</h2><br/>
Apple this week finally released the first beta of iOS 18.4 to developers for testing purposes, and while the beta is lacking some of the Apple Intelligence features we were hoping for, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/everything-new-ios-18-4-beta-1/">there are some notable new additions</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" /><br/>
Priority Notifications powered by Apple Intelligence, the addition of the Sketch style to Image Playground, numerous new languages for Apple Intelligence, and Ambient Music functionality built into Control Center, and more are included in iOS 18.4 so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases First visionOS 2.4 Beta With Apple Intelligence, Spatial Gallery and More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-visionos-2-4-beta-1/">Apple Intelligence is coming to the Vision Pro</a> with visionOS 2.4. Supported Apple Intelligence features include Writing Tools for generating, proofreading, and summarizing text, Genmoji for creating custom emoji characters, an Image Playground app for generating images, Memory Movie for creating custom slideshows, smart reply for generating quick responses to texts and emails, Priority Notifications and Notification Summaries, ChatGPT Siri integration and new ‌Siri‌ features, and Image Wand for adding images to the Notes app, complete with gesture support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/visionOS-2.4-Thumb-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991280" /><br/>
There's also a dedicated Spatial Gallery app coming to the Vision Pro, which will include a curated selection of spatial videos, spatial photos, and panorama images from artists, filmmakers, and photographers. A new Vision Pro app for iPhone will also allow users to get Vision Pro support and feature help, download apps to the Vision Pro, add content to a watch list, and get device info like serial number. The app can also be used to manage Guest Mode on Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Discontinues iPhone 14 and 14 Plus</h2><br/>
While it's unsurprising that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-discontinues-iphone-se/">discontinued the iPhone SE</a> alongside the introduction of the iPhone 16e, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-discontinues-iphone-14/">also discontinued the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus</a>, simplifying the overall lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Apple-iPhone-14-color-lineup-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888160" /><br/>
The discontinuation makes sense considering the pricing on the iPhone 16e and the fact that the iPhone 14 and 14 Plus would have been the only models in the lineup to still be using Lightning rather than USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/feb-20-2025">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/top-stories-iphone-16e-announced/">Top Stories: iPhone 16e Announced, iOS 18.4 Beta, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-iphone-16e-announced-ios-18-4-beta-and-more.2449953/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirTag 4-Pack Drops to Record Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/apples-airtag-4-pack-69-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airtag-4-pack-drops-to-record-low-69-99-price-on-amazon.2449952/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 05:28:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/apples-airtag-4-pack-69-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has Apple's AirTag 4-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. Amazon introduced this all-time low price back in January, and it's been reappearing throughout the month of February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airtag-orange-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957000" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon provides an estimated late February delivery date for most residences in the United States, and you won't need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see this deal. If you're shopping for just one AirTag, Amazon has the AirTag 1-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;22.99</strong></a>, which is about &#36;3 higher compared to that option's record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/22/apples-airtag-4-pack-69-2/">Apple&#039;s AirTag 4-Pack Drops to Record Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airtag-4-pack-drops-to-record-low-69-99-price-on-amazon.2449952/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>California Nominates Steve Jobs for &#36;1 American Innovation Coin</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/california-steve-jobs-innovation-coin/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-nominates-steve-jobs-for-1-american-innovation-coin.2449932/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:16:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/california-steve-jobs-innovation-coin/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>California</category>
		<category>Steve Jobs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[California Governor Gavin Newsom this week <a href="https://www.gov.ca.gov/2025/02/19/california-nominates-steve-jobs-for-its-american-innovation-coin-1-coin-to-be-produced-by-u-s-mint/">recommended former</a> Apple CEO Steve Jobs for the &#36;1 American Innovation Coin for the State of California that will be minted by the U.S. Mint.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/california-steve-jobs-coin.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991369" /><br/>
Each state is able to create a unique coin recognizing an innovation or innovator from their region as part of the Innovation Coin Program that was launched in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Newsom said that Steve Jobs "encapsulates the unique brand of innovation that California runs on."<blockquote>Jobs' legacy spans industries and products: Jobs was the co-founder and CEO of Pixar Animation Studios, bringing to life the world's first fully computer-animated feature: "Toy Story." But even that legacy-defining achievement is surpassed by his work as co-founder and two-time CEO of Apple, launching several revolutionary computers, including Apple II - the first mass-produced microcomputer - and Macintosh - the first mass-market personal computer that included a graphic display, so users could see what they were working on.<br/>
<br/>
The goal, according to Jobs, was to "bridge the gap between sophisticated technology and 'the rest of us' who make up most of humanity...to make complex technology easy to use and fun to use." That approach led to the iPod, iPhone, and iPad, devices that refined existing technology to make it more precise, more intuitive, and more functional.<br/>
<br/>
By focusing on who he was innovating for - other people - Jobs was able to use technology to connect people to each other and to the broader world, bringing people onto the same level by providing them with equal access. And that approach was built on a willingness to try new ideas and push the boundaries of what was possible - an approach that embodies the California spirit.</blockquote>California's nomination has been presented to the Citizens Coinage Advisory Committee (CCAC), which will take design recommendations to the Treasury Secretary for final approval. The CCAC decided to recommend a coin with Steve Jobs in his iconic turtleneck and glasses, but the design is not finalized and could be updated before the coin is made.<br/>
<br/>
The coin is expected to be produced and made available in 2026.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/california/">California</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/steve-jobs/">Steve Jobs</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/california-steve-jobs-innovation-coin/">California Nominates Steve Jobs for &#36;1 American Innovation Coin</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/california-nominates-steve-jobs-for-1-american-innovation-coin.2449932/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s a Look at Apple&#039;s Secret Modem Testing Lab Where C1 Was Developed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-c1-modem-lab/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-a-look-at-apples-secret-modem-testing-lab-where-c1-was-developed.2449929/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 15:22:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-c1-modem-lab/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>C1</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> includes Apple's first custom designed modem chip, the C1. To promote the new chip, Apple invited several YouTubers and journalists to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>, including Andru Edwards. Edwards got a first-hand look at Apple's modem testing labs, and he was able to speak to Apple engineers about the C1.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple's C1 Modem Revealed: Exclusive Behind-the-Scenes Tour" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4UiSuWEtMY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
According to Apple, the C1 is the most power efficient modem that's been included in an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to date, and that's the edge that the C1 has over Qualcomm's modems. The &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; has the longest battery life of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a 6.1-inch form factor, and it lasts for up to 26 hours when watching video.<br/>
<br/>
At Apple's modem testing labs, Apple engineers spent years testing the C1, determining how it would behave under various conditions using a range of equipment. Apple's testing lab allows it to identify and fix issues before a modem chip ever leaves the design stage.<br/>
<br/>
The C1 was tested in environmental chambers where it was exposed to different extreme temperatures to ensure that it can operate in the harshest conditions. Repeated physical tests also ensure that the chip is able to stand up to daily wear and tear. Network tests cover the heavy data traffic of a packed stadium to remote rural areas with minimal signal.<br/>
<br/>
Apple tested the C1 with over 180 carriers across 55 countries to ensure that it delivers reliable connectivity. The C1 is designed to integrate with the A18 chip, with the A18 able to optimize C1 network load for faster speeds.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the C1 is built on a 4-nanometer processor for the baseband and a 7-nanometer process for the transceiver, and it is a robust platform that's built for the future. Right now, the C1 does not support the faster mmWave 5G speeds, but future versions are likely to add the functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-already-testing-a-c2-modem/">next-generation C2 chip</a> is already in development for future &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/c1/">C1</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-c1-modem-lab/">Here&#039;s a Look at Apple&#039;s Secret Modem Testing Lab Where C1 Was Developed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-a-look-at-apples-secret-modem-testing-lab-where-c1-was-developed.2449929/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in iOS 18.4 Beta 1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/everything-new-ios-18-4-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-18-4-beta-1.2449921/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:08:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/everything-new-ios-18-4-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple finally released the first beta of iOS 18.4 to developers for testing purposes, and while the beta is lacking some of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features we were hoping for, there are some notable new additions.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Hh2OUPe41KM" title="Everything New in iOS 18.4 Beta 1!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<h2>Priority Notifications - Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
There is a new Priority Notifications feature that can show you your most important notifications first. Priority Notifications is disabled by default, but it can be turned on by going to Settings > Notifications > Prioritize Notifications and tapping the toggle.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991317" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/prioritize-notifications-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
With the feature enabled, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will show notifications that may be important in a dedicated section of the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Image Playground Sketch Style</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> now includes a Sketch style that joins the Animation and Illustration styles. Sketch was previously available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-wand/">Image Wand</a>, but now it is a third style that can be used in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991330" /><br/>
Swap styles by tapping on the "+" button in the &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also replaced the "Winter Holidays" theme with a new "Spring" theme. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Apple Intelligence Languages</h2><br/>
French, German, Italian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish, Japanese, Korean, and Chinese (simplified), along with localized English for Singapore and India.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple News+ Food</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 include a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a> Food section for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers. The Food section features tens of thousands of recipes, stories about restaurants, tips for healthy eating, kitchen essentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991301" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-food-news.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Content will come from top food publishers such as Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food &amp; Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats.&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; editors will curate food-related stories, and there will be a dedicated Recipe Catalog section where new recipes are added regularly. An included cook mode provides step-by-step instructions, and users can save favorite recipes for offline access.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Ambient Music</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 includes a new Ambient Music option that can be added to Control Center. There are four different sound categories, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991311" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-ambient-music.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Each category can be added to Control Center separately, and tapping one plays a random selection of sounds or music from that particular category.<br/>
<br/>
You can't choose what's playing from Control Center, but if you play a category and then tap into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> at the top or access the Now Playing widget, you can skip songs and see the name of what's currently playing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mail Categorization for iPadOS 18.4</h2><br/>
With iPadOS 18.4, an updated Mail app is available with categorization. The new Mail app organizes incoming emails into different sections. Important emails are displayed in the Primary category, with other emails organized into sections highlighting product orders, newsletters, deals, and social notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Mail categorization was previously introduced for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in iOS 18.2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Privacy Indication Dots</h2><br/>
The small dots that show up on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s menu bar when the camera or microphone is in use have been moved to the left and are now more apparent thanks to a black background.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/new-siri-indicator-dot-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1134" height="182" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991331" /><br/>
<h2>Siri Voices</h2><br/>
There are two new Australian voices for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-australian-siri-voice.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991334" /><br/>
<h2>Genmoji</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> icon for the Emoji keyboard now says "&zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;" instead of just featuring a multi-colored smiley face. The change should make it more obvious where users go to create a &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; character.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-genmoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991332" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Maps</h2><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> Settings, there is a new option to set a Preferred Language. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-maps-preferred.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1267" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991350" /><br/>
<h2>Podcasts Widget</h2><br/>
There are new Library and Shows widgets that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The Library widget features saved content, while the Shows option displays shows that you are subscribed to.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-podcast-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991338" /><br/>
In the Podcasts app, if you tap on your profile picture, there are new options for Podcasts Settings and Notification Settings. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Cellular Control Center Toggle</h2><br/>
The Cellular toggle in the Control Center now shows your cellular signal strength represented in bars.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-cellular-signal-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991333" /><br/>
<h2>Shortcuts Actions</h2><br/>
Apple added a new Shortcuts action to open a specific conversation in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-shortcuts-open-conversation.jpg" alt="" width="1688" height="950" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991336" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>CarPlay</h2><br/>
Some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> users are seeing a third row of &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; icons on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; rather than just two rows. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/carplay-view-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991341" /><em>Image <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-1-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2449908/post-33753569">via the MacRumors Forums</a></em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Default Apps</h2><br/>
There is a new option to set a different Translation app as the default in the Default Apps section of the Settings app. In the EU, there is also an option to choose a different Navigation app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-translate-default-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991344" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Notification Center</h2><br/>
The animation when swiping out of the Notification Center is now smoother. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wi-Fi Calling Issue</h2><br/>
Apple's developer notes for the update say that Wi-Fi Calling might not work for US Cellular customers in iOS 18.4. Apple says that users should revert to iOS 18.3 to enable Wi-Fi Calling.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Japan 'My Number Card' Support in Wallet</h2><br/>
The iOS 18.4 beta appears to include integration for Japanese "My Number Card" Digital IDs in the Wallet app. Apple said last year that it would be adding support for the ID cards in spring 2025.<br/>
<br/>
More than 100 million Japanese residents have My Number Card IDs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MDM Changes</h2><br/>
For enterprise and education users, Apple made some updates to Mobile Device Management. MDM can disable &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; reports, Mail smart replies, Safari summarize content, and the Idle Reboot feature that causes iPhones to restart after inactivity.<br/>
<br/>
There are also options for preventing the modification of default calling and messaging apps, and there is a feature that allows a nearby &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to be used to sign into a Mac with an Apple Account.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Vision Pro App and Guest Setup</h2><br/>
For Vision Pro owners, Apple has designed a Vision Pro app for managing the headset. It's designed to help users find content and learn about new features, so it includes tools for downloading apps and visionOS content, a tips page, and a My Vision Pro section for setting up Personalized Spatial Audio and getting information like headset serial number.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/vision-pro-app-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991289" /><br/>
Guest setup can now be managed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; linked to a Vision Pro, making it easier for Vision Pro owners to let others test their headset. There are controls for limiting what apps a guest is able to use, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> mode for guiding the guest through Vision Pro experiences. When a guest user puts on the Vision Pro, a prompt to enable Guest Mode will appear on the headset owner's device.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro app isn't in this beta, but it will be coming in a later iOS 18.4 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Emojis</h2><br/>
There are no new emoji in the current beta, but iOS 18.4 code confirms a future beta will add new characters. New emoji will include bags under eyes, fingerprint, leafless tree, root vegetable, harp, shovel, and splatter.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18.4 Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple plans to release iOS 18.4 to the public in April.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/everything-new-ios-18-4-beta-1/">Everything New in iOS 18.4 Beta 1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-18-4-beta-1.2449921/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Adds Apple Intelligence Priority Notifications Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-priority-notifications/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-adds-apple-intelligence-priority-notifications-feature.2449918/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:23:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-priority-notifications/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 18.4, iPadOS 18.4, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 betas, Apple is introducing a new Priority Notifications feature that can show you your most important notifications first.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/prioritize-notifications-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991317" /><br/>
Apple first announced Priority Notifications when showing off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in June, but it wasn't implemented until now. Priority Notifications is disabled by default, but it can be turned on by going to Settings &gt; Notifications &gt; Prioritize Notifications and tapping the toggle.<br/>
<br/>
With the feature enabled, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will show notifications that may be important in a dedicated section of the Lock Screen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-priority-notifications/">iOS 18.4 Adds Apple Intelligence Priority Notifications Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-adds-apple-intelligence-priority-notifications-feature.2449918/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Revamped Mail App With Built-In Categorization Comes to Mac and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/revamped-mail-app-mac-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revamped-mail-app-with-built-in-categorization-comes-to-mac-and-ipad.2449915/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:08:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/revamped-mail-app-mac-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The initial iPadOS 18.4 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 betas that Apple provided to developers today expand the revamped Mail app to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/General-macOS-Mail-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900439" /><br/>
The new Mail app features built-in categorization that organizes incoming emails into different sections. Important emails are displayed in the Primary category, with other emails organized into sections highlighting product orders, newsletters, deals, and social notifications.<br/>
<br/>
A "Transactions" section aggregates receipts, orders, and deliveries to make it easy to find orders that you've placed and shipping information for those orders.<br/>
<br/>
In an "Updates" section, you'll find newsletters, alerts for doctor's appointments and correspondence, and subscription emails. A "Promotions" category includes emails with offers and deals.<br/>
<br/>
Categories is the default view after updating to the new software, but in the upper right corner of the Mail app, you can swap back to a list view that shows all emails in chronological order, without separation into categories. Devices that have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> support will show priority emails in the Primary inbox, so you can see what's most important first. Emails in the Transactions, Updates, or Promotions section that have time-sensitive information will also be shown in the Primary section.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already brought Mail categorization to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with the iOS 18.2 update, but now it has expanded to the Mac and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; as well.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/revamped-mail-app-mac-ipad/">Revamped Mail App With Built-In Categorization Comes to Mac and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revamped-mail-app-with-built-in-categorization-comes-to-mac-and-ipad.2449915/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.4 Adds New Ambient Music Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-ambient-music/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-adds-new-ambient-music-feature.2449914/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:06:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-ambient-music/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18.4, there's a new Ambient Music option that can be added to Control Center. There are four different sound categories, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-ambient-music.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991311" /><br/>
Each category can be added to Control Center separately, and tapping one plays a random selection of sounds or music from that particular category.<br/>
<br/>
You can't choose what's playing from Control Center, but if you play a category and then tap into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> at the top or access the Now Playing widget, you can skip songs and see the name of what's currently playing.<br/>
<br/>
There is no dedicated app for the feature, but Apple has a hidden app that provides more control through skipping songs.<br/>
<br/>
Ambient Music is available on both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/ios-18-4-ambient-music/">iOS 18.4 Adds New Ambient Music Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-adds-new-ambient-music-feature.2449914/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple News+ Gains Recipes, Restaurant Reviews, and More in iOS 18.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-news-plus-food-ios-18-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-news-gains-recipes-restaurant-reviews-and-more-in-ios-18-4.2449913/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:36:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-news-plus-food-ios-18-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4, Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/02/apple-introduces-news-plus-food/">plans to introduce</a> new features for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a>+ subscription service. Apple is adding &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food, a section that features tens of thousands of recipes, stories about restaurants, tips for healthy eating, kitchen essentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-food-news.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991301" /><br/>
Content will come from top food publishers such as Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food &amp; Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; editors will curate food-related stories, and there will be a dedicated Recipe Catalog section where new recipes are added regularly. An included cook mode provides step-by-step instructions, and users can save favorite recipes for offline access.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ Food is coming to &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers with the launch of iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 in April.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-news-plus-food-ios-18-4/">Apple News+ Gains Recipes, Restaurant Reviews, and More in iOS 18.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-news-gains-recipes-restaurant-reviews-and-more-in-ios-18-4.2449913/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Beta of iOS 18.4 With New Vision Pro App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-ios-18-4-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-beta-of-ios-18-4-with-new-vision-pro-app.2449907/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:02:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-ios-18-4-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a month after Apple released iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984205" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Generic-iOS-18.4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 can be downloaded from the Settings app on a compatible device by going to General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.4 includes a dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> app, which will show up on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> if you have a Vision Pro headset that's also connected to your Apple Account. If you don't have a Vision Pro, it can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro app is designed to help users find content, get help, and learn about new Vision Pro features. It includes tools for adding content to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app to watch later, downloading apps remotely, and viewing information about the Vision Pro such as device serial number with a dedicated My Vision Pro section.<br/>
<br/>
There is a dedicated Discover page that offers curated recommendations for new experiences that are available on Vision Pro. Users can see popular apps and games, a list of more than 300 3D movies, Apple Immersive videos, Vision Pro video content on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app, and spatial photos, videos, and panoramas included in the new Spatial Gallery.<br/>
<br/>
With a My Vision Pro page, users can find tips for getting the most out of the Vision Pro, and set up features like vision correction and Personalized Spatial Audio.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/vision-pro-app-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991289" /><br/>
Guest setup for the Vision Pro can now be managed on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which makes it easier for Vision Pro owners to allow others to test the headset. There are controls for limiting what apps a guest can access, along with an option to view what the guest user is doing for guidance purposes. When a guest user puts on the Vision Pro, a prompt to enable Guest Mode will appear on the headset owner's device.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggested that iOS 18.4 would include new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features, but the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; options <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/14/apple-intelligence-siri-overhaul-could-get-delayed/">may be delayed</a>. Apple is reportedly running into engineering problems and software bugs, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is not yet working as intended, so there may be no new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features in the beta as of yet.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has promised &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will get personal context, on-screen awareness, and the ability to do more in and between apps. Apple also plans to expand &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; to additional languages in the iOS 18.4 update, so the new language support could be available. We're also still waiting on Priority Notifications, another &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; feature that Apple says is coming in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
With testing starting in late February, iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 are expected to see a launch in April.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-ios-18-4-beta-1/">Apple Releases First Beta of iOS 18.4 With New Vision Pro App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-beta-of-ios-18-4-with-new-vision-pro-app.2449907/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First visionOS 2.4 Beta With Apple Intelligence, Spatial Gallery and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-visionos-2-4-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-visionos-2-4-beta-with-apple-intelligence-spatial-gallery-and-more.2449906/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:02:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-visionos-2-4-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/02/apple-intelligence-comes-to-apple-vision-pro-in-april/">seeded the first beta</a> of an upcoming visionOS 2.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming almost a month after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/27/apple-releases-visionos-2-3/">launch of visionOS 2.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rF4GRFYcaM0" title="visionOS 2.4 Beta Out Now! A Big Update to Apple Vision Pro!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
visionOS 2.4 can be installed by going to the Software Update section of the Settings app on the Vision Pro and opting into Beta Updates. A developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.4 will be one of the most significant visionOS updates to date, because it brings <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> to the Vision Pro for the first time. Apple started rolling out &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac last year, but the Vision Pro was not included until now.<blockquote>"Apple Vision Pro is helping users communicate, collaborate, and experience entertainment in entirely new ways -- and we're continuing to push the boundaries of what's possible in spatial computing with visionOS 2.4," said Mike Rockwell, Apple's vice president of the Vision Products Group. "With Apple Intelligence, Vision Pro users will be able to take their productivity and creativity to new heights using features like Writing Tools, Image Playground, and Genmoji. And we're excited for users to discover and share incredible new experiences with Spatial Gallery."</blockquote>Apple Intelligence features that are accessible on the Vision Pro include Writing Tools for generating, proofreading, and summarizing text, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> for creating custom emoji characters, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> app for generating images, Memory Movie for creating custom slideshows, smart reply for generating quick responses to texts and emails, Priority Notifications and Notification Summaries, ChatGPT <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration and new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-wand/">Image Wand</a> for adding images to the Notes app, complete with gesture support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/visionos-2-4-apple-intelligence-writing-tools.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991277" /><br/>
Apple is debuting a dedicated Spatial Gallery app for the Vision Pro, which includes a curated selection of spatial videos, spatial photos, and panorama images from artists, filmmakers, and photographers. Apple plans to offer a range of content featuring sports, culture, arts, lifestyle, nature, travel, entertainment, and more. Content at launch includes images and experiences from Cirque du Soleil, Red Bull, Porsche, Samba Diop, and Jonpaul Douglass, along with behind the scenes content from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ shows.<br/>
<br/>
For Vision Pro management, there is a new Vision Pro app that's available on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The Vision Pro app is designed to help Vision Pro users discover new content, and it has a number of features. Users can get Vision Pro support and feature help, download apps to the Vision Pro, add content to a watch list, and get device info like serial number. The app will automatically download for iOS 18.4 users who have a Vision Pro headset, but it can also be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro app has a discover page that provides curated recommendations for new and noteworthy experiences. Users can see popular apps and games, including Apple Immersive titles.<br/>
<br/>
Most notably, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can now be used to set up the Guest Mode on the Vision Pro, which is a much more useful way to let people demo the headset than having to set it up on the Vision Pro itself. When a guest is ready to use the Vision Pro, a prompt will appear on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and the Vision Pro user can select what the guest can access and see what the guest is doing using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> to provide navigation guidance and content suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
Guests are able to save their eye and hand setup for up to 30 days after their last use.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to release visionOS 2.4 to the public in April.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-visionos-2-4-beta-1/">Apple Releases First visionOS 2.4 Beta With Apple Intelligence, Spatial Gallery and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-visionos-2-4-beta-with-apple-intelligence-spatial-gallery-and-more.2449906/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Beta of macOS Sequoia 15.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-4.2449905/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:01:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 update to developers, with the new update coming a month after Apple released &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
It's not yet clear what's included in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4, but the update is expected to feature new emoji characters and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> in additional languages. When we learn what's new in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4, we'll update this article. <br/>
<br/>
macOS 15.4 is set to be released in April. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-4/">Apple Seeds First Beta of macOS Sequoia 15.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sequoia-15-4.2449905/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Betas of tvOS 18.4 and watchOS 11.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-18-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-tvos-18-4-and-watchos-11-4.2449910/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-18-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the first betas of upcoming watchOS 11.4 and tvOS 18.4 updates for testing purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-developer-app-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-795934" /><br/>
The betas are available to registered developers, and can be downloaded from the Settings app on each device.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word yet on what's included in the new software, but should any new features be found, we'll update this article.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-tvos-18-4/">Apple Seeds First Betas of tvOS 18.4 and watchOS 11.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-betas-of-tvos-18-4-and-watchos-11-4.2449910/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Big Apple Watch Series 10 Discounts Hit Alongside AirPods and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-21-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-big-apple-watch-series-10-discounts-hit-alongside-airpods-and-more.2449902/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:47:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-21-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week we saw the return of a big sale on Apple Watch Series 10, plus numerous record low prices on iPad Pro, iPad Air, Apple Studio Display, and Apple Pencil Pro. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-new-purple-hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960078" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/airpods-4-new-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991268" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;30 off AirPods 4</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/airpods-4-for-all-time-low-price/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;148.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best AirPods deal this week was on the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation, which is available for &#36;148.99, down from &#36;179.00. This is just about &#36;10 higher compared to the lowest-ever price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-watch-series-10-new-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991270" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;70 off Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-watch-series-10-amazon-329/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ2QH6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon this week has <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ5KQL7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">numerous all-time low prices</a> on Apple Watch Series 10, including both GPS and cellular models. You'll find &#36;70 off both 42mm and 46mm GPS Series 10 models in multiple case colors and band styles, and this time the deals do not require any coupon codes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-pencil-pro-new-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991272" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;30 off Apple Pencil Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-pencil-pro-and-studio-display-deal/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Another all-time low price available on Amazon this week was on the Apple Pencil Pro, and it's still available for &#36;99.00 today, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/studio-display-new-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991273" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;299 off Apple Studio Display</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-pencil-pro-and-studio-display-deal/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Studio Display returned to its all-time low price of &#36;1,299.99 this week on Amazon, down from &#36;1,599.00. This is the Standard Glass model of the Studio Display, and right now it's the only model hitting a record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPads</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ipad-pro-new-purple.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991274" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;200 off iPad Pro, and iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.link/0na9oyivhj6s1">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/amazons-new-ipad-sale-air-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/0na9oyivhj6s1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cm5pPmQKHqy"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Pro for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon and Best Buy introduced numerous discounts across the iPad Air and iPad Pro lineup this week, with the return of best-ever prices on multiple models. iPad Air tablets start at &#36;499.00 and reach up to &#36;200 off, while iPad Pro tablets start at &#36;849.00 and also reach up to &#36;200 off. You can find more details about all of these deals <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/amazons-new-ipad-sale-air-pro/">in our original post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-21-25/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Big Apple Watch Series 10 Discounts Hit Alongside AirPods and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-big-apple-watch-series-10-discounts-hit-alongside-airpods-and-more.2449902/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16e Continues Apple&#039;s Transition to Manufacturing in India</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-made-in-india/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16e-continues-apples-transition-to-manufacturing-in-india.2449897/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 09:17:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-made-in-india/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16e</category>
		<category>India</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> will join the four other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models  in being made in India, Apple has revealed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-16e-USB-C-Port.jpg" alt="" width="1680" height="952" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-990934" /><br/>
<br/>
In a response to a query from India's <a href="https://economictimes.indiatimes.com/industry/cons-products/electronics/iphone-16e-being-assembled-in-india-for-local-sale-exports-to-select-countries/articleshow/118413654.cms"><em>Economic Times</em></a>, Apple said that "the entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup, including &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj;, is being assembled in India for Indian consumers and for export to select countries."<br/>
<br/>
In recent years, Apple has significantly increased its production footprint in the country. <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Apple-seeks-to-rely-less-on-China-by-building-iPhone-16e-in-India"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> suggests that the share of iPhones made in India will rise from around 15% today to 25% by 2027. The 16e is reportedly likely to be assembled on the same Indian production lines as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 14.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are the first high-end &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-to-manufacture-pro-iphone-models-in-india/">made in India</a>. Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/29/iphone-exports-india-surge/">exports from the country</a> reached nearly &#36;6 billion in the six months leading up to September 2024, representing a 33% increase compared to the same period last year. Apple is expected to begin <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/13/airpods-made-in-india-from-next-year/">production of AirPods in India</a> for the first time later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/india/">India</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16e">iPhone 16e (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-made-in-india/">iPhone 16e Continues Apple&#039;s Transition to Manufacturing in India</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16e-continues-apples-transition-to-manufacturing-in-india.2449897/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>An Apple Store is on the Move in the UK</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-trafford-centre-moving/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/an-apple-store-is-on-the-move-in-the-uk.2449892/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:42:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-trafford-centre-moving/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new Apple Store will be opening March 1 <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/retail/traffordcentre/">at the Trafford Centre</a> shopping mall outside of Manchester, in the United Kingdom.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Launch-Logo.jpg" alt="" width="1516" height="850" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991259" /><br/>
Apple's existing store at the mall will be permanently closed starting February 27.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not shared photos or details about the new Trafford Centre store, but you can expect a modern design that will likely include an Apple Pickup station for in-store pickup of orders that customers have placed on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Trafford Centre originally opened in 2005.<br/>
<br/>
In other store news, Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/apple-previews-miami-worldcenter-store/">opened a new store in Miami</a>, and it says <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/14/apple-store-downtown-detroit-coming-soon/">another store in Downtown Detroit is coming soon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="http://choreographics.me/">Filip Chudzinski</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-trafford-centre-moving/">An Apple Store is on the Move in the UK</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/an-apple-store-is-on-the-move-in-the-uk.2449892/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iPhone 16e Announced!</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16e/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16e-announced.2449891/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:42:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16e/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/apples-iphone-16e-love-it-or-hate-it/id1602394741?i=1000694785019">The MacRumors Show</a>, we unpack Apple's announcement of the all-new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9VXQOC9Id14?si=0sRYU6uQXupDRswz" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; is the newest member of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup, offering a massive upgrade over the now-discontinued third-generation &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; SE. It features a 6.1-inch OLED display with a notch for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, a Ceramic Shield front cover, a USB-C port, and an Action button, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
It is powered by an A18 chip, enabling support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features, such as notification summaries and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> for creating custom emoji. It also supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj;, the A18 chip has a 6-core CPU and a 16-core Neural Engine, but a binned 4-core GPU, making it slightly less powerful than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus. It also has IP68-rated water resistance, Wi-Fi 6, and Bluetooth 5.3. <br/>
<br/>
The device is equipped with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">Apple-designed 5G modem called the C1</a>, whereas other iPhones have a Qualcomm modem. Apple says its own modem is so power efficient that the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; offers the longest battery life of any 6.1-inch &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model ever at up to 26 hours.<br/>
<br/>
On the back of the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; is a single 48-megapixel Fusion camera, which provides a 2x "optical-quality" Telephoto option, according to Apple. On the front, there is a 12-megapixel camera with autofocus. The device does not have the Camera Control button that was introduced across the rest of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup last year. It also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/iphone-16e-doesnt-have-magsafe/">lacks MagSafe</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; supports Apple's satellite features. When outside of cellular and Wi-Fi coverage, the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; supports Emergency SOS, Roadside Assistance, Messages, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> via satellite. <br/>
<br/>
The device is available in white or black, and with 128GB, 256GB, or 512GB storage capacities. In the U.S., pricing starts at &#36;599. <br/>
<br/>
We talk through how the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; compares to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, which sit at &#36;699 and &#36;799, respectively. We also contemplate what the discontinuation of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; SE line means for the rumored third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, which is rumored to launch later this year. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/the-macrumors-show-invites-app/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the imminent Apple product "launch" that is widely expected to be the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; SE.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/15/the-macrumors-show-apple-pro-apps-updates/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/the-macrumors-show-jon-prosser-talks-m4-macs/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16e/">The MacRumors Show: iPhone 16e Announced!</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-16e-announced.2449891/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Denies Speculation Surrounding iPhone 16e&#039;s Lack of MagSafe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-no-magsafe-unrelated-to-c1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-denies-speculation-surrounding-iphone-16es-lack-of-magsafe.2449889/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 08:01:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-no-magsafe-unrelated-to-c1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16e</category>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has confirmed that its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">custom-designed C1 modem</a> in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-announces-iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a> has nothing to do with the device's lack of MagSafe support, <a href="https://www.macworld.com/article/2614585/iphone-16e-without-magsafe-apple-modem-c1-is-the-reason.html">according to <em>Macworld</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-16e-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990895" /><br/>
Following the launch of the iPhone 16e, there was some speculation online about how MagSafe magnets might have interfered with the C1 modem's cellular connectivity performance, and this was considered to be a potential reason for the device not supporting MagSafe. But, that explanation is not true, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
From the report:<blockquote><strong>Update 11:18am ET:</strong> Apple has confirmed to Macworld that the C1 modem is not responsible for the decision to leave MagSafe charging off the new iPhone 16e.</blockquote>A well-known iPhone case maker told <em>MacRumors</em> that it completed testing that confirmed MagSafe cases do not impact the C1 modem's performance.<br/>
<br/>
So, why does the iPhone 16e lack MagSafe? Apple has not disclosed its actual reasoning, but we would wager that it simply comes down to pricing considerations.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-now-available-for-pre-order-ahead-of-february-28-launch/">iPhone 16e pre-ordering</a> started today, and the device launches Friday, February 28.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16e">iPhone 16e (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-16e-no-magsafe-unrelated-to-c1/">Apple Denies Speculation Surrounding iPhone 16e&#039;s Lack of MagSafe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-denies-speculation-surrounding-iphone-16es-lack-of-magsafe.2449889/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pulls Encrypted iCloud Security Feature in UK Amid Government Backdoor Demands</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-uk/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-in-uk-amid-government-backdoor-demands.2449885/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 07:17:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-uk/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has withdrawn its Advanced Data Protection iCloud feature from the United Kingdom following government demands for backdoor access to encrypted user data, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-21/apple-removes-end-to-end-encryption-feature-from-uk-after-backdoor-order"><em>Bloomberg</em></a>. The move comes after UK officials secretly ordered Apple to provide unrestricted access to encrypted iCloud content worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iCloud-Versus-UK-Key-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988727" /><br/>
Customers who are already using Advanced Data Protection, or ADP, will need to manually disable it during an unspecified grace period to keep their iCloud accounts, according to the report. Apple said it will issue additional guidance in the future to affected users and that it "does not have the ability to automatically disable it on their behalf."<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/07/uk-government-orders-access-icloud/">UK government's demand</a> came through a "technical capability notice" under the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), requiring Apple to create a backdoor that would allow British security officials to access encrypted user data globally. The order would have compromised Apple's Advanced Data Protection feature, which provides end-to-end encryption for iCloud data including Photos, Notes, Messages backups, and device backups.<br/>
<blockquote>"We are gravely disappointed that the protections provided by ADP will not be available to our customers in the UK given the continuing rise of data breaches and other threats to customer privacy," Apple said in a statement. "ADP protects iCloud data with end-to-end encryption, which means the data can only be decrypted by the user who owns it, and only on their trusted devices."</blockquote>Apple's decision to pull the feature rather than comply with the UK's demands is consistent with the company's previous statements that it would consider withdrawing encrypted services from the UK rather than compromise security. Apple has long opposed creating backdoors in its products, maintaining that such access points would inevitably be discovered by malicious actors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/advanced-data-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1072" height="388" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991218" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Notice UK iCloud users now see after the feature was pulled</em></div><br/>
The UK order was particularly controversial as it would have required Apple to provide access to data from users outside the UK without their governments' knowledge. Additionally, the IPA makes it illegal for companies to disclose the existence of such government demands.<br/>
<br/>
US security agencies, including the FBI and NSA, have been advocating for increased use of encryption to protect against Chinese cyber threats, creating potential conflicts between UK and US security interests.<br/>
<br/>
"Enhancing the security of cloud storage with end-to-end encryption is more urgent than ever before,” said Apple on Friday, per <em>Bloomberg</em>. The company added that it "remains committed to offering our users the highest level of security for their personal data and are hopeful that we will be able to do so in the future in the United Kingdom."<br/>
<br/>
Note that the loss of Advanced Data Protection in the UK does not affect the existing end-to-end encryption of several other Apple features available in the country, including iMessage, FaceTime, password management and health data.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-uk/">Apple Pulls Encrypted iCloud Security Feature in UK Amid Government Backdoor Demands</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-encrypted-icloud-security-feature-in-uk-amid-government-backdoor-demands.2449885/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All Four iPhone 17 Models Said to Feature Apple-Designed Wi-Fi 7 Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-17-models-said-to-feature-apple-designed-wi-fi-7-chip.2449882/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 06:58:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Pro</category>
		<category>Jeff Pu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this week, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said all four iPhone 17 models will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/kuo-iphone-17-models-apple-designed-wi-fi-7-chip/">equipped with Apple's first-ever custom-designed Wi-Fi chip</a>. He did not say which Wi-Fi version the chip will support, but it appears that it will be Wi-Fi 7.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-Wi-Fi-Chip-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883034" /><br/>
All four iPhone 17 models will feature an Apple-designed Wi-Fi 7 chip, according to Jeff Pu, an analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain. He shared this information in a research note with GF Securities earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
The entire iPhone 16 lineup already supports Wi-Fi 7, so this is not much of a surprise, but the fact that the chip will be designed by Apple is notable. Apple recently debuted its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apple-says-c1-modem-is-just-the-start/">custom-designed C1 modem</a> in the iPhone 16e, for cellular connectivity, and now the company is expected to debut an in-house Wi-Fi chip in the iPhone 17 models later this year. By designing more of its own chips, Apple can reduce and eventually eliminate its reliance on external suppliers, including Qualcomm for modems and Broadcom for Wi-Fi chips.<br/>
<br/>
Wi-Fi 7 allows for data transmission over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously with a supported router, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. Wi-Fi 7 can provide peak speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E, if a device supports the maximum specifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil the iPhone 17 lineup in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-pu/">Jeff Pu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/">All Four iPhone 17 Models Said to Feature Apple-Designed Wi-Fi 7 Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-four-iphone-17-models-said-to-feature-apple-designed-wi-fi-7-chip.2449882/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
