<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 03:03:18 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Launches Office 2024 for Mac and PC</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/microsoft-launches-office-2024-mac-pc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-launches-office-2024-for-mac-and-pc.2438897/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 02:41:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/microsoft-launches-office-2024-mac-pc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft Office</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft this week <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/blog/2024/09/30/office-2024-for-consumers-available-october-1/">announced</a> Office 2024, a new standalone version of its productivity suite for both Mac and PC users. Available now, Office 2024 offers an alternative for those who prefer a one-time purchase over the subscription-based Microsoft 365.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/microsoft-office-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="1620" height="846" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969005" /><br/>
The new release includes updated versions of Word, Excel, PowerPoint, OneNote, and Outlook. These applications come as "locked-in-time" versions, meaning they won't receive ongoing feature updates like their Microsoft 365 counterparts.<br/>
<br/>
For Mac users, Office 2024 brings several notable improvements, according to Microsoft. Excel now boasts faster performance, particularly when working with multiple open workbooks. Meanwhile, Outlook for Mac introduces customizable swipe gestures that are designed to enhance email management and work with Magic Trackpad and Magic Mouse.<br/>
<br/>
PowerPoint gains new features such as "cameo," which allows users to embed a live camera feed directly into slides, and "recording studio" for capturing narration, animations, transitions, and inking. Elsewhere, Word and PowerPoint now support liking and reacting to comments in collaborative documents.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft say Mac users will also benefit from an enhanced inking experience in OneNote, including a full-screen pen-focused view. Additionally, the suite now supports version 1.4 of the OpenDocument format (ODF) across Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.<br/>
<br/>
Office 2024 is compatible with macOS Ventura, macOS Sonoma, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>. The suite of apps requires both a Microsoft account and an internet connection for installation and activation. Two editions are available: Office Home 2024, priced at &#36;149.99, includes Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and OneNote. Office Home & Business 2024, at &#36;249.99, adds Outlook and includes commercial use rights. Both editions are available now from retailers worldwide and via the <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/">Microsoft website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While Office 2024 provides a non-subscription option, Microsoft continues to position Microsoft 365 as the recommended choice for those seeking the latest features and regular updates. However, the standalone Office 2024 offers a familiar alternative for Mac users who prefer a traditional licensing model.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft-office/">Microsoft Office</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/microsoft-launches-office-2024-mac-pc/">Microsoft Launches Office 2024 for Mac and PC</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-launches-office-2024-for-mac-and-pc.2438897/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Rolls Out New Filters and Backgrounds for Video Calls</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/whatsapp-new-filters-backgrounds-video-calls/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-new-filters-and-backgrounds-for-video-calls.2438893/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:49:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/whatsapp-new-filters-backgrounds-video-calls/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp has <a href="https://blog.whatsapp.com/introducing-filters-and-backgrounds-for-video-calls">announced</a> it is rolling out new filters and backgrounds for users to personalize their video calls. The popular chat platform said the new effects are designed to make video conversations "more engaging" and give them a "more personal touch."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/whatsapp-filters-backgrounds-video-calls.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968997" /><br/>
The update includes 10 filters and 10 backgrounds that users can apply to improve their video calling experience. Filters range from classic options like "Black & White" and "Vintage TV" to more artistic effects such as "Light leak" and "Prism light." Background choices offer variety, from practical settings like "Office" and "Cafe" to scenic options like "Beach" and "Sunset."<br/>
<br/>
In addition to filters and backgrounds, WhatsApp is introducing "Touch up" and "Low Light" options. These features are aimed at enhancing the user's appearance and improving video quality in suboptimal lighting conditions, potentially avoiding embarrassment during calls.<br/>
<br/>
To access these new effects, users can select the effects icons located in the top right corner of the screen during a video call. The functionality will be available for both one-on-one and group video calls. The new filters and backgrounds are expected to be available to all WhatsApp users in the coming weeks. <br/>
<br/>
The introduction of new video call effects follows the rollout in August of a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/whatsapp-rolls-out-events-group-chats/">event planning feature</a> that lets WhatsApp users organize events, meetings, and social gatherings directly within a group chat.  <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/02/whatsapp-new-filters-backgrounds-video-calls/">WhatsApp Rolls Out New Filters and Backgrounds for Video Calls</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-new-filters-and-backgrounds-for-video-calls.2438893/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Promises to Recommit to Software Quality and Customer Experience After App Disaster</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/sonos-customer-service-software-quality/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-promises-to-recommit-to-software-quality-and-customer-experience-after-app-disaster.2438870/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/sonos-customer-service-software-quality/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/blog/commitments">today announced</a> a series of new commitments that are meant to demonstrate the company's "renewed focus" on software quality and customer experience. The announcement and an accompanying video from Sonos CEO Patrick Spence come as Sonos tries to ameliorate the negative experience customers have had with the May Sonos app update.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Recommitting to Quality and Customer Experience" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JWvJYeG5kfY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Going forward, Sonos says that it isn't just going to fix its app mistake, but also build a better Sonos experience. To that end, Sonos made seven pledges:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Unwavering focus on customer experience with ambitious quality benchmarks, and a promise to not launch products that don't meet the standards customers expect.</li><br/>
 	<li>More stringent pre-launch testing with a broader range of customers to resolve issues before new software comes out.</li><br/>
 	<li>No more all-at-once app releases. Any new major changes to the Sonos app will be released gradually, and customers will be able to opt-in to test new features before they become default.</li><br/>
 	<li>There will be a new Quality Ombudsperson role that will give employees a clear path to raise concerns regarding quality and customer experience.</li><br/>
 	<li>Home speaker products currently under warranty will have their warranty extended for an additional year.</li><br/>
 	<li>App updates will come every two to four weeks to "optimize and enhance" the app experience. This includes after the current issues are fixed.</li><br/>
 	<li>Sonos is establishing a Customer Advisory Board to provide feedback and insights from a customer perspective to shape and improve products before they launch.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Sonos says that its Executive Leadership Team will not accept any bonus payout for the October 2024 to September 2025 fiscal year unless Sonos is able to improve the quality of the app and rebuild customer trust.<br/>
<br/>
According to Sonos, more than 80 percent of the missing features from the app have now been reintroduced, and the company expects to be at close to 100 percent in the coming weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Recent reports have suggested that Sonos employees <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/sonos-app-development-insight/">raised an alarm</a> prior to when the redesigned Sonos app launched in May. The app was an immediate disappointment to customers because it was riddled with bugs and missing many key Sonos features, and there was significant outcry over the downgrade. Sonos was not able to roll back the changes, and has spent 2024 trying to fix the app.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos has delayed new product launches to focus on software, and as a result, will miss its annual revenue target by &#36;200 million.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/sonos-customer-service-software-quality/">Sonos Promises to Recommit to Software Quality and Customer Experience After App Disaster</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-promises-to-recommit-to-software-quality-and-customer-experience-after-app-disaster.2438870/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Halide Maker Does Deep Dive Into iPhone 16 Pro Camera</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-iphone-16-pro-camera-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-maker-does-deep-dive-into-iphone-16-pro-camera.2438864/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:24:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-iphone-16-pro-camera-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Halide</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Each year, the developers behind well-known <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> camera app Halide take an in-depth look at the new camera technology that Apple has introduced. This year, Sebastiaan de With <a href="https://www.lux.camera/the-iphone-16-pro-camera-review-control/">took more than 1,000 photos</a> with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> to examine changes to the camera setup, Apple's image processing, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/halide-iphone-16-pro-review.jpg" alt="" width="1982" height="1116" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968873" /><br/>
Apple added an upgraded 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera to the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models this year. De With found it to take photos that have "impressive sharpness," but Apple did not add a larger sensor, so you're still not going to get the level of detail that you get with the Wide camera, which has a much bigger sensor.<br/>
<br/>
For macro photos, the 48-megapixel lens "does wonders" for up-close shots. In prior iPhones, the Ultra Wide was cropping in from a 12-megapixel photo, which meant you ended up with an image that was approximately three megapixels. With the 48-megapixel lens, cropping in provides a true 12-megapixel image with more detail.<br/>
<br/>
As for the Main camera, which Apple now calls the "Fusion" camera, it is using a sensor that is the same physical size as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro sensor. While both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; have a "Fusion" camera, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; has a larger and higher quality sensor. As with the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; combines pixels and can produce better 24-megapixel and 12-megapixel images using that data, in addition to full 48-megapixel photos. Processing is about the same as last year, and there is little difference between images captured with the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; with the standard Wide camera.<br/>
<br/>
There are some notable internal changes that speed up image capture. The Apple Camera Interface provides faster sensor readout times for improvements to QuickTake. QuickTake also supports 4K Dolby Vision HDR, which is a noticeable improvement, according to de With. Capturing 48-megapixel ProRAW images is also a lot faster with quicker shutter speeds, and there's little delay.<br/>
<br/>
For those interested in more info on everything new with the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; related to photography, including Camera Control, the Telephoto lens, Night mode, and more, <a href="https://www.lux.camera/the-iphone-16-pro-camera-review-control/">the full Halide review</a> is well worth a read.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/halide/">Halide</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-iphone-16-pro-camera-review/">Halide Maker Does Deep Dive Into iPhone 16 Pro Camera</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-maker-does-deep-dive-into-iphone-16-pro-camera.2438864/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta is Probably Training AI on Images Taken by Meta Ray-Bans</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/meta-ray-bans-ai-training/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-is-probably-training-ai-on-images-taken-by-meta-ray-bans.2438861/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:59:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/meta-ray-bans-ai-training/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Facebook</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Facebook parent company Meta last week <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2024/09/ray-ban-meta-glasses-new-ai-features-and-partner-integrations/">added new AI features</a> to its camera-equipped Ray-Ban Meta Glasses. You can use the camera feature on the glasses to get information about what's around you and to remember things like where you parked. There's also now support for video for AI purposes, for "continuous real-time help."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/meta-ray-bans.jpg" alt="" width="1724" height="970" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968917" /><br/>
With all of these new features that involve the camera continually viewing what's around the wearer, there are new questions about what Meta is doing with that data. <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/09/30/meta-wont-say-whether-it-trains-ai-on-ray-ban-meta-smart-glasses-photos/">TechCrunch</a></em> specifically asked Meta if it was using the images collected by the Meta Glasses to train AI models, and Meta declined to say.<br/>
<br/>
"We're not publicly discussing that," Anuj Kumar told <em>TechCrunch</em>. Kumar is a senior director that works on AI wearables. "That's not something we typically share externally," another spokesperson said. When asked for clarification on whether images are being used to train AI, the spokesperson said "we're not saying either way."<br/>
<br/>
<em>TechCrunch</em> doesn't come out and say it, but if the answer is not a clear and definitive "no," it's likely that Meta does indeed plan to use images captured by the Meta Glasses to train Meta AI. If that wasn't the case, it doesn't seem like there would be a reason for Meta to be ambiguous about answering, especially with all of the public commentary on the methods and data that companies use for training.<br/>
<br/>
Meta does train its AI on publicly posted Instagram and Facebook images and stories, which it considers publicly available data. But data collected from the Meta Ray-Ban Glasses that's specifically for interacting with AI in private isn't the same as a publicly posted Instagram image, and it's concerning.<br/>
<br/>
As <em>TechCrunch</em> notes, the new AI features for the Meta Glasses are going to be capturing a lot of passive images to feed to AI to answer questions about the wearer's surroundings. Asking the Meta Glasses for help picking an outfit, for example, will see dozens of images of the inside of the wearer's home captured, with those images uploaded to the cloud.<br/>
<br/>
The Meta Glasses have always been used for images and video, but in an active way. You generally know when you're capturing a photo or video because it's for the express purpose of uploading to social media or saving a memory, as with any camera. With AI, though, you aren't keeping those images because they're being collected for the express purpose of interacting with the AI assistant.<br/>
<br/>
Meta is definitively not confirming what happens to images from the Meta Glasses that are uploaded to its cloud servers for AI use, and that's something Meta Glasses owners should be aware of. Using these new AI features could result in Meta collecting hundreds of private photos that wearers had no intention or awareness of sharing.<br/>
<br/>
If Meta is in fact not using the Meta Glasses this way, it should explicitly state that so customers can be aware of exactly what's being shared with Meta and what that is being used for.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facebook/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/meta-ray-bans-ai-training/">Meta is Probably Training AI on Images Taken by Meta Ray-Bans</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-is-probably-training-ai-on-images-taken-by-meta-ray-bans.2438861/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-beta-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware.2438860/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:55:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-beta-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new beta firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, with the software available for both the Lightning and USB-C versions of the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;. The firmware has a build number of 7B5013c, and as it is a beta, it is only available for developers at the current time. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803705" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/AirPods-Pro-Beta-Firmware.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1081" /><br/>
It is not clear what's included in the firmware update at this time, but Apple is planning to introduce hearing aid and hearing test functionality for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 sometime this year. <br/>
<br/>
While the current firmware is limited to developers right now, it will be released for all &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 users in the future. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-2-usb-c-beta-firmware/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Beta Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware.2438860/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Debuts Photoshop and Premiere Elements 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/adobe-premiere-photoshop-elements-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-debuts-photoshop-and-premiere-elements-2025.2438857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:26:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/adobe-premiere-photoshop-elements-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Adobe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Adobe today unveiled new versions of <a href="https://www.adobe.com/products/photoshop-premiere-elements/whats-new.html">Photoshop Elements and Premiere Elements</a>, the company's affordable photo and video editing software aimed at users who want to enhance their photos and videos with simple editing tools.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/photoshop-premiere-elements-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968926" /><br/>
Photoshop Elements 2025 incorporates multiple new AI-powered tools to make editing quicker than ever. There's a new Remove tool that lets users select an area in the image to remove with a brush, plus it is accompanied by an Object Removal Guided Edit.<br/>
<br/>
There's also an option to change the color of objects in an image by selecting them with the automatic selection tools and then choosing a new color.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/photoshop-elements-remove-object.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="628" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968928" /><br/>
A new Depth Blur filter adds blur to images to mimic a depth of field effect, with controls for adjusting blur strength, focal distance, and focal range. It's a useful way to change the focus of an image.<br/>
<br/>
There is a Combine <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> Guided Edit that walks users through blending the subject from one image and the background from another to create an all-new image. It can use parts of multiple photos for unique looks.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include options for textured photo backgrounds and graphics and a one-click option for adding effects like camera motion, animated sparkles, or an animated frame.<br/>
<br/>
Premiere Elements 2025 has several new features for videos. There's a new White Balance tool for adjusting the look of clouds, snow, and similar white elements, plus there are new color correction Curves for making more precise color and brightness adjustments.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/premiere-elements-change-color.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="628" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968930" /><br/>
There are additional templates for dynamic titles with more control over text alignment, size, color, and spacing. There are preset LUTs for tweaking color, and a simplified Timeline speeds up editing.<br/>
<br/>
For both Photoshop and Premiere Elements, there are enhancements for Macs with the new M3 chip, so the software will run faster on new M3 machines.<br/>
<br/>
Photoshop and Premiere Elements are priced at &#36;100 each individually, with a bundle available for &#36;150. More information is <a href="https://www.adobe.com/products/photoshop-premiere-elements/whats-new.html">available on Adobe's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/adobe/">Adobe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/adobe-premiere-photoshop-elements-2025/">Adobe Debuts Photoshop and Premiere Elements 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-debuts-photoshop-and-premiere-elements-2025.2438857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Microsoft Discontinuing Mixed Reality HoloLens 2 Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/microsoft-discontinues-hololens-2-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-discontinuing-mixed-reality-hololens-2-headset.2438855/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 15:07:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/microsoft-discontinues-hololens-2-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft is planning to discontinue its mixed reality HoloLens 2 headsets, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.uploadvr.com/microsoft-discontinuing-hololens-2/">UploadVR</a></em>. Production on the HoloLens 2 is ending, and sales will cease when stock runs out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/microsoft-hololens-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968878" /><br/>
Security updates will be provided until December 31, 2027, but after that point, Microsoft plans to end software support for the HoloLens 2.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft was one of the first companies to delve into mixed reality technology, and it introduced the original HoloLens in 2016, following up with the HoloLens 2 in 2019. The HoloLens headsets have always been expensive and Microsoft has targeted them to enterprise customers rather than the general public.<br/>
<br/>
At the current time, Microsoft does not appear to have plans for another HoloLens headset. There were rumors of a version three back in 2022, but work was <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/microsoft-hololens-3-metaverse-mixed-reality-strategy-confusion-rivalries-2022-2">reportedly canceled</a> due to a lack of focus and internal hardware development challenges. Microsoft has also been downsizing its mixed reality team in 2023 and 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft does apparently plan to continue supporting its HoloLens IVAS, which stands for integrated visual augmentation system. It is an AR headset that Microsoft is creating for the U.S. Army, and it is set to be tested in early 2025 to determine its feasibility for full-scale production.<br/>
<br/>
As Microsoft has been winding down its work on the HoloLens, it has partnered with Meta to bring Xbox Cloud Gaming and its Office apps to the Quest headsets, and it is also working on Windows 11 integration with the Quest.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Vision Pro headset has been marketed to both consumers and enterprise customers unlike the HoloLens, but it currently shares some of the same shortcomings, such as a high price tag. Apple is not yet ready to abandon mixed reality, and there is another version of the Vision Pro in the works. A second AR/VR headset could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/27/kuo-apple-vision-pro-m5-chip-apple-intelligence/">come as soon as 2025</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/microsoft-discontinues-hololens-2-headset/">Microsoft Discontinuing Mixed Reality HoloLens 2 Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microsoft-discontinuing-mixed-reality-hololens-2-headset.2438855/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Juno YouTube App for Vision Pro Removed From App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/juno-vision-pro-removed-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/juno-youtube-app-for-vision-pro-removed-from-app-store.2438853/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:38:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/juno-vision-pro-removed-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Juno, an app designed for watching YouTube on the Vision Pro, has been removed from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, developer Christian Selig <a href="https://christianselig.com/2024/10/juno-removed/">said today</a>. Back in April, YouTube emailed Selig and said that Juno was violating the YouTube Terms of Service and the YouTube API by modifying the native YouTube.com web user interface, and used YouTube trademarks and iconography that could be confusing to customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/juno-removed-from-app-store.jpg" alt="" width="1951" height="1097" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968969" /><br/>
In response, Selig switched from using the embed player to the website player, made it clear that Juno was an unofficial YouTube viewer, and explained to YouTube that as a web viewer, Juno is not using YouTube APIs. At the same time, though, YouTube filed a complaint with the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and Selig went on to warn customers that he would not fight Google on any decision regarding Juno.<br/>
<br/>
Juno has now been removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; by Apple in response to YouTube's complaint. Selig says that he does not agree with the decision because Juno is a simple web view and that that modifies CSS to make the player look more "visionOS like," but he does not plan to appeal the decision.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/juno-1-1-youtube.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936542" /><br/>
Selig, for those unaware, was the developer of the Reddit app Apollo, and he faced a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/30/apollo-app-shutting-down-today/">public fight with Reddit</a> over its third-party API changes and fees last year. The dispute ultimately ended up with Apollo shutting down. According to Selig, Juno was just a fun hobby project.<br/>
<blockquote>Juno was a fun hobby project for me to build. As a developer I wanted to get some experience building for the Vision Pro, and as a user I wanted a nice way to watch YouTube on this cool new device. As a result, I really enjoyed building Juno, but it was always something I saw as fundamentally a little app I built for fun.</blockquote><br/>
YouTube does not have a dedicated app for the Vision Pro, which is why Selig designed and released Juno <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/juno-app-youtube-apple-vision-pro/">last February</a>. Prior to when the Vision Pro launched, YouTube said that it would not develop a Vision Pro app, nor would it allow the YouTube <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> app to run on the headset. With Juno removed, those who want to watch YouTube on Vision Pro will need to use Safari.<br/>
<br/>
Juno for YouTube was priced at &#36;4.99, and Selig says that customers who purchased the app should still be able to use it even though it's been removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/juno-vision-pro-removed-app-store/">Juno YouTube App for Vision Pro Removed From App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/juno-youtube-app-for-vision-pro-removed-from-app-store.2438853/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Home Depot Launches Smart Glass Doors That Turn From Clear to Opaque</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/home-depot-smart-glass-doors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/home-depot-launches-smart-glass-doors-that-turn-from-clear-to-opaque.2438850/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:15:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/home-depot-smart-glass-doors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Home Deport</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Home Depot today launched new <a href="https://www.homedepot.com/b/Featured-Products-Smart-Glass-Door/N-5yc1vZ2fkpfet">Smart Glass Door options</a> that are able to transform from clear glass to opaque glass with a smartphone app, providing versatility for customers who want to be able to block light or people from seeing inside a home at select times of the day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/home-depot-smart-door.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968966" /><br/>
The Smart Glass Doors are made by Feather River Doors and are powered through Hubspace, a smart home app that integrates with several products sold by Home Depot, including light bulbs, ceiling fans, blinds, outlets, and locks.<br/>
<br/>
The Smart Glass Doors can be controlled with an app that's available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but there is no <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> integration or support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, which is a major downside for people who have a &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; setup. There is, however, support for Alexa and Google voice control.<br/>
<br/>
When activated, the glass in the door is able to change from clear to privacy, which is a more opaque look. The glass is laminated for energy efficiency, and the door itself is made from fiberglass filled with high density polyurethane foam. It is unpainted, so it can be painted to match a home.<br/>
<br/>
There are several models with different amounts of glass, with pricing that starts at &#36;800. The doors will be available in select Home Depot stores starting on October 28.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-deport/">Home Deport</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/home-depot-smart-glass-doors/">Home Depot Launches Smart Glass Doors That Turn From Clear to Opaque</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/home-depot-launches-smart-glass-doors-that-turn-from-clear-to-opaque.2438850/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Celebrating &#039;Mindful Month&#039; With October 10 Apple Watch Activity Challenge</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-mindful-month-activity-challenge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-mindful-month-with-october-10-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2438848/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:02:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-mindful-month-activity-challenge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will hold a new "Mindful Month" Apple Watch Activity Challenge that is set to take place on October 10. It is meant to bring awareness to caring for mental health.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-watch-mindful-month-activity-challenge.jpg" alt="" width="786" height="442" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968950" /><br/>
<blockquote>Let's bring awareness to all the ways we can take care of our mental health. On October 10, record 10 mindful minutes with any app that adds to Health to get this award.</blockquote><br/>
Like all Activity Challenges, the Mindful Month event will come with animated stickers that can be used in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/mindful_month_2024_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968945" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/mindful_month_2024_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968944" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/mindful_month_2024_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968943" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/mindful_month_2024_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968942" /><br/>
Mindful Month appears to be a new addition to the Apple Watch Activity Challenge lineup. Apple's last Activity Challenge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/national-parks-activity-challenge-august-25/">took place in August</a> for National Park Day.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-mindful-month-activity-challenge/">Apple Celebrating &#039;Mindful Month&#039; With October 10 Apple Watch Activity Challenge</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-mindful-month-with-october-10-apple-watch-activity-challenge.2438848/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Pro, iMac, and Redesigned Mac Mini With M4 Chips on Track to Launch &#039;This Year&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m4-macs-reportedly-on-track-for-this-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-imac-and-redesigned-mac-mini-with-m4-chips-on-track-to-launch-this-year.2438847/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:57:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m4-macs-reportedly-on-track-for-this-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release new MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini models with the M4 series of chips "this year," according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-01/apple-readies-iphone-se-4-upgraded-ipad-air-for-early-2025"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-wwdc-2022-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878408" /><br/>
Gurman initially said these Macs would likely be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-ipad-mini-rumored-for-october/">during a virtual event this October</a>, but he has been more vague about the timing lately, with wording such as "in the coming weeks" and now merely "this year." In any case, it is clear that he expects the first Macs with M4 chips to be introduced before the calendar turns to 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last updated the MacBook Pro and iMac lines during a virtual event <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">on October 30 last year</a>, while the Mac mini was last updated in January last year.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, the M4 chip already exists in the latest iPad Pro models, which launched in May. Geekbench 6 benchmark results showed the M4 chip offers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/m4-ipad-pro-cpu-benchmark/">up to 25% faster multi-core CPU performance</a> compared to the M3 chip found in several current Macs. The M4 chip is available with up to a 10-core CPU, whereas the M3 chip has an 8-core CPU. Apple has yet to announce higher-end M4 Pro and M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we reiterate what has been rumored for these first M4 Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
Apple plans to announce updated 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/15/m4-macs-and-new-ipads-at-next-apple-event/">in the coming weeks</a>, according to Gurman. No design changes have been rumored for the laptops this year, with improvements such as an OLED display and thinner design not expected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/macbook-pro-wont-switch-to-oled-in-2025-rumor/">until 2026 at the earliest</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last redesigned the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro in 2021, and the latest models with M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips were released last October.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iMac</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946085" /><br/>
Apple also plans to update the iMac with the M4 chip in the coming weeks, according to Gurman. No design changes are expected for the desktop computer.<br/>
<br/>
An unanswered question: Will the Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad accessories for the iMac finally switch from Lightning to USB-C this year?<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Mac mini</h2><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/M4-Mac-mini-Black-Ortho-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961271" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini</em></div><br/>
Gurman expects the Mac mini to be updated with M4 and M4 Pro chips in the coming weeks, and he said the desktop computer will be redesigned to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">become nearly as small as an Apple TV</a>. The new Mac mini will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/mac-mini-to-lose-usb-a-ports-later-this-year/">apparently lack USB-A ports</a>, and instead <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/mac-mini-5-usb-c-ports-leak/">feature five USB-C ports</a>, including two on the front of the computer.<br/>
<br/>
This would be the Mac mini's first major redesign since 2010.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m4-macs-reportedly-on-track-for-this-year/">MacBook Pro, iMac, and Redesigned Mac Mini With M4 Chips on Track to Launch &#039;This Year&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-imac-and-redesigned-mac-mini-with-m4-chips-on-track-to-launch-this-year.2438847/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE With Apple Intelligence, New iPad Air, and More Reportedly Launching &#039;Early Next Year&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-with-apple-intelligence-new-ipad-air-and-more-reportedly-launching-early-next-year.2438836/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:38:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release a new iPhone SE with Apple Intelligence support, new iPad Air models, and an updated Magic Keyboard for the iPad Air at some point "early next year," according to a report today from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-01/apple-readies-iphone-se-4-upgraded-ipad-air-for-early-2025"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
The next iPhone SE will have a similar design as the iPhone 14, including an edge-to-edge screen with a notch, according to Gurman. This means the device will likely support Face ID, whereas the current iPhone SE has a Touch ID button. As mentioned, he also expects the device to support Apple Intelligence, which is currently available on the iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, and any of the new iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad Air models will apparently have "internal improvements," but Gurman did not provide any specific details. He also expects an updated version of the Magic Keyboard for both the 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Air, with some of the new features previously introduced on the latest iPad Pro version of the keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ipad-air-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967393" /><br/>
March and April are common months for Apple to announce new iPhone SE and iPad Air models, with a virtual event or press releases both possibilities.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last updated the iPhone SE in March 2022, while the iPad Air lineup was last updated in May this year with the M2 chip and a first-ever 13-inch model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">iPhone SE With Apple Intelligence, New iPad Air, and More Reportedly Launching &#039;Early Next Year&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-with-apple-intelligence-new-ipad-air-and-more-reportedly-launching-early-next-year.2438836/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third visionOS 2.1 Update to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-visionos-2-1-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-visionos-2-1-update-to-developers.2438819/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:11:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-visionos-2-1-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming visionOS 2.1 update to developers for testing purposes, with the new software coming a week after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/apple-seeds-visionos-2-1-beta-2/">second visionOS 2.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app on their device, going to the Software Update Section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on what's included in visionOS 2.1, but there are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> features that Apple has not yet released, such as the option to use a larger ultrawide screen for the Mac Virtual Display and support for Multiview for MLS and MLB games.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-visionos-2-1-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third visionOS 2.1 Update to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-visionos-2-1-update-to-developers.2438819/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 11.1 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-3-to-developers-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-11-1-to-developers.2438818/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:11:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-3-to-developers-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 11.1 update to developers for testing purposes. The third beta comes a week after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/apple-seeds-watchos-11-1-beta-2/">second watchOS 11.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Activities-Day-of-the-Week.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956006" /><br/>
To install the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>.1 update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;.1 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
It's not yet clear what new features are included in the watchOS 11.1 update at this time, as the update primarily focuses on Apple Intelligence, and Apple Intelligence features are not available on watchOS.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-watchos-11-beta-3-to-developers-2/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 11.1 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-11-1-to-developers.2438818/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third tvOS 18.1 Beta to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-tvos-18-1-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-1-beta-to-developers.2438817/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:10:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-tvos-18-1-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 18.1 beta to developers for testing purposes, with the new software coming a week after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/23/apple-seeds-tvos-18-1-beta-2-to-developers/">second tvOS 18.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953895" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-4k-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 18.1 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes. We don't know what's included in tvOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/apple-seeds-tvos-18-1-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third tvOS 18.1 Beta to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-tvos-18-1-beta-to-developers.2438817/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Halide App Gains Added iPhone 16 Camera Control Functionality</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-camera-control-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-app-gains-added-iphone-16-camera-control-functionality.2438809/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:39:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-camera-control-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Halide</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular camera app Halide was today updated with new features for the Camera Control button available on the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. Halide already supported opening the app with Camera Control, but now users can also make adjustments.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/halide-camera-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968869" /><br/>
Using the Camera Control's touch and swipe-based gesture support, Halide users can adjust focus and exposure, and lock their settings in place. The dedicated "Locked" adjustment makes sure that no settings can be disturbed from accidental swipes on the Camera Control button, and it is designed for people who do not want to use manual adjustments.<br/>
<br/>
The Exposure setting allows users to set an exposure bias that exceeds what's possible with Apple's Camera app (-/+ 6 EV vs. 2), and Focus allows for manual focusing on a subject or scene using the Camera Control button. Halide says that Focus provides a smooth manual focus experience with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to these changes, Halide has added a quicker way to capture a photo. Halide takes the photo when the Camera Control button is pressed, while the Camera app from Apple takes the image when the button is released. The difference is minor, but fractions of a second can sometimes make a difference.<br/>
<br/>
Halide says that the quick snap feature works well with the 48-megapixel ProRAW Zero Shutter Lag feature in the app, as well as with Process Zero, an option that Halide added to take 12-megapixel images with no AI and minimal processing.<br/>
<br/>
Halide can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. The app is priced at &#36;2.99 per month, &#36;19.99 per year, or &#36;59.99 for a one-time purchase. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/halide-mark-ii-pro-camera/id885697368">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/halide/">Halide</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/halide-camera-control-new-features/">Halide App Gains Added iPhone 16 Camera Control Functionality</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/halide-app-gains-added-iphone-16-camera-control-functionality.2438809/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M1 iMac Owners Complain About Horizontal Lines Appearing on Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m1-imac-horizontal-lines-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m1-imac-owners-complain-about-horizontal-lines-appearing-on-screen.2438806/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 09:13:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m1-imac-horizontal-lines-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past year and a half or so, some owners of the 24-inch iMac with the M1 chip have encountered horizontal lines abruptly appearing on the computer's screen. There are complaints about this issue across the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255220596">Apple Support Community</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/imac-m1-2021-display-issue.2423630/">MacRumors Forums</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/applehelp/comments/17oopbw/imac_2021_suddenly_show_horizontal_lines/">Reddit</a>, <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/Answers/View/805617/Horizontal+lines+over+iMac+24+screen">iFixit Answers</a>, and several other websites, but it is unclear how many customers are affected in total, or what the underlying cause of the problem is.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/M1-iMac-Horizontal-Lines.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="901" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968865" /><br/>
The lines continue to appear on the screen even after the iMac is restarted, and no other solutions have been identified, according to the complaints.<br/>
<br/>
Many affected users said the lines began appearing on the screen around 18 to 24 months after they purchased the iMac. As a result, the affected iMac units are often no longer covered by Apple's standard one-year warranty at the time the issue begins, unless the customer purchased extended AppleCare+ coverage. Some customers who contacted Apple about the issue said the company offered them an exemption, resulting in their iMac being repaired for free, but other customers said they had to pay for service.<br/>
<br/>
One symptom commonly mentioned is the top-right corner of the iMac becoming hot to the touch after the issue begins, but there is no confirmed cause.<br/>
<br/>
Given that these complaints have been continuously popping up for nearly two years now, there may be a hardware issue with this particular iMac model, which launched in May 2021. We have not seen widespread complaints about this issue affecting the iMac with the M3 chip, although that model was released less than a year ago.<br/>
<br/>
Apple offers <a href="https://support.apple.com/service-programs">service programs</a> for some hardware issues, but it is unclear if it will ever launch one for this iMac issue. We have reached out to Apple for comment on this matter, and we will update this story if we receive a response.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/m1-imac-horizontal-lines-issue/">M1 iMac Owners Complain About Horizontal Lines Appearing on Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m1-imac-owners-complain-about-horizontal-lines-appearing-on-screen.2438806/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Early Prime Day Deals Hit Anker and Jackery Accessories on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/early-prime-day-deals-hit-anker/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/early-prime-day-deals-hit-anker-and-jackery-accessories-on-amazon.2438803/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 08:44:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/early-prime-day-deals-hit-anker/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're just one week out from Amazon Prime Day, and today we're already tracking a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2Fpage%2F2A25B7A1-3EFE-419E-B3A6-3BD8FF119DAD%3Fingress%3D2%26visitId%3D35aac3e4-9c99-4fdb-b9ec-7799f3a85a5c%26store_ref%3Dbl_ast_dp_brandLogo_sto%26ref_%3Dast_bln">big collection of deals</a> from popular brands including Anker and Jackery on Amazon. These deals include portable power stations, which are high-capacity portable batteries that can provide backup power to a wide variety of devices, from laptops to RVs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/anker-jackery-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958617" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For the Anker deals, you'll need to have a Prime membership in order to see some of these discounted prices, while others require an on-page coupon to be clipped before you see the final deal price. In regards to the Jackery discounts, some of these also require an on-page coupon in order to see the deal prices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1727796613682">SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D25VW1%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3K6WIELT3R9WM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3K6WIELT3R9WM_1727796277488">10,000 mAh Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;31.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;44.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDXP8VR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3K6WIELT3R9WM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3K6WIELT3R9WM_1727796277487">20,000 mAh Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;47.99 with Prime, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CZDPLK6P%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.27UES0CTOXN3I%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.27UES0CTOXN3I_1727796221243">MagGo 10,000 mAh Power Bank with Apple Watch Charger</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Certified-Ultra-Fast-MagSafe-Compatible-Portable%2Fdp%2FB0CFDPQXN4%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">MagGo Power Bank</a> - &#36;69.99 with Prime, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Battery-Supports-Recharging-Portable%2Fdp%2FB0CZ9J3QMY%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">9,600 mAh Power Bank</a> - &#36;79.99 with Prime, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Magnetic-Charger-Portable-Station%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">MagSafe Charger Stand 3-in-1 Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1CBVLK7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.QPKHVRT410PA%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.QPKHVRT410PA_1727795671512">Explorer 100 Plus with Solar Panel</a> - &#36;169.00, down from &#36;229.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CYL81MS3%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.139B5OVGIHGT2_1727795997993">Solar Generator with Mini Solar Panel</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QYH6YGJP7QXZ_1727796039758">Solar Generator 300 Plus</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.12YF8Q7LZR2JP%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.12YF8Q7LZR2JP_1727795709880">Explorer 1000 Plus Expansion Battery</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08P42QKWK%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2OQFGXBQQGR9Y%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2OQFGXBQQGR9Y_1727796122171">Explorer 500</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2934EWK71TJ3A_1727795943164">Explorer 2000 Plus Expansion Battery</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3DEZ1HJGW9026%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3DEZ1HJGW9026_1727796109673">Explorer 3000 Pro Generator</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;2,799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO_1727795891811">Solar Generator 4000 Kit</a> - &#36;2,599.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CMD799WY%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO_1727795761927">Explorer 2000 Plus Solar Generator + Expansion Battery + Solar Panels</a> - &#36;2,899.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;5,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGGQ7TZX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.31M3RQG1RZXPO_1727795823462">Solar Generator 2000 Plus Kit</a> - &#36;3,599.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;6,799.00</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/early-prime-day-deals-hit-anker/">Early Prime Day Deals Hit Anker and Jackery Accessories on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/early-prime-day-deals-hit-anker-and-jackery-accessories-on-amazon.2438803/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 3 Expected Next Year: Here&#039;s What We Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-3-everything-we-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-3-expected-next-year-heres-what-we-know.2438787/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 05:47:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-3-everything-we-know/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Despite being released over two years ago, Apple's AirPods Pro 2 continue to dominate the wireless earbud market. However, with the AirPods Pro 3 expected to launch sometime in 2025, anyone thinking of buying Apple's premium earbuds may be wondering if the next generation is worth holding out for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/airpods-pro-2-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967392" /><br/>
Apart from their audio and noise-canceling performance, which are generally regarded as excellent for such small buds, one of the reasons the AirPods Pro 2 have remained popular is Apple's commitment to updating their feature set with software updates. <br/>
<br/>
When iOS 17 was released last year, AirPods Pro 2 got new Adaptive Audio features, mute controls, and faster automatic device switching. And with iOS 18, released last month, Apple added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-airpods-pro/">head gestures</a>, allowing users to control Siri on the AirPods Pro with a shake or a nod of the head. Apple also added Voice Isolation to the AirPods Pro to cut down on loud background sounds to make you easier to hear, along with more granular Adaptive Audio controls and a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-airpods-pro/">Personalized Spatial Audio feature specific to gaming</a>. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, AirPods Pro 2 are set to receive a significant upgrade in October with the release of iOS 18.1. This update is expected to introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/airpods-pro-2-to-gain-new-hearing-features/">hearing aid functionality</a>, allowing the earbuds to function as an over-the-counter hearing aid for those with mild to moderate hearing loss. Apple has already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/12/airpods-pro-2-hearing-aid-fda-authorization/">received FDA authorization</a> for this feature, which could be a game-changer for many users.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2025 AirPods Pro: What the Rumors Say</h2><br/>
Any future generation of AirPods Pro will surely inherit all of these features, but we are also expecting more dramatic changes. Looking ahead to the AirPods Pro 3, multiple reports suggest Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/airpods-lineup-overhaul-2024/">planning a redesign for both the earbuds and the charging case</a>. While details are scarce, this indicates the next iteration may sport a fresh look compared to their predecessors, which have maintained a similar design since the original AirPods Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Under the hood, Apple is also said to be focusing on sonic improvements, with Apple adding a faster audio processor. This has been a consistent trend with each AirPods iteration. Perhaps more intriguing however are rumors of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/airpods-pro-3-much-better-anc-rumor/">"much better" Active Noise Cancellation capabilities</a> compared to the already impressive AirPods Pro 2.<br/>
<br/>
Health features appear to be a major focus for the AirPods Pro 3 as well. Apple is reportedly developing new sensors that could allow the earbuds to measure body temperature from within the ear canal. This aligns with the company's broader push into health monitoring across its product line, but whether the sensor will be ready in time for next year's model is unknown.<br/>
<br/>
Looking further ahead, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/30/new-airpods-to-feature-ir-cameras/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> believes we could see AirPods with integrated infrared cameras as soon as 2026. These would improve spatial audio experiences when paired with the Vision Pro headset, although it's unlikely that this technology will debut with next year's AirPods Pro 3.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 4 Hints</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/02/airpods-4-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964768" /><br/>
The fourth-generation AirPods could offer a hint as to what other design changes we could see in AirPods Pro 3. AirPods 4 eliminate the familiar setup button found on the back of earlier models' charging cases. Instead, Apple has integrated a concealed capacitive button on the front of the case, just below the status light. To initiate pairing mode, users simply open the case and double-tap the front-center area. <br/>
<br/>
The AirPods 4's status light has also received a stealthy makeover. When the case is closed or not charging, the LED is completely invisible. It only reveals itself when the case is opened or placed on a charger. These design changes contribute to the smallest and lightest AirPods charging case to date, and there's a good chance Apple will bring them over to the next-generation AirPods Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summing Up</h2><br/>
With the AirPods Pro 3 potentially arriving within the next 12 months, anyone looking to invest in some new AirPods has a decision to make. The recently released AirPods 4 bring some Pro features like Active Noise Cancellation to a more affordable &#36;179 price point. However, those who prioritize cutting-edge features and are willing to wait might find the upcoming AirPods Pro 3 to be a more compelling option, especially if they build upon the hearing aid functionality soon to be introduced in the AirPods Pro 2 and retain the current &#36;249 price tag.<br/>
<br/>
Are you holding out for AirPods Pro 3? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/airpods-pro-3-everything-we-know/">AirPods Pro 3 Expected Next Year: Here&#039;s What We Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-3-expected-next-year-heres-what-we-know.2438787/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
