<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 08:03:15 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Focusing on These Eight New Low-Cost Devices in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/11/apple-low-cost-devices-in-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-focusing-on-these-eight-new-low-cost-devices-in-2025.2447184/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/11/apple-low-cost-devices-in-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's slate of 2025 products look to be dominated by a large number of low-cost and entry-level devices. Here's what to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/AppleEventLogoFeature.jpg" alt="" width="2236" height="1258" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-757986" /><br/>
With advancements like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> and all-new in-house chip designs, Apple is reportedly looking to enhance many of its budget-friendly offerings, ensuring they remain competitive in an increasingly crowded market. These updates also indicate a slight shift in Apple's approach to low-cost devices, moving beyond entry-level hardware to introduce features once reserved for premium models, such as OLED displays, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a>, and advanced wireless technology.<br/>
<br/>
Indeed, Apple's first custom modem and Bluetooth chip is coming to entry-level devices first. Similarly, the company is focusing on lower-end smart home devices such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and Command Center, before devoting attention to higher-end models. We're expecting a total of eight new or refreshed low-cost Apple devices this year:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> (M4)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> (fourth generation)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> (11th generation)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> (second-generation)</li><br/>
<li>Command Center</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; (second generation)</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K (fourth generation)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> (third-generation)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; will finally be upgraded to the M4 chip, delivering up to 25% faster multi-core CPU performance than the current model. It could also gain support for two external displays and a 12MP webcam with Center Stage. Launching in spring 2025, the new models will likely maintain their current starting price of &#36;1,099. All models now start with 16GB of memory as standard.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/29/iphone-se-4-rumored-features/">iPhone SE 4</a> is rumored to feature a design similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, including a 6.1-inch OLED display, &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;, a USB-C port, and a 48MP rear camera. It will likely be powered by the A18 chip with 8GB of RAM to support &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; and will debut Apple's first in-house 5G modem. Expected to launch in March 2025, the new &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; is expected to be priced between &#36;400 and &#36;500, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/30/iphone-se-4-could-be-more-expensive/">slight increase</a> from the current &#36;429 due to significant upgrades.<br/>
<br/>
The 11th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will retain the 10.9-inch display and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button but will likely upgrade to an A17 Pro or A18 chip with 8GB of RAM to enable &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;. Expected in spring 2025, the device may continue to start at &#36;349, with the possibility of a base storage upgrade to 128GB. <br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags-2/">AirTag 2</a> will include an upgraded Ultra Wideband chip for a threefold increase in tracking range, better Vision Pro integration, and a tamper-proof speaker for enhanced anti-stalking measures. Launching in mid-2025, it is expected to maintain the current &#36;29 price point. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's Command Center will serve as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-command-center/">all-new smart home hub</a> product with a 7-inch display, built-in speakers, a camera for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, and proximity sensors for dynamic interface adjustments. It will run a new "homeOS" with widget-focused controls and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> integration. Expected to launch around March 2025, the price is yet to be confirmed but is expected to be competitive with similar products like Amazon's Echo Show, which is priced at &#36;90. A higher-end version of the device on a robotic arm is expected to debut in 2026, so the initial Command Center is likely to be an entry-level device akin to the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homepod-mini-2/">second-generation HomePod mini</a> is expect to gain a new in-house Wi-Fi and Bluetooth chip supporting Wi-Fi 6E, improved audio quality, and a second-generation Ultra Wideband chip for better handoff. Likely to launch in mid-2025, the device will likely retain its &#36;99 price point.<br/>
<br/>
A new &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K is rumored to feature an updated A-series chip, likely the A16 or newer, Wi-Fi 6E support, and possibly a built-in camera for &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj;. Expected to launch in 2025, the device could see a starting price <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">drop to &#36;99</a> from the current &#36;129, aligning better with competitors like Amazon's Fire Stick.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; 3 will likely feature larger displays, a faster chip, the S10 or S11 chip, and may adopt a more affordable plastic casing. The current model will be three years old this fall. Expected in late 2025, the device could maintain its &#36;249 starting price or potentially decrease slightly to compete with rival devices and appeal to parents purchasing for children.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/11/apple-low-cost-devices-in-2025/">Apple Focusing on These Eight New Low-Cost Devices in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-focusing-on-these-eight-new-low-cost-devices-in-2025.2447184/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 Tips to Get the Most From Your iPhone&#039;s Battery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/10-iphone-battery-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-tips-to-get-the-most-from-your-iphones-battery.2447168/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:37:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/10-iphone-battery-tips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you have regular access to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> charger during the day and a healthy battery, you probably don't need to worry much about extending your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery. For days when you're away from home for long periods of time, though, you might need to take some steps to make sure you get the most out of your battery.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971681" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iPhone-16-Battery-Life-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
We've rounded up 10 tips that will help ensure your battery lasts all day.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>1. Disable iPhone Mirroring</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring lets you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac, and when it's turned on, you'll get &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; notifications on your Mac display even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
When it's in active use it can be helpful, but there is a connection between the Mac and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to relay notifications. Notifications can show up on the Mac even when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring app is closed, and there is anecdotal evidence from <em>MacRumors</em> readers suggesting this can be a notable battery drain.<br/>
<br/>
If you're not using &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, it's worth turning it off. To do so, go to Settings > General > <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> and Continuity and tap on Edit. From there, delete the Macs that your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; connects to.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2. Be Mindful of Apple Intelligence Usage</h2><br/>
On <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> can have a major impact on battery life. Processing for features like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a>, and Writing Tools is done entirely on-device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-crocodile.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972927" /><br/>
In a test, a little over an hour of making emojis with the &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; feature drained an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/13/ios-18-2-genmoji/">iPhone 16 Pro Max's battery</a> 50 percent, so keep that in mind. If you're in a situation where your battery needs to last for a long time, stay away from generating images with &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Use Dark Mode When Possible</h2><br/>
On OLED &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; displays, activating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a> preserves battery life because there's less power draw when darker colored pixels are displayed. Activating &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; when outside on a sunny day can save you a ton of battery, according to a <a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/3458864.3467682">2021 Purdue study</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956931" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-dark-mode-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Lower levels of brightness in Light Mode use the same battery as higher levels of brightness in &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj;, so &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; can save battery even when brightness is turned up when you're in a sunny location.<br/>
<br/>
When you're somewhere that has dimmer lighting and screen brightness is lower, turning on &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; won't save as much battery life, but it still draws a bit less power.<br/>
<br/>
As of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, you can set a Dark option for your icons that turns them darker when &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; is enabled (or all the time, if you prefer). Dark icons are easier on the eyes when &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; is on, and it might save just a little extra battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Along with &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj;, keep your screen brightness as low as is comfortable, because that's also going to preserve battery. You can quickly adjust brightness using the Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>4. Connect to Wi-Fi When It's Available</h2><br/>
This tip is <a href="https://www.apple.com/batteries/maximizing-performance/">straight from Apple</a>. Whenever you're somewhere that has a Wi-Fi connection available, it's a good idea to use it over cellular.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iphone-wi-fi.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984992" /><br/>
Wi-Fi uses less power than cellular, and a cellular connection can be one of the biggest battery drains.<br/>
<br/>
When in a place with low signal that's constantly cutting out or no signal, go even further and turn on Airplane mode. When your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is constantly searching for a better cellular signal, it impacts battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5. Turn Off Haptic Keyboard Feedback</h2><br/>
Haptic feedback on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s keyboard is satisfying to feel when you tap on the on-screen keys, but it<a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102463"> does drain your battery</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iphone-haptic-keyboard-feedback.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984993" /><br/>
You can turn it off by going to Settings > Sounds & Haptics > Keyboard Feedback and toggling off Haptic.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6. Set Up Focus Modes and Scheduled Summary</h2><br/>
Most of us have tons of notifications coming in throughout the day, and constantly getting alerts and activating the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s display can cost you battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-reduce-interruptions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960225" /><br/>
If you haven't already, it's a good idea to set up Focus modes to tailor the notifications you're getting to what you need for any given activity. If you're at home, for example, you can set up a "Personal" mode that filters work notifications, or at work, a mode that filters notifications from games and other apps you don't need while working.<br/>
<br/>
Focus modes are entirely customizable, so you can choose which apps and people can contact you in each mode, and there are even options for filtering out select emails, messages, calendars, and more.<br/>
<br/>
On iPhones that support &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;, Apple added a "Reduce Interruptions" Focus mode that intelligently filters what's not important while delivering what you need to see immediately. If you don't want to hassle with Focus modes, this is a good option.<br/>
<br/>
Note that when you use a Focus mode, you'll still get all of your notifications when the Focus mode ends, but in a single alert rather than multiple. Focus modes can be set up in the Focus section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
On a related note, set up Scheduled Summary for any app that sends you unimportant notifications. Scheduled Summary aggregates all of your notifications and sends them to you just once or twice a day.<br/>
<br/>
You can toggle on Scheduled Summary for apps in the Notifications section of the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>7. Use Offline Maps</h2><br/>
In an off-grid area or a place with low cellular signal, Offline Maps can be a real help. When driving or hiking somewhere where signal is low, download a map so you can have full maps access and turn-by-turn directions without a cellular connection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Maps-Offline.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899235" /><br/>
Offline Maps is a good option to pair with Airplane mode in areas where cellular signal is hit or miss.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>8. Automate Low Power Mode</h2><br/>
Turning on Low Power Mode is the most obvious way to preserve battery life on your device, and it's a good idea to automate it so it can be set to turn on at a specific battery percentage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/low-power-mode-shortcut.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984994" /><br/>
Apple will prompt you to turn on Low Power Mode when your battery is at 20 percent, but it's often helpful to turn it on even earlier. To set up a Low Power Mode shortcut, open up the Shortcuts app, and create a new Automation. From there, search for Battery Level and choose a target battery percentage. Hit the "Next" button, search for Low Power Mode, and select it. That will cause Low Power Mode to activate automatically when your battery hits your target level.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9. Turn Off Fitness Tracking</h2><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has a Fitness Tracking feature that stores motion data to estimate your body movements, mobility, step counts, stairs climbed, and more. If you have an Apple Watch or another fitness tracker, you don't need this setting and it could be contributing to unnecessary battery usage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/motion-and-fitness-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984995" /><br/>
To turn it off, open up the Settings app and go to Privacy and Security > Motion and Fitness and then toggle off the Fitness Tracking setting.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10. Check App Access Settings</h2><br/>
Many apps request access permissions that they don't need and probably shouldn't have access to. Apps that don't need but use Bluetooth or Location can drain your battery life, so it's best to check all of your app settings for both battery preservation and privacy purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iphone-location-services.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984996" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Location</strong> - Settings > Privacy and Security > Location Services.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Bluetooth</strong> - Settings > Privacy and Security > Bluetooth.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
In each of these sections, toggle off access for apps that don't need this data. An app that connects to something in your home via Bluetooth <em>does</em> need Bluetooth, but apps like Waze, Facebook, and YouTube often don't need it.<br/>
<br/>
It's also a good idea to turn off background refresh for apps that don't need to be updating in the background. Go to Settings > General > Background App Refresh to check your settings.<br/>
<br/>
Have a useful battery saving tip that we didn't mention here? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/10-iphone-battery-tips/">10 Tips to Get the Most From Your iPhone&#039;s Battery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-tips-to-get-the-most-from-your-iphones-battery.2447168/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook Earned &#36;74.6 Million in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tim-cook-2024-salary/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-earned-74-6-million-in-2024.2447167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:48:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tim-cook-2024-salary/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> earned &#36;74.6 million in 2024, up from &#36;63.2 million in 2023, Apple said in its <a href="https://www.sec.gov/ix?doc=/Archives/edgar/data/320193/000130817925000008/aapl4359751-def14a.htm">annual proxy filing</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Tim-Cook-MacBook-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-894618" /><br/>
Cook's earnings included a &#36;3 million base salary, &#36;58 million in stock awards, &#36;12 million in performance-based awards, and &#36;1.5 million in other compensation, such as 401(k) contributions, life insurance premiums, vacation cash-out, security expenses, and personal air travel expenses. Cook is required by Apple to use private aircraft for both business and personal travel.<br/>
<br/>
Apple set a target compensation of &#36;59 million for Cook, but Cook earned more through the cash incentive payout that executives receive when Apple performs well.<br/>
<br/>
Though Cook's 2024 compensation exceeded what he earned in 2023, it was still down from the &#36;99 million that he was awarded in 2022. Cook and the Board of Directors opted to decrease Cook's total compensation after his 2022 earnings reached almost &#36;100 million.<br/>
<br/>
Other Apple executives, including Luca Maestri, Kate Adams, Deirdre O'Brien, and Jeff Williams, earned &#36;27.2 million.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tim-cook-2024-salary/">Apple CEO Tim Cook Earned &#36;74.6 Million in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-earned-74-6-million-in-2024.2447167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Annual Shareholders Meeting Will Take Place on February 25</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-shareholders-meeting-february-25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-annual-shareholders-meeting-will-take-place-on-february-25.2447166/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:24:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-shareholders-meeting-february-25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 2025 shareholders meeting will be held on Tuesday, February 25 at 8:00 a.m. Pacific Time, according to an SEC filing that was released today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/Apple-Logo-Cash-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2676" height="1504" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834996" /><br/>
Apple shareholders of record as of January 2, 2025 can attend, vote, and submit questions during the meeting by logging in to Apple's <a href="https://east.virtualshareholdermeeting.com/vsm/web?pvskey=AAPL2025">virtual meeting website</a> 15 minutes before it kicks off. A control number included in the Notice of Internet Availability of Proxy Materials that's provided to shareholders is required to join.<br/>
<br/>
At the meeting, shareholders will vote to re-elect the Board of Directors, approve executive compensation, and ratify Ernst &amp; Young LLP as Apple's public accounting firm. There will also be votes on shareholder proposals.<br/>
<br/>
Most of Apple's shareholder meetings are not of interest to the public. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and other executives share little about Apple's future plans at these meetings, but sometimes there are a few interesting tidbits. Last year, for example, &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; spoke about the potential of artificial intelligence before <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features were highlighted in June 2024.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-shareholders-meeting-february-25/">Apple&#039;s Annual Shareholders Meeting Will Take Place on February 25</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-annual-shareholders-meeting-will-take-place-on-february-25.2447166/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Isn&#039;t Driving iPhone Upgrades</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-intelligence-not-driving-iphone-upgrades/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-isnt-driving-iphone-upgrades.2447165/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:17:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-intelligence-not-driving-iphone-upgrades/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> hasn't convinced people to buy an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple-likely-to-face-fiercer-challenges-in-2025-requiring-caution-against-potential-downside-risks-5cec099e1d5d">said today</a>. According to Kuo, a supply chain survey suggests &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; is not pushing people to upgrade their devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
The delay between the &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; introduction in June 2024 and a launch even after &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models came out was a contributing factor, and &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; "appeal has significantly declined" compared to cloud-based services like ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
There is also no indication that &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will drive Services revenue, as Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said in December that Apple has never discussed charging for &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj;. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/apple-intelligence-fees-2027/">could start charging</a> for &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; in 2027 or beyond, but it remains to be seen if that will happen.<br/>
<br/>
All in all, Kuo does not feel that &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; is going to benefit Apple in terms of user upgrades or revenue, but there's some hope for the long-term prospects.<br/>
<blockquote>I'm not bearish on Apple Intelligence's long-term prospects; however, given the points discussed above, there is no evidence of Apple Intelligence's ability to benefit hardware replacement cycles or service business. As such, it should be cautious of potential downside risks created by earlier market over-optimism.</blockquote><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; was the main focus of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, but when the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models launched in September, there were no &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features available. Writing Tools and other capabilities came in the first update to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; in October, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> didn't roll out until December.<br/>
<br/>
There are still &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; features that have not been implemented, including major changes to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> that are rumored to be coming in April. <br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/16/survey-users-uninterested-in-apple-intelligence/">December survey suggested</a> that many <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users feel that &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; has added little or no value to their &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; experience, though that sentiment could change as &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; matures.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-intelligence-not-driving-iphone-upgrades/">Apple Intelligence Isn&#039;t Driving iPhone Upgrades</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-isnt-driving-iphone-upgrades.2447165/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Ban Looking Likely After U.S. Supreme Court Hears Case</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tiktok-ban-looking-likely-after-u-s-supreme-court-hears-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-ban-looking-likely-after-u-s-supreme-court-hears-case.2447160/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 13:12:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tiktok-ban-looking-likely-after-u-s-supreme-court-hears-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[TikTok is likely to be banned in the United States on January 19, after the United States Supreme Court indicated that it's leaning toward upholding the sell or ban law.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-752609" /><br/>
As highlighted by <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-01-10/supreme-court-signals-it-s-likely-to-uphold-tiktok-ban-in-us">Bloomberg</a></em>, the Supreme Court heard arguments on the case today, and it didn't go well for TikTok. Most of the justices indicated that worry over U.S. national security overrides free speech, and there were concerns about the personal data that TikTok collects from users, content manipulation, and the influence that China has over ByteDance.<br/>
<br/>
Justice Elena Kagan wasn't a fan of TikTok's argument that its constitutional rights were being violated. "The law is only targeted at this foreign corporation, which doesn't have First Amendment rights," she said.<br/>
<br/>
Justice John Roberts said that "Congress is fine with the expression," but "not fine with a foreign adversary ... gathering all this information about the 170 million people who use TikTok." He also questioned China's influence on ByteDance. "Are we supposed to ignore the fact that the ultimate parent is in fact subject to doing intelligence work for the Chinese government?" he asked TikTok's lawyer.<br/>
<br/>
The Supreme Court could give a ruling on TikTok before January 19, or postpone the date that the law goes into effect to give more time for consideration. TikTok asked the court to halt the ban while it waits for the appeals process to play out, but the court elected to hear the case ahead of January 19.<br/>
<br/>
If the court upholds the law, U.S. app stores will not be able to distribute the TikTok app as of January 19. TikTok users who already have the app will be able to continue using it, but it will stop functioning over time because updates weren't be permitted.<br/>
<br/>
ByteDance can opt to sell TikTok to an approved company, which would allow TikTok to continue to operate. A sale won't happen before January 19, but if TikTok is banned, it could be reinstated after a sale. ByteDance has claimed that a sale is not possible, and that China would not approve the divestiture of TikTok and its algorithm.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/tiktok-ban-looking-likely-after-u-s-supreme-court-hears-case/">TikTok Ban Looking Likely After U.S. Supreme Court Hears Case</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-ban-looking-likely-after-u-s-supreme-court-hears-case.2447160/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best of CES 2025: LG 6K Display, SanDisk MagSafe SSD, Satechi Chargers and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/best-of-ces-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-of-ces-2025-lg-6k-display-sandisk-magsafe-ssd-satechi-chargers-and-more.2447156/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 12:07:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/best-of-ces-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>CES 2025</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[CES 2025 is wrapping up today, and attendees are preparing to head home after a long week of exploring the latest tech products. <em>MacRumors</em> Dan Barbera spent the last few days checking out what's new, and we're wrapping up the week with our Best of CES 2025 list.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JoXb3RFH6VI" title="Best of CES 2025 in 10 Minutes!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
LG showed off a new UltraFine 6K display with Thunderbolt 5 support, and it's a serious Pro Display XDR competitor. The 32-inch display has a sleek stand with adjustable height, and almost no bezels at all. Launch date and price aren't available just yet. Samsung also had the Smart Monitor M9, a 4K OLED display with an AI Picture Optimizer feature that makes adjustments based on what's on the screen.<br/>
<br/>
TP-Link's Tapo brand had some interesting security cameras and locks, including one that's able to verify your identity by reading the veins in your palm before unlocking the door. The cameras aren't <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> or Matter-enabled, but Tapo has detailed notifications that give you insight into what's going on rather than just a standard motion detected alert.<br/>
<br/>
As for Apple-related accessories, Satechi's 3-in-1 magnetic travel chargers in bright colors were a win and SanDisk showed off a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> SSD with USB-C that's perfect for transferring content from your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or recording video directly to the external drive.<br/>
<br/>
OhSnap demoed a &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; wallet that has a super strong grip and can hold up to eight cards, and for &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; users, Flic Duo had a Matter-compatible button that supports gesture control for controlling your devices.<br/>
<br/>
Other highlights included Honda and Sony's Afeela electric vehicle, the cord-free Displace TV, and a spoon that zaps your tongue to make you taste salt so you can cut down on sodium.<br/>
<br/>
For all of the news from CES 2025, make sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2025/">check out our CES 2025 hub</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2025/">CES 2025</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/best-of-ces-2025/">Best of CES 2025: LG 6K Display, SanDisk MagSafe SSD, Satechi Chargers and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-of-ces-2025-lg-6k-display-sandisk-magsafe-ssd-satechi-chargers-and-more.2447156/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Now Lets You Pay Later With Synchrony [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-pay-synchrony/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-now-lets-you-pay-later-with-synchrony-updated.2447152/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:34:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-pay-synchrony/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Synchrony is now available as a buy-now, pay-later option when checking out with Apple Pay online and in apps on iPhone and iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
Synchrony was added to a list of Apple Pay installment providers in the U.S. in an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT204916">Apple support document</a> that was updated today, joining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/16/apple-pay-affirm-partnership/">Affirm</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/17/apple-pay-klarna/">Klarna</a>. The addition was spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a>.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 users can select "Other Cards & Pay Later Options" when checking out with Apple Pay to access payment plans available from Synchrony.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-discontinuing-apple-pay-later/">discontinued its own buy-now, pay-later service</a> called Apple Pay Later last year, and started partnering with third-party providers. Apple Pay Later let qualifying customers split a purchase made with Apple Pay into four equal payments over six weeks, with no interest or fees. Affirm, Klarna, and now Synchrony offer similar financing options.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> Apple removed Synchrony from the support document after we published. This integration is not yet live.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-pay-synchrony/">Apple Pay Now Lets You Pay Later With Synchrony [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-now-lets-you-pay-later-with-synchrony-updated.2447152/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces New Miami Worldcenter Store With Special Wallpaper</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-miami-worldcenter/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-miami-worldcenter-store-with-special-wallpaper.2447146/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 09:44:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-miami-worldcenter/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it will be opening an all-new retail store <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/miamiworldcenter/">at the Miami Worldcenter</a> complex, near the city's downtown core, on Friday, January 24. A grand opening time has not been disclosed, but it will likely be 10 a.m. local time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Miami-Wallpaper.jpg" alt="" width="930" height="526" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984963" /><br/>
The store incorporates a biophilic garden that is designed to make vistors feel more connected with nature, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
"Our brand-new store in downtown Miami is opening soon," says Apple. "Get ready to discover an oasis in the heart of the city, where nature thrives and creativity flourishes. We can't wait to see what blooms in you."<br/>
<br/>
To celebrate the occasion, Apple has shared a specially-designed, garden-themed wallpaper for the <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/downloads/miamiworldcenter/wallpapers/mwc_mobile.png">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/downloads/miamiworldcenter/wallpapers/mwc_tablet.png">iPad</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/downloads/miamiworldcenter/wallpapers/mwc_desktop.png">Mac</a>. In addition, the store has an <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/apple-miami-worldcenter/pl.fcdd759dcfab4928bb911f1d3a938816">Apple Music playlist</a> featuring some of Miami's most popular Latin music artists.<br/>
<br/>
"Created from the ground up to reflect Apple's values, Miami Worldcenter is Apple's most sustainable store-centred on universal design principles, while creating an inviting space where everyone is welcome," says Apple. "In that spirit, we've put together a playlist featuring some of Miami's favorite Latin music stars to help us celebrate the store's opening."<br/>
<br/>
Apple Miami Worldcenter will be the company's 10th store in the Miami area.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-miami-worldcenter/">Apple Announces New Miami Worldcenter Store With Special Wallpaper</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-new-miami-worldcenter-store-with-special-wallpaper.2447146/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect the iPhone SE 4 or So-Called &#039;iPhone 16E&#039; to Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/when-to-expect-new-iphone-se/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-the-iphone-se-4-or-so-called-iphone-16e-to-launch.2447142/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 09:20:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/when-to-expect-new-iphone-se/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is widely rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">planning a new iPhone SE</a>, and multiple sources lately have commented on the device's launch timing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/se-4-for-2025.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983629" /><br/>
The latest word comes from Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple%E5%9C%A82025%E5%B9%B4%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E5%B0%87%E9%9D%A2%E8%87%A8%E6%9B%B4%E7%82%BA%E5%9A%B4%E5%B3%BB%E7%9A%84%E6%8C%91%E6%88%B0-%E9%A0%88%E8%AC%B9%E6%85%8E%E9%9D%A2%E5%B0%8D%E5%B8%82%E5%A0%B4%E5%85%88%E5%89%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%BA%A6%E6%A8%82%E8%A7%80%E5%B0%8E%E8%87%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%BD%9B%E5%9C%A8%E4%B8%8B%E8%A1%8C%E9%A2%A8%E9%9A%AA-6256c091f06d">blog post today</a>, he said the device will be released around the middle of the first half of 2025. In other words, around the quarter mark of 2025. That means the next iPhone SE will likely be released this March or April, just like all previous models of the device.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo did not reveal any other details about the next iPhone SE, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e/">apparently might end up being named "iPhone 16E"</a> or similar.<br/>
<br/>
One leaker recently claimed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/07/iphone-se-4-and-ipad-11-launch-timing/">the device will launch with iOS 18.3</a>, which is expected to be released in late January. However, that rumor was quickly shot down by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, who said Apple is aiming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/07/iphone-se-4-and-ipad-11-by-april/">release the device "by April."</a> Kuo's timeframe also suggests that a March or April release is more likely than January.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPhone SE is said to have a similar design as the base iPhone 14. Rumored features for the device include a 6.1-inch OLED display, Face ID, a USB-C port, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, a newer A-series chip and 8GB of RAM <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">for Apple Intelligence support</a>, and the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/apple-5g-modem-plans-report/">Apple-designed 5G modem</a>. It is not entirely clear if the device will have an Action button, which debuted on the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
The current iPhone SE looks similar to the iPhone 8, with outdated features such as a Touch ID button, Lightning port, and thick bezels around the display. Pricing starts at &#36;429, but at least a slight price increase seems probable for the next model.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/when-to-expect-new-iphone-se/">When to Expect the iPhone SE 4 or So-Called &#039;iPhone 16E&#039; to Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-the-iphone-se-4-or-so-called-iphone-16e-to-launch.2447142/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumors: Ultra-Thin 5.5mm Design, No SIM Card Slot</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-17-air-rumors-ultra-thin-5-5mm-design-no-sim-card-slot.2447140/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 08:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The so-called "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/#iphone_17_air">iPhone 17 Air</a>" model expected to launch later this year will have an ultra-thin design that is 5.5mm at its thinnest point, according to the latest information shared by reputable Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iPhone-17-Slim-Feature-Single-Camera-1-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-974628" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/apple%E5%9C%A82025%E5%B9%B4%E5%8F%AF%E8%83%BD%E5%B0%87%E9%9D%A2%E8%87%A8%E6%9B%B4%E7%82%BA%E5%9A%B4%E5%B3%BB%E7%9A%84%E6%8C%91%E6%88%B0-%E9%A0%88%E8%AC%B9%E6%85%8E%E9%9D%A2%E5%B0%8D%E5%B8%82%E5%A0%B4%E5%85%88%E5%89%8D%E9%81%8E%E5%BA%A6%E6%A8%82%E8%A7%80%E5%B0%8E%E8%87%B4%E7%9A%84%E6%BD%9B%E5%9C%A8%E4%B8%8B%E8%A1%8C%E9%A2%A8%E9%9A%AA-6256c091f06d">blog post today</a>, Kuo added that the device will lack a physical SIM card slot, and instead rely entirely on digital eSIM technology. This is something we've heard before for this device, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-esim-only-in-more-countries-report/">entire iPhone 17 lineup could be eSIM-only in more countries</a>.<br/>
<br/>
If the 5.5mm measurement ends up being accurate, the "iPhone 17 Air" would become the thinnest iPhone ever, topping the current 6.9mm record set by the iPhone 6. It also means the device would be around 30% thinner than the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, and around 33% thinner than the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
The device measuring 5.5mm only at its "thinnest point" likely means it will have an ultra-thin chassis with a thicker rear camera bump. The device is expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">only a single 48-megapixel rear camera</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There have been conflicting rumors about the device's exact thinness, but several sources have agreed on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">around a 5mm</a> to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/iphone-17-air-2mm-thinner/">mid-6mm range</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The latest 13-inch iPad Pro model measures <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/08/ipod-nano-appears-in-new-ipad-pro-ad/">just 5.1mm thick</a>, so the "iPhone 17 Air" could be approaching that impressive territory.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said the ultra-thin iPhone 17 model will enter mass production in the second half of 2025. The device is expected to launch in September alongside the iPhone 17, iPhone 17 Pro, and iPhone 17 Pro Max. There is no iPhone 17 Plus expected, with the "iPhone 17 Air" effectively set to become a replacement for the Plus model in this year's lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Due to its thin design, the "iPhone 17 Air" is expected to have some reduced specifications compared to the Pro models. In addition to the single rear camera, the device is rumored to have a standard A19 chip instead of the A19 Pro chip, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">only a single speaker</a>. However, Kuo believes Apple will still charge a "high price" for the device.<br/>
<br/>
Other rumored "iPhone 17 Air" specifications include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">a 6.6-inch display</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence</a>, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/">Apple-designed 5G modem</a>, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">New &#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; Rumors: Ultra-Thin 5.5mm Design, No SIM Card Slot</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-17-air-rumors-ultra-thin-5-5mm-design-no-sim-card-slot.2447140/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Woot&#039;s Big Apple Watch Band Sale Has Solo/Braided Loops at Massive Discounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/woots-big-apple-watch-band-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woots-big-apple-watch-band-sale-has-solo-braided-loops-at-massive-discounts.2447136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:52:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/woots-big-apple-watch-band-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot has brought back a massive sale on the <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-black-white-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">Braided Solo Loop</a> and <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-black-white-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">Solo Loop bands</a> for Apple Watch, which we last tracked before the Christmas holiday. All bands are in brand new condition and come with a one year Apple limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/apple-watch-bands-january.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-984898" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the Solo Loop for just <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-black-white-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a> (&#36;29 off) and the Braided Solo Loop for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-black-white-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"><strong>&#36;29.99</strong></a> (&#36;69 off) in this sale. Woot says the sale will run through January 17, but it'll probably end sooner when stock runs out, so make your purchases soon if you're interested.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-solo-loop%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_tl"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 70% OFF</div>Apple Watch Bands at Woot</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should note that this sale is focused on colors of the Braided Solo Loop and Solo Loop that Apple has stopped selling, and it doesn't include any of the new band colors. That being said, all of the bands in this sale are in new condition.<br/>
<br/>
The entire sale is focused on Solo Loop and Braided Solo Loop Apple Watch bands, so you'll need to know the size that works best for you before you buy. Apple has a measurement tool <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MXY33AM/A/42mm-denim-braided-solo-loop-size-0">on its website</a> that you can use to determine your exact size.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Solo Loop</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-black-white-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3">Black/White Hues</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-blue-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_6">Blue Hues</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-green-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_7">Green Hues</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-purple-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_11">Purple Hues</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-solo-loop-red-orange-yellow-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_8">Red/Orange/Yellow Hues</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Braided Solo Loop</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-black-white-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">Black/White Hues</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-blue-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2">Blue Hues</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-green-hues-3%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_9">Green Hues</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-purple-hues-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_10">Purple Hues</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-red-orange-yellow-hues-2%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_4">Red/Orange/Yellow Hues</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-braided-solo-loop-pride-edition-2021z-1%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_5">Pride</a> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;99.00</li></ul> If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/woots-big-apple-watch-band-sale/">Woot&#039;s Big Apple Watch Band Sale Has Solo/Braided Loops at Massive Discounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/woots-big-apple-watch-band-sale-has-solo-braided-loops-at-massive-discounts.2447136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Arcade Gains New Games and Updates for 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-arcade-gains-games-updates-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-gains-new-games-and-updates-for-2025.2447135/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:39:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-arcade-gains-games-updates-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2025/01/apple-arcade-launches-into-2025-with-10-new-games-including-pga-tour-pro-golf/">announced</a> that ten new games are coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, including the service's first officially licensed PGA TOUR game, while updating several existing titles.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-Arcade-hero.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-984891" /><br/>
The year begins with the launch of seven titles available immediately, accompanied by announcements of three additional games debuting on February 6, 2025. The new games include:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li><strong>Skate City: New York</strong>: A skateboarding game set in iconic real-world New York City skate spots, offering detailed environments.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>Gears & Goo for Apple Vision Pro</strong>: A spatial computing game combining tower defense and base-building mechanics with immersive 3D gameplay for the Vision Pro.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>Three Kingdoms HEROES</strong>: The latest installment in Koei Tecmo's <em>Romance of the Three Kingdoms</em> series, focusing on strategy and dynamic storytelling based on Chinese history.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>FINAL FANTASY+</strong>: A remastered version of the original entry in the iconic RPG series, containing enhanced 2D visuals and mobile-optimized features.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>Trials of Mana+</strong>: A mobile port of SQUARE ENIX's action RPG, delivering console-quality gameplay on Apple devices.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>Rodeo Stampede+</strong>: A Wild West adventure game where players tame animals and create their own zoo.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>It's Literally Just Mowing+</strong>: A relaxing game where players can enjoy the simple, zen-like task of mowing lawns.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>PGA TOUR Pro Golf</strong>: An immersive golf simulation game featuring iconic PGA TOUR courses, competitive tournaments, and cross-platform gameplay.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>Doodle Jump 2+</strong>: A sequel to the popular platforming game, featuring new environments, challenges, and characters.</li><br/>
  <li><strong>My Dear Farm+</strong>: A customizable farming simulator where players design their dream farm, grow crops, and manage their agricultural empire.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; also sees significant updates for several of its most popular games. "WHAT THE CAR?" has received new levels and gameplay refinements to enhance its racing mechanics, while "Game Room" has been expanded with additional game modes and challenges. "Hello Kitty Island Adventure" now includes fresh content such as new quests, customization options, and interactive features. Updates are also coming this month for "NBA 2K25 Arcade Edition," "Outlanders 2: Second Nature," "Wheel of Fortune Daily," "Snake.io+," "Ridiculous Fishing EX," and more.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is Apple's subscription-based gaming service that offers unlimited access to a curated library of premium games across <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>. All games on the platform are ad-free and do not include in-app purchase.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is available as a standalone subscription for &#36;6.99 per month, with a one-month free trial for new users. Alternatively, it can be bundled with other Apple services, such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>+, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+, through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription plan. &zwnj;Apple One&zwnj; starts at &#36;19.95 per month for the Individual plan.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-arcade-gains-games-updates-2025/">Apple Arcade Gains New Games and Updates for 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-arcade-gains-new-games-and-updates-for-2025.2447135/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 Get First Notable Discount of the Year at &#36;179.99 (&#36;69 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/airpods-pro-2-first-discount-year/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-get-first-notable-discount-of-the-year-at-179-99-69-off.2447131/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:21:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/airpods-pro-2-first-discount-year/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has Apple's AirPods Pro 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This is the first time in 2025 that the headphones have dropped under their typical sale price of &#36;189.99, and Amazon is providing a mid-January delivery date for most United States residences.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895408" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, we saw a better deal over the holiday season, but it's very unlikely that all-time low price will return any time soon. Amazon's price today is still a solid deal on the AirPods Pro 2, which feature USB-C charging and Active Noise Cancellation.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/airpods-pro-2-first-discount-year/">AirPods Pro 2 Get First Notable Discount of the Year at &#36;179.99 (&#36;69 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-get-first-notable-discount-of-the-year-at-179-99-69-off.2447131/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announced the MacBook Pro 19 Years Ago Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/macbook-pro-announced-19-years-ago/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-macbook-pro-19-years-ago-today.2447129/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 07:11:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/macbook-pro-announced-19-years-ago/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Steve Jobs <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2006/01/10Apple-Introduces-MacBook-Pro/">announced</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> 19 years ago today at the 2006 Macworld Conference & Expo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/original-macbook-pro-2006.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-984873" /><br/>
Jobs unveiled the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; as the first Mac notebook to transition from PowerPC processors to Intel's Core Duo architecture. Designed to be an Intel-based replacement for the PowerBook line, the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; took a similar aluminum chassis and added an Intel Core processor, a webcam, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> power connector. Its display was 67% brighter than its predecessor, matching the luminance of Apple's standalone Cinema Displays.<br/>
<br/>
Apple claimed that the Intel processors delivered "up to four times the performance of the PowerBook G4." The transition was supported by Rosetta, a software translation layer that allowed PowerPC applications to run on Intel-based Macs.<br/>
<br/>
The original &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; came in two configurations, both with 15.4-inch widescreen displays offering 1440 x 900 resolution. The entry-level model featured a 1.67 GHz Intel Core Duo processor, 512MB of DDR2 RAM, and an 80GB hard drive, while the higher-end model boasted a 1.83 GHz processor, 1GB of RAM, and a 100GB hard drive. Both models included ATI Mobility Radeon X1600 graphics cards. The 15-inch model weighed just 5.6 pounds and was only one inch thick.<br/>
<br/>
It also featured two USB 2.0 ports, a FireWire 400 port, a Gigabit Ethernet port, and an ExpressCard/34 slot for expandability. The exclusion of FireWire 800 in the initial 15-inch models drew criticism from some users, but this port was later restored in subsequent revisions. Initially only available with a 15-inch display, Apple introduced a 17-inch variant in April 2006.<br/>
<br/>
Over the years, the &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; line evolved through various design and technological iterations, including the unibody construction in 2008, the Retina display in 2012, and the controversial Touch Bar in 2016. The transition from Intel to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a> in 2020 marked the end of the Intel-based &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; era, as Apple moved to its proprietary <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-max/">M1 Max</a> chips.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/macbook-pro-announced-19-years-ago/">Apple Announced the MacBook Pro 19 Years Ago Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-macbook-pro-19-years-ago-today.2447129/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 18 Rumored to Feature Upgraded Camera Sensor From Samsung With Many Benefits</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-18-samsung-camera-sensor-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-rumored-to-feature-upgraded-camera-sensor-from-samsung-with-many-benefits.2447128/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 06:39:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-18-samsung-camera-sensor-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		<category>iPhone 18</category>
		<category>Jukanlosreve</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 17 series is still more than eight months away from launching, there are already rumors about the iPhone 18 models coming next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-16-pro-design-cameras.jpg" alt="" width="923" height="517" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966096" /><br/>
Taiwanese supply chain publication <a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20250107PD208.html"><em>DigiTimes</em> today reported</a> that Samsung is developing a new three-layer stacked camera sensor that is targeted for the iPhone 18. This advanced image sensor would make the iPhone 18's camera more responsive, with other benefits including reduced noise in photos, increased dynamic range, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The exact technology is called "PD-TR-Logic," according to the report, and it refers to a camera sensor with three layers of circuitry affixed to it. A <a href="https://x.com/Jukanlosreve/status/1874358213011005628">leaker known as "Jukanlosreve"</a> first revealed Samsung's alleged plans for the sensor last week.<br/>
<br/>
Sony has long been the exclusive supplier of image sensors for iPhone cameras, so Samsung entering the fray would be notable.<br/>
<br/>
In July 2024, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said he expected Samsung to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/2026-iphone-48mp-camera-sensor-samsung/">begin shipping 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera sensors to Apple</a> for iPhones as early as 2026, which is when iPhone 18 models are expected to be released. It is unclear if Samsung's sensor will also be used for the Fusion and/or Telephoto cameras on iPhone 18 models, and it is unclear if the sensor will be limited to iPhone 18 Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
With at least three sources having revealed Samsung's plans to become an iPhone camera sensor supplier, this rumor seems to be quite solidified. iPhone 18 models are still more than a year and a half away, though, so the plans could change.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-18/">iPhone 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jukanlosreve/">Jukanlosreve</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-18-samsung-camera-sensor-report/">iPhone 18 Rumored to Feature Upgraded Camera Sensor From Samsung With Many Benefits</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-18-rumored-to-feature-upgraded-camera-sensor-from-samsung-with-many-benefits.2447128/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Discontinued iPhone 15 Pro Refurbs in Europe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-selling-iphone-15-pro-refurbs-europe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-discontinued-iphone-15-pro-refurbs-in-europe.2447123/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 04:28:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-selling-iphone-15-pro-refurbs-europe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today started selling refurbished iPhone 15 Pro models in <a href="https://www.apple.com/fr/shop/refurbished/iphone/iphone-15">France</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/shop/refurbished/iphone">Germany</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/it/shop/refurbished/iphone/iphone-15">Italy</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/es/shop/refurbished/iphone/iphone-15">Spain</a>, offering the discontinued iPhones at a discount for the first time since their 2023 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are available in the above countries with a 15% discount compared to the equivalent brand new models. Apple began selling standard refurbished iPhone 15 models in select European countries earlier this week, despite them having not yet arrived on the domestic US market.<br/>
<br/>
All refurbished iPhones from Apple are unlocked and compatible with any carrier. Each refurbished iPhone is equipped with a new battery, a new outer shell, and a USB-C to USB-C cable, making them virtually indistinguishable from brand-new devices.<br/>
<br/>
Refurbished iPhones also come with Apple's standard one-year warranty, and buyers have the option to extend coverage with AppleCare+.<br/>
<br/>
With the launch of the iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max in September 2024, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-discontinues-iphone-15-pro-iphone-13/">discontinued</a> the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max. Apple continues to sell new iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus models on its main online storefront.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/apple-selling-iphone-15-pro-refurbs-europe/">Apple Now Selling Discontinued iPhone 15 Pro Refurbs in Europe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-discontinued-iphone-15-pro-refurbs-in-europe.2447123/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro Main Camera Sensor &#039;Smaller&#039; Than iPhone 16 Pro Sensor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller-than-iphone-16-pro-sensor.2447120/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 03:14:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year's iPhone 17 Pro models will feature a smaller main camera sensor than the one used in the Fusion camera currently found in iPhone 16 Pro models, according to Weibo-based leaker Digital Chat Station. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/iPhone-17-Pro-Dual-Tone-Horizontal-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-983587" /><br/>
The Chinese leaker <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/P8WbLbOeF">claims</a> that Apple will adopt a 1/1.3" sensor for the 48MP main camera in the iPhone 17 Pro and iPhone 17 Pro Max, down from the 1/1.28" sensor used in the iPhone 16 Pro models. The claim is part of a wider  leak allegedly revealing that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/both-iphone-17-pro-models-three-48mp-cameras/">both iPhone 17 Pro models will have three 48MP cameras</a> for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
The sensor size notation originates from an old system used for video camera tubes, where the fraction represents the sensor's "type" rather than its actual physical dimensions. That's why a 1/1.3" sensor is slightly smaller than a 1/1.28" sensor. (For comparison's sake, the 48MP Fusion camera on the standard iPhone 16 model uses a smaller 1/1.56" sensor.)<br/>
<br/>
The difference however is minimal, with the existing 1/1.28" sensor offering a marginally larger surface area than a 1/1.3" sensor. In practical terms, this size difference is unlikely to result in a noticeable impact on everyday photography. Apple's shift to using a smaller main camera could represent a worthwhile trade-off, with potential advancements elsewhere in the camera system to maintain or enhance overall performance. <br/>
<br/>
If the downgrade is true, Apple's shift from 1/1.28" to 1/1.3" could be due to space constraints caused by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/first-iphone-17-pro-design-leak/">rumored new camera bump design</a>.  As part of a return to using aluminum, Apple is believed to be using a larger rectangular-style camera bump on the iPhone 17 Pro models that is made from aluminum rather than glass. <br/>
<br/>
Supply chain leaks have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/12/iphone-17-pro-redesign-backed-by-supply-chain-info/">backed up</a> a report by <em>The Information</em> about a camera design change. Leaks coming out of China suggest that the module is an "elongated oval shape," rather than a rectangular shape, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/06/iphone-17-design-smoother-edge-to-back/">smoother transition</a> between the camera bump and the rear cover. The iPhone 17 series is expected to arrive around the usual mid-September time frame.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller/">iPhone 17 Pro Main Camera Sensor &#039;Smaller&#039; Than iPhone 16 Pro Sensor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller-than-iphone-16-pro-sensor.2447120/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Both iPhone 17 Pro Models Rumored to Feature Three 48MP Cameras</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/both-iphone-17-pro-models-three-48mp-cameras/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-17-pro-models-rumored-to-feature-three-48mp-cameras.2447118/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 02:35:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/both-iphone-17-pro-models-three-48mp-cameras/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Digital Chat Station</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Both the iPhone 17 Pro and the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature an upgraded 48-megapixel Tetraprism camera, making them the first iPhone models to have a rear camera system entirely made up of 48-megapixel lenses, claims a new rumor out of China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPhone-17-Pro-Dual-Tone-Horizontal-Single-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-984820" /><br/>
According to the Weibo account <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/P8WbLbOeF">Digital Chat Station</a>, the iPhone 17 Pro camera specs will include a 1/1.3" 48MP Fusion lens, a 48MP Ultra Wide lens, and a new upgraded 48MP Tetraprism telephoto lens (up from 12MP on the iPhone 16 Pro models). Both the main and telephoto cameras are said to be hybrid glass-plastic lenses. Meanwhile on the front, both Pro models will feature a 24MP front camera, said the leaker.<br/>
<br/>
The claim lines up with a prediction made by Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">June 2024 report</a>, Kuo said the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature an upgraded 48MP Tetraprism camera for enhanced photo quality and zoom functionality. Kuo said he was uncertain whether only the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature the upgraded Tetraprism camera, but today's rumor indicates that both Pro models will get the upgrade. The new camera requires all-new designed prisms, which must have a shorter form factor to reduce the camera's height, according to Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
Today's rumor also corroborates Apple analyst Jeff Pu's claim in August that all four iPhone 17 models will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/iphone-17-24mp-front-camera-rumor/">upgraded 24-megapixel front-facing camera</a>. By comparison, all iPhone 16 models have a 12-megapixel front camera. Kuo also last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/">claimed</a> that at least one iPhone 17 model would be equipped with a 24-megapixel front camera with a six-piece lens, so this upgrade has now been rumored by multiple sources, making it more likely. Kuo said these changes will "significantly improve the image quality" and low-light performance.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 17 models are expected to launch in September 2025. Apple is rumored to be introducing a new four-model lineup that drops the iPhone "Plus" model <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/06/iphone-17-air-2mm-thinner/">in favor of a slimmer device</a> that we are provisionally calling "iPhone 17 Air," while the iPhone 17 Pro models are said to have a totally redesigned half-aluminum, half-glass back cover with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/first-iphone-17-pro-design-leak/">new rectangular camera module</a> that could result in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-pro-main-camera-sensor-smaller/">smaller main camera sensor being used</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digital-chat-station/">Digital Chat Station</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/both-iphone-17-pro-models-three-48mp-cameras/">Both iPhone 17 Pro Models Rumored to Feature Three 48MP Cameras</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/both-iphone-17-pro-models-rumored-to-feature-three-48mp-cameras.2447118/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hearing a Mysterious Chime From Your AirPods Pro Case? It&#039;s a Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/09/airpods-pro-chime-sound/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hearing-a-mysterious-chime-from-your-airpods-pro-case-its-a-feature.2447096/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 15:42:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/09/airpods-pro-chime-sound/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you've been hearing a chiming sound from your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 case when the AirPods are charging, it's a feature that Apple added with the launch of Hearing Health last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/airpods-pro-2-botw.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949019" /><br/>
In a support guide, Apple says that the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; may play a sound every so often while in the case to ensure the microphones and speakers are working as intended. From Apple:<br/>
<blockquote>To help ensure that your AirPods microphones and speakers are operating at their best (for example, to help provide high-quality hearing test results), your AirPods may periodically play a quiet chime when they're in their charging case.</blockquote><br/>
Information on the mysterious chime was <a href="https://mastodon.online/@tuckerjj/113797353737201900">highlighted on Mastodon</a> after Apple's unclear AirPods sounds were discussed on today's <a href="https://atp.fm">ATP podcast</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As noted on the podcast, Apple does not have an established guide that provides insight into the different sounds that the AirPods make, so it can be confusing.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; will play a sound when battery is low or when the charging case is placed on a charger or plugged in. Some sounds can be disabled by connecting the AirPods to an Apple device, going to Settings, tapping on the AirPods icon, and turning off Enable Charging Case Sounds.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/09/airpods-pro-chime-sound/">Hearing a Mysterious Chime From Your AirPods Pro Case? It&#039;s a Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hearing-a-mysterious-chime-from-your-airpods-pro-case-its-a-feature.2447096/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
