<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 09:02:49 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>New &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Macs May Launch on Wednesday, November 8</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/new-macs-may-launch-on-november-8/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-scary-fast-macs-may-launch-on-wednesday-november-8.2408637/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 07:32:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/new-macs-may-launch-on-november-8/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple may be planning to launch new Mac models announced at its "Scary Fast" event on Wednesday, November 8, <em>MacRumors</em> has learned.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/scary-fast-apple-event-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-918418" /><br/>
At the start of the month, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/trade-in-changes-may-indicate-new-mac-this-month/"><em>MacRumors</em> reported</a> that Apple was proceeding with plans to announce at least one new Mac model in October. Apple yesterday <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">announced</a> its "Scary Fast" event for Monday, October 30, featuring a Finder hint, which virtually confirms the arrival of new Macs. Now, related information provided to <em>MacRumors</em> suggests that new Mac models could launch on Wednesday, November 8 – nine days after the "Scary Fast" event.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple product launches often take place on a Friday, there is precedent for Apple opting for the first Wednesday in November following an October event. For example, at its "There's more in the making" event on Tuesday, October 30, 2018, Apple announced new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models. The machines launched on Wednesday, November 7 – eight days later.<br/>
<br/>
Analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> says that Apple's upcoming event <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">will focus on</a> new MacBook Pro models with M3 series chips, which could include the 13-, 14-, and 16-inch models with the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips. In addition to these machines, a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> featuring the M3 chip is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/">also on the table</a> for announcement at the event.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip is widely expected to be fabricated using TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process for performance and efficiency improvements compared to the current, 5nm-based ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>‌ chip, which debuted in June 2022. It will also likely feature an all new GPU with hardware ray-tracing, first introduced on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>'s A17 Pro chip last month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/new-macs-may-launch-on-november-8/">New &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Macs May Launch on Wednesday, November 8</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-scary-fast-macs-may-launch-on-wednesday-november-8.2408637/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, and Apple News+ Receiving Price Increases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-apple-arcade-and-apple-news-receiving-price-increases.2408634/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:46:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		<category>Apple One</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it is increasing the prices of some of its subscription-based services, including Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, and Apple News+, for new and existing subscribers in the U.S. and <a href="https://www.macg.co/services/2023/10/augmentation-imminente-des-abonnements-apple-arcade-apple-tv-et-apple-one-140063">many other countries around the world</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-TV-Arcade-and-News-Price-Increase-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="910" height="511" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-918548" /><br/>
The price changes in the U.S. are as follows:<ul><li><strong>Apple TV+:</strong> &#36;6.99 per month → &#36;9.99 per month</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Arcade:</strong> &#36;4.99 per month → &#36;6.99 per month</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple News+:</strong> &#36;9.99 per month → &#36;12.99 per month</li></ul>For those who subscribe to Apple TV+ on an annual basis, the price has increased from &#36;69 per year to &#36;99 per year accordingly.<br/>
<br/>
Prices for the Apple One bundles that include these services are also increasing as a result:<ul><li><strong>Individual:</strong> &#36;16.95 per month → &#36;19.95 per month</li><br/>
<li><strong>Family:</strong> &#36;22.95 per month → &#36;25.95 per month</li><br/>
<li><strong>Premier:</strong> &#36;32.95 per month → &#36;37.95 per month</li></ul>The price increases take effect immediately for new subscribers, and in 30 days from today for existing subscribers, on their next renewal date after that grace period. Apple should send out emails to existing subscribers notifying them about the changes over time, as it did following price increases to some services last year.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., these are the first-ever price increases for Apple Arcade and Apple News+ since the services launched in November 2019, while Apple TV+ had its first price increase from &#36;4.99 per month to &#36;6.99 per month <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/24/apple-price-increase-services/">in October 2022</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a statement shared with <em>MacRumors</em>, Apple said it is "focused on delivering the best experiences possible for our customers by consistently adding high-quality entertainment, content, and innovative features to our services."<br/>
<br/>
There are no price increases for Apple Music and Apple Fitness+ today.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, and Apple News+ Receiving Price Increases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-apple-arcade-and-apple-news-receiving-price-increases.2408634/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Continues to Explore Health Capabilities of Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-explores-vision-pro-health-capabilities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-continues-to-explore-health-capabilities-of-vision-pro.2408633/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:44:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-explores-vision-pro-health-capabilities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>The Information</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has explored using its Vision Pro headset to diagnose and treat mental health problems, among other health monitoring capabilities, <a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-has-discussed-using-vision-pro-for-mental-health-diagnosis-treatment"><em>The Information</em></a>'s Wayne Ma reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
Citing sources with direct knowledge of the matter, Ma explains that Apple has experimented with using the Vision Pro to track a user's facial expressions to detect depression, anxiety, stress, post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD), and other mental health issues. Specifically, eye-tracking, pupil dilation, and external cameras can measure a person's "affect," a psychological term that refers to how an individual expresses emotions.<br/>
<br/>
A so-called "flat affect," otherwise known as an emotionless facial expression, can be a sign of specific mental health difficulties. Upon detection of such a problem, the Vision Pro would then display relevant images and play sounds that could improve the wearer's mental state. Virtual reality headsets have already been used by researchers to diagnose and treat phobias and PTSD by safely exposing patients to their fears.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also apparently discussed using the Vision Pro's infrared eye tracking-cameras to detect swelling in the blood vessels of the eyes to spot an early sign of heart failure. The company explored using the headset to detect weight changes and evaluate a user's movement over time, using this data to screen for health issues such as Parkinson's disease, but the feature had a major setback when Apple removed the full body-tracking capabilities from the Vision Pro due to unreliability.<br/>
<br/>
Features that claim to diagnose or treat health issues would need to undergo clinical studies and receive approval from health regulators before being released to the public, but some Apple employees are apparently concerned about the legal liability of making more health-related claims, which could limit the scope of the features. Other employees are said to be skeptical that the Vision Pro will be as effective as other methods of treatment, such as medicine.<br/>
<br/>
Teams and significant individuals inside Apple are said to have extensively discussed or explored health, wellness, and fitness features for the Vision Pro, including Mike Rockwell, the head of Apple's Vision Products Group. The company has reportedly hired health experts to explore features for the device. <em>The Information</em> was unable to learn whether mental health features will arrive on the first-generation Vision Pro headset, or if it will be reserved for future models. The sources added that such features may never launch at all, but the company continues to brainstorm health-related uses for the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Ma added that Apple has also explored the mental health detection capabilities of other devices such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, using the front-facing camera to track a user's mood, as well as monitor app usage and typed words to detect early signs of Alzheimer's disease.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theinformation-com/">The Information</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-explores-vision-pro-health-capabilities/">Report: Apple Continues to Explore Health Capabilities of Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-continues-to-explore-health-capabilities-of-vision-pro.2408633/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Apple Watch Ultra 1 Drops to Best-Ever Price of &#36;629 (&#36;170 Off) [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/deals-apple-watch-ultra-1-629/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apple-watch-ultra-1-drops-to-best-ever-price-of-629-170-off-updated.2408629/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 06:17:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/deals-apple-watch-ultra-1-629/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first generation Apple Watch Ultra has hit a new all-time low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT39HM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;629.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. The version on sale is the Titanium Case with Yellow/Beige Trail Loop in the S/M size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watch-ultra-1-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918496" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
There is another model on sale for slightly more at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT6Q8V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;659.00</strong></a>, but as of now these are the only first generation models of the Apple Watch Ultra on sale. This second device is the Titanium Case with Orange Alpine Loop.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHT39HM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;170 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra for &#36;629.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We aren't tracking any all-time low prices on the new Apple Watch Ultra 2 at this time, with the steepest discount on Amazon measuring <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">about &#36;25 off</a>. The second generation model is a very minor upgrade on the first generation device, so if your priority is saving money you'd do well to check out Amazon's sale on the original Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
If you want a specific breakdown on how the two wearables compare, we have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2/">Buyer's Guide</a> on the major differences between the Apple Watch Ultra and Apple Watch Ultra 2. Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This sale has expired, but you can still get the Orange Alpine Loop model for the second-best price of &#36;659.00.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/deals-apple-watch-ultra-1-629/">Deals: Apple Watch Ultra 1 Drops to Best-Ever Price of &#36;629 (&#36;170 Off) [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apple-watch-ultra-1-drops-to-best-ever-price-of-629-170-off-updated.2408629/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next-Generation iMac Chip, Stand, and Color Details Rumored Ahead of Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/next-gen-imac-details-rumored-ahead-of-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-generation-imac-chip-stand-and-color-details-rumored-ahead-of-apple-event.2408626/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 05:19:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/next-gen-imac-details-rumored-ahead-of-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> refresh will feature a new chip, an internally redesigned stand, and a similar array of color options to the current model, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iMac-M3-Blue-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917291" /><br/>
Following Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">announcement</a> of its "Scary Fast" event scheduled for Monday, October 30, <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1716872367631446288?s=20">Gurman reposted</a> a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-03-05/when-is-apple-aapl-releasing-new-mac-pro-15-inch-macbook-air-new-imac-m3-levgn4yc?sref=9hGJlFio">Power On newsletter</a> published in March on X (formerly Twitter) and reiterated several key details:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple has been planning an M3 iMac for a while, with the machine going into production months ago. No other major changes other than the chip, but the stand’s internal design has been tweaked. I’d expect colors to remain similar. <a href="https://t.co/7nm7Zyq94b">https://t.co/7nm7Zyq94b</a></p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1716872367631446288?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 24, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The main change to the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; will apparently be its processor, with the new machine featuring Apple's M3 chip. The current model has the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip and Gurman has repeatedly said that the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/06/no-m2-imac-on-the-horizon-for-2022/">skip the M2 chip entirely</a>. He previously remarked that he expects it to be "one of the company's first M3-based machines."<br/>
<br/>
Gurman mentioned the new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;'s internally redesigned stand back in March, explaining that "the computer will see some of its internal components relocated and redesigned, and the manufacturing process for attaching the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;'s stand is different." According to his latest comments, the internally redesigned stand remains on the new machine.<br/>
<br/>
The current, M1-based &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is available in green, yellow, orange, pink, purple, blue, and silver. In March, Gurman said that the new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; was being tested in orange, pink, blue, and silver finishes. Gurman has now reiterated his claim that the color options of the new machine will remain "similar," which suggests that there may still be some changes.<br/>
<br/>
The next-generation &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is otherwise expected to be the same as the current 24-inch model. Gurman's information indicates that the new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; entered mass production sometime between June and August, suggesting that it is now ready to launch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/next-gen-imac-details-rumored-ahead-of-event/">Next-Generation iMac Chip, Stand, and Color Details Rumored Ahead of Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-generation-imac-chip-stand-and-color-details-rumored-ahead-of-apple-event.2408626/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Considering Low-Cost MacBook Launch in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/kuo-apple-low-cost-macbook-launch-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-considering-low-cost-macbook-launch-in-2024.2408619/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 03:30:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/kuo-apple-low-cost-macbook-launch-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last month, a seemingly unlikely rumor out of Asia claimed that Apple could be planning to launch a low-cost MacBook series next year in order to compete with Google's popular and more affordable Chromebook models. On Tuesday, that rumor was revived by respected Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-logo-backlit-mac.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1280" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-871954" /><br/>
A <em>DigiTimes</em> report in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/apple-low-cost-macbook-rival-chromebook/">September</a> said Apple could launch a more affordable MacBook line in late 2024 to differentiate it from the company's existing MacBook Air and Pro lines. Kuo now also <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1716885306933411885?s=20">believes</a> Apple could be considering such a move to boost ailing MacBook shipments, with a target of 8-10+ million units per year. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo's prediction came in response to Apple's upcoming Mac event that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">announced</a> on Tuesday. The analyst suggested Apple's "Scary Fast" event on October 30 will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">focus on multiple M3 chips</a>, hinting at the possibility of M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max variants. If Apple does release M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips at once, they will likely feature in new 13-inch, 14-inch, and 16-inch MacBook Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo previously predicted that Apple would be unlikely to introduce new MacBook Pro models in 2023 because of "limited 4Q 23 shipments." He now says that if new MacBook Pros do come out in November or December, the tight supply will last until the first quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
The analyst said Mac shipments have declined due to the "limited M2 computing power upgrade," which may be the reason why Apple is prepared to launch M3 MacBook Pro models with low production volume. "Theoretically, the M3 should offer a more significant boost in computing power," said Kuo, but if the M3 fails to boost shipments, that may trigger Apple's plan to introduce a "more affordable MacBook model."<br/>
<br/>
According to the original report out of Taiwan, Apple's more affordable MacBooks will adopt some design changes to enable Apple to achieve the low price. While the outer appearance will still use a metal casing to maintain the distinctive Apple Mac aesthetic, it could be made of "different materials." <br/>
<br/>
If Apple does unveil a low-cost Mac, it could potentially come in the form of a new 12-inch MacBook. Introduced in March 2015, the original 12-inch MacBook featured a thin and light design that weighed just two pounds, and was Apple's first notebook to feature a fanless design, USB-C port, and butterfly switch keyboard. Unfortunately, due to Apple's use of Intel Core M processors, many felt it was too underpowered to justify its &#36;1,299 price. Apple discontinued the model in 2019.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/12-inch-MacBook-side.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853147" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple's discontinued 12-inch MacBook</em></div><br/>
Reports about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/31/12-inch-macbook-apple-silicon-this-year/">possibility of the 12-inch MacBook returning</a> have circulated ever since Apple adopted custom Apple silicon processors across its devices and began offering the M1 ‌MacBook Air‌ with a &#36;999 starting price. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">first</a> to spark serious rumors about Apple reintroducing a 12-inch MacBook model with Apple silicon, saying last year that the device could come at the end of 2023 or in 2024. In January 2023, Gurman said that a 12-inch MacBook was no longer on the company's near-term roadmap, but stopped short of ruling the device out completely, meaning that it being pushed into 2024 or later may still be possible.<br/>
<br/>
That was followed in February by another <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/15/apple-may-still-reintroduce-12-inch-macbook/">rumor</a> that Apple plans to bring the 12-inch MacBook back into its lineup. According to the report, production activities related to the device were ongoing, and Apple planned to decide whether to move forward with mass production as soon as the second half of this year. Whether this alleged activity relates to claims made by ‌<em>DigiTimes‌</em>, and now Kuo, about a low-cost MacBook remains to be seen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/kuo-apple-low-cost-macbook-launch-in-2024/">Kuo: Apple Considering Low-Cost MacBook Launch in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-considering-low-cost-macbook-launch-in-2024.2408619/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Alleged New MacBook Pro Box Image Surfaces on China&#039;s Weibo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/alleged-macbook-pro-box-image/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alleged-new-macbook-pro-box-image-surfaces-on-chinas-weibo.2408615/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 02:45:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/alleged-macbook-pro-box-image/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>ShrimpApplePro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An image allegedly showing the box for a new unreleased MacBook Pro has emerged on Chinese social media platform Weibo.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/alleged-m3-macbook-pro-box.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1243" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918435" /><br/>
The picture, re-shared on X by <a href="https://twitter.com/VNchocoTaco/status/1717105054287826967/photo/1">ShrimpApplePro</a>, shows what looks like Apple packaging featuring a MacBook Pro image with previously unseen wallpaper on the display. The wallpaper bears a passing resemblance to the one Apple used for the iPhone 15 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear whether the image is legitimate or simply faked.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">"Scary Fast" event</a> on October 30 will focus on the M3 series MacBook Pro models, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1716872016970854533"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> also says that Apple has been testing M3 Max and M3 Pro MacBook Pro models, suggesting that these machines are going to be refreshed. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman just last week claimed that Apple would not update the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips until early 2024, so it seems that his predictions have since changed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Scary fastest? <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/M3?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#M3</a> <a href="https://t.co/0YiRhCw8Ta">pic.twitter.com/0YiRhCw8Ta</a></p>&mdash; Tim Hardwick (@waxeditorial) <a href="https://twitter.com/waxeditorial/status/1716876571846586500?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 24, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
In its <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/?useASL=true">promotional graphics for the event on its website</a>, Apple has included the smiling Finder icon, essentially confirming that Macs are the focus of the event. <br/>
<br/>
Another hint that we should expect new MacBook Pro models is Apple's use of "Scary Fast" as a tagline: When Apple launched the first Apple silicon-based 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models in October 2021, the company's marketing <a href="https://x.com/waxeditorial/status/1716876571846586500?s=20">described</a> the M1 Pro as "Scary Fast" and the M1 Max as "Scary Faster."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shrimpapplepro/">ShrimpApplePro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/alleged-macbook-pro-box-image/">Alleged New MacBook Pro Box Image Surfaces on China&#039;s Weibo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alleged-new-macbook-pro-box-image-surfaces-on-chinas-weibo.2408615/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expanding Device Repair Programs for Consumers and Independent Shops</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs-for-consumers-and-independent-shops.2408561/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:29:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expanding its Self-Service Repair and Independent Repair Provider programs and will make parts, tools, and documentation needed for product repairs available to repair shops and consumers nationwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895789" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-Program-iPhone.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
The news was announced by the White House as part of an event focused on right to repair policies, and <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apple-make-tools-parts-fix-phones-computers-available-nationwide-white-house-2023-10-24/">was shared by <em>Reuters</em></a>. Apple has not yet made a formal announcement, but more information is expected later today.<br/>
<br/>
The White House is aiming for a nationwide right to repair law, which Apple is endorsing. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/">recently supported</a> right to repair legislation in California because California's bill requires all repair parts to come from Apple. Third-party components must be disclosed by non-authorized repair shops.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been offering a self-service repair program for consumers since 2022, providing genuine repair manuals, parts, and tools through its <a href="https://www.selfservicerepair.com/en-US/home">Self-Service Repair Store</a>. At the current time, Apple offers repair kits and parts for iPhones, Mac notebooks, Mac desktops, and Apple displays.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/08/29/apple-independent-repair-program/">offers a similar repair program</a> for some independent repair shops, allowing them to source genuine parts to repair out-of-warranty Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's Self-Service Repair Program is often more expensive than taking a device to an Apple retail location or Authorized Service Provider for repair, but it is a option for those who want to conduct their own repairs. Independent Repair Provider Program participants <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/02/06/apple-independent-repair-shops-contracts/">have also complained</a> about Apple's invasive contracts and high component prices.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs/">Apple Expanding Device Repair Programs for Consumers and Independent Shops</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs-for-consumers-and-independent-shops.2408561/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Overhaul TV App, Remove Standalone Apps from Apple TV</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-tv-app-revamp/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-overhaul-tv-app-remove-standalone-apps-from-apple-tv.2408557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 11:05:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-tv-app-revamp/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to overhaul the TV app in an effort to consolidate its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> streaming service and its standalone movie and TV show purchase options, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-24/apple-to-revamp-tv-app-in-step-toward-simplifying-video-services"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. A tvOS update in December will introduce the changes that Apple has planned.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-4K-hero-221018.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869591" /><br/>
To push users to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, Apple plans to remove its standalone &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; apps that are available for renting and purchasing TV shows and movies. The movie and TV show sections from the iTunes Store app on iPhones and iPads will also be eliminated.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants to push customers to the TV app, which already houses purchased movies and shows, &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; content, and third-party channels that customers can subscribe to.<br/>
<br/>
The TV app will serve as a hub for streaming content, and Gurman says the redesigned app will have a side panel at the left that can be used to navigate between different video categories.<br/>
<br/>
Updated navigation should make the TV app less confusing for consumers, making it clearer which content is from Apple and available through the &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; subscription and which content requires a separate subscription.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-tv-app-revamp/">Apple to Overhaul TV App, Remove Standalone Apps from Apple TV</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-overhaul-tv-app-remove-standalone-apps-from-apple-tv.2408557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: &#039;M3 Series MacBook Pro&#039; to Be Focus of Apple&#039;s October 30 Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-m3-series-macbook-pro-to-be-focus-of-apples-october-30-event.2408552/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:43:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 13&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming "Scary Fast" event will focus on the M3 series MacBook Pro models, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1716871328794620072">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo's wording suggests that he is expecting multiple M3 chips rather than just a single M3 chip, hinting at the possibility of M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/macbook-pro-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904044" /><br/>
If Apple does release M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips at once, we can expect to see the new chips introduced in 13-inch, 14-inch, and 16-inch MacBook Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
Kuo says that he previously predicted that Apple would not likely introduce new MacBook Pro models in 2023 because of "limited 4Q 23 shipments," and if new MacBook Pros do come out in November or December, the tight supply will last until the first quarter of 2024. Kuo <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1716885306933411885">further says</a> that Mac shipments have declined due to the "limited <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> computing power upgrade," which may be the reason why Apple might launch M3 MacBook Pro models with low production volume. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1716872016970854533"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> also says that Apple has been testing M3 Max and M3 Pro MacBook Pro models, suggesting that these machines are going to be refreshed. Gurman just last week claimed that Apple would not update the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/four-new-macbooks-on-schedule-for-launch-in-2024/">until early 2024</a>, so it seems that his predictions have since changed. <br/>
<br/>
That Kuo and Gurman are both now suggesting that we'll see 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models at Apple's October event comes as a surprise because much of their prior information pointed toward a 2024 refresh for these devices. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman maintains that Apple will not refresh the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> at this time, which leaves the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, 13-inch MacBook Pro, 14-inch MacBook Pro, and 16-inch MacBook Pro for the October event. As Gurman has previously pointed out, these are the machines that are facing extended shipping times in Apple's online store. <br/>
<br/>
According to Kuo, if the M3 models don't end up boosting MacBook shipments, there is an increased likelihood of an "all-new design MacBook Pro in 2025" and also a chance Apple will consider a "more affordable MacBook model."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro-13/">MacBook Pro 13"</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_13">13" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/kuo-m3-macbook-pro-october-30/">Kuo: &#039;M3 Series MacBook Pro&#039; to Be Focus of Apple&#039;s October 30 Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-m3-series-macbook-pro-to-be-focus-of-apples-october-30-event.2408552/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iTunes for Windows Update With Option to Listen to Podcasts and Audiobooks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/itunes-for-windows-12-13/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-itunes-for-windows-update-with-option-to-listen-to-podcasts-and-audiobooks.2408549/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:29:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/itunes-for-windows-12-13/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iTunes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released an iTunes 12.13 update for Windows users, with the update adding new functionality for podcasts and audiobooks.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-846163" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/itunes-for-windows.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
According to Apple's release notes, downloading iTunes 12.13 will allow Windows users to listen to podcasts and audiobooks through the iTunes app so long as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> apps are installed.<br/>
<br/>
iTunes for Windows is not typically updated on a regular basis, and this is the first new software release <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-itunes-for-windows-iphone-15/">since September</a> when Apple added support for new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
iTunes has been phased out on the Mac for several years now and it has been replaced with Finder and the TV app, but Apple has continued to keep the Windows version available.<br/>
<br/>
iTunes for Windows can be downloaded from the <a href="https://apps.microsoft.com/store/detail/itunes/9PB2MZ1ZMB1S?hl=en-us&amp;gl=US">Microsoft Store</a> or <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT210384">from Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itunes/">iTunes</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-apps.2">Mac Apps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/itunes-for-windows-12-13/">Apple Releases iTunes for Windows Update With Option to Listen to Podcasts and Audiobooks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-itunes-for-windows-update-with-option-to-listen-to-podcasts-and-audiobooks.2408549/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pay Later Officially Launches in U.S. Following Early Access Period</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-pay-later-launches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-later-officially-launches-in-u-s-following-early-access-period.2408548/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 10:22:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-pay-later-launches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Pay Later</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Pay Later appears to have officially launched for all qualifying U.S. residents today, as it is now widely available in the Wallet app on the iPhone. The feature had been available on an invite-only "early access" basis <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/28/apple-pay-later-early-access/">since March</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/Apple-Pay-Later.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893903" /><br/>
Apple removed the following sentence from all Apple Pay Later support documents today:<blockquote>Apple Pay Later is currently only available to customers invited to access a prerelease version.</blockquote>Apple Pay Later is a "buy now, pay later" feature that lets qualifying customers split a purchase made with Apple Pay into four equal payments over six weeks, with no interest or fees. The feature is available for eligible purchases between &#36;75 and &#36;1,000 made on an iPhone or iPad on most websites and apps that accept Apple Pay.<br/>
<br/>
The minimum purchase amount required to use Apple Pay Later was &#36;50 during the early access period, but Apple has now raised it to &#36;75.<br/>
<br/>
Every purchase made using Apple Pay Later is a separate loan and requires a new application, which has no impact on your credit score, according to Apple. The feature is available to U.S. residents who are 18 years of age or older. Apple Pay Later is currently unavailable in Hawaii, New Mexico, Wisconsin, and the U.S. territories.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Pay Later is part of the Wallet app on the iPhone, and found in the Settings app under Wallet & Apple Pay on the iPad. Users can view, track, and manage loans, with upcoming payments shown on a calendar and payment reminders sent via Wallet notifications and email. Users must set up a debit card as a loan repayment method.<br/>
<br/>
A software researcher known as @aaronp613 had <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1716092920338559385">previously discovered</a> that Apple Pay Later would launch by November 1 following invite-only testing.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pay-later/">Apple Pay Later</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-pay-later-launches/">Apple Pay Later Officially Launches in U.S. Following Early Access Period</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-later-officially-launches-in-u-s-following-early-access-period.2408548/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Adds &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Event Livestream Placeholder to YouTube and Website</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-scary-fast-event-livestream/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-scary-fast-event-livestream-placeholder-to-youtube-and-website.2408544/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:55:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-scary-fast-event-livestream/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Event</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing for the upcoming Mac-focused "Scary Fast" event that is set to take place on Monday, October 30 at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time, and the company has added livestream placeholders both to the Events website and to YouTube.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ctkW3V0Mh-k" title="Apple Event - October 30" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
On <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/?useASL=true">the Events website</a>, Apple has added an option to add the event to your calendar, and on YouTube, there is an option to get a reminder when the event begins. While the YouTube placeholder features a static Apple logo, Apple's Events website includes an animated logo that morphs into a Finder icon, hinting at the subject of the event.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has never held a worldwide event at night before, so this is a first for the company. The livestream will begin at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time on the night before Halloween, which equates to 8:00 p.m. Eastern Time, 12:00 a.m. in the UK, 1:00 to 2:00 a.m. in much of continental Europe, and 9:00 a.m. in several countries in Asia.<br/>
<br/>
Given the late hour of the event, it will be online only, with no in-person component. The "Scary Fast" event will be able to be streamed via the Events website, on YouTube, and through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> will have full coverage of the September 12 event as well, both on MacRumors.com and through our <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive?lang=en">MacRumorsLive Twitter account</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-event/">Apple Event</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-scary-fast-event-livestream/">Apple Adds &#039;Scary Fast&#039; Event Livestream Placeholder to YouTube and Website</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-adds-scary-fast-event-livestream-placeholder-to-youtube-and-website.2408544/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces October Event for Macs: &#039;Scary Fast&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-october-event-for-macs-scary-fast.2408536/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:01:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Event</category>
		<category>October 2023 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced its second fall event of 2023, with the online event set to be held on Monday, October 30 at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time. Apple's October event will be about the Mac, and the company is expected to refresh several Macs in the lineup. Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">Events website</a> features an Apple logo on a black background that morphs into the Mac Finder icon, confirming the event's Mac focus. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-october-scary-fast-event.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918335" /><br/>
As with prior events, this October event will be prerecorded, and it will be held online only with no in-person component.<br/>
<br/>
Mac rumors have been confusing in recent months, but there are several possibilities. We could see a refreshed version of the 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, as that machine is still using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> Apple silicon chip. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/gurman-apple-to-announce-new-macs-this-month/">not to expect a MacBook Air refresh</a>, but the 13-inch MacBook Pro, 14-inch MacBook Pro, and 16-inch MacBook Pro could potentially get new chips.<br/>
<br/>
It is not clear if the refresh will focus on new M3-series chips, but depending on what's being overhauled, we could see the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; and the MacBook Pro models adopting the 3-nanometer M3 chip lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/w3edrMIXMKw" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Given the confusion surrounding the Mac lineup right now, this is one of the more mysterious events we've had, though we are likely to hear more as October 30 approaches.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to stream the event <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">live on its website</a>, on YouTube, and through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app. For those unable to watch, MacRumors will be providing full event coverage on MacRumors.com and the <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive Twitter account</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-event/">Apple Event</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/october-2023-apple-event/">October 2023 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">Apple Announces October Event for Macs: &#039;Scary Fast&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-october-event-for-macs-scary-fast.2408536/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Webex App Will Soon Be Available on Apple TV for Video Conferencing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/webex-app-will-soon-be-available-on-apple-tv-for-video-conferencing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/webex-app-will-soon-be-available-on-apple-tv-for-video-conferencing.2408535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/webex-app-will-soon-be-available-on-apple-tv-for-video-conferencing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Cisco today <a href="https://blog.webex.com/hybrid-work/webex-apple-watch-and-tv/">announced</a> that its Webex Meetings app will soon be available for the Apple TV, allowing for video conferencing on a TV.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-TV-2x2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918248" /><br/>
tvOS 17's new Continuity Camera support will allow Webex users to wirelessly connect their iPhone or iPad to the second-generation Apple TV 4K or newer and use the device's camera and microphone to participate in meetings. After installing the Webex app on the Apple TV, users will scan a QR code on the TV with their iPhone to log in.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/06/tvos-17-brings-facetime-and-video-conferencing-to-apple-tv-4k/">announced</a> that video conferencing apps like Webex and Zoom would launch on the Apple TV later this year. Continuity Camera is the same feature that powers Apple's own FaceTime app for video calls on tvOS 17.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/webex-app-will-soon-be-available-on-apple-tv-for-video-conferencing/">Webex App Will Soon Be Available on Apple TV for Video Conferencing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/webex-app-will-soon-be-available-on-apple-tv-for-video-conferencing.2408535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stores Begin Same-Unit iPhone 15 Repairs as Parts Now Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/iphone-15-same-unit-repairs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-begin-same-unit-iphone-15-repairs-as-parts-now-available.2408534/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 08:54:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/iphone-15-same-unit-repairs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Authorized Service Providers</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For a brief period following the release of new iPhone models, Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers must replace the entire device if a customer requires a repair, as individual parts are not immediately available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Internal-Chassis.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910920" /><br/>
Starting this week, parts are available for all four iPhone 15 models, allowing Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers to complete same-unit repairs for these devices, according to an internal memo obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>. This includes the back glass, battery, speakers, display, rear camera, and mid-frame.<br/>
<br/>
A whole-unit replacement is still required for repairs involving the Taptic Engine or the main microphone on the iPhone 15 Pro or the iPhone 15 Pro Max, as those parts will not be available until a later time, according to the memo.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models are equipped with removable back glass, allowing technicians to open the devices from both the front and back sides for repairs. This change results in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/">significantly lower repair fees</a> for iPhone 15 models with cracked back glass for customers without AppleCare+ compared to models without removable back glass. Apple first made this design change with the lower-end iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus last year.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple's battery replacement fee is set at &#36;99 for all four iPhone 15 models, which is unchanged from the iPhone 14 series.<br/>
<br/>
To book an iPhone 15 repair appointment, visit <a href="https://getsupport.apple.com/">Apple's Get Support page</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aasp/">Apple Authorized Service Providers</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/iphone-15-same-unit-repairs/">Apple Stores Begin Same-Unit iPhone 15 Repairs as Parts Now Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stores-begin-same-unit-iphone-15-repairs-as-parts-now-available.2408534/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Accessory Maker Pad &amp; Quill Shutting Down, Offering 50% Off Sitewide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/pad-quill-shutting-down/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-accessory-maker-pad-quill-shutting-down-offering-50-off-sitewide.2408529/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:47:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/pad-quill-shutting-down/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Pad &amp;amp; Quill</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular Apple accessory maker <a href="https://www.padandquill.com">Pad & Quill</a> has announced that it is going out of business, and in the process it is offering shoppers 50 percent off everything on its website. Pad & Quill sells a wide variety of Apple product accessories, so this event covers everything from iPhone cases to iPad folios, laptop bags, and Apple Watch bands.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Pad-and-Quill-Winter-Clearance-Sale-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-789821" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Pad & Quill. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Pad & Quill has been known for its high-quality leather accessories for over a decade now, following its debut in 2010. The company began with a focus on iPad and iPhone cases and expanded to unique leather goods including large bags, wallets, journals, and other Apple-related accessories like Apple Watch bands.<br/>
<br/>
Regarding the closure, Pad & Quill President Brian Holmes stated: "We at Pad & Quill have had headwinds that are too large to overcome, and we have decided to close the business. We are thankful for our customers over the years. It's been a blast creating unique accessories for Apple products."<br/>
<br/>
In terms of the going out of business sale, shoppers should note that all purchases made during this event are final. This is a huge sale, covering everything on Pad & Quill's website, so we've highlighted a few of the best on offer below. A selection of the items on sale even reach beyond 50 percent off.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.padandquill.com"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">50% OFF SITEWIDE</div>Pad & Quill Going Out Of Business Sale</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://www.padandquill.com/leather-techfolio-pro-cord-organizer.html">Techfolio PRO Leather Cord Organizer</a> - &#36;44.99, down from &#36;179.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.padandquill.com/pocket-book-wallet-case-iphone-15-pro-max.html">Pocket Book Wallet Case for iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> - &#36;49.98, down from &#36;99.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.padandquill.com/cartella-2021-macbook-pro-16-inch-case.html">Cartella Slim Case for 16-inch MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;64.98, down from &#36;129.95</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.padandquill.com/oxford-slim-leather-ipad-pro-case-11.html">Oxford Slim Leather Case for 11-inch iPad Pro</a> - &#36;69.98, down from &#36;139.95</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/pad-quill/">Pad &amp; Quill</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/pad-quill-shutting-down/">Apple Accessory Maker Pad &amp; Quill Shutting Down, Offering 50% Off Sitewide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-accessory-maker-pad-quill-shutting-down-offering-50-off-sitewide.2408529/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE 3: Everything We Know So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-watch-se-3-everything-we-know/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2408525/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 07:05:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-watch-se-3-everything-we-know/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> is expected to launch next year, but with few rumors about the new low-cost Apple smartwatch, what can we expect to see?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Watch-SE-3-Mock-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-918243" /><br/>
Earlier this year, technology research firm Omdia <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/08/apple-watch-series-x-larger-display-rumor/">reported</a> that the third-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; will feature the same display sizes as the Apple Watch Series 8. The Apple Watch Series 8 and Series 9 have the same display size as the Apple Watch Series 7, which introduced a slightly more rounded and larger casing design to accommodate bigger displays that have slimmer bezels.<br/>
<br/>
As such, it seems highly likely that the third-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; will adopt the design of the Apple Watch Series 7, as well as its larger displays and casing sizes. This means it would be available in 41mm and 45mm case sizes, compared to 40mm and 44mm for the current &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, providing almost 20% more display area.<br/>
<br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; features the S8 chip, which is based on the A13 Bionic and effectively analogous to the previous S6 and S7 chips. With a third-generation version of the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, it is highly likely that the device will get an upgrade to the S9 chip, which is based on A15 Bionic chip, at minimum. It could even get the "S10" chip from next year's other Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
The S9 contains 60% more transistors to deliver 30% faster performance compared to the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;'s S8 chip. It also has a four-core Neural Engine that is up to twice as fast. These improvements allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> requests to be processed on-device, resulting in quicker and more reliable responses, as well as access to health and fitness data. Dictation is also 25% more accurate as a result of the processor bump.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-se-vs-series-9/">Apple Watch SE vs. Series 9 Buyer's Guide: 25+ Differences Compared</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; features Apple's second-generation optical heart sensor. Apple introduced the third-generation optical heart sensor on the Series 6 back in 2020, so in 2024, it could finally be time to bring the updated sensor to the low-cost Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Fast charging was introduced on the Apple Watch Series 7 to reach up to 80% charge in about 45 minutes. The functionality was withheld from the second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;, but it seems like a feature that Apple could decide to finally bring over with the third-generation of the device. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>What Will Stay the Same?</h3><br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; introduced a color-matched nylon composite back case to reduce costs. The third-generation model is likely to carry over this feature, reserving the more premium ceramic back case for the main Apple Watch line.<br/>
<br/>
The blood oxygen sensor and Blood Oxygen app, electrical heart sensor and ECG app, and body temperature sensing functionality are likely to be exluded from the third-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj;. Both the first- and second-generation &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; models have offered a more basic selection of health monitoring features, with Apple upselling customers to the main Apple Watch series to obtain capabilities like ECG capture. If it does gain any new health features from the main Apple Watch line, ECG is the most likely since it was introduced on 2018's Series 4.<br/>
<br/>
Likewise, the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; has never possessed an Ultra Wideband chip, so the chance of Apple giving the new model the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip also seems slim.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Release Date</h3><br/>
The previous generations of the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; launched in September 2020 and September 2022, as outlined in the <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">MacRumors Buyer's Guide</a>. The &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/30/no-apple-watch-se-3-expected-this-year/">stick to a two-year upgrade cycle</a> going forward, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, suggesting that the third-generation model will arrive in September 2024.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-watch-se-3-everything-we-know/">Apple Watch SE 3: Everything We Know So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-3-everything-we-know-so-far.2408525/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad and MacBook Rumored to Feature Specialized Display Materials</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/oled-ipad-and-macbook-specialized-materials/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-and-macbook-rumored-to-feature-specialized-display-materials.2408513/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 05:06:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/oled-ipad-and-macbook-specialized-materials/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>LG Display</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and MacBook models equipped with OLED panels will adopt new, specialized display materials, <a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=23616"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/Oled-iPads-and-MackBook-Pro-Notch.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1403" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-824300" /><br/>
Apple has apparently collaborated with LG Display to integrate new OLED material sets in some of its future devices, including forthcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and MacBook models. LG's "RDE" OLED material set will apparently be used in the upcoming 11- and 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, while a next-generation MacBook, slated to launch in 2027, will adopt LG's subsequent "RDG" OLED material set.<br/>
<br/>
Historically, LG Display's initial "RD" series material set was indiscriminately applied to both IT products and vehicles, but with "RDE" and subsequent sets, LG aims to demarcate its OLED materials, ensuring specialized applications for different industries. This means that future OLED Apple devices will have access to an OLED materials set that is tailored for its unique requirements.<br/>
<br/>
The OLED panels designed for upcoming &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and MacBook models features a two-stack tandem structure, which consists of two light-emitting layers stacked together. The two-stack OLED design can generate the same brightness levels as its single-stack counterparts, but with significantly reduced power consumption and extended lifespan. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> currently uses a single stack OLED display with one light-emitting layer.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg-display/">LG Display</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/oled-ipad-and-macbook-specialized-materials/">OLED iPad and MacBook Rumored to Feature Specialized Display Materials</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-and-macbook-rumored-to-feature-specialized-display-materials.2408513/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1: How to Shuffle a Photo Album on Your Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-how-to-shuffle-a-photo-album-on-your-lock-screen.2408507/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 04:11:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album&#038;post_date=1698156665/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to release iOS 17.1 this week, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-1-beta-features/">amongst other features</a> the update includes a new Lock Screen personalization option for iPhones. Here's how to make your Lock Screen wallpaper shuffle through photos from a specific album in your photo library.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/shuffle-photos-lock-screen.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848808" /><br/>
In recent versions of iOS, Apple has made it possible for users to customize the Lock Screen in ways that were simply not possible in earlier versions of its mobile software, and one feature in particular that has proven popular is the ability to shuffle photos on your Lock Screen wallpaper at specific intervals or whenever you wake or tap the screen. <br/>
<br/>
In iOS 17.1, Apple has extended this feature so that you can now shuffle pictures from a specific album from your photo library, rather than having to manually select individual photos or rely on Apple's preset options of People, Pets, Nature, and Cities. The following steps show you how it's done on iPhones running iOS 17.1.<br/>
<ol><li>Wake your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> to unlock it, but don't swipe up on the Lock Screen.</li><br/>
<li>Press and hold on the Lock Screen until the wallpaper gallery appears, then tap the blue <strong>+</strong> button in the bottom-right corner of the screen.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Photo Shuffle</strong> from the wallpaper menu.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/lock-screen-photo-shuffle.jpg" alt="Lock Screen" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918216" /><br/>
<li>Tap the new <strong>Album</strong> option, then choose the album of photos from your library that you'd like to shuffle between.</li><br/>
<li>Next, choose a <strong>Shuffle Frequency</strong>: <strong>Daily</strong>, <strong>Hourly</strong>, <strong>On Lock</strong>, or <strong>On Tap</strong>.<br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Use Album</strong> to move on.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/choose-shuffle-album.jpg" alt="shuffle" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918217" /><br/>
<li>Tap the screen to preview the photos in your chosen album as they will appear on your Lock Screen, and tap the clock to adjust the font style and color so that the time, date, and any widgets remain legible against all of your pictures.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Done</strong> in the top-right corner to finish, then choose either <strong>Set as Wallpaper Pair</strong> to finish or <strong>Customize Home Screen</strong> to tweak its look separately, then tap <strong>Done</strong>.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/photo-shuffle-preview.jpg" alt="photo shuffle" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918219" /></ol>Tap your new album-specific photo shuffle wallpaper in the gallery to make it live. Then you can tap or wake your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s screen to change the photo, or wait for it to change automatically, depending on your chosen option.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-lock-screen-shuffle-between-photos-album/">iOS 17.1: How to Shuffle a Photo Album on Your Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-how-to-shuffle-a-photo-album-on-your-lock-screen.2408507/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
