<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 02:03:31 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify&#039;s Car Thing Accessory is Officially Dead</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/spotify-car-thing-officially-dead/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotifys-car-thing-accessory-is-officially-dead.2445072/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 16:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/spotify-car-thing-officially-dead/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify today shut down all Car Thing accessories, several months after announcing plans to discontinue the product. As of this week, Car Thing is no longer functional and will not work with the Spotify streaming service.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/spotify-car-thing-1.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="1879" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793755" /><br/>
Car Thing owners who power on the device now only see the following message:<blockquote>Car Thing is discontinued and no longer operational.<br/>
<br/>
Thank you for being on this journey with us, safe travels. For more information, visit carthing.com Contact customer service by no later than January 14, 2025 to discuss your refund options.</blockquote>Spotify's Car Thing was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/13/spotify-announces-the-car-thing-hardware-device/">first introduced</a> in April 2021, and it was Spotify's first hardware product. The accessory was designed to provide simple access to Spotify music while in a vehicle, and it was especially useful in vehicles without modern infotainment systems.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/29/spotify-stops-making-dash-mounted-car-thing/">stopped making Car Thing</a> just five months after it launched due to low product demand and supply chain issues. Existing Car Thing accessories continued to function as expected, until this week.<br/>
<br/>
Back in May, Spotify announced that it was discontinuing Car Thing, and earlier this month, it told customers that the device would stop working at some point in December. Spotify says that Car Thing was discontinued in an effort to streamline product offerings.<br/>
<br/>
Car Thing cost &#36;90 when it launched, and existing units are entirely non-operational now that Spotify has decided to brick them. Spotify has directed customers to recycle their Car Things.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/spotify-car-thing-officially-dead/">Spotify&#039;s Car Thing Accessory is Officially Dead</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotifys-car-thing-accessory-is-officially-dead.2445072/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Keep Track of Your Passport With Satechi&#039;s Wallet With Find My Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/satechi-passport-cover-find-my/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-keep-track-of-your-passport-with-satechis-wallet-with-find-my-support.2445071/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 16:06:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/satechi-passport-cover-find-my&#038;post_date=1733886419/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Satechi recently came out with <a href="https://satechi.net/products/vegan-leather-passport-cover-with-find-my">a Find My wallet</a> that's designed to work with a passport, allowing you to keep tabs on your most important documents when you're traveling.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/satechi-wallet-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981478" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;60, the Passport Cover with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> is made from a simple but attractive black vegan leather material. It has a book-like shape and it is sized to hold a passport on one side, with four card slots for IDs and credit cards on the other side. There's also a pocket that can be used for holding money or an airline ticket.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately, there is no strap, zipper, or other closure method included, so if you have it stuffed with several things, there is a possibility that something could come out. Cards slot into the holders and there's also a holder for the passport, but it would be nice to have an extra layer of security keeping everything closed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/satechi-wallet-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981479" /><br/>
Satechi's Passport Cover can be added to the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app alongside AirTags and other Find My-equipped devices. It is able to be tracked through the "Items" tab in the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app, and setup is as simple as pushing a button and holding it near the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
All of the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; features are included, so the Passport Cover can be tracked on a map with directions to it, it can play a sound out loud, and you can get alerts when it is left behind and separated from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; devices use the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network when you're out of range, so if someone's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is near the Passport Cover, you'll be updated with its location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/satechi-wallet-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981480" /><br/>
There is a built-in battery that Satechi says lasts for up to five months. It can be recharged using Qi, Qi2, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, so while there is no cable to hassle with, you do need to have a wireless charger available. I much prefer the Qi-based charging to charging with a cable, and there is a ring on the front that lets you know where to charge.<br/>
<br/>
The four card slots inside the Passport Cover have RFID protection to prevent card skimming from contactless credit cards for peace of mind.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/satechi-wallet-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981481" /><br/>
I haven't had the Passport Cover on hand long enough to test its longevity, but the material is soft to the touch, pleasant to hold, and it feels durable. It is worth noting that while Satechi calls this a vegan leather, the texture does not resemble leather and it will not develop the same patina over time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
There are passport holders that have built-in slots for AirTags, but Satechi's Passport Cover is sleeker and more convenient with built-in wireless charging. There are also several other &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; passport holders on the market, but many of them are more expensive. Some are cheaper, but for something as important as a passport, it's a good idea to go with a recognized brand.<br/>
<br/>
If you're someone who travels often or if you have a big trip coming up where you want to make sure you can keep an eye on your passport, Satechi's Passport Cover is worth considering.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
Satechi's Passport Cover with &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; can be <a href="https://satechi.net/products/vegan-leather-passport-cover-with-find-my">purchased from the Satechi website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSatechi-Passport-Wireless-Charging-protection%2Fdp%2FB0DC1PLG2L">from Amazon</a> for &#36;59.99.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Satechi provided MacRumors with a Passport Cover for the purpose of the review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/satechi-passport-cover-find-my/">Review: Keep Track of Your Passport With Satechi&#039;s Wallet With Find My Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-keep-track-of-your-passport-with-satechis-wallet-with-find-my-support.2445071/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Yelp Gets New AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/yelp-gets-new-ai-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/yelp-gets-new-ai-features.2445070/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:59:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/yelp-gets-new-ai-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Yelp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Yelp <a href="https://blog.yelp.com/news/end-of-year-product-release-2024/">today announced</a> several new features powered by artificial intelligence, including a new integration with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> that's available to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users and an option for summarizing review content.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/yelp.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981473" /><br/>
Review Insights uses large language models to surface reviews and information tailored to details that you are looking for when searching for a restaurant or other location to visit. Review Insights can discern reviewer sentiment about food quality, service, ambiance, wait time, and drinks. The LLM behind the feature can understand context in a review to provide relevant information even if a a key word you're looking for isn't in a review.<br/>
<br/>
Yelp says that Review Insights are aggregated as sentiment scores that range from 1 to 100 and are positive, neutral, or critical. Tapping into the score provides the review related to a specific topic of interest. Review insights are available for restaurant, food, and nightlife businesses on iOS devices.<br/>
<br/>
The Yelp homepage is gaining more personalized content and trending searches to make it easier to find new places to visit, and the company is testing AI videos that use real photos, videos, and information from Yelp to create videos about local restaurants. Unfortunately, the homepage is gaining autoplay user videos that unmute and expand to full screen<br/>
<br/>
Business pages will now show information on a location's tipping policies and payment policies, and Yelp Assistant allows for quote requests using texts and calls after a project is submitted.<br/>
<br/>
In &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj;, there's a new integration for connecting directly to pros and requesting a quote via Yelp. &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; has a "Quote" button on businesses pages that links to the Request a Quote flow in the Yelp app or the Yelp mobile web experience.<br/>
<br/>
The new Yelp features are available to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users starting today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/yelp/">Yelp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/yelp-gets-new-ai-features/">Yelp Gets New AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/yelp-gets-new-ai-features.2445070/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tap to Pay on iPhone Launches in Chile</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-chile/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-launches-in-chile.2445067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:27:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-chile/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Chile</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today launched Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in Chile, which means independent sellers, small businesses, and other merchants in the country can use an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a contactless payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-chile.jpg" alt="" width="1254" height="707" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981465" /><br/>
With Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is able to accept payment using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, contactless credit and debit cards, and other digital wallets using NFC technology. Transactions are encrypted and Apple does not have information about what is purchased or the person that made the purchase.<br/>
<br/>
On the customer end, using Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; works like any standard &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; transaction. Sellers open up an app on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS or later, register a sale, and present an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the buyer, who can then use a contactless payment method to complete the transaction.<br/>
<br/>
In Chile, SumUp is supporting the Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; feature for merchants. SumUp is known for its iPhone-connected card reader, and the Tap to Pay feature uses the same infrastructure, but without the need for additional hardware.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; launched in February 2022 in the United States, and since then, Apple has been working to expand it to additional countries. The feature is available in Australia, Austria, Brazil, Canada, Chile, Czech Republic, France, Germany, Ireland, Italy, Japan, New Zealand, Netherlands, Romania, Sweden, Taiwan, Ukraine, United Arab Emirates, the United Kingdom, and the United States.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chile/">Chile</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-chile/">Tap to Pay on iPhone Launches in Chile</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-launches-in-chile.2445067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Wrap Up Your Holiday Shopping With Our Exclusive Apple Accessory Sales at Satechi, Nomad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/wrap-up-your-holiday-shopping-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wrap-up-your-holiday-shopping-with-our-exclusive-apple-accessory-sales-at-satechi-nomad-and-more.2445066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:47:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/wrap-up-your-holiday-shopping-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're already just two weeks away from the Christmas holiday, so in an effort to aid in any last-minute holiday shopping we've accumulated a list of exclusive sales from popular Apple accessory companies. These sales offer the perfect chance to do some online Christmas shopping before it's too late for items to arrive before the 25th.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/2021-Exclusive-Apple-Accessories-Deals-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828174" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In total, you'll find exclusive offers from <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=satechi%2Enet%2F&afftrack=">Satechi</a>, <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2F&afftrack=">Twelve South</a>, <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2F">Nomad</a>, <a href="https://www.pjatr.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2F%3Fsource%3Daffiliate%26utm_medium%3Dpepperjam%26publisherId%3D164757%26clickId%3D4943130754">Nimble</a>, and <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">Grid Studio</a>. These exclusive deals run the gamut of Apple accessories, and you can shop for iPhone cases, MacBook sleeves, Apple Watch bands, screen protectors, bags, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
Each sale has a different end date, and shipping will vary from site-to-site, so be sure to read on for more information. Most brands are still offering delivery for Christmas, as long as you place orders soon. Every sale below is exclusive to our readers, and will require a coupon code, which you can find listed below as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=satechi%2Enet%2F&afftrack=">Satechi</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/2021-Exclusive-Apple-Accessories-Deals-Satechi.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828181" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 30% off sitewide with <strong>MACRUMORS30</strong></li><br/>
<li><strong>How long does it last?</strong> It ends on December 23</li><br/>
<li><strong>What do they sell?</strong> <a href="http://shrsl.com/4s3zn">USB-C hubs</a>, <a href="http://shrsl.com/4s3zp">MagSafe-compatible chargers</a>, <a href="http://shrsl.com/4s3zq">keyboards</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=satechi%2Enet%2F&afftrack="target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">30% OFF</div>Satechi Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=satechi%2Enet%2F&afftrack=">Satechi</a> is well known for its large collection of charging products, and with our exclusive code you can take 30 percent off sitewide, even on already-discounted products. The company sells portable batteries, USB-C hubs, wireless chargers that are compatible with MagSafe, and more. The exclusive code has a few exclusions on select new and upcoming products, but otherwise will work on any product sitewide.<br/>
<br/>
One of the best products to use the coupon on is the <a href="http://shrsl.com/4s408">Qi2 Trio Wireless Charging Pad</a>, which is priced at just &#36;70 with our code, down from &#36;129.99. Our code is compatible with all of <a href="http://shrsl.com/4s40c">Satechi's new Qi2 chargers and hubs</a>, making solid gift options for tech lovers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2F">Nomad</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/2021-Exclusive-Apple-Accessories-Deals-Nomad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828179" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save 20% off sitewide with code <strong>MACRUMORS2024</strong></li><br/>
<li><strong>How long does it last?</strong> It ends on December 15</li><br/>
<li><strong>What do they sell?</strong> <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fphone-cases">iPhone 16 cases</a>, <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fheadphone-cases">AirPods cases</a>, <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fpower">MagSafe-compatible accessories</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>Nomad Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Over at <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2F">Nomad</a>, you can get 20 percent off all in stock and full price items sitewide with our exclusive code MACRUMORS2024. This sale will last through December 15, and most things on Nomad's website are in stock and ready to ship for Christmas.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad offers a variety of high-quality accessories for Apple products, like the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fproducts%2Fbase-max-carbide-qi2">Base One Max wireless charger</a>, <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fipad">folio cases for iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fscreen-protectors">iPhone 16 screen protectors</a>, and even a <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14527713?url=https%3A%2F%2Fnomadgoods.com%2Fcollections%2Fbands">variety of straps for the Apple Watch</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://www.pjatr.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2F%3Fsource%3Daffiliate%26utm_medium%3Dpepperjam%26publisherId%3D164757%26clickId%3D4943130754">Nimble</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/2021-Exclusive-Apple-Accessories-Deals-Nimble.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828178" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 20 percent off your order with <strong>MACRUMORS20</strong></li><br/>
<li><strong>How long does it last?</strong> It ends on December 20</li><br/>
<li><strong>What do they sell?</strong> <a href="https://www.gopjn.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fportable-battery-chargers">Eco-friendly portable chargers</a>, <a href="https://www.pjtra.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fwireless-charging">wireless chargers</a>, <a href="https://www.pntrac.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2Fcollections%2Fphone-cases">iPhone cases</a></li></ul> <br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.pjatr.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2F%3Fsource%3Daffiliate%26utm_medium%3Dpepperjam%26publisherId%3D164757%26clickId%3D4943130754"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">30% OFF</div>Nimble Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
Eco-friendly brand <a href="https://www.pjatr.com/t/TUJGR0hHSEJGS0lMSkxCRk5KSk1N?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.gonimble.com%2F%3Fsource%3Daffiliate%26utm_medium%3Dpepperjam%26publisherId%3D164757%26clickId%3D4943130754">Nimble</a> is offering our readers 20 percent off their order this holiday season with the exclusive promo code MACRUMORS20. With this promotion you can save on Nimble's portable chargers, wireless chargers, iPhone cases, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Nimble's products are made from highly sustainable materials and come inside plastic-free packaging. The company also runs a one-for-one tech recovery project, placing a disposable bag with every product it sells. In these bags, customers can send back their old or unused tech so that it can be recycled responsibly.<br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should note that our code only works on Nimble's website and can not be used on any of Nimble's products that are available exclusively on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-Accessories-Deals-2024-Grid-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981381" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 20 percent off sitewide with <strong>MacRumors20</strong></li><br/>
<li><strong>How long does it last?</strong> It ends on December 31</li><br/>
<li><strong>What do they sell?</strong> Disassembled and framed versions of old products like <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-ipod-classic-3rd-generation">iPods</a>, <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/game-boy-color">Nintendo consoles</a>, and more</li></ul> <br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://gridstudio.cc/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>GRID Studio Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio buys and recycles old electronics, taking them apart and arranging each component carefully under a glass frame. Their work turns a hodgepodge of parts into display pieces designed for Apple enthusiasts who want to own a piece of Apple's history. You can also find similar frames for products from Nintendo, Sony, BlackBerry, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2F&afftrack=">Twelve South</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/2021-Exclusive-Apple-Accessories-Deals-Twelve-South.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828182" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 15 percent off orders of &#36;150 or more with <strong>MacRumors</strong></li><br/>
<li><strong>How long does it last?</strong> It ends on December 22</li><br/>
<li><strong>What do they sell?</strong> Products designed specifically for Apple devices like <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2Fproducts%2Fbutterfly%2Dse%2D2%2Din%2D1%2Dqi2%2Dcharger&afftrack=">iPhone chargers</a>, <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2Fproducts%2Fbookarc%2Dflex&afftrack=">MacBook stands</a>, and more</li></ul> <br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2F&afftrack="target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">15% OFF</div>Twelve South Sitewide Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
At <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=www%2Etwelvesouth%2Ecom%2F&afftrack=">Twelve South</a>, you can get 15 percent off your order worth &#36;150 or more with the promo code MacRumors. This promo code will last through December 22 for users in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
Twelve South has numerous accessories that are specifically made for Apple products, like AirSnap for AirPods, HiRise Wireless for iPhone, and BookBook for iPad Pro. You can browse for some holiday shopping ideas of your own on Twelve South's website, and shoppers should note that the code will not work on any items that are available for pre-order.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find during the holiday season? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/wrap-up-your-holiday-shopping-2024/">Wrap Up Your Holiday Shopping With Our Exclusive Apple Accessory Sales at Satechi, Nomad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/wrap-up-your-holiday-shopping-with-our-exclusive-apple-accessory-sales-at-satechi-nomad-and-more.2445066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Lets Creators Test Content With Trial Reels Feature</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/instagram-trial-reels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-lets-creators-test-content-with-trial-reels-feature.2445063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:26:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/instagram-trial-reels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram today gained a <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2024/12/trial-reels-try-content-non-followers-first-see-what-perfoms-best/">new trial reels feature</a>, which is designed to allow content creators to try out new formants and content to see what performs best. Trial reels are shared with people who do not follow a creator, giving insights into what performs well so it can then be shared with followers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786417" /><br/>
Trial Reels let creators experiment with new ideas and post frequency without worrying about losing followers or creating content that followers don't want to see. Instagram says that the feature will "help take the guesswork out of how your content will perform."<br/>
<br/>
Content that is performing well in a trial reel can be shared with followers with a tap, or it can be set to be shared with followers automatically if it's performed well after the trial period.<br/>
<br/>
Sharing a trial reel can be done by creating a reel and then tapping on the "Trial" toggle when uploading it. Trial reels are not shown to people on the creator's main grid or the Reels tab unless they are lated shared with all users.<br/>
<br/>
The trial period lasts for 24 hours, and then Instagram provides key engagement metrics like views, likes, comments, and shares so creators can see how the content is performing.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/instagram-trial-reels/">Instagram Lets Creators Test Content With Trial Reels Feature</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-lets-creators-test-content-with-trial-reels-feature.2445063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Investment in the UK Exceeds £18 Billion</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apples-investment-in-the-uk-exceeds-18-billion/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-investment-in-the-uk-exceeds-£18-billion.2445059/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 13:12:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apples-investment-in-the-uk-exceeds-18-billion/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/newsroom/2024/12/apple-expands-uk-investment-and-doubles-local-engineering-teams/">today announced</a> that it has invested more than £18 billion in the United Kingdom over the last five years, plus it has doubled the number of engineering teams in the country.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/apple-store-uk.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981463" /><br/>
Apple says that it supports 550,000 jobs in the UK through direct employment, its product supply chain, and the iOS app economy. Apple's UK engineering teams work on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, Private Cloud Compute, and silicon engineering.<blockquote>"We've been serving customers in the U.K. for more than 40 years, and we're proud of our deep connection with communities across this country," said Tim Cook, Apple's CEO. "We're thrilled to be growing our Apple teams here, and to keep supporting the extraordinary innovators, creators, and entrepreneurs who are pushing the boundaries of technology in so many ways."</blockquote>Apple has also added jobs in the country through expanded <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ production, which has tripled in the past two years. &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ adds jobs for cast and crew in the UK, but also hundreds of suppliers across business sectors like construction, manufacturing, and hospitality.<br/>
<br/>
Since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> launched in 2008, Apple says that UK developers have earned £9 billion from selling digital goods and services.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Thrilled to be back in London for an exciting and special week ahead! Thank you to the teams and customers at Apple Battersea for such a great visit during a busy time of year! <a href="https://t.co/kxILR3IXWT">pic.twitter.com/kxILR3IXWT</a></p>&mdash; Greg Joswiak (@gregjoz) <a href="https://twitter.com/gregjoz/status/1866586753873965537?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">There’s nothing like London during the holidays. It was great to meet with Slow Horses star, Jack Lowden, to tell him how excited we are for season 5 on Apple TV+! <a href="https://t.co/soFlPbBPQf">pic.twitter.com/soFlPbBPQf</a></p>&mdash; Tim Cook (@tim_cook) <a href="https://twitter.com/tim_cook/status/1866586161373655095?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple's Greg Joswiak is in the UK this week, and today he shared a photo at Apple Battersea and said that he was looking for an "exciting and special week ahead." Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> is in the country as well, and today he met with Slow Horses Star Jack Lowden.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apples-investment-in-the-uk-exceeds-18-billion/">Apple&#039;s Investment in the UK Exceeds £18 Billion</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-investment-in-the-uk-exceeds-£18-billion.2445059/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Could Get Blood Pressure Monitoring in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-blood-pressure-monitoring-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-could-get-blood-pressure-monitoring-in-2025.2445058/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 11:51:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-blood-pressure-monitoring-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is ramping up work on a blood pressure monitoring feature for the Apple Watch and it could be ready as soon as 2025, reports <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-12-10/apple-plans-apple-watch-ultra-3-next-year-with-satellite-texting-and-5g"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Blood pressure monitoring is a health addition that Apple has been working on for the last several years, and based on rumors, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/apple-watch-2024-health-features/">wanted to debut it in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Watch-Series-10-lineup-240909-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964982" /><br/>
The feature would not provide exact systolic and diastolic blood pressure measurements, instead tracking whether a user's blood pressure is trending upwards and sending an alert if hypertension is detected. After receiving an alert, the Apple Watch user could provide the information to a medical professional for additional testing.<br/>
<br/>
Hypertension is known as a silent killer because it can go undetected and undiagnosed, leading to heart damage and death. High blood pressure often has few symptoms until it is notably advanced, and early detection via the Apple Watch has the potential to save lives. The Apple Watch already has the ability to detect atrial fibrillation or an irregular heart beat, plus it can be used to take one-lead ECG readings. There is also a blood oxygen monitoring feature, but it is disabled in current models in the United States due to patent issues. <br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman, Apple is aiming to introduce the feature in the Apple Watch Ultra 3, and it would also presumably be included in the standard Apple Watch coming in 2025 as well. It is not yet entirely clear if Apple will be able to launch the feature in 2025, given that it was previously delayed. In 2022, Apple was reportedly dealing with accuracy issues during testing, but those problems may have been solved.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also continuing to work on noninvasive blood glucose monitoring, but that feature is not yet ready to launch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-blood-pressure-monitoring-2025/">Apple Watch Could Get Blood Pressure Monitoring in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-could-get-blood-pressure-monitoring-in-2025.2445058/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Firmware Update for Beats Pill</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/beats-pill-first-firmware-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-firmware-update-for-beats-pill.2445056/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 11:35:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/beats-pill-first-firmware-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a firmware update for the Beats Pill, marking the first new software the speaker has received since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/beats-pill-bluetooth-speaker-announced/">its June 2024 launch</a>. The firmware has a build number of 2C336, up from the 2C289 firmware the Beats Pill shipped with. Users will see version 2.2 in the Settings app when the device is connected to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-pill-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956812" /><br/>
We don't know what's included in the new firmware, and Apple does not typically provide information about Beats firmware updates.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced the Beats Pill earlier this year after discontinuing the prior Beats Pill+ back in 2022. The new model is priced at &#36;150 and it features an all-new speaker system, a removable lanyard, USB-C and Bluetooth connectivity, IP67 water resistance, and a 24-hour battery life.<br/>
<br/>
The Beats Pill is designed to work seamlessly with both Android and Apple devices, and it supports both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> and &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; Device for tracking purposes.<br/>
<br/>
Firmware updates for the Beats Pill are delivered over-the-air. Firmware will be installed while the Beats Pill is charging and in Bluetooth range of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi. On Android devices, users need to download the Beats app for Android and connect the Android device to a power outlet to initiate a firmware update.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/beats-pill-first-firmware-update/">Apple Releases First Firmware Update for Beats Pill</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-firmware-update-for-beats-pill.2445056/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 3 Will Support Texting via Satellite</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-ultra-3-satellite-connectivity/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-will-support-texting-via-satellite.2445054/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 11:26:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-ultra-3-satellite-connectivity/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation Apple Watch Ultra is set to gain satellite connectivity, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-12-10/apple-plans-apple-watch-ultra-3-next-year-with-satellite-texting-and-5g">Bloomberg</a></em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. Apple first introduced satellite connectivity for off-grid texting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, and the feature has been included in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, but no Apple Watch to date.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-watch-ultra-2-new-black.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-965050" /><br/>
Apple's 2025 Apple Watch Ultra will be able to connect to a satellite network like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, allowing users to send texts via satellite when cellular networks and Wi-Fi are unavailable. When satellite connectivity first launched, it was limited to emergency text messages, but in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple expanded it to allow users to send texts to anyone.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is hoping that the satellite feature will encourage Apple Watch owners to update to a new Apple Watch Ultra, with the third-generation model set to come out in September 2025. Satellite connectivity would also allow Apple to better compete with companies like Garmin that manufacture dedicated satellite hardware for use in off-grid emergencies.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra is aimed at hikers, scuba divers, and adventurers, and satellite connectivity for the device would add another layer of safety for activities that are not near cellular towers.<br/>
<br/>
As of right now, Apple still does not charge for satellite connectivity, and there is no word yet on what the company might charge. All iPhones come with two years of connectivity for free, and that will also likely be the case for the Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also planning to stop using Intel cellular modems in future Apple Watch models, instead transitioning to technology from MediaTek. MediaTek's modem chip adds support or 5G Recap, a 5G service that's designed for connected devices and wearables that don't need standard 5G speeds. The current cellular Apple Watch models still use 4G LTE, even though Apple has been using 5G in iPhones for several years. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-ultra-3-satellite-connectivity/">Apple Watch Ultra 3 Will Support Texting via Satellite</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-3-will-support-texting-via-satellite.2445054/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the 11-Inch M2 iPad Air for &#36;469 at Best Buy Today Only (&#36;130 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/get-the-11-inch-m2-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-11-inch-m2-ipad-air-for-469-at-best-buy-today-only-130-off.2445042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 08:32:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/get-the-11-inch-m2-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has Apple's 11-inch M2 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for <a href="https://howl.link/b6iyvb3dkir53"><strong>&#36;469.00</strong></a> today, down from &#36;599.00. This is a new record low price on the tablet, and it's only available in Blue.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-air-early-black-friday.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-974478" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The other three colors are currently priced at &#36;499.00 on Best Buy, which is still a solid second-best price for the M2 iPad Air. The deal on the Blue model will only last for today, so if you're interested be sure to make your purchase soon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/b6iyvb3dkir53"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>11-inch M2 iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;469.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy is currently taking &#36;100 off nearly <a href="https://howl.link/j5h18xbyh24yk">every other model of the M2 iPad Air</a>, including both 11-inch and 13-inch tablets. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find during the holiday season? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/get-the-11-inch-m2-ipad-air/">Get the 11-Inch M2 iPad Air for &#36;469 at Best Buy Today Only (&#36;130 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-11-inch-m2-ipad-air-for-469-at-best-buy-today-only-130-off.2445042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iCloud+ Storage Prices Increased in 10 Countries This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/icloud-storage-price-increases/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-storage-prices-increased-in-10-countries-this-year.2445038/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 08:02:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/icloud-storage-price-increases/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past several months, Apple has raised its prices for some or all iCloud+ storage plans in 10 countries, including Japan, South Korea, Thailand, Indonesia, Turkey, Pakistan, Nigeria, Egypt, Tanzania, and the Philippines. The updated prices for each of these countries are listed <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/108047">in a support document</a> on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
In Japan, for example, prices have increased by around 15%.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Storage Tier</th><br/>
 <th>Old Pricing</th><br/>
 <th>New Pricing</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>50GB</td><br/>
 <td>¥130</td><br/>
 <td>¥150</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>200GB</td><br/>
 <td>¥400</td><br/>
 <td>¥450</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>2TB</td><br/>
 <td>¥1300</td><br/>
 <td>¥1500</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6TB</td><br/>
 <td>¥3900</td><br/>
 <td>¥4500</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12TB</td><br/>
 <td>¥7900</td><br/>
 <td>¥9000</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div>Local currencies in many of the affected countries have declined against the U.S. dollar over the past few years, and that is likely the underlying reason for the price increases. iCloud+ prices in the U.S. have not changed this year.<br/>
<br/>
iCloud+ plans provide users with extra storage beyond the 5GB of free storage included with iCloud by default. The plans also include some other perks, such as iCloud Private Relay, Hide My Email, and HomeKit Secure Video.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/icloud-storage-price-increases/">iCloud+ Storage Prices Increased in 10 Countries This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/icloud-storage-prices-increased-in-10-countries-this-year.2445038/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Winter Sale Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off The Frame TV, &#36;300 Off Smart Monitor M8, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/samsung-winter-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-winter-sale-takes-up-to-1-000-off-the-frame-tv-300-off-smart-monitor-m8-and-more.2445035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 07:24:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/samsung-winter-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung this week kicked off a new <a href="https://howl.link/0ufxm5ick33dz">Winter Sale</a>, offering discounts across smartphones, smartwatches, tablets, computers, and home appliances. Many of the deals in this sale are the same prices we tracked during Samsung's Black Friday and Cyber Week sales, making it a great last-minute opportunity to shop steep discounts on products that can still arrive before Christmas.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-best-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923404" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Right now, Amazon has the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Display at an all-time low price, beating Samsung's deal. You can get this monitor for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;767.99</strong></a> (&#36;832 off). Another notable Samsung monitor deal is on the 32-inch Smart Monitor M8, available for <a href="https://howl.link/m79zwydm8axba"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Samsung's own website (&#36;300 off).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.link/0ufxm5ick33dz"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Samsung Winter Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
During this sale, if you purchase a <a href="https://howl.link/ekxaws4sul7id">select Samsung gaming monitor</a>, you'll also get the 27-inch Odyssey G3 Gaming Monitor for free (&#36;229.99 value). One of the best monitors to purchase with this offer is the 57-inch Odssey Neo G9 Curved Gaming Monitor for <a href="https://howl.link/ezd2zzv2k1wyv"><strong>&#36;1,599.99</strong></a> (&#36;1,129.99 off).<br/>
<br/>
Similar to events like Prime Day, Samsung's Winter Sale has exclusive "deals of the day" that swap out every day. Today's offer is taking <a href="https://howl.link/x33y89tesmjcl">up to &#36;1,000 off The Frame TVs</a>, including every size currently sold on Samsung's website. This drops the popular 65-inch model down to <a href="https://howl.link/x33y89tesmjcl"><strong>&#36;1,599.99</strong></a>, from &#36;1,999.99.<br/>
<br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/p7y8pcx52jg1k">Monitors and Storage</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smart-monitor-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923411" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVMG7DfcK">990 EVO 5.0 NVMe SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVLMVgenn">2TB Portable SSD</a> - &#36;159.99, down from &#36;284.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/m79zwydm8axba">Smart Monitor M80D</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKayx1Nx">34-inch Odyssey OLED G8 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKXc8UKH">32-inch Odyssey Quantum Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26psc%3D1">27-inch ViewFinity S9 Smart Monitor</a> - &#36;767.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,078.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmSCTMeMf1L">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/gmsd1fl5cpubb">TVs</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/the-frame-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923410" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/vzsts7mj2hogy">The Frame</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/basyw1q0kj7hr">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX0OsAHAg">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ykww20f4u23u4">65-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,699.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/btdmfxv0poeju">65-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,499.99, down from &#36;2,699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVRaSFAOn">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,579.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVQujFbtE">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;3,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/g0apfewviypne">Refrigerators</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/fridge-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923409" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.link/rj0skwxvkajxt">Large Capacity Side-by-Side Fridge</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,666.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/wvh01oaq72v2w">4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,699.00, down from &#36;2,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ozmz1x8zug5xn">Mega Capacity 3-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;2,499.00, down from &#36;3,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/2ywoezhcm8c5r">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;2,699.00, down from &#36;4,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.link/ot6h8iqi1q361">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge</a> - &#36;3,499.00, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h2><a href="https://howl.link/5tyldrblhkwko">Galaxy Products</a></h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smartphone-samsung.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923408" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbV7Ybcky">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,600 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbXJFsJWi">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;900 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbYxetDfM">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;460</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbZknUAIi">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;190</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find during the holiday season? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/samsung-winter-sale/">Samsung Winter Sale Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off The Frame TV, &#36;300 Off Smart Monitor M8, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-winter-sale-takes-up-to-1-000-off-the-frame-tv-300-off-smart-monitor-m8-and-more.2445035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Three All-New Radio Stations Arrive on Apple Music</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/three-new-apple-music-radio-stations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/three-all-new-radio-stations-arrive-on-apple-music.2445029/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 06:10:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/three-new-apple-music-radio-stations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/12/apple-music-expands-live-global-radio-offering-with-three-brand-new-stations/">announced</a> the addition of three new global radio stations: Apple Música Uno, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Club, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Chill.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Apple-Music-Radio.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-981383" /><br/>
The stations join &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; 1, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Hits, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Country. Oliver Schusser, Apple's vice president of Music, Sports, and Beats, said:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Apple Music Radio is the beating heart of our service, representing the intersection of exceptional human voices and curation with cutting-edge technology that shapes and influences culture. We put a lot of time and care into making sure these new radio stations are really bespoke, highly curated, and hosted by some of the world's best music commentators with unique programming that we know our listeners will love.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The stations are hosted from state-of-the-art studios in Los Angeles, New York, Nashville, London, Paris, and Berlin. Each has a different theme:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://music.apple.com/us/station/ra.1740613864/">Apple Música Uno</a></strong>: Latin music from around the world, focusing on new and current releases, including Música Mexicana and reggaetón, tropical, Latin pop, and more. The station is hosted by Becky G, followed by Evelyn Sicairos and Lechero. Rauw Alejandro and Grupo Frontera have special shows of their own. On-air talent will speak Spanish and English.</li><br/>
	<li><strong><a href="https://music.apple.com/us/station/ra.1740613859/">Apple Music Club</a></strong>: Dance and electronic music with a focus on global club culture, hosted by Tim Sweeney and NAINA.</li><br/>
	<li><a href="https://music.apple.com/us/station/ra.1740614260/"><strong>Apple Music Chill</strong></a>: Mood-focused music for respite, wellbeing, and ease, interspersed with "mindful moments" to remind listeners to find center and remain calm, hosted by Sabi with shows from Brian Eno, Stephan Moccio, and Zane Lowe.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple Música Uno, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Club, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Chill are available to listen to now in the newly updated Radio tab of the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app, as well as for free, without a subscription, on the <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/radio/">Apple Music Radio</a> website.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/three-new-apple-music-radio-stations/">Three All-New Radio Stations Arrive on Apple Music</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/three-all-new-radio-stations-arrive-on-apple-music.2445029/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Pro Display XDR Is Five Years Old Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/pro-display-xdr-five-years-old-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-pro-display-xdr-is-five-years-old-today.2445012/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 02:45:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/pro-display-xdr-five-years-old-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Displays</category>
		<category>Pro Display XDR</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Pro Display XDR is five years old today, marking half a decade since its release alongside the 2019 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/05/Pro-Display-XDR-Yella.jpg" alt="" width="2590" height="1456" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-743451" /><br/>
Released on December 10, 2019, the Pro Display XDR was Apple's re-entry into the high-end external monitor market, following a three-year hiatus after discontinuing the Thunderbolt Display in 2016. The announcement came at Apple's Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) in June 2019, where the company presented the display as a rival to traditional reference monitors. The XDR in its name stands for "Extreme Dynamic Range," a feature that Apple emphasized as a key differentiator from other high-resolution monitors available at the time.<br/>
<br/>
It features a 32-inch Retina display with a 6K resolution of 6,016 by 3,384 pixels, powered by Apple's proprietary LED backlighting system. Apple utilized blue-colored LEDs with custom lenses and reflectors to achieve a maximum brightness of up to 1,600 nits in HDR mode, while sustaining 1,000 nits across the entire screen indefinitely. This allows for what Apple describes as "stunningly accurate colors and contrast," supporting the P3 wide color gamut and delivering a claimed 1,000,000:1 contrast ratio.<br/>
<br/>
The rear of the display features the same lattice pattern used on the 2019 &zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj;, which functions as a heatsink to aid thermal management. The display is also available with matte nano-texture glass to cut down on glare—the first Apple product it's featured on. <br/>
<br/>
Upon its release, the Pro Display XDR garnered significant attention for its high price. In the United States, the display starts at &#36;4,999, and users who opt for the adjustable Pro Stand must pay an additional &#36;999. The Pro Stand, which is sold separately, was met with mixed reactions upon its unveiling. Apple justified the cost by highlighting the engineering involved, with the Pro Stand offering height, tilt, and rotation adjustments, as well as support for both landscape and portrait modes. A VESA mount adapter is also available for those who prefer third-party mounting solutions.<br/>
<br/>
As of its fifth anniversary, the Pro Display XDR remains one of only two external monitors sold by Apple, alongside the Studio Display, which was released in March 2022. Unlike the Pro Display XDR, the Studio Display comes with an integrated A13 Bionic chip, enabling features such as Center Stage for its built-in webcam, spatial audio, and support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands. The Pro Display XDR, however, has no webcam or any internal Apple silicon chip.<br/>
<br/>
Speculation about a second-generation Pro Display XDR has been circulating for some time. In December 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reported that Apple was working on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/18/updated-pro-display-xdr-gurman/">updated version of the display</a>, this time with an Apple silicon chip to enhance its capabilities. In July 2023, Gurman reiterated that Apple was still developing multiple new displays. Display supply chain analyst Ross Young <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/pro-display-xdr-2-quantom-dot-rumor/">recently said</a> that the next-generation Pro Display XDR will feature quantum dot technology, just like the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> models. However, no further details have emerged regarding what other specific upgrades the Pro Display XDR might receive or a potential release time frame. For now, the Pro Display XDR remains Apple's flagship display offering.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/displays/">Apple Pro Display XDR</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Apple Studio Display</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/pro-display-xdr/">Pro Display XDR</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-accessories.77">Mac Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/pro-display-xdr-five-years-old-today/">Apple&#039;s Pro Display XDR Is Five Years Old Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-pro-display-xdr-is-five-years-old-today.2445012/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Resident Evil 2 Now Available on iPhone, iPad, and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/resident-evil-2-debuts-iphone-ipad-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-2-now-available-on-iphone-ipad-and-mac.2445011/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 02:22:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/resident-evil-2-debuts-iphone-ipad-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Capcom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Capcom's <em>Resident Evil 2</em> remake has <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/resident-evil-2/id1640632432">debuted on Apple devices</a>, making it the fourth Resident Evil title to arrive on Apple's mobile platforms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/resident-evil-2.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981367" /><br/>
The survival horror shooter is available as a free download with a limited part of the game being playable, after which players must purchase the full game to continue. The good news is that Capcom is running a promotional discount of 75% off the usual price for a limited time.<br/>
<br/>
From now until January 8, the base game can be purchased for &#36;9.99, while all in-game rewards can be unlocked for &#36;1.99. After that date, the game will be sold for &#36;39.99.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Resident Evil 2</em> requires an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 16 series model to run, along with iPads and Macs equipped with M1 chips or later. The game supports cross-progression across supported Apple devices, so players can continue their progress whether playing on iPhone, iPad, or Mac. It's also a universal purchase, meaning a single purchase grants access across all compatible Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
Capcom says the app is approximately 31GB in size, and that the installation process requires the target drive to have at least twice the size of the app in storage space available. An internet connection is also required to start the game. <em>Resident Evil 2</em> can be downloaded from the App Store. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/resident-evil-2/id1640632432">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/capcom/">Capcom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/resident-evil-2-debuts-iphone-ipad-mac/">Resident Evil 2 Now Available on iPhone, iPad, and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/resident-evil-2-now-available-on-iphone-ipad-and-mac.2445011/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tap to Pay on iPhone Now Available in the UAE</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-in-the-uae/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-the-uae.2445007/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 01:51:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-in-the-uae/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		<category>UAE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/ae/newsroom/2024/12/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-the-uae/">announced</a> Tap to Pay on iPhone in the UAE, allowing independent sellers, small merchants, and large retailers in the country to use ‌iPhones‌ as a payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-credit-card.jpeg" alt="" width="1306" height="735" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836335" /><br/>
Tap to Pay allows iPhones to accept payments via Apple Pay, contactless credit and debit cards, and other digital wallets‌‌‌. All transactions are encrypted, and Apple has no information about what is purchased or the person who made the purchase.<br/>
<br/>
No additional hardware or credit card machine is required‌ to use Tap to Pay on iPhone. The feature uses NFC technology to securely authenticate the contactless payments, plus the feature also supports PIN entry, which includes accessibility options.<br/>
<br/>
Adyen, Magnati, and Network International are the first payment platforms in the UAE to offer Tap to Pay on iPhone, which works with cards from leading payment networks, including American Express, Mastercard, and Visa.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on ‌‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌‌ requires ‌‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌‌ XS or newer models, and works for customers as any normal ‌‌‌‌‌Apple Pay‌‌‌‌‌ transaction would. Sellers just need to open up the app, register the sale, and present their ‌‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌‌ to the buyer, who can then use an appropriate contactless payment method.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on ‌iPhone‌ launched in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">February 2022</a> in the United States, and since then, Apple has been working to expand it to additional countries. The feature is available in Australia, Austria, Brazil, Canada, Czech Republic, France, Germany, Ireland, Italy, Japan, New Zealand, Netherlands, Romania, Sweden, Taiwan, the UAE, Ukraine, the United Kingdom, and the United States.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/uae/">UAE</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-in-the-uae/">Tap to Pay on iPhone Now Available in the UAE</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tap-to-pay-on-iphone-now-available-in-the-uae.2445007/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Several Apple TV+ Shows Score Golden Globe Nominations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/apple-tv-plus-golden-globe-2024-nominations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/several-apple-tv-shows-score-golden-globe-nominations.2444990/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:14:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/apple-tv-plus-golden-globe-2024-nominations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/12/apples-slow-horses-disclaimer-shrinking-and-presumed-innocent-score-nominations-for-the-golden-globe-awards/">today announced</a> that several of its TV shows have been nominated for the 82nd Annual Golden Globe Awards. Popular series Slow Horses has been nominated for Best Drama, while Disclaimer, a psychological thriller miniseries starring Cate Blanchett, has been nominated for Best Limited Series.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/slow-horses-apple-tv-plus.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981341" /><br/>
Slow Horses stars Gary Oldman and Jack Lowden have been nominated for Best Performance by a Male Actor in a Drama, while Disclaimer's Cate Blanchett and Kevin Kline have been nominated for best actor awards for a limited series.<br/>
<br/>
Jason Segel and Harrison Ford, the stars of hit comedy Shrinking, have been nominated for best comedy performance and best supporting role, respectively. Jake Gyllenhaal, star of Presumed Innocent, has also been nominated for best actor in a TV drama.<br/>
<br/>
The Golden Globe winners are set to be announced on January 5, 2025. Apple previously won Golden Globes for Killers of the Flower Moon and Black Bird, and its original TV shows, movies, and documentaries have earned a total of 535 wins and 2,402 award nominations across the Oscars, Golden Globes, Emmys, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+ is priced at &#36;9.99 per month in the United States, and it is available in more than 100 countries and regions. Customers who purchase and activate a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, or Mac can get three months of &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ for free.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/apple-tv-plus-golden-globe-2024-nominations/">Several Apple TV+ Shows Score Golden Globe Nominations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/several-apple-tv-shows-score-golden-globe-nominations.2444990/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Ugreen&#039;s Line of &#039;Uno&#039; Chargers and Hubs Brings a Bit of Whimsy to Utilitarian Products</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/ugreen-uno-chargers-power-adapters/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ugreens-line-of-uno-chargers-and-hubs-brings-a-bit-of-whimsy-to-utilitarian-products.2444988/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:58:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/ugreen-uno-chargers-power-adapters&#038;post_date=1733795939/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ugreen caught my attention earlier this year when it launched a new line of "Uno" accessories that are equipped with LED screens that can display fun emoji faces. The Uno range has everything from wireless chargers to power banks, and I've spent several months testing the products to see how they perform.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964026" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ugreen-uno-series.jpg" alt="" width="1491" height="839" /><br/>
Everything in the Uno line was designed with a "robot-inspired" aesthetic, according to Ugreen, which equates to a boxy style with an LED screen that can display emoji-like faces. The emoji faces are amusing and bring some fun to accessories that are typically boring, but they're also useful and can change based on power level and other factors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Ugreen Uno Magnetic Wireless Power Bank</h2><br/>
Priced at &#36;45, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FUGREEN-Portable-Certified-Magnetic-10000mAh%2Fdp%2FB0D7CFCRBN">Magnetic Wireless Power Bank</a> looks like a lot of other power banks on the market at first glance, featuring a rectangular design that mirrors the shape of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. An LED screen and an attached stand that happens to look like a set of headphones set it apart, though.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-power-bank-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981330" /><br/>
The power bank is made from a smooth, metallic plastic material, with a soft silicone on the back where it attaches magnetically to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. It feels relatively lightweight, but it is a bit over 3/4ths of an inch thick, so it does add some bulk to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. It comes in black, which looks similar to Apple's space black, and a light purple shade. Though it's a bit thick, it is pocketable, measuring in at 4.2 inches by 2.8 inches. The plastic material feels a little cheap, but it's light and I don't expect too much more for the price.<br/>
<br/>
The LED display protrudes slightly which does indeed give it a distinctly robot-like look, and it often displays an emoji face that corresponds to power level. I say "often" because a lot of the time, it actually shows a percent reading of the exact power level. I don't know what triggers the emoji face to show up, and I wish there was a button to toggle between the power percent and the face.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-power-bank-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981331" /><br/>
You need to turn the power bank on by pressing the side button when it is attached to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, which initiates charging. More than once, I've attached it to my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and forgotten to activate it, but having a sleep state seems to preserve battery level when it's not in use. The button has other functions as well, and a single press will turn on the LCD, while a double press will turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
When the power is on, it displays a "Hi" message, and when it's powering down, it shows a "bye" message. The emoji face that's displayed changes based on power level. At 100 percent, the face shows heart eyes, and at 99 to 80 percent, it changes to a happy face with smiling eyes. At 79 to 21 percent, it's a happy face with a more neutral eye expression, and 20 percent or below, there's a sad face. Each face animates slightly, with the eyes and mouth changing position.<br/>
<br/>
This is a Qi2 charger, so it can charge &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; iPhones at up to 15W. 15W is no longer the maximum charging speed because <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models support 25W &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging, but it is equivalent to the original 15W &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging. It has a 10,000mAh capacity, which is standard for smaller chargers these days.<br/>
<br/>
In an hour-long test, it charged my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max from one percent to 39 percent, and there was 67 percent of the battery left. After charging my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to 80 percent (the maximum I have set), the power bank had 20 percent power remaining.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-power-bank-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981332" /><br/>
I've tested several times, and I am able to reliably get one full charge of the 16 Pro Max from the power bank, and I've had no issues with it during my testing. My &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does sometimes get warm, but it does that with any &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; power bank that I use.<br/>
<br/>
Along with Qi2 charging, there is a USB-C port that can be used for charging iPhones and other accessories, plus it's used for charging the power bank. The USB-C port is 20W, so you can get faster &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charging using a USB-C to USB-C cable (included) or a USB-C to Lightning cable depending on which &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; you have. 20W can also charge an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> at a reasonable speed, but it's not enough for fast charging. Passthrough charging is supported, so you can charge the power bank via USB-C while also charging an attached &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There is an included stand on the power bank that flips down from the top. It holds an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in an ideal position for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls or watching videos, and it's sturdy. The stand has multiple positions so the viewing angle is adjustable, and it can be used in landscape or portrait mode. When not in use, it folds up at the top of the power bank and looks like a set of headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Ugreen Uno 30W Power Bank</h2><br/>
The &#36;38 10,000mAh <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FUGREEN-Portable-Charger-Charging-Battery%2Fdp%2FB0D1XKS2LP">Ugreen Uno USB-C Power Bank</a> is similar to the Magnetic Wireless Power Bank in design, but it doesn't have wireless charging. Instead, it offers 30W charging over USB-C, and it has a built-in USB-C cable.<br/>
<br/>
All the emoji faces are the same and the build quality is identical, but the power bank is slightly slimmer and taller at 4.6 inches by 2.8 inches. This model is a little over a half inch thick, and does not magnetically attach to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
While it has the same headphone-like design at the top, there is no stand. Instead, one side of the "headphones" features a power button for turning the power bank on and off.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the built-in USB-C cable, there are additional USB-C and USB-A ports at the top, so more than one device can be charged at once. The flat USB-C cable tucks into a slot at the back of the charger, and it feels well-attached. I couldn't get it to budge by pulling on it, but there's always a danger that attached cables will break.<br/>
<br/>
30W is fast charging for an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and my &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max charged from one percent to 54 percent in a 30-minute period when testing, which is in line with fast charging tests using standard 30W power adapters. I was able to get one full charge out of the power bank before exhausting the battery.<br/>
<br/>
Because it has a built-in USB-C cable, this model is best for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models that have USB-C ports, but since it has an extra USB-C and USB-A port, it can be used with a Lightning cable, too.<br/>
<br/>
For charging at fast speeds, the USB-C Uno power bank is the better pick over the Qi2 model, and it's nice not to have to carry a USB-C cable around.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>100W USB-C Charger</h2><br/>
Ugreen's <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FUGREEN-Charger-Compact-Adapter-MacBook%2Fdp%2FB0D3XR6S47">&#36;48 100W USB-C Uno Charger</a> is probably my favorite of the bunch, and it has the most robot-like design. It's a square-shaped charger but there's an LED display that shows emoji faces, a headphone-like band at the top, and a set of feet that cover the plug at the bottom.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-100w-power-adapter-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981335" /><br/>
The feet detach so that you can plug the Uno Charger into an outlet, and it's best suited as a desktop charger because of the position of the prongs. If you plug it into a standard wall outlet, the face will be either up or down, but it can definitely be used that way. I haven't lost the little feet yet, and they do have a magnet inside that can attach to a laptop when the charger is plugged in if it's being used while on the go.<br/>
<br/>
This charger is surprisingly compact and heavy, and it's made from the same black plastic material as the power banks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-100w-power-adapter-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981336" /><br/>
When plugged in, the LCD face is continually active. I have the charger on top of my desk, and it sits and blinks at me all day. If you have this in your line of sight, it might get annoying. When something is charging, there are three faces, including one with shining eyes and an eating face. When a device is fully charged, there's a face with sunglasses.<br/>
<br/>
There are four ports at the top of the charger, including three USB-C ports and one USB-A port. Since this is a 100W charger, it can charge a 16-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a> and anything below that. To get the fastest charging with a &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj; (the full 100W), you'll need to plug it in by itself in one of the top two ports.<br/>
<br/>
With multiple devices charging, the power is split up between the ports. When two devices are plugged in, the split is 65W/30W with the USB-C ports, or 65W/22.5W with one USB-C and one USB-A port.<br/>
<br/>
The three port split has 45W/30W/20W, 45W/30W/22.5W, and 80W/7.5W/7.5W options, while four ports in use will split the power to 45W/30W/7.5W/7.5W. The manual that comes with the charger has more specific information on how power is divided to each port.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-100w-power-adapter-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981337" /><br/>
Ugreen says that the charger has overvoltage, overcurrent, overload, and temperature protections, and I haven't run into any issues using the charger.<br/>
<br/>
There's <a href="https://www.ugreen.com/collections/ugreen-uno-iphone-accessories/products/ugreen-uno-charger-65w-pink-blue">also a 65W version</a> that comes in white/purple and blue/pink shades, and it's nice to see options that aren't the standard black.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>USB-C Cable</h2><br/>
Ugreen has an &#36;8 <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FUGREEN-Charging-Display-iPhone-MacBook%2Fdp%2FB0D7BL2JBN%2Fr">Uno USB-C to USB-C 100W PD cable</a> that has little emoji eyes on it, and it's a good companion to the 100W charger. It's braided nylon and feels like a good quality cable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-usb-c-cable.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981327" /><br/>
The base cable is 1.6 feet, but there are more expensive 3.3 foot, 6.6 foot, and 10 foot models. For data transfers, it supports speeds up to 480Mb/s.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2-in-1 Wireless Charger</h2><br/>
Ugreen's &#36;49 Uno 2-in-1 Wireless Charger is also Qi2, with support for up to 15W charging on &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; iPhones. It has a fold-out design with a charging puck for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and a second 5W charging space for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; charger can be adjusted to different angles, and an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be placed in either landscape or portrait mode, so you can use StandBy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-iphone-magsafe-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981328" /><br/>
The square-shaped 2-in-1 Wireless Charger looks like the other Uno products, and it's made from the same black plastic material. It has an LCD face at the front, and the headphone-style design at the top. The face isn't as animated as other models, but it does show two happy eyes when turned on and in standby mode, and a happy face with a mouth when a device is charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-magsafe-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981329" /><br/>
Ugreen includes a USB-C cable that plugs into the back, but you'll need to supply your own power adapter. You can also buy an optional Apple Watch charger to add to the side so you can charge three devices at once.<br/>
<br/>
The charger is relatively compact, so it doesn't take up much space on a desk at all, but it's weighted so it's not going to tip over.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Uno 6-in-1 Hub</h2><br/>
Ugreen's final product in the Uno line is the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FUGREEN-10Gbps-MacBook-Surface-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0D2Q5XJY9">6-in-1 USB-C Hub</a>, which is &#36;18. This is a cheap hub, but it's serviceable for passthrough charging and connecting accessories to your Mac. Design wise, it has the black plastic that Ugreen uses for most of the Uno line, and an LCD face that displays different emoji animations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-usb-c-hub.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981333" /><br/>
The build quality of the hub feels cheap, and I wasn't impressed with it. It's the same plastic as Ugreen's other products, but the hub feels so lightweight and almost flimsy. The emoji faces were also less useful on the hub, featuring only separate idle faces and charging faces.<br/>
<br/>
There are three USB-C ports, two USB-A ports, and an HDMI port that supports up to 4K/60Hz. It offers 85W passthrough charging for a Mac, with 15W available for connecting peripherals. 85W is generally fine for all Mac notebooks, but you're not going to get maximum charging speed for the 16-inch &zwnj;MacBook Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/ugreen-usb-c-hub-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-981334" /><br/>
I've had some issues with data transfers using this hub, with a transfer stopping in the middle. I'm not sure why, but multiple ports were affected. I doubt this is a problem with all models, but I don't like the size or the utility of this hub, and I think there are better options out there.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
If you're looking for an accessory that's brings a little more fun to your desk than the standard power adapter or power bank, I think Ugreen's Uno line is well worth checking out. I especially liked the 100W USB-C charger and the Qi2 Magnetic Wireless Charger, though everything but the hub performed well.<br/>
<br/>
Ugreen's Uno products also make for fun gifts, and I think a power bank with a little emoji face would go over well with anyone that has an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. I do want to note that the Qi2 Charger seems to be &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; only, as some of the reviews mentioned that it does not work with Android devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
Ugreen's Uno products can be <a href="https://www.ugreen.com/pages/ugreen-uno-release">purchased from the Ugreen website</a> or <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fstores%2FUGREEN%2FUGREENUnoSeries_NexodeSeries%2Fpage%2F488CA5D7-F4E6-42B7-97AB-EA509E3BAAD7">from Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Ugreen provided MacRumors with the Uno products included in the review for the purpose of the review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/ugreen-uno-chargers-power-adapters/">Review: Ugreen&#039;s Line of &#039;Uno&#039; Chargers and Hubs Brings a Bit of Whimsy to Utilitarian Products</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-ugreens-line-of-uno-chargers-and-hubs-brings-a-bit-of-whimsy-to-utilitarian-products.2444988/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Holiday Sale Brings Back Black Friday Prices on Ace Headphones, Arc Soundbar, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/sonos-holiday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-holiday-sale-brings-back-black-friday-prices-on-ace-headphones-arc-soundbar-and-more.2444970/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 10:36:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/sonos-holiday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos is hosting a new <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">holiday sale</a>, where you can find multiple all-time low Black Friday prices return for popular Sonos products. This includes the new Sonos Ace headphones, Arc soundbar, Roam 2 portable speaker, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/sonos-black-friday-red.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-979950" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
All discounts in this sale have been automatically applied, so you don't need to enter a coupon code in order to see the final sale prices. We've collected all of the deals in the list below, but you can also find a few bundle discounts on sale on the Sonos website.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 20% OFF</div>Sonos Holiday Sale</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sonos-ace-black">Ace Headphones</a> - &#36;349, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc-black">Arc Soundbar</a> - &#36;699, down from &#36;899</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/beam-black">Beam (Gen 2) Soundbar</a> - &#36;369, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100-black">Era 100 Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-2-black">Roam 2 Portable Speaker</a> - &#36;139, down from &#36;179</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move-2-black">Move 2 Portable Speaker</a> - &#36;359, down from &#36;449</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find during the holiday season? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/09/sonos-holiday-sale/">Sonos Holiday Sale Brings Back Black Friday Prices on Ace Headphones, Arc Soundbar, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-holiday-sale-brings-back-black-friday-prices-on-ace-headphones-arc-soundbar-and-more.2444970/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
