<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 02:03:19 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Close to a Deal to Lift iPhone 16 Ban in Indonesia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/apple-deal-to-lift-iphone-16-ban-indonesia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-close-to-a-deal-to-lift-iphone-16-ban-in-indonesia.2447878/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:41:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/apple-deal-to-lift-iphone-16-ban-indonesia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Indonesia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is closing in on an investment plan deal with Indonesian authorities that would allow it to resume iPhone 16 sales in the country, <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-01-22/apple-close-to-deal-to-lift-indonesian-iphone-ban-minister-says">Bloomberg</a></em> reported on Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/iPhone-16-Apple-Store.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-976828" /><br/>
Indonesia banned sales of the device in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/indonesia-bans-iphone-16-sales/">October</a>, claiming Apple had failed to comply with local manufacturing requirements of 35% domestic content for smartphones and tablets. Apple has offered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-iphone-ban/">&#36;1 billion</a> investment in the country that includes building an AirTag factory. The offer is a significant increase from its previous offers of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/">&#36;10 million</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ups-invest-offer-indonesia-iphone-16-ban/">&#36;100 million</a>, which were rejected by the government.<br/>
<br/>
“I strongly believe it will resolve very, very soon,” the country's investment minister Rosan Roeslani said in an interview with Bloomberg Television in Davos on Tuesday. "Hopefully within one or two weeks this issue can be resolved."<br/>
<br/>
"The way they calculate it is different I think," he said, referring to the local content requirement. "Now they find a solution on that one, so hopefully they accept the discrepancies so we can have the iPhone 16 sold in Indonesia."<br/>
<br/>
Indonesia represents a significant market for Apple, with the country's population of 280 million operating some 354 million active mobile phones. The company has maintained developer academies there since 2018, but the country currently hosts no Apple manufacturing facilities. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/indonesia/">Indonesia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/22/apple-deal-to-lift-iphone-16-ban-indonesia/">Apple Reportedly Close to a Deal to Lift iPhone 16 Ban in Indonesia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-close-to-a-deal-to-lift-iphone-16-ban-in-indonesia.2447878/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are Apple&#039;s Full Release Notes for iOS 18.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-release-notes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-apples-full-release-notes-for-ios-18-3.2447858/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:31:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-release-notes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple provided developers and public beta testers with the release candidate version of iOS 18.3 today, and with it comes release notes confirming what's new. While we knew about several of the features that are in the update, there are some lesser known tweaks and bug fixes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Generic-iOS-18.3-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980522" /><br/>
The update adds new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a> features for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, it tweaks Notification summaries on all devices that support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, and there are also bug fixes for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<blockquote><strong>Visual intelligence with Camera Control (All iPhone 16 models)</strong><br/>
- Add an event to Calendar from a poster or flyer<br/>
- Easily identify plants and animals<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Notification summaries (All iPhone 16 models, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max)</strong><br/>
- Easily manage settings for notification summaries from the Lock Screen<br/>
- Updated style for summarized notifications better distinguishes them from other notifications by using italicized text as well as the glyph<br/>
- Notification summaries for News &amp; Entertainment apps are temporarily unavailable, and users who opt-in will see them again when the feature becomes available<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update includes the following enhancements and bug fixes:</strong> - Calculator repeats the last mathematical operation when you tap the equals sign again<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the keyboard might disappear when initiating a typed Siri request<br/>
- Resolves an issue where audio playback continues until the song ends even after closing Apple Music<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit:<br/>
<a href="https://support.apple.com/100100">https://support.apple.com/100100</a></blockquote>The release candidate version of iOS 18.3 represents the final version of the software that will be released to the public in the near future should no additional bugs be found;<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting iOS 18.3 to see a launch alongside iPadOS 18.3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3, tvOS 18.3, visionOS 2.3, and watchOS 11.3 next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-release-notes/">Here Are Apple&#039;s Full Release Notes for iOS 18.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-apples-full-release-notes-for-ios-18-3.2447858/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.3 Tweaks Calculator App Functionality</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-calculator-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-3-tweaks-calculator-app-functionality.2447854/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:14:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-calculator-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 18.3, Apple made a small but meaningful change to the way the Calculator app works, reintroducing repeating operations. When you tap the equals sign twice, the app will now repeat the last mathematical operation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Calculator-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960038" /><br/>
So, for example, if you type in 5x5 and tap the equals sign, you'll get 25 as a result. If you hit the equals sign again, it will multiply 25x5, and will continue multiplying by 5 every time you tap the equals symbol.<br/>
<br/>
Repeating operations were an option in the Calculator app prior to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, but &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; removed the functionality. Users who have missed the feature will get it back after updating to iOS 18.3. Being able to repeat operations is useful for calculating compound interest. <br/>
<br/>
Note that this feature has also been missing in macOS 15, but the macOS 15.3 update reinstates it. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-calculator-app/">iOS 18.3 Tweaks Calculator App Functionality</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-3-tweaks-calculator-app-functionality.2447854/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix Increases Prices Again</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/netflix-2025-price-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-increases-prices-again.2447848/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:10:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/netflix-2025-price-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix is raising its prices for all plans in several countries, including the United States, Canada, Portugal, and Argentina. The cheapest Standard with ads plan will be &#36;1 more expensive in the U.S., going from &#36;6.99 to &#36;7.99 per month.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-884793" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/Netflix-Smaller-3.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" /><br/>
The Standard plan's price will increase from &#36;15.49 to &#36;17.99 per month, and the Premium plan will now cost &#36;24.99 per month, up from &#36;22.99 per month. The Standard plan offers 1080p HD video, and the Premium plan is the only plan that supports 4K streaming.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix last increased prices <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/netflix-price-increase-2023/">in October 2023</a>, and this is the first price increase the ad-supported plan has seen since its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/04/netflix-basic-with-ads-plan-doesnt-work-apple-tv/">late 2022 launch</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The price hikes were announced during Netflix's Q4 2024 earnings results [<a href="https://s22.q4cdn.com/959853165/files/doc_financials/2024/q4/FINAL-Q4-24-Shareholder-Letter.pdf">PDF</a>], which saw the company report 19 million new subscribers, a quarterly record, and 16 percent revenue growth. Netflix now has over 300 million paying subscribers worldwide, and the company forecasts continued growth in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
On the price increase, Netflix said the following: "As we continue to invest in programming and deliver more value for our members, we will occasionally ask our members to pay a little more so that we can re-invest to further improve Netflix."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/netflix-2025-price-increase/">Netflix Increases Prices Again</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-increases-prices-again.2447848/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UK Announces Digital Wallet for IDs and Driver&#039;s Licenses</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/uk-digital-wallet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-announces-digital-wallet-for-ids-and-drivers-licenses.2447847/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:37:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/uk-digital-wallet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The UK government <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/digital-driving-licence-coming-this-year">today announced plans</a> for a digital wallet that will house digital driver's licenses. It is not yet clear if the digital wallet that the UK government has planned will integrate with Apple Wallet, but UK users will be able to access their driver's licenses through a GOV.UK app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> when the initiative launches.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/uk-wallet-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986385" /><br/>
The digital driver's license will allow users to prove their age when purchasing age-restricted items, and it will serve as proof of the right to drive. Personal information will be protected with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> for security even if a device is lost.<br/>
<br/>
Along with driver's licenses, the UK digital wallet will eventually include veteran cards, DBS checks, and other documents issued by the government, but traditional physical documents will also remain available.<br/>
<br/>
The UK digital wallet app is launching alongside a GOV.UK app that will feature a built-in "GOV.UK Chat" chatbot that is being created in partnership with OpenAI, and the chat service is already being tested. The chatbot will let UK residents make payments and receive notifications and reminders about government services.<br/>
<br/>
In the United States, Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/13/iphone-drivers-license-support-illinois/">partnered with several states</a> to bring digital driver's licenses and ID cards to the Wallet app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Apple Watch. Digital IDs are available in nine states, as well as Puerto Rico. At least six additional states have pledged future support for the functionality.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/uk-digital-wallet/">UK Announces Digital Wallet for IDs and Driver&#039;s Licenses</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uk-announces-digital-wallet-for-ids-and-drivers-licenses.2447847/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; With Rear Camera Bar Allegedly Shown in Leaked Photo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/alleged-iphone-17-air-shell/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-with-rear-camera-bar-allegedly-shown-in-leaked-photo.2447843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:46:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/alleged-iphone-17-air-shell/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A leaker known as "Majin Bu" today <a href="https://x.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1881695823618301990">shared an alleged image</a> of a component for the rumored, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/17/iphone-17-air-mockups/">ultra-thin "iPhone 17 Air" model</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPhone-17-Air-Size-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985933" /><br/>
The blurry, pixelated image shows a pair of rear iPhone shells with a pill-shaped, raised camera bar along the top. On the left side of the bar, there is a circular cutout that appears to be for a single rear camera. On the right side of the bar, there appears to be an LED camera flash and a tiny microphone hole. The ultra-thin "iPhone 17 Air" is the only iPhone 17 model that is expected to have a single rear camera, so the shell could be for that device.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/19/iphone-se-4-launch-timeframe-revealed/">fourth-generation iPhone SE</a> is also expected to have a single rear camera, but an elongated camera ridge has not been rumored for that device.<br/>
<br/>
In the world of AI-generated photos, and counterfeit iPhones, we do not know if this image shows the actual "iPhone 17 Air." Sometimes leaks like these end up being real, but in many cases they end up being fake. Skepticism is warranted.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">iPhone 17, the design seems confirmed. <a href="https://t.co/5Wh6alUiMr">pic.twitter.com/5Wh6alUiMr</a></p>&mdash; Majin Bu (@MajinBuOfficial) <a href="https://twitter.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1881695823618301990?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 21, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Majin Bu accurately <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-16-pro-two-new-color-options/">revealed the "Desert Titanium" color name</a> for iPhone 16 Pro models seven months before the devices launched, but some of his information has been wrong, including a rumor about an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/leaker-claims-low-cost-ipad-launching-tomorrow/">iPad 11 being imminent in 2023</a>.<br/>
<br/>
An elongated camera bump has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">rumored for both the "iPhone 17 Air"</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/first-iphone-17-pro-design-leak/">iPhone 17 Pro models</a>, so perhaps this alleged design change will be coming to the entire iPhone 17 lineup. Apple is expected to announce the iPhone 17, the "iPhone 17 Air," the iPhone 17 Pro, and the iPhone 17 Pro Max in September.<br/>
<br/>
There are already some Android phones with a camera bar, such as Google's Pixel 9.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, the "iPhone 17 Air" will measure <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">just 5.5mm at its thinnest point</a>, which would make it the thinnest iPhone ever. Apple does not include the rear camera bump in its iPhone dimensions.<br/>
<br/>
Due to its ultra-thin design, the "iPhone 17 Air" is expected to have limited specs, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">only a single rear camera</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">a single speaker</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">no SIM card slot worldwide</a>, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">A19 chip</a> instead of the more powerful A19 Pro chip. Of course, the device will also be equipped with a smaller battery than other iPhone 17 models due to size constraints.<br/>
<br/>
Other rumored features include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">6.6-inch OLED display</a> with a Dynamic Island, Face ID, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Bookmark our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17 roundup</a> to stay up to date with more rumors over the coming months.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/alleged-iphone-17-air-shell/">&#039;iPhone 17 Air&#039; With Rear Camera Bar Allegedly Shown in Leaked Photo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-with-rear-camera-bar-allegedly-shown-in-leaked-photo.2447843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia 15.3 Launching Soon: Here Are the Release Notes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-release-notes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-launching-soon-here-are-the-release-notes.2447841/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:10:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-release-notes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded out the release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3 update, and provided there are no underlying bugs discovered, the RC is the version of macOS that will be released to the public in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
With the RC, Apple provided the release notes for &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3, so if you want to know exactly what's coming, here are the details.<br/>
<blockquote>This update introduces Genmoji, powered by Apple Intelligence, and also includes other enhancements, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.<br/>
- Genmoji creation in Messages and other apps<br/>
- Calculator repeats the last mathematical operation when you click the equals sign again<br/>
- Easily manage settings for notification summaries from the Lock Screen (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Updated style for summarized notifications better distinguishes them from other notifications by using italicized text as well as the glyph (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
- Notification summaries for News &amp; Entertainment apps are temporarily unavailable, and users who opt-in will see them again when the feature becomes available (Mac with Apple silicon)<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit: https://support.apple.com/100100</blockquote><br/>
With the exception of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a>, a feature that was already available in iOS and iPadOS, these release notes also pertain to iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3.<br/>
<br/>
We're expecting &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3, iOS 18.3, and iPadOS 18.3 to see a public launch next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-release-notes/">macOS Sequoia 15.3 Launching Soon: Here Are the Release Notes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-launching-soon-here-are-the-release-notes.2447841/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia 15.3 and iOS 18.3 Enable Apple Intelligence Automatically</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-apple-intelligence-opt-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-and-ios-18-3-enable-apple-intelligence-automatically.2447837/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:01:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-apple-intelligence-opt-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When installing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3, iOS 18.3, or iPadOS 18.3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> will be turned on automatically on compatible devices, Apple says in the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/macos-release-notes/macos-15_3-release-notes">developer release notes</a> for the updates.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963424" /><br/>
<blockquote>For users new or upgrading to iOS 18.3, Apple Intelligence will be enabled automatically during iPhone onboarding. Users will have access to Apple Intelligence features after setting up their devices. To disable Apple Intelligence, users will need to navigate to the Apple Intelligence & Siri Settings pane and turn off the Apple Intelligence toggle. This will disable Apple Intelligence features on their device</blockquote>With &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.2, iOS 18.1, and iOS 18.2, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; was opt-in rather than opt-out, and users who wanted the feature needed to turn it on in the Settings app. Going forward, it will be enabled by default, and Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users who do not want to use the feature will need to turn it off.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3 also brings <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> to the Mac for the first time, so Mac users will be able to create custom emoji characters after installing the update. All three new software updates add tweaks to the Notification summaries feature to make it more clear when a notification contains AI-generated information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple provided developers and public beta testers with the release candidate versions of iOS 18.3, iPadOS 18.3, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3 today, which means the software updates will see a release in the near future. We are expecting the updates to launch to the public next week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/macos-sequoia-15-3-apple-intelligence-opt-out/">macOS Sequoia 15.3 and iOS 18.3 Enable Apple Intelligence Automatically</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-15-3-and-ios-18-3-enable-apple-intelligence-automatically.2447837/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.3 Adds New Visual Intelligence Features for iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-new-visual-intelligence-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-3-adds-new-visual-intelligence-features-for-iphone-16.2447833/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:39:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-new-visual-intelligence-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Visual Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 18.3 update, Apple is adding new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a> features for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. After installing the software, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users will be able to add an event to the Calendar app when using the Camera Control &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; option to view a poster or a flyer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Visual-Intelligence-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-982217" /><br/>
Using &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; to add an event to Calendar was a promised function that Apple showed off when introducing Camera Control, and it will be usable in iOS 18.3. To add an event, view a document such as a poster with a date, and then tap on the date when the feature pops up in the &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; interface. <br/>
<br/>
The update also adds a feature for easily identifying plants and animals with &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj;. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app is already able to provide insight into plants, animals, and insects when opting to view additional information in the editing interface, but Camera Control will now show these details in real-time.<br/>
<br/>
When viewing an animal or a plant with &zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj;, you may see a tappable bubble that lets you know what you're looking at. Tapping it provides more information. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/ios-18-3-camera-control-animals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986365" /><br/>
&zwnj;Visual Intelligence&zwnj; is an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> feature that is exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. It can be activated by long pressing on the Camera Control button.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/visual-intelligence/">Visual Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/ios-18-3-new-visual-intelligence-features/">iOS 18.3 Adds New Visual Intelligence Features for iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-3-adds-new-visual-intelligence-features-for-iphone-16.2447833/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3 and visionOS 2.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-tvos-18-3-visionos-2-3-rcs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-watchos-11-3-tvos-18-3-and-visionos-2-3.2447831/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:14:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-tvos-18-3-visionos-2-3-rcs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the release candidate versions of upcoming watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3, and visionOS 2.3 updates for testing purposes. The RCs come a week after the third betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Thumb-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955941" /><br/>
The betas are available to registered developers, and can be downloaded from the Settings app on each device.<br/>
<br/>
There were no notable new features found in the updates, but code suggests that Apple will add support for robot vacuums to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, which means it will be a supported category in the Home app in visionOS, tvOS, and watchOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/17/whats-new-in-tvos-18-3-so-far/">add a new notice</a> about digital movie and TV show sales in tvOS 18.3.<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting tvOS 18.3, watchOS 11.3, and visionOS 2.3 to be released sometime in late January alongside iOS 18.3, iPadOS 18.3, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-watchos-11-3-tvos-18-3-visionos-2-3-rcs/">Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of watchOS 11.3, tvOS 18.3 and visionOS 2.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-watchos-11-3-tvos-18-3-and-visionos-2-3.2447831/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds macOS Sequoia 15.3 Release Candidate to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-3-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-3-release-candidate-to-developers.2447829/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:08:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-3-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers with the release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.3 update, with the update coming a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/07/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-3-beta-2/">released the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macOS-Sequoia-Night-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961501" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.3 brings <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> to the Mac, a feature that was previously limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. With &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;, Mac users can create custom characters with a text-based prompt, similar to how <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> works.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; characters behave just like emoji on devices running iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, ‌&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;‌ 15.1 and later, but on earlier versions of iOS, macOS, iPadOS, and Android devices, &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; are sent as images. &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; can be added from the emoji interface, and image generation is done on-device.<br/>
<br/>
All macs with an Apple silicon chip support &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; and other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-3-rc/">Apple Seeds macOS Sequoia 15.3 Release Candidate to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-3-release-candidate-to-developers.2447829/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-releases-ios-18-3-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-ios-18-3-and-ipados-18-3.2447828/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 10:05:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-releases-ios-18-3-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate versions of upcoming iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple released the third betas.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-980522" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/12/Generic-iOS-18.3-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3 can be downloaded from the Settings app on a compatible device by going to General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
With the update, Apple made several changes to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> Notification Summaries, such as removing news-related summaries temporarily.<br/>
<br/>
Additional &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> updates are coming later in iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 updates that will follow iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3. We're expecting to see the new software launch toward the end of January.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-releases-ios-18-3-rc/">Apple Seeds Release Candidate Versions of iOS 18.3 and iPadOS 18.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-release-candidate-versions-of-ios-18-3-and-ipados-18-3.2447828/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirTag 4-Pack Available for Record Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apples-airtag-4-pack-69/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airtag-4-pack-available-for-record-low-69-99-price-on-amazon.2447824/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 07:42:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apples-airtag-4-pack-69/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week has Apple's AirTag 4-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. Amazon introduced this all-time low price earlier in January, and it's been consistently available for most of the month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/airtag-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-889772" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon provides an estimated late January delivery date for most residences in the United States, and you won't need to clip an on-page coupon in order to see this deal. If you're shopping for just one AirTag, Amazon has the AirTag 1-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;22.99</strong></a>, which is about &#36;3 higher compared to that option's record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apples-airtag-4-pack-69/">Apple&#039;s AirTag 4-Pack Available for Record Low &#36;69.99 Price on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airtag-4-pack-available-for-record-low-69-99-price-on-amazon.2447824/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Pro Reportedly Launching This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/new-ipad-pro-this-year-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-reportedly-launching-this-year.2447821/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 06:40:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/new-ipad-pro-this-year-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to release at least one new iPad Pro model this year, according to a supplier-focused report today from <a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=32427">Korean website <em>The Elec</em></a>. It is likely that the 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro models would be updated simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipad-pro-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949477" /><br/>
After <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-announces-new-ipad-pro/">receiving an OLED display last year</a>, the report said the iPad Pro will receive only "minor" changes this year. Overall, the next iPad Pro is expected to look "similar" to the current models, suggesting that the device will not receive any major design changes this year. All in all, expect a spec bump only for the next iPad Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
The report is focused on the possibility of South Korean company LX Semicon supplying display drivers for the new iPad Pro this year. It said that components for the device would go into mass production in April or May, suggesting that the next iPad Pro models are still many months away. A launch will likely occur later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2025-01-12/apple-2025-plans-iphone-17-smart-home-hub-ios-19-ai-apple-watch-ipads-m5"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said</a> Apple could have its next-generation M5 chip ready for the next iPad Pro by late 2025 or early 2026.<br/>
<br/>
The current iPad Pro models with OLED displays and the M4 chip launched in May 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple is expected to release new iPad Air and entry-level iPad 11 models. Those devices will likely launch by March or April. According to Gurman, the iPad 11 will be equipped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/12/ipad-11-rumored-specs/">with an A17 Pro chip and 8GB of RAM</a> for Apple Intelligence, while a recent leak indicated that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-leak/">new iPad Air models will have an M3 chip</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if the iPad mini will be updated this year, but it is typically only updated once every several years. After receiving the A17 Pro chip and more last year, the iPad mini might be the only iPad model that is not updated in 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/new-ipad-pro-this-year-report/">New iPad Pro Reportedly Launching This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-reportedly-launching-this-year.2447821/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Falls to Third Place in China&#039;s Smartphone Market Amid Sales Decline</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-falls-to-third-place-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-falls-to-third-place-in-chinas-smartphone-market-amid-sales-decline.2447818/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 05:49:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-falls-to-third-place-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Counterpoint</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has experienced a significant decline in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China, dropping from the leading position to third place in the country's smartphone market during the fourth quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="3020" height="1698" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-967113" /><br/>
According to a new report from <a href="https://www.counterpointresearch.com/insight/post-insight-research-notes-blogs-china-smartphone-sales-fall-32-yoy-in-q4-only-quarter-with-yoy-decline-in-2024">Counterpoint Research</a>, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; shipments in China fell by 18.2% year-on-year in the final quarter of 2024. This decline resulted in a 17.1% market share for the company, placing it behind Huawei and Xiaomi, which captured 18.1% and 17.2% of the market, respectively. The fall comes just a year after Apple held the top position in the market with a 19% share. This is apparently the first time since the U.S. ban on Huawei that Apple has been displaced by its Chinese competitor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's reduced performance in China has been attributed to several factors, including heightened competition from domestic brands and its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/apple-struggling-to-adapt-ai-for-china/">inability to bring Apple Intelligence to the region</a>. While <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> was introduced alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup in September 2024 in the United States, it has not been made available in China due to regulatory constraints. The company is believed to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-ai-partner-china/">partnering with Chinese companies</a> to deliver the features at a later date. Huawei's strong growth in the fourth quarter—up 15.5% year-on-year—has been largely credited to AI features in its flagship Mate 70 devices and the mid-range Nova 13 series.<br/>
<br/>
It is also of note that China's smartphone market experienced a 3.2% year-on-year decline in the fourth quarter of 2024, marking the only quarter of the year with negative growth. Despite these obstacles, Apple maintained its position as the third-largest smartphone brand in China for the quarter, and its sales were closely matched with Xiaomi, which recorded a 17.2% market share. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/counterpoint/">Counterpoint</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/apple-falls-to-third-place-in-china/">Apple Falls to Third Place in China&#039;s Smartphone Market Amid Sales Decline</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-falls-to-third-place-in-chinas-smartphone-market-amid-sales-decline.2447818/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 Leak Shows Dynamic Island, Casts Doubt on Rumored &#039;iPhone 16E&#039; Name</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/iphone-se-4th-gen-leak/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-leak-shows-dynamic-island-casts-doubt-on-rumored-iphone-16e-name.2447774/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 09:01:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/iphone-se-4th-gen-leak/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Evan Blass</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new iPhone SE is widely rumored to launch this year, and the device has potentially been confirmed today by known leaker Evan Blass.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-SE-Dynamic-Island-Majin-Bu.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935672" /><br/>
In a private <a href="https://x.com/evleaks/status/1881274150351962611">social media post</a>, Blass shared an image of what appears to be source code mentioning an iPhone SE (4th Gen), which casts doubt on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/01/iphone-se-4-rumored-to-be-named-iphone-16e/">alternative "iPhone 16E" name</a> rumored for the device. However, the name in the source code could be a placeholder, so there is no guarantee one way or the other yet.<br/>
<br/>
Blass also shared a purported image of the new iPhone SE, and the device has a Dynamic Island instead of a notch. So far, the Dynamic Island is available on the iPhone 14 Pro models, all four iPhone 15 models, and all four iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPhone-SE-4-Evan-Blass.jpeg" alt="" width="1419" height="1006" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986306" /><br/>
There have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/iphone-se-dynamic-island-rumor/">conflicting rumors</a> about whether the next iPhone SE will have a Dynamic Island or a notch, so we will ultimately have to wait and see.<br/>
<br/>
No further details were revealed about the next iPhone SE in this leak.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPhone SE is said to have a similar design as the base iPhone 14 or iPhone 16. Rumored features for the device include a 6.1-inch OLED display, Face ID, a USB-C port, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, a newer A-series chip and an increased 8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support, and the first Apple-designed 5G modem.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo, the iPhone SE 4 will be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/when-to-expect-new-iphone-se/">around the quarter mark of 2025</a>. That means the device will likely be released this March or April, just like all three previous iPhone SE models were.<br/>
<br/>
The current iPhone SE looks similar to the iPhone 8, with outdated features such as a Touch ID button, Lightning port, and thick bezels around the display. Pricing starts at &#36;429, but at least a slight price increase seems probable for the next model.<br/>
<br/>
The leak from Blass also mentioned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-leak/">new iPad Air and entry-level iPad 11 models</a>, which do not appear to have any obvious design changes. Those devices are also likely to be announced by March or April this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/evan-blass/">Evan Blass</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/iphone-se-4th-gen-leak/">iPhone SE 4 Leak Shows Dynamic Island, Casts Doubt on Rumored &#039;iPhone 16E&#039; Name</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-leak-shows-dynamic-island-casts-doubt-on-rumored-iphone-16e-name.2447774/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 4 With ANC Drop to &#36;164.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-amazon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-to-164-99-on-amazon.2447771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 07:58:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-amazon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has one of the first notable discounts of the year on the AirPods 4 with Active Noise Cancellation, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;164.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;179.00. If you're looking for the AirPods 4 without ANC, they're available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/airpods-4-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972562" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Regarding the AirPods 4 with ANC, today's deal is the best price we've tracked so far in 2025, but it's not an all-time low price. We tracked a fairly steep discount on the AirPods 4 over the holiday season last year, but it's unlikely to reappear anytime soon, so Amazon's discount is a solid option if you're shopping for the newest AirPods right now.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;164.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to Active Noise Cancellation (ANC) on this model, the AirPods 4 also feature a redesigned earbud for increased comfort, the H2 chip for improved audio performance, up to 30 hours of battery life, and an IP54 rating for dust, water, and sweat resistance.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about the best deals you can find in 2025? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-amazon/">AirPods 4 With ANC Drop to &#36;164.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-4-with-anc-drop-to-164-99-on-amazon.2447771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Unveils &#039;Edits&#039; App as CapCut Rival</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/instagram-unveils-edits-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-unveils-edits-app-as-capcut-rival.2447768/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 07:04:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/instagram-unveils-edits-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram has unveiled a new video editing app called Edits, which aims to fill the void left by CapCut's removal from U.S. app stores following federal restrictions on ByteDance-owned applications.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/instagram-edits.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-986242" /><br/>
The announcement came from head <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mosseri/post/DFBL3J7yEmn?xmt=AQGzQqzIYiM_Xgn2QrsrdYf4Ry6ZDSybaTvMEftcg_u8sQ">Adam Mosseri</a>, explaining that Edits as a "full suite of creative tools" for mobile video creators. According to Mosseri, Edits is aimed at creators who produce short-form videos on mobile devices: <br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Edits will have a much broader range of creative tools and probably a smaller addressable audience. Think a place to track all your ideas instead of templates. Think AI video editing tools on a per clip or per video basis. Think new insights on why your videos are succeeding or struggling.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The app includes AI-powered animation for images, green screen effects, video overlays, automatic captions with customization options, and tools for reducing background noise. It also allows users to save drafts, share projects with collaborators, and leverage a dedicated tab for inspiration and trending audio. Videos created with Edits and shared on Instagram Reels will benefit from advanced performance analytics, allowing creators to monitor engagement metrics such as follower interaction, video skips, and overall reach. <br/>
<br/>
The app arrives in the wake of CapCut's recent delisting from the Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and Google Play Store due to U.S. law. Mosseri said that Edits will "end up pretty different than CapCut," noting that it is designed to cater to creators who want a more comprehensive toolset rather than casual video makers or users of desktop editing software. The app also stands out by offering export options without watermarks, a feature that has recently become a limitation in CapCut's free version.<br/>
<br/>
Edits launches in February on iOS, and Android at a later date. It is available to <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/edits-an-instagram-app/id6738967378">pre-order on the App Store now</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/instagram-unveils-edits-app/">Instagram Unveils &#039;Edits&#039; App as CapCut Rival</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-unveils-edits-app-as-capcut-rival.2447768/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Air Models With M3 Chip Seemingly Confirmed by Leaker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-leak/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-seemingly-confirmed-by-leaker.2447766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 06:54:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-leak/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Evan Blass</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation iPad Air and entry-level iPad models have seemingly been confirmed today by known leaker Evan Blass.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m2-ipad-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954134" /><br/>
In a private <a href="https://x.com/evleaks/status/1881274150351962611">social media post</a>, Blass shared an image of what appears to be source code mentioning unreleased 11-inch iPad Air, 13-inch iPad Air, and iPad 11 models. It is unclear where this information was obtained from, but Blass has a pretty good track record with leaks. In 2020, for example, he revealed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/iphone-12-pro-colors-leaked/">marketing images for the iPhone 12 lineup</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/apple-announces-homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> a few hours before those devices were announced.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, the leak reveals the next iPad Air models will apparently be equipped with the M3 chip. There had been speculation that Apple might use the iPad Pro's M4 chip for the next iPad Air models instead, in a move away from chips manufactured with TSMC's expensive and lower-yield first-generation 3nm process, known as N3B. There was a six-month period in 2022 where both the iPad Pro and iPad Air had the M1 chip, so there is precedent for such a thing. Nonetheless, it appears the iPad Air will use the M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The leak does not mention which chip the iPad 11 will use, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman previously said the device will be equipped with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/12/ipad-11-rumored-specs/">A17 Pro chip and 8GB of RAM</a> to enable Apple Intelligence support on the entry-level iPad.<br/>
<br/>
The leak also seems to confirm the widely-rumored iPhone SE 4.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPad-11-iPad-Air-M3-Leak.jpeg" alt="" width="587" height="1523" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986267" /><br/>
iPad 10 models have an A14 Bionic chip and 4GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
Apple unveiled the iPad 10 in October 2022, with pricing starting at &#36;449 at the time. Apple lowered the iPad 10's starting price to &#36;349 in the U.S. in May 2024. It is unclear if the iPad 11 will start at &#36;349, or if pricing will return to a higher level.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last updated the iPad Air in May 2024 with the M2 chip, and it also introduced the first-ever 13-inch iPad Air model at the time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will likely announce these new iPads by March or April this year. No major design changes have been rumored for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPads are expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/19/new-magic-keyboard-for-ipads-coming-soon/">accompanied by new Magic Keyboards</a> too.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/evan-blass/">Evan Blass</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-leak/">New iPad Air Models With M3 Chip Seemingly Confirmed by Leaker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-air-models-with-m3-chip-seemingly-confirmed-by-leaker.2447766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Honors Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/apple-honors-martin-luther-king-jr/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-honors-dr-martin-luther-king-jr.2447758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 05:26:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/apple-honors-martin-luther-king-jr/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Martin Luther King Jr</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has updated the <a href="https://www.apple.com/">home page of its website</a> to honor Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. today. The page highlights some of King's most impactful quotes, and invites people to explore his legacy further through the Apple Books and Apple News apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/Apple-2025-MLK-Day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986238" /><br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook also honored King in a <a href="https://x.com/tim_cook/status/1881310716226916777">social media post</a> today.<br/>
<br/>
Today is Martin Luther King Jr. Day in the United States. As a result of this federal holiday, along with U.S. President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration later today, it is likely to be a slower day for Apple-related product news. Cook will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/15/tim-cook-trump-inauguration/">reportedly be in attendance</a> at Trump's inauguration, alongside many other high-profile CEOs.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/martin-luther-king-jr/">Martin Luther King Jr</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/20/apple-honors-martin-luther-king-jr/">Apple Honors Dr. Martin Luther King Jr.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-honors-dr-martin-luther-king-jr.2447758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
