<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 04:03:59 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Focusing on OLED Rather Than Foldable iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad.2413800/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 03:20:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Nikkei</category>
		<category>Foldable iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is focusing on bringing OLED displays to its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and MacBook lineups rather than offering its first foldable, <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Spotlight/Supply-Chain/Apple-to-switch-to-OLED-displays-for-iPads-and-MacBooks"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/Foldable-iPhone-2023-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1458" height="820" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-797663" /><br/>
Apple is widely expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">bring OLED displays</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> for the first time next year ahead of a wider expansion across the MacBook lineup. <em>Nikkei</em> today corroborated this information citing sources said to be to be familiar with the matter, adding that the first OLED MacBook model is under development for production in the second half of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Nikkei</em> claims that Apple is currently evaluating the potential of offering a foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; after the transition to OLED is complete, but it is not a main focus and the company does not yet have a solid timeline for releasing such a device, mirroring a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/25/apple-considering-foldable-ipad-digitimes/">report from <em>DigiTimes</em></a> earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
Reports from a multitude of reliable sources are fairly consistent that Apple plans to launch a foldable &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; before a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. In October, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/foldable-ipad-now-in-intensive-development-could-be-announced-as-soon-as-late-2024/"><em>DigiTimes</em> reported</a> a range of details about Apple's tentative work on foldable iPads, including necessary design changes and small-scale production plans.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nikkei-com/">Nikkei</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-ipad/">Foldable iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad/">Report: Apple Focusing on OLED Rather Than Foldable iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-focusing-on-oled-rather-than-foldable-ipad.2413800/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 10.2: How to Change Watch Faces With a Swipe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/change-apple-watch-faces-with-a-swipe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-10-2-how-to-change-watch-faces-with-a-swipe.2413793/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/change-apple-watch-faces-with-a-swipe&#038;post_date=1702641600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In watchOS 10.2, you can enable a swipe gesture to switch between Apple Watch faces more easily, just like you used to be able to in watchOS 9. Keep reading to learn how it's done.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-watch-ultra-1-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918496" /><br/>
If you are a long-time Apple Watch user, you probably remember a time when it was possible to switch watch faces with a simple swipe gesture across the display. That was the default interaction in watchOS 9, but then Apple removed the gesture with the upgrade to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple changed the interaction because of user complaints that it was too easy to accidentally change watch faces. But for anyone who never had this problem, Apple just made things harder – by requiring a long press before swiping to change the active watch face.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, prior to the release of watchOS 10.2, Apple seemed to realize what it had done, and it has introduced a setting that re-instates the earlier method of swiping to change watch faces. If you preferred the older interaction, the following steps show you how to enable it.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app on your watch.</li><br/>
<li>Tap Clock.</li><br/>
<li>Toggle on the switch next to Swipe to Switch Watch Face.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/swipe-to-change-watch-face.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="940" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926616" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. If you have more than one watch face assigned to your Apple Watch, you will now be able to swipe quickly and easily between them.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/change-apple-watch-faces-with-a-swipe/">watchOS 10.2: How to Change Watch Faces With a Swipe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-10-2-how-to-change-watch-faces-with-a-swipe.2413793/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.3 Beta: All the New Features So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-beta-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2413770/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 15:20:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-beta-features&#038;post_date=1702606858/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple started testing the iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas in December, and while we are not expecting these updates to be as feature rich as iOS and iPadOS 17.2, there are some notable features that have been found so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" /><br/>
This guide aggregates everything that is coming in the iOS 17.3 update, and we'll update it throughout the beta testing period.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="stolen_device_protection">Stolen Device Protection</h2><br/>
Earlier this year, there were news reports about a slate of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> thefts where the thief spied on a victim to learn the device passcode before stealing the phone, leading to drained bank accounts and an untraceable &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ios-stolen-device-protection.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926120" /><br/>
As a solution, Apple introduced Stolen Device Mode in iOS 17.3 to add extra security. If someone should obtain both your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and your passcode, this feature prevents total catastrophe. With Stolen Device Mode enabled, accessing passwords in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, turning off Lost Mode, erasing content, and making purchases in Safari requires biometric authentication with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Certain actions such as changing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password require &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; and have a one-hour security delay. So if you (or someone else) tried to change your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; login, you would need both &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; authentication and then an hour wait period before the password could be updated. These wait periods are waived when you are in a trusted location like home or work.<br/>
<br/>
As outlined in our report on the feature, here are actions that require biometric authentication when the Stolen Device Protection is activated:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Viewing/using passwords or passkeys saved in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; Keychain</li><br/>
 <li>Applying for a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></li><br/>
 <li>Viewing an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; virtual card</li><br/>
 <li>Turning off Lost Mode</li><br/>
 <li>Erasing all content and settings</li><br/>
 <li>Taking certain Apple Cash and Savings actions in Wallet</li><br/>
 <li>Using payment methods saved in Safari</li><br/>
 <li>Using your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to set up a new device</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Note that these actions do not have a passcode backup, so you can't use a passcode to skirt &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;. Actions that require biometric authentication and have a one-hour security delay include the following:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Changing your &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; password</li><br/>
 <li>Updating select &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; account security settings, including adding or removing a trusted device, trusted phone number, Recovery Key, or Recovery Contact</li><br/>
 <li>Changing your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode</li><br/>
 <li>Adding or removing &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>Turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a></li><br/>
 <li>Turning off Stolen Device Protection</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Stolen Device Protection is available on all iPhones that are able to run <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, which includes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS and newer. It is an opt-in feature that can be turned on in the Settings app by going to &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; &amp; Passcode and toggling on Stolen Device Protection.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collaborative_apple_music_playlists">Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</h2><br/>
Apple first tested collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists in iOS 17.2, but the feature was removed before the software was released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
Collaborative &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlists are back in the iOS 17.3 beta, suggesting Apple just needed a little bit more time to work out the kinks.<br/>
<br/>
In iOS 17.3, you can take any of your existing playlists or create a new one and then invite others to join in to add songs and listen to the playlist. You can invite friends, family members, and others who share your musical preferences, and there doesn't appear to be a limit on how many people can contribute.<br/>
<br/>
We have a <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/pl.u-kaJH7JG97e?a=join&amp;it=zr6IZVEGZ6tVoblq">MacRumors collaborative music playlist</a> available for those who want to join in and share music with other MacRumors readers.<br/>
<br/>
To use the collaboration feature, go to a playlist in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app and then tap on the person icon. You will be able to generate a link that you can send to others, and everyone who is invited can access the playlist. There is an option to approve each person that joins, and leaving this off just opens it up to anyone with the link.<br/>
<br/>
The person who created the playlist can remove people, remove songs, and turn off collaboration at any time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in iOS 17.3 added a neat emoji reaction feature that allows listeners to add an emoji to any song that's playing to express their feelings about it. There are standard quick access emoji options like a heart and thumbs up, but with the "+" button, any emoji can be added.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-music-collaborative-playlist-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926541" /><br/>
When you're listening to a song in the playlist that has emoji reactions, those emoji animate as the song begins to play.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
iOS 17.3, iPadOS 17.3, macOS 14.3, tvOS 17.3, and watchOS 10.3 are all expected to see a public release sometime around January. Beta testing will be slightly delayed by the Christmas and New Year's holidays.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-3-beta-features/">iOS 17.3 Beta: All the New Features So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2413770/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beeper Mini on Continued Outages: &#039;It&#039;s Super Annoying That Apple is Penalizing Their Own Customers&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/beeper-mini-continued-outages/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beeper-mini-on-continued-outages-its-super-annoying-that-apple-is-penalizing-their-own-customers.2413763/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 13:21:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/beeper-mini-continued-outages/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iMessage for Android app Beeper Mini is once again having connectivity issues, which it has attributed to Apple. Last night, Beeper Mini <a href="https://twitter.com/onbeeper/status/1735127340357918874">stopped working</a> for some people, and the company confirmed that Apple was "deliberately blocking iMessages from being delivered" to approximately five percent of Beeper Mini users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/beeper-mini.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925247" /><br/>
At the time, Beeper Mini said that uninstalling and reinstalling Beeper Mini could serve as a workaround while a fix was developed. As of now, issues with the Beeper Cloud service have been resolved, but some Beeper Mini users are still having connectivity issues.<br/>
<br/>
On Twitter, Beeper's developers have been complaining about Apple's continued efforts to block the app, even though Apple made it clear that Beeper Mini was not going to be allowed.<br/>
<br/>
"It's super annoying that Apple is penalizing their own customers and Android users who just want secure and encrypted chats," says a <a href="https://twitter.com/onbeeper/status/1735315504880123995">message on the Beeper account</a>. "We understand if you choose to uninstall Beeper Mini at this time."<br/>
<br/>
Beeper Mini <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/beeper-mini-brings-imessage-to-android/">launched last week</a>, promising to bring a full iMessage experience to Android users. The app used iMessage reverse engineering to function, registering the phone numbers of Android users with Apple's own iMessage servers.<br/>
<br/>
Android users were able to have "blue bubbles" in conversations with iMessage users, and all iMessage features worked, such as read receipts, typing indicators, reactions, and more. Beeper Mini essentially worked by making Android devices look like they were Apple devices, and it didn't take long for Apple to put a stop to it.<br/>
<br/>
Three days after Beeper Mini launched, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/beeper-mini-imessage-for-android-shutdown/">app quit working</a>, and Apple confirmed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/apple-confirms-it-shut-down-beeper-mini/">it shut the app down</a>. Apple said that it blocked Beeper Mini from exploiting fake credentials to gain access to iMessage, as this posed "significant risks to user security and privacy."<br/>
<blockquote>At Apple, we build our products and services with industry-leading privacy and security technologies designed to give users control of their data and keep personal information safe. We took steps to protect our users by blocking techniques that exploit fake credentials in order to gain access to iMessage. These techniques posed significant risks to user security and privacy, including the potential for metadata exposure and enabling unwanted messages, spam, and phishing attacks. We will continue to make updates in the future to protect our users.</blockquote><br/>
In a blog post, Beeper Mini's development team said that it would work to restore service, while also criticizing Apple for the decision. The team claims that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> customers have "less security and privacy than before" because Beeper Mini encrypted messages sent between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android devices.<br/>
<blockquote>We deeply object to the allegation that Beeper Mini 'poses significant risks to user security and privacy'. This is completely untrue. As we explained above, the opposite is actually true. Beeper Mini increases the security and privacy of both Android and iPhone customers. To prove this, we published a detailed blog post about how the app keeps data secure and private. Beeper Mini is end-to-end encrypted.</blockquote><br/>
The Beeper Mini team says that it has not spoken with Apple directly. On Monday of this week, Beeper developers did find a way to get the Android app working again, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/beeper-mini-android-imessage-app-back/">with some major changes</a>. The updated version of the app requires users to sign in with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> (not required with the prior version), and it only supports sending and receiving messages through an email address instead of a phone number.<br/>
<br/>
The team behind Beeper Mini is still working to find a way to get phone numbers to work with iMessage again, but Apple has blocked the backdoor that was used to register Android numbers as fake Apple users.<br/>
<br/>
Many of the complaints about security and functionality from the Beeper Mini team will be solved with Rich Communication Services, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, which Apple plans to adopt next year. &zwnj;RCS&zwnj; will be used for chats between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users, and it includes support for high quality video and images, emoji reactions, typing indicators, read receipts, and more.<br/>
<br/>
If Beeper Mini does indeed find a way to get phone numbers to work and to keep Beeper Mini running, it likely will not be long before Apple puts a stop to it again. Apple has made it clear that it does not plan to willingly allow Beeper Mini to use iMessage servers.<br/>
<br/>
Beeper founder Eric Migicovsky said on Twitter that Tim Sweeney and Epic "won this week against Big Tech," referencing the Epic v. Google trial, and that Beeper Mini has a chance. "We're not giving up," he wrote.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/beeper-mini-continued-outages/">Beeper Mini on Continued Outages: &#039;It&#039;s Super Annoying That Apple is Penalizing Their Own Customers&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beeper-mini-on-continued-outages-its-super-annoying-that-apple-is-penalizing-their-own-customers.2413763/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Aura&#039;s 15&quot; Walden Smart Photo Frame Makes a Touching Gift</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/aura-smart-photo-frame/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-auras-15-walden-smart-photo-frame-makes-a-touching-gift.2413759/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 13:00:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/aura-smart-photo-frame&#038;post_date=1702598416/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://auraframes.com">Aura</a>, a company known for its range of smart photo frames, this fall <a href="https://auraframes.com/digital-frames/color/walden-ink-mat">introduced the Walden</a>, its largest photo frame to date. Measuring in at 15 inches, the Walden has a huge display that makes digital photos a focal point in the home.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-zoom.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926670" /><br/>
We've previously reviewed (and liked) the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/aura-mason-digital-frame/">9-inch Aura Mason frame</a>, but the new Walden model is 66 percent larger and it is also Aura's first frame that can be mounted on the wall, so we thought we'd revisit the smart frames ahead of the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of size, the Walden frame is 15.7 inches long, 12.7 inches tall, and 1.2 inches in depth, so it's a little bit thicker than your average photo frame. Compared to the 9-inch Mason frame, the Walden frame is much more eye-catching in a room because of the space that it takes up on a wall. A 9-inch frame looks odd when hung on the wall, but a 15-inch frame is the ideal size for it.<br/>
<br/>
The Walden Frame fits right in on a wall in the living room, entry way, or bedroom, but it can also be placed on a table or other surface if desired with the built-in stand. The display is bright, the colors are largely accurate (the frame tends to add some saturation) and the images look vibrant, but one downside is that it is limited to a 1600x1200 resolution with 133 pixels per inch.<br/>
<br/>
Aura's smaller frames all have better pixel density, and the resolution does impact the quality here. The Mason frame with the same resolution and a smaller size looks better up close, but the resolution is not a dealbreaker. Aura is using a matte display that has anti-reflective coating, so even in a bright room with sunlight or lights that hit the glass, the pictures are visible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-in-room.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926672" /><br/>
The frame itself is black with a textured white mat around the display. The mat feels about standard size for a photo frame of this size, so it blends in well with other picture frames that you might have. Unfortunately, there are no other frame colors available, and that's one of the main downsides of the Walden.<br/>
<br/>
Aura does have other frames fthat come in different colors and without mats, but on the whole, color selection is limited. On the plus side, the thin frame of the Walden does look sleek, but I am torn on the mat size with some of the images.<br/>
<br/>
The Walden frame can be positioned in either horizontal or landscape mode as it supports both orientations with a 4:3 aspect ratio. Your photos will rotate and resize to fit in the frame regardless of the orientation you choose, but it is best to pick the position that fits the majority of your photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-landscape.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926664" /><br/>
When you put the frame in a specific orientation and it displays a photo in another orientation, one of two things happens. It either crops in to the main subject of the photo, or it adds black bars so the whole image remains visible. For portrait mode images that are close to the subject with nothing to crop in to, this means that you'll see bars at the sides of the frame, which doesn't always look great with the white matte. You can opt to have photo backgrounds used as filler, kind of like what YouTube does for portrait images, in landscape mode, but it still looks off.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-with-bars.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926669" /><br/>
When the frame is in portrait mode, landscape images are typically cut off because they're zoomed in to fit, so there are compromises to be made if you have a lot of images in both orientations. I do think Aura's frames do a decent job of making images look as good as possible by zooming in.<br/>
<br/>
Aura ships the Walden with both a tabletop kickstand and a mounting kit, so you can display it wherever it fits best into your home. The mounting kit uses a single Floreat-style hanger, so it's just one nail that goes in the wall. These hangers are strong, so there's little risk of the frame falling down, plus wall damage is limited to the size of a nail hole.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-rear-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1278" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926663" /><br/>
Touch controls at the top of the frame can be used for turning it on and off, changing the photos, viewing details like the date, playing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/live-photos/">Live Photos</a>, deleting photos, and liking photos that were added to the frame by someone else, but all of these actions can also be done through the app if the frame is somewhere that's inaccessible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-dim-light.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926667" /><br/>
The Walden, like all of Aura's frames, is meant to be a more hands-off product. You basically upload images to it and leave it plugged in. It'll cycle through the images every 10 minutes by default, though you can change that in the app. There are a huge range of times to select from 15 seconds to 24 hours, so you can find the perfect photo change interval.<br/>
<br/>
You can upload both photos and videos to the frame, and videos can be set to autoplay. Videos play without sound by default, but can be replayed with sound using the in-app remote or with the touch controls at the top. Speaker volume is controlled in the app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-remote.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926665" /><br/>
The frame is set to turn on when it's light out and turn off when it's dark, but there is an option for an on/off schedule for rooms where the frame might not be able to use its ambient light sensor well or for when you want it active at specific times. I do wish the Walden had better dimming and color matching. With bright images, it can be a little too bright when the room is darker, and it isn't able to match the color temperature of lighting. You'll sometimes get a blue-toned photo that looks odd in a room with soft yellow lighting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-bright.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926668" /><br/>
The app has a built-in remote control accessed through the settings section, and this provides easy access for deleting an image, resizing it properly, playing a video, or switching to the next image. Resizing is particularly useful because if you don't like the way Aura has opted to crop an image, you can fix it and the frame will remember that position going forward.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-adjust-position.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926661" /><br/>
There is no built-in storage in the Walden frame, or in Aura's products in general. Images are uploaded to the cloud, and there is unlimited storage so you can add as many photos and videos as you want. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> are uploaded through the Aura app, through a unique email address for each frame, or through the web, so there are plenty of ways to get images on it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-size.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926666" /><br/>
The Aura app is the best part about Aura's frames. In addition to adding photos yourself, you can also invite friends and family members to connect to your frame so they can add photos too. If a family member has a frame, you can connect to it and upload images to it at any time.<br/>
<br/>
I bought an Aura frame for a family member a few years back, and we still all upload photos to it regularly. It has a prominent place in the living room, and the photos that it displays are frequently talked about. It's such a great way to get photos off of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> with little hassle. I don't know about most people, but I so rarely print my images that I take them and forget about them until a random day when I'm browsing through my &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app. Aura frames provide a way to surface memories them more often.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/aura-frame-onboarding.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926662" /><br/>
Aura is set up for gifting, and you can even preload a frame with photos before the gift recipient opens it. I'm sometimes hesitant to give "smart" Wi-Fi connected devices to my less tech savvy family, but Aura frames are dead simple to set up. I think any person that can operate the basic functions of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can set up the Walden or any other Aura option. You plug in the frame, download the Aura app, and the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; detects it automatically. A pairing code is displayed, and once the code is input (which happens automatically too), it connects to Wi-Fi. You don't need to enter the Wi-Fi password again if the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is already connected to a Wi-Fi network in the home (truly a major stopping point for other smart products I've tried to gift), and that's it. After that, images can be uploaded from the app or by family members who have the app.<br/>
<br/>
The option to upload photos to the Aura from anywhere and the option to have multiple contributors makes this a great gift for grandparents, siblings, friends, or basically anyone you would want to share a photo with. For a grandparent, you can set up the frame ahead of time, load it with photos, and then invite other friends and family members all with no interaction from the recipient. The person I gifted a frame to doesn't upload their own photos, but has six other family members who do.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/adding-images-family-frame.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926660" /><br/>
If you have multiple friends or family members with Aura frames, you can upload photos to all of the frames at the same time, making it a fun way to share photos from birthday parties, trips, and other activities with several people basically instantaneously.<br/>
<br/>
You can definitely use an old <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> or other tablet in lieu of something like the Aura frame, but Aura's products are easier to use for the specific purpose of displaying photos, plus they look like an actual photo frame rather than an electronic device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
Whenever I need a gift for someone and I'm not sure what to get, Aura is my go-to. I have not met anyone who doesn't like Aura's frames, and for grandparents and/or less technically inclined people, it's like magic.<br/>
<br/>
I think the Walden in particular is a great choice because of its size. It's much more visible in a room than Aura's smaller frames, and the frame to get if you want to put a lot of focus on your digital images. It's also the option I'd get for grandparents or older adults who might be having a harder time with their vision, but it's not the frame I'd pick for subtlety or for displaying high-resolution images where quality is a concern.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Aura Walden frame can be <a href="https://auraframes.com/digital-frames/color/walden-ink-mat">purchased from the Aura website</a> for &#36;250.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Aura provided MacRumors with a Walden Frame for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/aura-smart-photo-frame/">Review: Aura&#039;s 15&quot; Walden Smart Photo Frame Makes a Touching Gift</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-auras-15-walden-smart-photo-frame-makes-a-touching-gift.2413759/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Journalists Detail Seeing Their Own Spatial Videos on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/journalists-experience-spatial-videos-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/journalists-detail-seeing-their-own-spatial-videos-on-apple-vision-pro.2413756/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 12:05:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/journalists-experience-spatial-videos-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-features/">launch of iOS 17.2</a>, Apple added a camera feature that allows <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max models to record 3D spatial video that will be viewable on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> when it becomes available for purchase.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
To demonstrate the feature, Apple this week invited several members of the media to record spatial video with their iPhones and then view it on an &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; headset. Those who were able to experience their videos in 3D have now written about the experience and what it's like using the Vision Pro for reliving memories.<br/>
<br/>
<em><a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/computing/i-saw-my-iphone-spatial-movies-in-apple-vision-pro/">CNET</em>'s Scott Stein</a> found that videos of his family members were the most compelling, and a recording of his mother in particular seemed to make eye contact and made him feel like he was "almost there." In video with a lot of motion, the 30 fps limit was noticeable, though less so in videos with less motion. HDR photos "looked great," with Stein saying they appeared as good as or better than on a Mac or a TV, with HDR that "popped" and options to zoom in.<br/>
<blockquote>I also got a kick out of seeing some of my favorite exhibits at the Museum of Natural History in 3D. I went to the Hall of Ocean Life, where a trio of little tanks on the top floor house dioramas of prehistoric sea creatures that I've loved since I was a kid. I captured the ammonites and trilobites, gliding from case to case. In 3D on Vision Pro, it felt like a little home diorama revisited. I could see the joy of capturing little immersive installations, or spaces, that aren't easy to go back to, and having them in front of you again.</blockquote><br/>
<a href="https://www.techradar.com/computing/virtual-reality-augmented-reality/seeing-your-own-spatial-video-on-vision-pro-is-an-immersive-trip-and-i-highly-recommend-it"><em>TechRadar</em>'s Lance Ulanoff</a> said that he was "startled by the quality and immersive nature" of panoramic images that he had captured, and the wider view showed him details he had not seen before. A video of a model train looked like it would "ride right into [his] lap." Compared to standard videos, Ulanoff said the videos "felt more real" and resulted in heightened emotions. He said the level of emotion that can be experienced from family videos in 3D "can be quite intense."<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.inverse.com/tech/apple-vision-pro-photos-app-spatial-video-hands-on"><em>Inverse</em>'s Raymond Wong</a> said that spatial videos "feel alive" because of the way the border becomes "glowy and dream-like" when looked at, giving the content the "characteristics of a memory." In a spatial video of his mom, he says he was transported back to the moment, and it was "surreal" to see his mom "talking, laughing, and eating in spatial video."<br/>
<br/>
Wong said that spatial videos can "look life-sized" at a certain distance and window size, but even zoomed out, he felt emotional seeing his mother in 3D.<blockquote>I think Apple was right in suggesting I capture sentimental content in spatial video. Cool as it was to see my colleagues at the office and a bar with a little bit of the third dimension, I don't think rewatching those clips had the same impact on me as the ones of my family. I suspect once people have the opportunity to see their own content in Vision Pro, they'll get a better sense of when and when not to tap the spatial video icon in the camera app on their iPhones.</blockquote><br/>
Josh Rubin of <em><a href="https://coolhunting.com/tech/recording-spatial-video-and-viewing-it-in-apple-vision-pro/">Cool Hunting</a></em> said that even in recordings where he was warned there wasn't enough light, the video on the headset was "crisp and not grainy." He found that the best scenes had multiple focal points in a two to eight foot range. Too much movement in a spatial video can be disorienting, leading to nausea.<br/>
<blockquote>Shots with the camera stationary (such as on a tripod) are ideal, but camera movement is often necessary or desired to make a satisfying story. I found that recording linear and gently curved movements, especially in open spaces, created videos that were easy to view. By contrast, sharp turns in close quarters created more jarring videos.</blockquote><br/>
The Vision Pro headset is set to launch in early 2024, and Apple is hoping that customers who plan to buy it will have a selection of their own spatial videos ready to go when it comes out. Spatial video can be recorded right now on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, though the captured video will look normal until viewed in 3D on the Vision Pro headset.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/journalists-experience-spatial-videos-vision-pro/">Journalists Detail Seeing Their Own Spatial Videos on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/journalists-detail-seeing-their-own-spatial-videos-on-apple-vision-pro.2413756/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: The Philips Hue Line Now Has Security Cameras, But There&#039;s No HomeKit Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/philips-hue-secure-camera/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-the-philips-hue-line-now-has-security-cameras-but-theres-no-homekit-support.2413754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 11:53:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/philips-hue-secure-camera&#038;post_date=1702594391/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Philips Hue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Philips Hue line has long been focused on lighting products, but this year, Hue parent company Signify expanded the lineup with a set of Philips Hue Secure cameras and sensors designed for home security.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/hue-secure-camera-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908246" /><br/>
I was able to test out the &#36;200 Hue Secure Wired Camera to see how it measures up to some of the other smart camera options on the market. Hue's cameras can be used indoors or out, and the Hue Secure has 1080p video recording with night vision and motion trigger alerts, which at this point I'd expect from any security camera.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-design.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926641" /><br/>
The camera itself has a base that mounts to the wall with a screw, but if you want to sit it on a table or another flat surface, you need to pay an extra &#36;30 for the "Desktop" version. You can also buy the desktop stand after buying the camera, but it is &#36;50, which I feel is unreasonable for a plastic stand that should have come with the camera at no extra cost to begin with. I didn't want to use or test the camera mounted, so I did purchase the stand. You could probably rig something up, but the placement of the cord on the bottom of the camera prevents it from laying flat without the stand, and it's angled too high to use that way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-front.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926642" /><br/>
To allow for interchangeable wall mounting and desktop use, magnets are used for base attachment. The magnets are super strong, so while the camera is meant to be mounted to the wall, I'm not worried that it's going to become detached. You can take it off the mount, and attach the mount to either the top or the bottom to optimize the view regardless of where you're mounting it. The field of view is wide enough that you're able to see an entire room if the camera is indoors, or a good section of your yard if it is outdoors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-magnetic-components.jpg" alt="" width="4047" height="2276" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926644" /><br/>
The Hue Secure has a white plastic casing and a standard camera lens inside, and there is no mistaking it for a security camera. I was surprised at how long it is (a little over 3.5 inches), which means if you wall mount it, it's going to protrude a decent amount. The battery version of this camera is even longer in length at five inches, so it will protrude even further when mounted. I like the clean design and the magnetic attachment system, especially since the magnets allow it to be positioned in a range of ways that might not be possible with just a swivel mount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-standard-base.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926645" /><em><div class="center-wrap">This is the standard base the camera comes with. The other base is one I purchased for &#36;50 to allow it to be placed on a desk.</div></em><br/>
The video quality was totally fine for a 1080p indoor/outdoor camera, and on par with the HomeKit-enabled cameras that I've tested. So, speaking of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a>, these don't have it. Those with a lot of Philips Hue lights know they all work with &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, but that is not the case with the cameras. No &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; support is likely going to be a dealbreaker for those in Apple's ecosystem who want everything to be controllable through a central app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-live-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="988" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926646" /><br/>
To use Hue Cameras, a Hue Bridge is required. The cameras don't ship with the Bridge, which costs &#36;60 if you don't have one already for Hue lights. I prefer smart home products that have a hub or a bridge like the Hue Bridge because it improves reliability. I never have setup issues or connectivity problems with my Hue lights, and the same is true for the Hue Secure Camera. It works and it works well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-cord.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926647" /><br/>
It was easy to add the camera to the app, and it can be viewed through the new Hue Secure section of the app. In my testing, it never once went offline, and it was a more reliable than the Eve <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit-secure-video/">HomeKit Secure Video</a> camera I have outside, which is off more than it is on and has been a total headache these last few months.<br/>
<br/>
I've had similar problems with other &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; cameras, and I just don't find them to be the most reliable option. Compared to Ring, though, I don't think Hue has much of an edge. My Ring cameras rarely go offline or have connectivity issues, so Hue is about on par.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-side-view.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926648" /><br/>
The cameras can be paired to Hue lights with automations to activate the lights when motion is detected, and they can sound alarms should there be an intruder. According to Signify, there is end-to-end encryption (E2EE) to keep video clips and snapshots private, along with software that helps prevent hacking. Video data is stored in the Hue Cloud if you opt for that, and content is deleted after 30 or 60 days. With E2EE, video and audio recordings cannot be viewed if the Hue Cloud were hacked because a multi-word auto-generated passcode you have is required. On that note, you need to keep the passcode somewhere safe, and you also need to hold on to the Hue Secure "Ownership Card" that's required for setup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-timeline.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926649" /><br/>
Like other smart cameras, the Hue Secure can recognize people, pets, and packages to send tailored alerts, and there are options to set up Activity and Package zones. There is a mimic presence function that can turn on Hue lights to make it seem like you're home when you're not, and the cameras support two-way talk so you can interface with someone if you need, but these are all functions that are available on other smart security cameras.<br/>
<br/>
Up to 10 cameras can be linked to a Hue Bridge, and a Hue account is required to use them. While the cameras can be used without a subscription, some of the functionality does require a monthly payment. Live streaming, video snapshots, light and sound alarms, and notifications are accessible for free.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-paid-plans.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926650" /><br/>
Recording requires a Basic or Plus plan, priced starting at &#36;39.99 per year after a 90-day trial period that comes with the purchase. Other paywalled features include Activity zone setup, and package/people alerts. The Basic plan supports two cameras, but if you have more cameras, you need the Plus plan that costs &#36;100/year. That basically puts the full cost of a Hue Camera at &#36;200 for the camera itself (not counting any accessories), &#36;60 for a Bridge (though these are sometimes on sale for less), and at least &#36;3.30 a month if you want to have a 30-day log.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-video-feed.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="988" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926651" /><br/>
If you wanted to use Hue Secure for a whole-home security system, you're looking at &#36;570 for a three-camera bundle (wired, not battery), and &#36;275 for a set of four contact sensors, two motion sensors, and a Bridge. Depending on how many doors and windows you have and what you want to protect, that may only cover a small home.<br/>
<br/>
I found the Hue Secure portion of the Hue app to be a bit confusing at first. I expected to have the option to see my camera feed right when opening the app, but I don't. I have to tap on the "Disarmed" or "Armed" feature under Security, then I have to tap on the feed under "Cameras." It then takes several seconds for the camera to connect to my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> so that I can see my feed.<br/>
<br/>
The Hue Secure camera is not activated and set to recording unless the "Armed" option is enabled, so no alerts are received unless the camera is set to this state. The "Armed" feature can activate a siren or flash the lights when motion is detected, but by disabling everything, you can set it to Armed without having alarms and flashing lights going off if you simply want motion notifications.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-night-vision.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="988" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926652" /><br/>
There are separate Armed activation options for when at home and when away, with the Hue app using geofencing for the away option to turn on the Armed mode automatically. If you "armed" the system and then it detected motion while you were away, you could set it to send a notification, flash the lights, and sound an alarm, hopefully scaring off any would-be intruders. When motion is detected, a 60 to 90 second video is captured, depending on subscription plan.<br/>
<br/>
Hue also has "Take Action" buttons for turning on the lights or sounding an alarm, and there are buttons for calling 911 or an emergency contact. The Armed and Not Armed features are nice for those who want a one-touch button that enables or disables all recording.<br/>
<br/>
At home, if you have the camera armed, you need to ensure that it and any linked motion sensors are not in areas where they could be accidentally triggered, because there is no specific person recognition or way for the camera to tell an intruder from someone who lives in the home. If you have lights set to activate or a siren on, a middle of the night bathroom break might accidentally set everything off. I have an open floor plan, so none of the main entries in my home are sectioned off enough that I could arm an indoor Hue Secure camera and not have to worry about triggering it myself.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-take-action.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926653" /><br/>
With a paid plan, the Hue Secure camera can tell a person from another event that triggers motion like an animal or a vehicle, but without it, it's all or nothing motion sensing. Setting boundaries for recording is also a paid feature, but there are blackout zones that can stop the camera from recording everything that's marked.<br/>
<br/>
When not armed, the camera is not recording, but the live view can be accessed. If you want to record, you need to make sure you put it into armed mode before you leave the house, and there is an automation for this so you don't need to remember to do it manually. There are options to delete all timeline events under the privacy section, and individual recordings can also be removed.<br/>
<br/>
From the layout of the app and the function of the camera, it's clear that Hue intends its system to be used for detecting and deterring intruders rather than something like keeping an eye on a pet or general home monitoring. The two-way talk works well, and the microphone quality is fine as long as there isn't a lot of ambient noise. I didn't have an issue being heard or understanding what was said on the camera.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-interface.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1984" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926654" /><br/>
I have a lot of Hue lights and also several security cameras, so I'm probably the kind of person that's the ideal target market for Hue's new camera options, but I'm struggling to find something new here to entice me to upgrade to the Hue Secure system at this price point.<br/>
<br/>
At a minimum, I'd like to be able to integrate these cameras into &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; so I can see the cameras in the Home app on the TV, Mac, and other devices. There isn't a Hue app on the Mac or on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> so while the Hue app itself does have a live feed of the camera, I can't view it on anything but an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. I also don't have options to use the cameras with my other non-Hue &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; lights and sensors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bottom Line</h2><br/>
Given the number of &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; cameras on the market, I think the lack of &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; integration and the lack of &zwnj;HomeKit Secure Video&zwnj; support makes these a difficult sell to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; users. And for people who don't care about &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; integration, the cost of these cameras makes it hard for them to compete with cheaper cameras with similar specs, such as those from Ring. The Ring Stick Up Cam with 1080p video recording and a battery is &#36;100, Hue's equivalent is &#36;250.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/hue-camera-front-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926655" /><br/>
There's already a lot of competition in the smart camera market, and it's tough to see where the Hue cameras quite fit in at this point given the limited integration and the price. The Hue cameras with included floodlights make the most sense because they serve a dual purpose as a light and as a camera, so those I could see investing in, but only if I was able to integrate them into &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The Hue Secure System would most appeal to someone who has Hue lights but few other smart home products and wants to stay entirely in a single platform.<br/>
<h2>How to Buy</h2><br/>
The Hue Secure Wired Camera <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FPhilips-Hue-Secure-Security-Camera%2Fdp%2FB0CLBLFBNY">can be purchased from Amazon.com</a> or <a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us/products/smart-security/">from the Hue website</a> for &#36;200. The <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FPhilips-Hue-Secure-Battery-Powered-Security%2Fdp%2FB0CLBFNMW9">Battery Powered version is &#36;250</a> and the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FPhilips-Hue-Secure-Desktop-Security%2Fdp%2FB0CLBFD5JN">Desktop model is &#36;230</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Signify provided MacRumors with a Hue Secure Wired Camera for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/philips-hue/">Philips Hue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/philips-hue-secure-camera/">Review: The Philips Hue Line Now Has Security Cameras, But There&#039;s No HomeKit Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-the-philips-hue-line-now-has-security-cameras-but-theres-no-homekit-support.2413754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iTunes for Windows 12.13.1 With Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/itunes-for-windows-12-13-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-itunes-for-windows-12-13-1-with-security-fixes.2413746/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:45:46 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/itunes-for-windows-12-13-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iTunes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released an iTunes 12.13.1 update for Windows users, with the software introducing security improvements.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-846163" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/itunes-for-windows.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
According to Apple's release notes, there are no notable new features, but the new version of iTunes should be installed as soon as possible because of the security improvements<br/>
<br/>
iTunes for Windows is typically updated every few months, and this update follows an October release that saw Apple add options for listening to podcasts and audiobooks.<br/>
<br/>
iTunes has been phased out on the Mac for several years now and it has been replaced with Finder and the TV app, but Apple has continued to keep the Windows version available.<br/>
<br/>
iTunes for Windows can be downloaded from the <a href="https://apps.microsoft.com/store/detail/itunes/9PB2MZ1ZMB1S?hl=en-us&amp;gl=US">Microsoft Store</a> or <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT210384">from Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itunes/">iTunes</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-apps.2">Mac Apps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/itunes-for-windows-12-13-1/">Apple Releases iTunes for Windows 12.13.1 With Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-itunes-for-windows-12-13-1-with-security-fixes.2413746/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Public Beta of iOS 17.3 With Stolen Device Protection</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-3-with-stolen-device-protection.2413745/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:10:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its release. The public iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas come two days after Apple released the betas for developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">includes Stolen Device Protection</a>, a feature that offers an extra layer of security in case your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is stolen and the thief also obtains your passcode. With this turned on, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication is required for viewing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain passwords, turning off Lost Mode, erasing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s contents, using saved payment methods in Safari, and more. There is no passcode entry option should &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; fail.<br/>
<br/>
Certain actions, such as changing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password, updating a device passcode, turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, and removing &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; require authentication and also a one-hour security delay.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-beta-apple-music-collaborative-playlists/">collaborative Apple Music playlists</a>, a feature that lets <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers build playlists with friends, family members, and others who share their musical tastes. Any playlist can be turned into a collaborative playlist by tapping on the person-shaped icon and sharing the link.<br/>
<br/>
Those who want to try it out in iOS 17.3 can click on <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/pl.u-kaJH7JG97e?a=join&amp;it=zr6IZVEGZ6tVoblq">the MacRumors playlist link</a> to try adding a song.<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 to be released in January 2024.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-public-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Public Beta of iOS 17.3 With Stolen Device Protection</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-3-with-stolen-device-protection.2413745/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2413743/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 10:09:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The public beta comes two days after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-1/">the first developer beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 includes support for collaborative playlists in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, allowing &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscribers to build playlists with others. When creating a new playlist or selecting an existing playlist, there's a person-shaped icon that can be tapped to turn on collaboration.<br/>
<br/>
Enabling collaboration provides a link that can be shared with others, and anyone with the link is able to contribute to the playlist and listen to the songs. The person who started the playlist can choose to approve those who want to join or open it up to everyone. Anyone with the link to a playlist can add music, though the owner can turn off collaboration at any time or remove people.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3 is expected to see a launch at some point in January 2024.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-public-beta-1/">Apple Seeds First Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3.2413743/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Notebooks Available for Up to &#36;250 Off at Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/m2-macbook-air-best-buy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-notebooks-available-for-up-to-250-off-at-best-buy.2413735/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:49:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/m2-macbook-air-best-buy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air has dropped to <a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a> today on Best Buy, down from &#36;1,099.00. You can also get the 15-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a> at Best Buy right now, which is another record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-present.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924430" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The MacBook Air is a cheaper, but still powerful, alternative to the MacBook Pro lineup. They're perfect for students or anyone who needs a reliable laptop for daily use, and powerful enough for anyone whose workflow isn't too demanding.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Best Buy offers free next-day shipping as well as in-store pick-up for most locations, and has all four colors of the 13-inch MacBook Air at &#36;899.00. This is an all-time low price on the 13.6-inch 256GB M2 MacBook Air, and Best Buy has been one of the few retailers to offer this sale over the past few months. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQPZTZF5dZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has the 512GB model of the 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air on sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;,1399.00. Compared to past sales, this is a second-best price and still a solid discount on the 2022 notebook.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckQP5k7JDAC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13.6-Inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><h2>15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Best Buy has the 256GB 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00, which is a record low price at &#36;250 off. Similar to the 13-inch MacBook Air deals, you don't need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to see these discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxkzgComN"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There's also the 512GB 15.3-inch M2 MacBook Air at <a href="https://howl.me/ckYxm6NM1wV"><strong>&#36;1,249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00, which is another steep &#36;250 markdown on the 2023 MacBook Air. You'll find every color on sale for both of these computers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ckYxm6NM1wV"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15.3-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/m2-macbook-air-best-buy/">Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Notebooks Available for Up to &#36;250 Off at Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-notebooks-available-for-up-to-250-off-at-best-buy.2413735/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2: How to Translate Speech With iPhone&#039;s Action Button</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/translate-iphone-action-button/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-how-to-translate-speech-with-iphones-action-button.2413732/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 08:25:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/translate-iphone-action-button&#038;post_date=1702581908/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Translate</category>
		<category>Action Button</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Overcome communication barriers with the new custom Translation option for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s Action button in iOS 17.2. Keep reading to learn how to use it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-translate.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918874" /><br/>
If you have an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with an Action button, such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, Apple's iOS 17.2 software update brings a new translation option for the button that allows you to translate live conversations into multiple languages. <br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, the translation is not just accurate but also context-aware, ensuring that nuances and colloquialisms are captured effectively. The feature should be a boon for travelers, students, and anyone learning a language. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-pro-assign-two-shortcuts-action-button/">How to Assign Two Functions to the Action Button</a></li></ul><br/>
Before you use the Translate function, it's important to choose which language you want to translate. You can do this via Apple's built-in Translate app. On the app's main screen, use the chevrons next to the languages to make your selection. <br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/translate-choose-language.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925914" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Assign Translate to Action Button</h2><br/>
Once you have chosen your languages, you are ready to select the Translate option for the Action button.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
<li>Tap Action Button.</li><br/>
<li>Swipe to the Translate option to enable it.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/action-button-translate-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925915" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Using the Translate Function</h2><br/>
To Translate your speech to your chosen language, simply press and hold the Action button on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and begin speaking. Keep holding down the button for as long as you want to capture speech.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Action-Button-Translate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911022" /><br/>
Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will transcribe what you said and display it in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, and it will also provide a translation in the chosen language just beneath the transcription. Your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will automatically read aloud the translation, and you can replay it by pressing the play button to the right of it.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-translate/">Apple Translate</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/action-button/">Action Button</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/translate-iphone-action-button/">iOS 17.2: How to Translate Speech With iPhone&#039;s Action Button</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-how-to-translate-speech-with-iphones-action-button.2413732/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 and SE at Record Low Prices With Christmas Delivery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/best-buy-apple-watch-series-9/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-and-se-at-record-low-prices-with-christmas-delivery.2413716/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:52:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/best-buy-apple-watch-series-9/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy has introduced a <a href="https://howl.me/clcWSnq21fv">new sale on Apple Watch models</a> this week, with <a href="https://howl.me/clcWEaGlavX">all-time low prices available on Apple Watch Series 9</a>, as well as solid discounts on the Apple Watch SE.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-series-9-candy-canes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921455" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
All of these Apple Watches can be delivered before December 25 if ordered soon, thanks to Best Buy's free shipping options. You can also opt for in-store pick-up if a location near you has stock available for the Apple Watch you're looking to purchase.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9</h2><br/>
Starting with the 41mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9, this model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clcWEaGlavX"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;399.00. This is a match of the previous all-time low price, and it's available in all five colors on Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, Best Buy has all-time low prices on the 45mm GPS model and both cellular models of the Apple Watch Series 9, all at &#36;70 off. These sales are available to all shoppers and do not require the My Best Buy Plus or Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWEaGlavX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWFBWNXLo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWGhFXA7h"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;429.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWGVJwSdR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;459.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
Best Buy is taking &#36;50 off nearly every model of the Apple Watch SE, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clcWI64Prvm"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> for the 40mm GPS device. You'll also find both cellular models on sale in multiple colors, and all of these discounts represent record low prices for the Apple Watch SE.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWI64Prvm"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWJWBpIl5"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;229.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWLv9Ezdq"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm Cellular) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clcWLY3qWMH"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm Cellular) for &#36;279.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2</h2><br/>
Amazon is the place to buy Apple Watch Ultra 2 right now, with an all-time low price on the Indigo Alpine Loop model, priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYVS23%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.00</strong></a> with an on-page coupon. This device will not arrive before Christmas, unfortunately, but it's the best price we've ever seen on the Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
If you need an Ultra 2 in time for the 25th, you'll find solid second-best prices on many other models on Amazon, priced at &#36;729.99 with on-page coupons available. Most of these can still be delivered before the Christmas holiday if ordered soon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYVS23%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;699.00 (Delivery After Christmas)</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX59RZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;729.99 (Delivery Before Christmas)</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/best-buy-apple-watch-series-9/">Best Buy Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 and SE at Record Low Prices With Christmas Delivery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-and-se-at-record-low-prices-with-christmas-delivery.2413716/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Chipmaker Discusses Highly Advanced 1.4nm Chips for First Time</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/tsmc-mentions-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-chipmaker-discusses-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips-for-first-time.2413709/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:19:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/tsmc-mentions-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[TSMC has officially mentioned its work on 1.4nm fabrication technology that is likely destined to underpin future Apple silicon chips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-silicon-1-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1422" height="800" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-924673" /><br/>
In a slide (via <em>SemiAnalysis</em>'s <a href="https://x.com/dylan522p/status/1734766944774193291?s=20">Dylan Patel</a>) from its Future of Logic panel, TSMC disclosed the official name of its 1.4nm node for the first time, "A14." The company's 1.4nm technology is expected to follow its "N2" 2nm chips.<br/>
<br/>
N2 is scheduled for mass production in late 2025, to be followed by an enhanced "N2P" node in late 2026. As a result, it is unlikely that any A14 chips will arrive before 2027.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was the first company to utilize TSMC's 3nm technology with the A17 Pro chip in the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max, and the company is likely to follow suit with the chipmaker's upcoming nodes. Apple's latest chip technology has historically appeared in the iPhone before making its way to the iPad and Mac lineups. With all of the latest information, here's how the iPhone's chip technology could look going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>iPhone XR and XS (2018): A12 Bionic (7nm, N7)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 lineup (2019): A13 Bionic (7nm, N7P)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 lineup (2020): A14 Bionic (5nm, N5)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro (2021): A15 Bionic (5nm, N5P)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro (2022): A16 Bionic (4nm, N4P)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro (2023): A17 Pro (3nm, N3B)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Pro (2024): "A18" (3nm, N3E)</li></li><br/>
<li>"iPhone 17 Pro" (2025): "A19" (2nm, N2)</li><br/>
<li>"iPhone 18 Pro" (2026): "A20" (2nm, N2P)</li><br/>
<li>"iPhone 19 Pro" (2027): "A21" (1.4nm, A14)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The M1 series of Apple silicon chips is based on the A14 Bionic and uses TSMC's N5 node, while the M2 and M3 series use N5P and N3B, respectively. The Apple Watch's S4 and S5 chips use N7, the S6, S7, and S8 chips use N7P, and the latest S9 chip uses N4P.<br/>
<br/>
Each successive TSMC node surpasses its predecessor in terms of transistor density, performance, and efficiency. Earlier this week, it emerged that TSMC had already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/tsmc-demos-next-gen-chip-technology/">demonstrated prototype 2nm chips to Apple</a> ahead of their expected introduction in 2025.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/tsmc-mentions-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips/">Apple Chipmaker Discusses Highly Advanced 1.4nm Chips for First Time</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-chipmaker-discusses-highly-advanced-1-4nm-chips-for-first-time.2413709/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2: How to Disable iPhone Inline Predictive Text</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/disable-iphone-inline-predictive-text/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-how-to-disable-iphone-inline-predictive-text.2413705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:53:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/disable-iphone-inline-predictive-text&#038;post_date=1702572834/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in iOS 17 added inline predictive text for iPhones, but did not include a way to turn it off independently of predictive suggestions above the keyboard. In the latest iOS 17.2 update, that's changed. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/inline-predictive-text.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926577" /><br/>
Apple has improved its machine learning technology on iPhones in an effort to make iOS a lot more helpful, and one of the features in which this tech has been deployed is inline predictive text. <br/>
<br/>
Predictive text does just what it says - it predicts what you're going to type next, and offers to autocomplete it. As you type, the predicted text appears ahead of the cursor. If it has accurately predicted what you intend to type, all you need to do is tap the spacebar and iOS fills it in for you.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/how-to-disable-macos-inline-predictive-text/">How to Disable Inline Predictive Text on Mac</a></li></ul><br/>
In previous versions of iOS 17, you could only disable inline predictive text by turning off predictive text wholesale – which meant you would also lose the predicted words that appear above the keyboard as you type. Fortunately, in iOS 17.2 you can now toggle off inline predictive text separately without disabling the predictive suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Turning Off Inline Predictive Text</h2><br/>
<ol><li>Open Settings on your iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
<li>Under "All Keyboards," toggle off the switch next to Show Predictions Inline.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/disable-inline-predictive-text.jpg" alt="settings" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926320" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. The new option is likely to be welcomed by those who prefer a more manual typing experience or find inline predictive text suggestions distracting. Of course, if you find yourself missing the help that inline predictive text can provide, simply use the above steps to re-instate the feature.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/disable-iphone-inline-predictive-text/">iOS 17.2: How to Disable iPhone Inline Predictive Text</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-how-to-disable-iphone-inline-predictive-text.2413705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Threads Launches in the European Union</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/threads-launches-in-the-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-launches-in-the-european-union.2413701/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 05:17:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/threads-launches-in-the-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Threads is now available to users in the European Union, Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg has announced. The move comes five months after the social media network launched in most markets around the world, but remained unavailable to EU-based users due to <a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/technology/no-instagram-threads-app-in-the-eu-irish-dpc-says-metas-new-twitter-rival-wont-be-launched-here/a1927220337.html">regulatory hurdles</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
"Today we're opening Threads to more countries in Europe," wrote Zuckerberg in a <a href="https://www.threads.net/@zuck/post/C01LXhDrCAM">post on the platform</a>. "Welcome everyone." In addition to creating a Threads profile for posting, users in the EU can also simply browse Threads without having an Instagram account, an option likely introduced to comply with legislation surrounding online services.<br/>
<br/>
The company's delay in launching the service in EU countries is believed to have been caused by the EU's Digital Markets Act, or DMA, which is intended to make the tech sector more open and balance competition. <br/>
<br/>
When Meta launched Threads in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/05/instagram-threads-app-now-available/">July</a>, users signed up through their Instagram account, which allowed Threads to gain millions of users. The integration between the two platforms wasn't universally welcomed though, and led to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/06/deleting-threads-profile-also-deletes-instagram/">complaints</a> that it was impossible to delete your Threads profile without also deleting your Instagram account. <br/>
<br/>
Then in November, Meta loosened the integration by rolling out a way to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/">delete or deactivate a Threads profile separately</a> while leaving the associated Instagram account intact.<br/>
<br/>
The expansion into a market of 448 million people should see Threads' user numbers get a decent boost. Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg said on a company earnings call in <a href="https://s21.q4cdn.com/399680738/files/doc_earnings/2023/q3/transcript/META-Q3-2023-Earnings-Call-Transcript.pdf">October</a> that Threads now has "just under" 100 million monthly users. Since its launch earlier this year it has gained a web app, an ability to search for posts, and a post editing feature.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/14/threads-launches-in-the-eu/">Threads Launches in the European Union</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/threads-launches-in-the-european-union.2413701/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Five Features in macOS Sonoma 14.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/macos-sonoma-14-2-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-five-features-in-macos-sonoma-14-2.2413647/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 15:21:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/macos-sonoma-14-2-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Apple releases new software, iOS updates tend to get most of the attention, and there are sometimes useful new features in Mac updates that go under the radar. That's the case with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2. It doesn't have flashy features like the Journal app that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-releases-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2/">came in iOS 17.2</a>, but there are a number of useful improvements that make it worth installing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_4cCFzlDjDM" title="macOS Sonoma 14.2 Out Now: Here&#39;s What&#39;s NEW!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
We've rounded up five of the best features that are included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Messages</strong> - The Messages app includes a catch-up arrow that lets you jump to the first unread message in a conversation, plus there is an option to add a sticker to a message from the tapback interface. That makes it quicker to add non-emoji reactions during chats on the Mac.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>PDF AutoFill</strong> - AutoFill recognizes key fields in PDFs and other documents so you can fill them out quick. It will recognize addresses, phone numbers, and similar data that can be filled from the Contacts app.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Weather Widgets</strong> - There are several new Weather widgets that can be added to the Mac's desktop. Options include next-hour precipitation, daily forecast, sunrise and sunset, Air Quality, Feels Like, and wind speed.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Multiple Timer Support</strong> - The Clock app on the Mac supports multiple timers that are able to run simultaneously. There are also timer presets for quickly setting a timer.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Shazam Improvements</strong> - With a Shazam Music Recognition update, you can Shazam songs on Mac even when you're wearing your AirPods.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
For more on what's new in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2, make sure to watch our full video up above.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/macos-sonoma-14-2-features/">Top Five Features in macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-five-features-in-macos-sonoma-14-2.2413647/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Collecting Data to Improve Augmented Reality Location Accuracy in Maps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/apple-maps-ar-data-collection/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-collecting-data-to-improve-augmented-reality-location-accuracy-in-maps.2413645/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 14:58:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/apple-maps-ar-data-collection/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Maps</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of iOS 17.2, Apple has outlined the Maps-related data that it is collecting in order to improve the augmented reality location function. In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213957">new support document</a>, Apple says that it is aiming to bolster the speed and accuracy of augmented reality features in the Maps app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/apple-maps-3d-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="896" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841030" /><br/>
When using augmented reality features in Maps, including immersive walking directions or the refine location option, Apple collects information on "feature points" that represent the shape and appearance of stationary objects like buildings. The data does not include photos or images, and the feature points collected are not readable by a person.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, Maps uses on-device machine learning to compare feature points to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> reference data that is sent to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. The camera filters out moving objects like people and vehicles, with Apple collecting just the feature points of stationary objects.<br/>
<br/>
The comparison between the feature points and the &zwnj;Apple Maps&zwnj; reference data allows Maps to pinpoint a user location and provide detailed walking directions with AR context. Using either the AR Walking directions or Refine Location refreshes Apple's reference data to improve augmented reality accuracy.<br/>
<br/>
Data that Apple collects is encrypted and not associated with an individual user or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>. Apple also uses on-device machine learning to add "noise" to the feature points data to add irregular variations that prevent any "unlikely" attempt to use feature points to reconstruct an image from the data.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, only an "extremely sophisticated attacker" that has access to the company's encoding system would be able to recreate an image from feature points, but because the data is encrypted and limited only to Apple, "an attack and recreation are extremely unlikely."<br/>
<br/>
The use of AR data can be disabled to prevent Apple from collecting it. The "Improve AR Location Accuracy" toggle can be accessed in the Settings app by going to Privacy and Security and then tapping on Analytics and Improvements.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/apple-maps-ar-data-collection/">Apple Collecting Data to Improve Augmented Reality Location Accuracy in Maps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-collecting-data-to-improve-augmented-reality-location-accuracy-in-maps.2413645/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.3&#039;s Collaborative Apple Music Playlist Feature Includes Animated Emoji Reactions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3s-collaborative-apple-music-playlist-feature-includes-animated-emoji-reactions.2413639/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 13:54:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 17.3 update, Apple reintroduced the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-beta-apple-music-collaborative-playlists/">collaborative Apple Music playlist</a> feature, allowing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> users to build playlists with friends, family, and others who share their musical tastes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/apple-music-collaborative-playlist-emoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926541" /><br/>
For context, Apple initially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/ios-17-2-beta-4-features/">tested collaborative playlists in iOS 17.2</a>, but ended up pulling the feature from the fourth beta prior to when iOS 17.2 was released. Apple said on Monday that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">would instead be launching in 2024</a>, and on Tuesday, collaborative playlists showed up in the iOS 17.3 beta.<br/>
<br/>
The new implementation allows all of the collaborators on a specific playlist to provide emoji reactions, similar to how tapback reactions work in Messages. To add an emoji reaction, play a collaborative playlist and then while a song is in progress, you can tap on the music player to see the emoji interface.<br/>
<br/>
There are standard emoji reactions to choose from like heart and thumbs up, but tapping on the "+" button allows you to choose from any of the available emoji options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">iOS 17.3 Beta 1 adds Emojis reactions to Collaborative Playlists &#x203c;&#xfe0f;<br><br>Emoji Animations are insane &#x1f92a; <a href="https://t.co/RIQWYByfRE">pic.twitter.com/RIQWYByfRE</a></p>&mdash; Kevin Aubin (@kaubin) <a href="https://twitter.com/kaubin/status/1735005903630311449?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 13, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
When you play a song that others have added emoji reactions to, you can see those emoji pop up from the emoji interface. Those who want to see collaborative &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlists and emoji reactions in action <a href="https://music.apple.com/us/playlist/pl.u-kaJH7JG97e?a=join&amp;it=zr6IZVEGZ6tVoblq">can join the MacRumors Apple Music playlist</a> to add songs and listen to content from other MacRumors readers.<br/>
<br/>
Collaborative playlists in &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; are expected to be available to the public in January following the launch of iOS 17.3.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-17-3-collaborative-playlist-emoji/">iOS 17.3&#039;s Collaborative Apple Music Playlist Feature Includes Animated Emoji Reactions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-3s-collaborative-apple-music-playlist-feature-includes-animated-emoji-reactions.2413639/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Seven iOS Features Remain Available in the U.S. Only</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-features-in-us-only/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-seven-ios-features-remain-available-in-the-u-s-only.2413635/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 12:52:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-features-in-us-only/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While many iOS features are available internationally, some remain exclusive to the U.S., such as the Apple Card, Apple Card Savings, Apple Cash, Apple Pay Later, Wallet IDs, Roadside Assistance via Satellite, and Clean Energy Charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Logo-16x9-US-Flag-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926535" /><br/>
Below, we have provided more details about some iOS features available in the U.S. only.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Card</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/apple-card-1-iPhone-13.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-818915" /><br/>
Launched in 2019, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> remains available in the U.S. only. Apple's credit card can be managed completely through the Wallet app on the iPhone, with a physical version available for use at stores that do not accept contactless payments. The card has no fees beyond interest and offers up to 3% cashback known as Daily Cash.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Card's financial partner in the U.S. is currently Goldman Sachs, but that reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">might change in the next 12 to 15 months</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While there have been clues that the Apple Card might expand to additional countries in the future, such as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/03/canada-approves-apple-card-apple-cash-trademarks/">Apple Card trademark filing in Canada</a>, Apple has not confirmed any immediate plans to launch the card internationally.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Card Savings</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-card-savings-account-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892213" /><br/>
Earlier this year, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/apple-card-savings-account-launching-today/">Apple Card savings account</a> launched in the Wallet app on the iPhone, allowing Apple Card holders in the U.S. to earn interest on their Daily Cash and other cash deposits. The high-yield savings account has a 4.15% APY, with no fees, no minimum deposits, and no minimum balance requirements.<br/>
<br/>
Given the Apple Card is available in the U.S. only, so too is the savings account.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Cash</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-Cash-banner.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-879664" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/#apple_cash">Apple Cash</a> is a Venmo-like payment feature that allows iPhone users in the U.S. to send, request, and receive money in the Wallet and Messages apps. Users can transfer their Apple Cash balance to a connected bank account.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Cash remains available in the U.S. only, and despite clues like a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/03/canada-approves-apple-card-apple-cash-trademarks/">trademark filing in Canada</a>, it is unclear if the feature will expand to other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pay Later</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pay-Later-feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918417" /><br/>
Launched earlier this year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-pay-later-launches/">Apple Pay Later</a> is a "buy now, pay later" feature that lets qualifying U.S. residents split a purchase made with Apple Pay into four equal payments over six weeks, with no interest or fees. The feature is available for purchases between &#36;75 and &#36;1,000 made on an iPhone or iPad on most websites and apps that accept Apple Pay.<br/>
<br/>
Like the other financial features on this list, it is unclear if or when Apple Pay Later will expand to other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Wallet IDs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/apple-wallet-drivers-license-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1698" height="956" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-813979" /><br/>
In 2022, Apple started letting residents of participating U.S. states add their driver's license or state ID to the Wallet app on the iPhone and Apple Watch, providing a convenient and contactless way to display proof of identity or age. The feature is currently available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/23/apple-launches-ids-in-wallet-arizona/">Arizona</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/colorado-ids-wallet-app-support/">Colorado</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/25/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-maryland/">Maryland</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/18/iphone-drivers-license-georgia/">Georgia</a> only, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/iphone-ids-coming-to-these-8-us-states/">additional states to follow</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said it was working to offer the ID feature across the U.S. in the future, but the company has yet to announce any specific plans or a timeframe, and it has not indicated if the feature will ever launch in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Roadside Assistance via Satellite</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-roadside-assistance.jpg" alt="" width="1596" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910510" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 17, all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models offer a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-roadside-assistance-feature-tested/">roadside assistance via satellite feature</a> that allows users in the U.S. to contact roadside assistance company AAA for vehicle service when outside of cellular and Wi-Fi coverage.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the feature is available "beginning" in the U.S., so it will likely expand to some additional countries in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Clean Energy Charging</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/clean-energy-charging-ios-16-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864277" /><br/>
iOS 16.1 introduced a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/24/ios-16-1-clean-energy-charging-details/">Clean Energy Charging feature</a> that "aims to decrease the carbon footprint of the iPhone by optimizing charging times for when the grid is using cleaner energy sources," according to Apple. When the feature is toggled on, the iPhone will attempt to charge "when lower carbon-emission electricity is available."<br/>
<br/>
Clean Energy Charging is available in the U.S. only, and Apple has not indicated if or when it will be expanded to additional countries.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/ios-features-in-us-only/">These Seven iOS Features Remain Available in the U.S. Only</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-seven-ios-features-remain-available-in-the-u-s-only.2413635/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
