<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 02:03:49 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Graykey&#039; Tool Used by Law Enforcement Can Only Partially Unlock iOS 18 Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/graykey-ios-18-partial-unlock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/graykey-tool-used-by-law-enforcement-can-only-partially-unlock-ios-18-devices.2443494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:08:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/graykey-ios-18-partial-unlock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Graykey, a forensics tool used by law enforcement officials to break into locked iPhones, has limited access to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and iOS 18.0.1, <a href="https://www.404media.co/leaked-documents-show-what-phones-secretive-tech-graykey-can-unlock-2/"><em>404 Media</em> recently learned</a>. The site secured documents that describe Graykey's functionality in-depth, giving us a look at what the device is capable of.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/iphone-16-pro-pro-max.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964613" /><br/>
Graykey parent company Magnet Forensics does not share information about the tool, and complete details about the devices that Graykey can unlock have not surfaced before.<br/>
<br/>
Most iPhones that run &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; or iOS 18.0.1 are listed as eligible for a "partial" unlock, though the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 11 models can seemingly be unlocked in full. Data on iOS 18.1, a newer version of iOS, isn't included in the document, but iOS 18.1 betas were listed as inaccessible.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear what "partial" access means or what data can be garnered from iPhones with that access listing, but it might mean that law enforcement are limited to unencrypted files, file size information, and folder structure. On more vulnerable devices, Graykey can unlock an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with a 4-digit passcode in mere minutes, while longer passcodes can take hours.<br/>
<br/>
Graykey takes advantage of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; vulnerabilities to unlock devices, and its capabilities can change as Apple patches security flaws. In 2018, for example, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/10/24/graykey-iphone-unlocking-box-disabled-by-ios-12/">disabled Graykey</a> with an update to iOS 12, but new vulnerabilities were found that restored functionality. Eventually, Magnet Forensics may be able to find a flaw that will allow Graykey to get into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; devices as well.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, a leak from Israel-based mobile forensics company Cellebrite suggested that its tools are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/18/cellebrite-unable-to-unlock-iphones-on-ios-17-4/">unable to unlock iPhones</a> that are running iOS 17.4 or later, but it is now able to access devices running iOS 17.5.1.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/graykey-ios-18-partial-unlock/">&#039;Graykey&#039; Tool Used by Law Enforcement Can Only Partially Unlock iOS 18 Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/graykey-tool-used-by-law-enforcement-can-only-partially-unlock-ios-18-devices.2443494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Tests Recommendations Reset for Fresh Start</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/instagram-tests-recommendations-reset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-tests-recommendations-reset-for-fresh-start.2443489/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:12:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/instagram-tests-recommendations-reset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram parent company Meta <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2024/11/introducing-recommendations-reset-instagram">today said</a> that it is testing a new tool that's designed to allow users to reset their content recommendations for "a fresh start." Using the reset tool removes prior data that's used to power Explore, Reels, and Feed recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/instagram-reset-recommendations.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978350" /><br/>
Recommendations will start to personalize over time, providing content recommendations based on the content and accounts that users interact with. Using the reset option will provide users with an option to review the accounts they're following to unfollow content they no longer want to see, and review ad topics.<br/>
<br/>
The tool is designed for teen users, but Instagram is planning to make it available to all users following the test period. The feature will roll out globally "soon."<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/instagram-tests-recommendations-reset/">Instagram Tests Recommendations Reset for Fresh Start</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-tests-recommendations-reset-for-fresh-start.2443489/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Rebrands Switcher App to Lure iPhone Users to Android</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-rebrands-android-switcher-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-rebrands-switcher-app-to-lure-iphone-users-to-android.2443484/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 13:49:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-rebrands-android-switcher-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today revamped its Switch to Android app for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, introducing a streamlined interface, a new icon, and changing the name <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/android-switch/id6449987166">to Android Switch</a> as part of a rebranding effort to lure new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/google-android-switch-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978341" /><br/>
The app is designed to make it easy for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users to swap over to an Android-based device like a Google Pixel. It can transfer contacts, calendar events, photos, and videos, and it includes reminders to turn off iMessage to swap to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>/SMS.<br/>
<br/>
Google has also changed some of the wording on its Switch to Android website to reflect the new app name. The Switch to Android site walks through some of the common concerns that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users might have about switching platforms, such as texting, sharing files, making video calls, and transitioning accessories.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;RCS&zwnj;, Google says Android users can text &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users with no issues, and the company recommends Google Meet as an alternative to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>. There's no Android to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; replacement for AirDrop, but Google says that Quick Share can be used to share files with Android, ChromeOS, and Windows PC devices.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from design updates and a new look for the app, the basic functionality of the Android Switch app appears to be the same as before.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-rebrands-android-switcher-app/">Google Rebrands Switcher App to Lure iPhone Users to Android</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-rebrands-switcher-app-to-lure-iphone-users-to-android.2443484/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ends Butterfly Keyboard Repair Program for MacBooks</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ends-mac-butterfly-keyboard-service-program/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ends-butterfly-keyboard-repair-program-for-macbooks.2443482/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:50:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ends-mac-butterfly-keyboard-service-program/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Butterfly Keyboard Issues</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's free butterfly keyboard service program for select MacBooks models <a href="https://support.apple.com/keyboard-service-program-for-mac-notebooks">ended</a> late last week, nearly six and a half years after it launched.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/MacBook-Keyboard-Close.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941611" /><br/>
With the program now over, it is no longer guaranteed that customers with affected MacBook keyboards will be able to receive a free repair from Apple or an Apple Authorized Service Provider. However, exceptions could be made.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we take a look back at Apple's butterfly keyboard problems that led to the program.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Butterfly Keyboard</h2><br/>
For much of the 2000s, MacBook keyboards had a traditional scissor switch mechanism. That changed in March 2015, when Apple released an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/03/09/apple-new-macbook-2015/">ultra-thin 12-inch MacBook</a> with a low-profile keyboard that used a new butterfly switch mechanism. While the keyboard fit in the 12-inch MacBook's thin enclosure, it is prone to issues, such as letters repeating unexpectedly or failing to appear when keys are pressed.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Related:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/butterfly-keyboard-vs-scissor-keyboard/">Apple's Butterfly Keyboards vs. Scissor Switch Keyboards</a></li></ul><br/>
It was not until Apple updated the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Pro models with its second-generation butterfly keyboard in October 2016 that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/02/21/2016-macbook-pro-keyboard-issues/">customers began to complain</a> about sticky and unresponsive keys in earnest. Apple expanded the butterfly keyboard to the MacBook Air a few years later, leading to even more complaints.<br/>
<br/>
The situation came to a head in May 2018, when Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/05/14/macbook-pro-keyboard-class-action-lawsuit/">hit with a class action lawsuit</a> in the U.S. alleging that the company knew the butterfly keyboard was defective. An online <a href="https://www.change.org/p/apple-apple-recall-macbook-pro-w-defective-keyboard-replace-with-different-working-keyboard">petition about the issues</a> that year gained nearly 43,000 signatures.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Program</h2><br/>
In June 2018, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/06/22/apple-macbook-pro-keyboard-repair-program/">launched a "Keyboard Service Program"</a> worldwide after it determined that a "small percentage" of keyboards in certain MacBook, MacBook Air, and MacBook Pro models may exhibit one or more of the following behaviors:<ul><li>Letters or characters repeat unexpectedly</li><br/>
<li>Letters or characters do not appear</li><br/>
<li>Key(s) feel "sticky" or do not respond in a consistent manner</li></ul>Apple and Apple Authorized Service Providers had been repairing eligible MacBook keyboards, free of charge, for up to four years after the first retail sale of the affected laptop. That window is now closed, as all eligible models were discontinued more than four years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/ifixit-butterfly-keyboard-mac.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-823726" /><em>The butterfly switch mechanism for a 2018 MacBook Pro keyboard (iFixit)</em></div><br/>
The list of all models that were eligible:<ul><li>MacBook (Retina, 12-­inch, Early 2015)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook (Retina, 12­-inch, Early 2016)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook (Retina, 12-­inch, 2017)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Air (Retina, 13-inch, 2018)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Air (Retina, 13-inch, 2019)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13­-inch, 2016, Two Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-­inch, 2017, Two Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2019, Two Thunderbolt 3 ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-­inch, 2016, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-­inch, 2017, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (15-­inch, 2016)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (15-­inch, 2017)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2018, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (15-­inch, 2018)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2019, Four Thunderbolt 3 Ports)</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro (15-­inch, 2019)</li></ul><h2>The Apology</h2><br/>
In March 2019, Apple finally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/03/27/apple-apologizes-about-third-gen-keyboard-issues/">apologized about the keyboards</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"We are aware that a small number of users are having issues with their third-generation butterfly keyboard and for that we are sorry," an Apple spokesperson said, in a statement shared with <em>The Wall Street Journal</em>'s Joanna Stern. "The vast majority of Mac notebook customers are having a positive experience with the new keyboard."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Fix</h2><br/>
Starting with the 16-inch MacBook Pro in November 2019, Apple ditched the butterfly keyboard and returned to using a scissor switch mechanism. The change was extended to the MacBook Air in March 2020, and to the 13-inch MacBook Pro in May 2020, marking the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/05/04/rip-butterfly-keyboard/">end of the problematic butterfly keyboard era</a> for the Mac. All models of MacBooks with Apple silicon chips have continued to use scissor switch keyboards.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Settlement</h2><br/>
In July 2022, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/29/apple-butterfly-keyboard-settlement-approval/">agreed to pay &#36;50 million</a> to settle the U.S. class action lawsuit related to the butterfly keyboard issues. Affected customers who submitted a valid claim by the March 2023 deadline <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/macbook-faulty-keyboard-payouts/">received a payment</a> of between &#36;50 and &#36;395.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/butterfly-keyboard-issues/">Butterfly Keyboard Issues</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ends-mac-butterfly-keyboard-service-program/">Apple Ends Butterfly Keyboard Repair Program for MacBooks</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ends-butterfly-keyboard-repair-program-for-macbooks.2443482/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone SE 4 With Apple&#039;s Own 5G Modem &#039;Confirmed&#039; to Launch in March</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/iphone-se-4-expected-to-launch-in-march/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-with-apples-own-5g-modem-confirmed-to-launch-in-march.2443478/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:12:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/iphone-se-4-expected-to-launch-in-march/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone SE</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		<category>Barclays</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Barclays analyst Tom O'Malley and his colleagues recently traveled to Asia to meet with various electronics manufacturers and suppliers. In a research note this week, outlining key takeaways from the trip, the analysts said they have "confirmed" that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">fourth-generation iPhone SE</a> with an Apple-designed 5G modem is slated to launch towards the end of the first quarter next year. In line with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">previous rumors</a>, that timeframe suggests the new iPhone SE will be announced in March, just like the current model was in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
The fourth-generation iPhone SE is expected to have a similar design as the base iPhone 14, with rumored features including a 6.1-inch OLED display, Face ID, a newer A-series chip, a USB-C port, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, 8GB of RAM to enable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">Apple Intelligence support</a>, and the previously-mentioned Apple-designed 5G modem.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to have been working on its own 5G modem for iPhones since 2018, a move that will allow it to reduce and eventually eliminate its dependance on Qualcomm. Earlier this year, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/31/apple-extends-qualcomm-modem-licensing-deal/">extended its 5G modem supply agreement with Qualcomm</a> for iPhone launches through 2026, so Apple still has plenty of time to complete the transition to its in-house modem. Along with the fourth-generation iPhone SE, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo previously said the so-called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/">"iPhone 17 Air" will have an Apple-designed 5G modem</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if Apple's first 5G modem would unlock any consumer benefits compared to Qualcomm's modems, such as faster speeds.<br/>
<br/>
In 2017, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/01/20/apple-qualcomm-1-billion-lawsuit/">Apple sued Qualcomm</a> over anticompetitive practices and &#36;1 billion in unpaid royalty rebates. The two companies settled the lawsuit in 2019, and Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">acquired the majority of Intel's smartphone modem business</a> that same year. That purchase provided Apple with a portfolio of cellular-related patents to bolster its development. In another four months from now, it seems like we will finally see the fruit of this labor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the third-generation iPhone SE during an online event <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/08/apple-announces-new-iphone-se/">on March 8, 2022</a>. The device looks similar to the iPhone 8, with outdated features such as a Touch ID button, Lightning port, and thick bezels around the display. In the U.S., the iPhone SE currently starts at &#36;429, but the new model might see at least a slight price increase.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/barclays/">Barclays</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone_SE">iPhone SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/iphone-se-4-expected-to-launch-in-march/">iPhone SE 4 With Apple&#039;s Own 5G Modem &#039;Confirmed&#039; to Launch in March</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-se-4-with-apples-own-5g-modem-confirmed-to-launch-in-march.2443478/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Make Sure to Update: iOS 18.1.1 and macOS Sequoia 15.1.1 Fix Actively Exploited Vulnerabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/ios-18-1-1-active-exploit-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-18-1-1-and-macos-sequoia-15-1-1-fix-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities.2443465/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:52:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/ios-18-1-1-active-exploit-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iOS 18.1.1, iPadOS 18.1.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1.1 updates that Apple released today address <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/121752">JavaScriptCore and WebKit vulnerabilities</a> that Apple says have been actively exploited on some devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/bug-security-vulnerability-issue-fix-larry.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896108" /><br/>
With the JavaScriptCore vulnerability, processing maliciously crafted web content could lead to arbitrary code execution. The WebKit vulnerability had the same issue with maliciously crafted web content, and it could lead to a cross site scripting attack.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that it is aware of reports that these two issues may have been actively exploited on Intel-based Mac systems. While the vulnerabilities are only known to have impacted older Macs, other devices are vulnerable to attack because they have the same security flaws. <br/>
<br/>
For that reason, it is a good idea to update your devices to the latest software as soon as possible. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/ios-18-1-1-active-exploit-fix/">Make Sure to Update: iOS 18.1.1 and macOS Sequoia 15.1.1 Fix Actively Exploited Vulnerabilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/make-sure-to-update-ios-18-1-1-and-macos-sequoia-15-1-1-fix-actively-exploited-vulnerabilities.2443465/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Developer App Gains Custom Dark and Tinted Icons</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-developer-app-dark-icons/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developer-app-gains-custom-dark-and-tinted-icons.2443467/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:51:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-developer-app-dark-icons/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated the Apple Developer app that is available to the developer community, introducing a few new features that improve the app usage and navigation experience. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-developer-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="572" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757303" /><br/>
For viewing videos in a topic or event, users can now choose between grid or list views for easier sorting. There are now custom dark and tinted appearances for the Apple Developer app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and the detail view for videos provides an indicator when a video has been fully watched, so it's simpler to keep track of previously-viewed content. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says the app also includes bug fixes and "various other enhancements" that are minor enough not to make it into the app update release notes. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-developer-app-dark-icons/">Apple Developer App Gains Custom Dark and Tinted Icons</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-developer-app-gains-custom-dark-and-tinted-icons.2443467/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card 3% Daily Cash Back Now Available From Two More Apple Partners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-card-daily-cash-back-more-partners/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-3-daily-cash-back-now-available-from-two-more-apple-partners.2443462/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:36:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-card-daily-cash-back-more-partners/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has partnered with select merchants to offer <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> users three percent Daily Cash back on their purchases, and two new companies were added to the partner list today. When purchasing goods and services from Booking.com and ChargePoint, &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; users will now get more cash back.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/apple-card-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="1144" height="644" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-735877" /><br/>
Booking.com is a site for reserving flights, cars, cruises, and hotels, while ChargePoint sells charging equipment for electric vehicles and also offers more than 280,000 charging stations across multiple countries.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; users can get three percent Daily Cash back from Booking.com on eligible prepaid stays and car rentals when purchasing using &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, though Apple says that its <a href="https://www.booking.com/c/apple-card/index.html?aid=2417311">special Apple Card link</a> needs to be used when booking. Eligible stays include those that are paid for using the "Pay Now" rate.<br/>
<br/>
As for ChargePoint, &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; users will get three percent Daily Cash when using &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; with &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; to pay for electric vehicle charging at ChargePoint charging stations, as well as home charging purchases through the ChargePoint website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has several other partners that provide extra Daily Cash as well, including Duane Reade, Mobil, T-Mobile, Uber Eats, Ace Hardware, Nike, Uber, and Walgreens.<br/>
<br/>
Panera Bread has also been one of Apple's partners to offer three percent Daily Cash, but starting on February 1, 2025, Panera Bread Daily Cash back will be limited to two percent.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-card-daily-cash-back-more-partners/">Apple Card 3% Daily Cash Back Now Available From Two More Apple Partners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-3-daily-cash-back-now-available-from-two-more-apple-partners.2443462/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Accessory Sales Include Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99 and Record Lows on iPad Pro Magic Keyboards</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/amazon-accessory-sales-apple-pencil/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-accessory-sales-include-apple-pencil-pro-for-99-and-record-lows-on-ipad-pro-magic-keyboards.2443461/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:28:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/amazon-accessory-sales-apple-pencil/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a few solid Apple accessory discounts in the lead-up to Black Friday this week, including deals on the Apple Pencil Pro and Magic Keyboard for M4 iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-pencil-pro-dark-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970551" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the Apple Pencil Pro, you can get this stylus for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. Amazon also has the USB-C Apple Pencil available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;69.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil (USB-C) for &#36;69.00</div></a></div><h2>Magic Keyboard</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/magic-keyboard.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978264" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the new 2024 Magic Keyboards, you can get the 11-inch model in Black for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. This is an all-time low price on the accessory and it's only available in Black.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>11-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard on sale, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5ZBFR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;274.99</strong></a> in White, down from &#36;349.00. This is another record low price on the Magic Keyboard, and you'll find similar delivery estimates of mid-to-late November for this model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5ZBFR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;74 OFF</div>13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;274.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/amazon-accessory-sales-apple-pencil/">Amazon Accessory Sales Include Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;99 and Record Lows on iPad Pro Magic Keyboards</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-accessory-sales-include-apple-pencil-pro-for-99-and-record-lows-on-ipad-pro-magic-keyboards.2443461/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sequoia 15.1.1 With Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-1-1-with-security-fixes.2443456/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:15:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1.1, a minor update for the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; operating system. The 15.1.1 update comes three weeks after Apple released the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/macOS-Sequoia-Night-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961501" /><br/>
Mac users can download the ‌&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;‌ update by using the Software Update section of System Settings.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1.1 includes security fixes.  <br/>
<br/>
Details on the features that are included in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">found in our roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-1-1/">Apple Releases macOS Sequoia 15.1.1 With Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-15-1-1-with-security-fixes.2443456/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases visionOS 2.1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-visionos-2-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-2-1-1.2443458/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:14:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-visionos-2-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released visionOS 2.1.1, a minor update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> operating system that came out in September. visionOS 2.1.1 comes three weeks after the <a href="hhttps://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/apple-releases-visionos-2-1/">launch of visionOS 2.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955609" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-on-Apple-Vision-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
‌visionOS 2.1.1‌ can be downloaded on all Vision Pro headsets by navigating to the Settings app, selecting the General section, and choosing the Software Update option. To install an update, the Vision Pro headset needs to be removed, and there is a software progress bar available on the front EyeSight display.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update focuses on security fixes rather than new features, and it is recommended for all Vision Pro users. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS 2&zwnj; introduces 2D spatial photos, updates to Persona, a new version of the Guest Mode, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">available in our visionOS 2 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-visionos-2-1-1/">Apple Releases visionOS 2.1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-visionos-2-1-1.2443458/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 18.1.1 and iPadOS 18.1.1 With Security Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-ios-18-1-1-and-ipados-18-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-1-1-and-ipados-18-1-1-with-security-fixes.2443454/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:10:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-ios-18-1-1-and-ipados-18-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 18.1.1 and iPadOS 18.1.1, minor updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> operating systems that debuted earlier in September. iOS 18.1.1 and iPadOS 18.1.1 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/28/apple-releases-ios-18-1/">come three weeks</a> after the launch of iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
The new software can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update. Apple has also released iOS 17.7.2 for devices that are still running iOS 17. <br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the iOS 18.1.1 update provides important security fixes. It is recommended for all users.<br/>
<br/>
For more on the features available in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-releases-ios-18-1-1-and-ipados-18-1-1/">Apple Releases iOS 18.1.1 and iPadOS 18.1.1 With Security Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-18-1-1-and-ipados-18-1-1-with-security-fixes.2443454/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sends iPhone 16 Pro to Space in New Ad Promoting A18 Pro Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ad-sends-iphone-16-pro-to-space/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sends-iphone-16-pro-to-space-in-new-ad-promoting-a18-pro-chip.2443451/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:08:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ad-sends-iphone-16-pro-to-space/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past week and a bit, Apple has shared a new <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yU3KE5f7ZcQ">iPhone 16 Pro ad</a> called "All Systems Pro" on its YouTube channels in select countries, such as Japan, India, South Korea, and Singapore. Apple has yet to share the ad on its U.S. channel.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yU3KE5f7ZcQ?si=towzz6oyOlU2b2LU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the ad, a mission control center goes through a series of final checks before launching an iPhone 16 Pro into space like a rocket. During a 30-second countdown, the team ensures that all aspects of the A18 Pro chip are ready to go, such as the Neural Engine, 6-core GPU, and support for recording slow-mo 4K video at 120 fps. <br/>
<br/>
"A18 Pro has a faster Neural Engine, improved CPU and GPU, and a big jump in memory bandwidth," the video description says. "It also drives advanced video and photo features like Camera Control, and delivers great graphics performance for next-level gaming."<br/>
<br/>
When it announced the iPhone 16 Pro models in September, Apple said the A18 Pro chip is up to 15% faster than the A17 Pro chip in the iPhone 15 Pro models. The chip is manufactured with TSMC's second-generation 3nm process.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ad-sends-iphone-16-pro-to-space/">Apple Sends iPhone 16 Pro to Space in New Ad Promoting A18 Pro Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sends-iphone-16-pro-to-space-in-new-ad-promoting-a18-pro-chip.2443451/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pro Display XDR 2 Expected to Feature Quantum-Dot Technology</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/pro-display-xdr-2-quantom-dot-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pro-display-xdr-2-expected-to-feature-quantum-dot-technology.2443442/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 08:11:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/pro-display-xdr-2-quantom-dot-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Displays</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/blog/new-macbook-pros-are-the-first-apple-product-to-use-quantum-dots">blog post this week</a>, Display Supply Chain Consultants CEO Ross Young said that he expects Apple's next-generation Pro Display XDR to feature the same quantum-dot display technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/14/m4-macbook-pro-quantum-dot/">adopted by the latest MacBook Pro models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/11/Pro-Display-XDR-2-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-978197" /><br/>
It is unclear if Young confirmed this information with his sources, or if it is merely a prediction, but he is a display industry expert and his track record with display-related rumors for future Apple products is quite good. For example, he was the first source to reveal that iPhone 16 Pro models would feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/DSCCRoss/status/1857208745014776215">social media post</a> last week, Young said the latest quantum-dot display films have equal to better color gamut support, and offer improved motion performance, compared to the KSF phosphor film that he said Apple uses for the existing Pro Display XDR and previous MacBook Pro models. This means the Pro Display XDR 2 could have improved color accuracy and faster response times compared to the current model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released the Pro Display XDR in 2019, alongside an updated Mac Pro, and the external monitor has not received any hardware upgrades since then. The high-end 32-inch monitor features an LCD panel with LED backlighting, 6K resolution, a 60Hz refresh rate, up to 1,600 nits of brightness, one Thunderbolt 3 port, and three USB-C ports. In the U.S., the monitor starts at &#36;4,999, but the optional Pro Stand costs &#36;999 extra.<br/>
<br/>
In 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said Apple was working on an updated version of the Pro Display XDR <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/18/updated-pro-display-xdr-gurman/">with an Apple silicon chip</a>, something the current model lacks. In the Studio Display, an A13 Bionic chip powers features such as Center Stage camera framing, spatial audio, and Siri voice commands. Additional features that customers are hoping for include a built-in camera, speakers, and a higher refresh rate.<br/>
<br/>
At this point, it is unclear when Apple might release a Pro Display XDR 2.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/displays/">Apple Pro Display XDR</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Apple Studio Display</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-accessories.77">Mac Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/pro-display-xdr-2-quantom-dot-rumor/">Pro Display XDR 2 Expected to Feature Quantum-Dot Technology</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pro-display-xdr-2-expected-to-feature-quantum-dot-technology.2443442/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Further Expanding Into Ads, Now Directly Selling Ads in News App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-now-directly-selling-ads-in-news-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-further-expanding-into-ads-now-directly-selling-ads-in-news-app.2443441/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 08:07:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-now-directly-selling-ads-in-news-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has started directly selling ads shown in the Apple News app, according <a href="https://www.axios.com/2024/11/19/apple-news-ads-direct-sales-publishers">to <em>Axios</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/05/apple-news-banner.png" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-741688" /><br/>
The report said that Apple News publishers will receive a 70% cut of the revenue from ads sold by Apple within their articles, and added that publishers will continue to receive 100% of the revenue from in-article ads that they sell themselves.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been gradually expanding its advertising efforts over the past few years. For example, it started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/25/apple-now-showing-more-ads-in-app-store/">selling ads within the main "Today" tab in the App Store</a> in 2022, allowing developers to promote their apps to a wider audience.<br/>
<br/>
Apple selling ads directly within the Apple News app could further boost its services revenue.<br/>
<br/>
More details about the placement of ads in the Apple News app can be found in the <a href="https://www.axios.com/2024/11/19/apple-news-ads-direct-sales-publishers"><em>Axios</em> report</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-now-directly-selling-ads-in-news-app/">Apple Further Expanding Into Ads, Now Directly Selling Ads in News App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-further-expanding-into-ads-now-directly-selling-ads-in-news-app.2443441/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday AirTag Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/black-friday-airtag-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-airtag-deals.2443431/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 07:09:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/black-friday-airtag-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday is just over a week away, and in the lead-up to the shopping holiday we've seen great deals arrive for Apple's AirTag Bluetooth tracker. In this article we're sharing all the best deals you can currently get on the AirTag.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airtag-candycane-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874368" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on the AirTag arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently the best prices you will find online. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best AirTag Deals</h2><br/>
Amazon today has Apple's AirTag 4-Pack for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;72.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This is just about &#36;3 higher when compared to the all-time low price we saw last week, so it's still a great deal on the Bluetooth trackers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Fref%3Dods_ucc_kindle_B0CWXNS552_rc_nd_ucc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;9 OFF</div>AirTag 1-Pack for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;26 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;72.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for a single AirTag, Amazon has the AirTag 1-Pack for just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Fref%3Dods_ucc_kindle_B0CWXNS552_rc_nd_ucc"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.00. This one is a match of the all-time low price on the AirTag 1-Pack.<br/>
<br/>
You can find all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/01/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals-2024/"><strong>Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<div class="no-raptive"><br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL"  placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div><input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"></div><br/>
</div><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/black-friday-airtag-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday AirTag Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-airtag-deals.2443431/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Two Months With the Apple Watch Series 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-watch-series-10-two-month-review/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-months-with-the-apple-watch-series-10.2443430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 07:01:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-watch-series-10-two-month-review/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been two months since Apple released the Apple Watch Series 10, and <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera has been using the Series 10 alongside an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> to provide a longer term review and comparison.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Watch Series 10 Long Term Review: Switching From Ultra 2??" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sAE9cmHHOwc" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The larger version of the Series 10 has the biggest display of any Apple Watch, including the Ultra 2, but it's only a little bit bigger than the Ultra 2 so you're not missing out on much if you have Apple's more rugged watch. The Series 10 is lighter and thinner, though, so it can be more comfortable.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to having the largest display, the Series 10 has better visibility at an angle, so you can better see the time regardless of what you're doing. There's a 1Hz minimum refresh rate too so you get an always-on second hand with some watch faces.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added sleep apnea detection to the Series 10, but the Apple Watch Ultra got it too, so there's no real distinguishing health feature to set it apart. It basically has all the same features as the Ultra 2, including the Dive app and a Tides app, but it can't be used for deep water diving because it doesn't have the same depth resistance. Also unique to the Ultra 2 is the siren sound.<br/>
<br/>
Given the near feature parity, if you have an Ultra 2, there's probably no reason to get the Series 10 at this point, unless you want a watch that's slimmer and lighter. If you're trying to decide between the Ultra 2 and the Series 10, it's between weight and battery life. The Series 10 is lighter and more comfortable, but the Ultra 2 has much longer battery life.<br/>
<br/>
What are your Apple Watch Series 10 thoughts? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-watch-series-10-two-month-review/">Review: Two Months With the Apple Watch Series 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-months-with-the-apple-watch-series-10.2443430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ending Support for Safari Bookmark Syncing on iOS 10 and Earlier</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ending-safari-bookmark-syncing-below-ios-11/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ending-support-for-safari-bookmark-syncing-on-ios-10-and-earlier.2443429/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 06:41:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ending-safari-bookmark-syncing-below-ios-11/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iCloud</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117827">support document</a> published this week, Apple said it will be dropping support for Safari bookmark syncing on iPhones and iPads running iOS 10 or earlier, and on Macs running macOS Sierra 10.12.5 or earlier, starting December 18. Apple said it made this decision in accordance with its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/118308">minimum software requirements for iCloud</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/iCloud-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803318" /><br/>
Apple said Safari bookmarks on devices running those older iOS and macOS versions will no longer be synced to other devices or uploaded to iCloud.com:<blockquote>You won't lose any bookmarks already on your devices and you'll still be able to create new bookmarks on those devices. However, new bookmarks won't sync across devices with iOS 10 or earlier and macOS Sierra 10.12.5 or earlier. They also won't be recoverable on iCloud.com.</blockquote>Apple said users will need to update their devices to iOS 11 or macOS Sierra 10.12.6 or newer to continue syncing their Safari bookmarks with the newer iCloud Bookmarks system, with steps for iPhone, iPad, iPod touch, Mac, and PC users outlined in Apple's support document. If you cannot or do not want to update your device, you can copy or export your bookmarks, with the support document outlining steps for that option as well. <br/>
<br/>
If your devices are already running iOS 11 or later or macOS Sierra 10.12.6 or later, no action is required, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
As we previously reported, Apple also announced that iCloud device backups for the iPhone, iPad, and iPod touch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/18/apple-icloud-backup-ios-9-minimum/">will require iOS 9 or later starting December 18</a>. As outlined in another <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/120863">support document</a>, users will need to update their devices to iOS 9 or later or manually back up the device to a Mac or PC. After the deadline, Apple said any data backed up to iCloud from devices that have not been updated to iOS 9 will be deleted.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ending-safari-bookmark-syncing-below-ios-11/">Apple Ending Support for Safari Bookmark Syncing on iOS 10 and Earlier</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ending-support-for-safari-bookmark-syncing-on-ios-10-and-earlier.2443429/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reveals Most Popular Podcasts of 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/most-popular-podcasts-of-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-most-popular-podcasts-of-2024.2443419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 05:34:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/most-popular-podcasts-of-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/11/apple-shares-the-most-popular-podcasts-of-2024/">shared</a> the most popular podcasts of 2024, with <a href="http://apple.co/-TopCharts24">year-end charts</a> available in the Browse tab of the Podcasts app through the end of the year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Podcasts-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-798617" /><br/>
The 2024 charts include the top podcasts overall, the top new podcasts that debuted this year, the most followed podcasts, the most shared podcasts and episodes, and more. The most popular podcasts of 2024 in the U.S., according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a>:<blockquote><strong>Top Shows</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. The Daily<br/>
2. Crime Junkie<br/>
3. The Joe Rogan Experience<br/>
4. Dateline NBC<br/>
5. SmartLess<br/>
6. Huberman Lab<br/>
7. This American Life<br/>
8. New Heights with Jason & Travis Kelce<br/>
9. Up First from NPR<br/>
10. Morbid<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Top New Shows</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. The Tucker Carlson Show<br/>
2. Three<br/>
3. Mortal Sin<br/>
4. Drowning Creek<br/>
5. The Rise and Fall of Ruby Franke<br/>
6. Blood is Thicker: The Hargan Family Killings<br/>
7. Noble<br/>
8. Murder in the Hollywood Hills<br/>
9. Hysterical<br/>
10. Who Killed JFK?<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Top Series</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. Serial<br/>
2. Up and Vanished<br/>
3. Three<br/>
4. The Bakersfield Three<br/>
5. CounterClock<br/>
6. Something Was Wrong<br/>
7. Dr. Death<br/>
8. The Binge Cases<br/>
9. Rachel Maddow Presents: Ultra<br/>
10. The Binge Crimes<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Top Episodes</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. Crime Junkie: “SERIAL KILLER: The Alphabet Murders Part 1”<br/>
2. The Joe Rogan Experience: “#2219 - Donald Trump”<br/>
3. The Daily: “Harris Baits Trump: Inside Their Fiery Debate”<br/>
4. Dateline NBC: “Dangerous Secret”<br/>
5. The Bakersfield Three: “Episode 1: Fight Like a Mother”<br/>
6. SmartLess: “Vince Vaughn”<br/>
7. Three: “Skylar Is Missing | Chapter 1”<br/>
8. Serial: “Serial S04 - Ep. 1: Poor Baby Raul”<br/>
9. Mortal Sin: “1 – Ashes to Ashes”<br/>
10. New Heights with Jason & Travis Kelce: “Travis Wins on the Road, Jason Celebrates Shirtless and Full Divisional Round Recap | Ep 75”<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Most Shared Shows</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. Huberman Lab<br/>
2. Scamanda<br/>
3. Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus<br/>
4. The Daily<br/>
5. The Bible in a Year (with Fr. Mike Schmitz)<br/>
6. The Bible Recap<br/>
7. The Mel Robbins Podcast<br/>
8. Sold a Story<br/>
9. Who Killed JFK?<br/>
10. Crime Junkie<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Most Shared Episodes</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. The Tucker Carlson Show: “Calley & Casey Means: The Truth About Ozempic, the Pill, and How Big Pharma Keeps You Sick”<br/>
2. The Mel Robbins Podcast: “The #1 Menopause Doctor: How to Lose Belly Fat, Sleep Better, & Stop Suffering Now”<br/>
3. The Daily: “The Year of Taylor Swift”<br/>
4. Huberman Lab: “Dr. Stacy Sims: Female-Specific Exercise & Nutrition for Health, Performance & Longevity”<br/>
5. The Joe Rogan Experience: “#2219 - Donald Trump”<br/>
6. The Ezra Klein Show: “Is Tim Walz the Midwestern Dad Democrats Need?”<br/>
7. Honestly with Bari Weiss: “Why the Kids Aren’t Alright”<br/>
8. We Can Do Hard Things: “263. Healing from Emotionally Immature Parents with Lindsay C. Gibson”<br/>
9. Call Her Daddy: “Vice President Kamala Harris”<br/>
10. Good Inside with Dr. Becky: “The Anxious Generation with Jonathan Haidt”<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Most Followed Shows</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. The Joe Rogan Experience<br/>
2. New Heights with Jason & Travis Kelce<br/>
3. Huberman Lab<br/>
4. Call Her Daddy<br/>
5. The Tucker Carlson Show<br/>
6. The Mel Robbins Podcast<br/>
7. SmartLess<br/>
8. Wiser Than Me with Julia Louis-Dreyfus<br/>
9. Crime Junkie<br/>
10. The Daily<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Top Subscriber Shows</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. Apple News+ Narrated<br/>
2. Morbid<br/>
3. Dateline NBC<br/>
4. The Rise and Fall of Ruby Franke<br/>
5. Dr. Death<br/>
6. SmartLess<br/>
7. Something Was Wrong<br/>
8. Scamtown<br/>
9. American Scandal<br/>
10. Mortal Sin<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Top Channels</strong><br/>
<br/>
1. Wondery<br/>
2. iHeartPodcasts<br/>
3. The New York Times<br/>
4. audiochuck<br/>
5. SiriusXM Podcasts<br/>
6. Dateline NBC<br/>
7. Dear Media<br/>
8. iHeart True Crime<br/>
9. Scicomm Media<br/>
10. Cumulus Podcast Network</blockquote>These charts in the Podcasts app are localized for listeners in nearly 100 countries and regions. Listeners can also explore "Shows We Love," a curated collection of standout narrative and episodic series that Apple says resonated this year. Apple added that it will reveal its Show of the Year on Tuesday, December 3.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/most-popular-podcasts-of-2024/">Apple Reveals Most Popular Podcasts of 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-most-popular-podcasts-of-2024.2443419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Google Merging Chrome OS Into Android to Rival iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-merging-chrome-os-android-rival-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-google-merging-chrome-os-into-android-to-rival-ipad.2443414/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 04:24:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-merging-chrome-os-android-rival-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google is working on a multi-year project to fully migrate Chrome OS to Android as part of an effort to better compete with Apple's iPad, according to a new report from <em><a href="https://www.androidauthority.com/chrome-os-becoming-android-3500661/">Android Authority</a></em> citing an internal source at the company.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/google-chromebook-lifestyle-shot.jpeg" alt="" width="2132" height="1200" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-814012" /><br/>
The initiative would apparently see future Chromebook devices shipping with a desktop-optimized version of Android rather than Chrome OS, which would be a major shift in Google's operating system strategy. Google announced in June 2024 that Chrome OS would begin incorporating portions of Android's technical foundation, but the reported plans go much further toward a complete merger of the two platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Google is already laying groundwork for the transition by developing a new version of Chrome for Android with extension support and a Terminal application for running Linux apps. The company is also working on improved keyboard, mouse, and external display support for Android, along with features like multiple desktop spaces.<br/>
<br/>
The consolidation aims to create a more unified platform that can better challenge Apple's dominance in the high-end tablet market while allowing Google to more efficiently manage its development resources. Currently, neither Chrome OS nor Android has successfully competed with iPad, despite the multitasking shortcomings of iPadOS.<br/>
<br/>
The report notes that the strategy could also benefit the Android ecosystem by expanding its user base and making it more attractive to developers. Meanwhile, a separate report from <em><a href="https://www.androidheadlines.com/exclusive-google-pixel-laptop-development.html">Android Headlines</a></em> suggests Google is developing a high-end Pixel-branded laptop, which could potentially showcase the new desktop-oriented Android platform.<br/>
<br/>
Google has not officially confirmed plans to phase out Chrome OS in favor of Android, and the company declined to comment on the report when contacted by <em>Android Authority</em>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/google-merging-chrome-os-android-rival-ipad/">Report: Google Merging Chrome OS Into Android to Rival iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-google-merging-chrome-os-into-android-to-rival-ipad.2443414/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
