<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:03:26 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Every iPad Air Hits All-Time Low Price in Best Buy&#039;s New Sale, Available From &#36;449.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/best-buy-has-every-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/every-ipad-air-hits-all-time-low-price-in-best-buys-new-sale-available-from-449-99.2419205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 09:31:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/best-buy-has-every-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's <a href="https://howl.me/clB33hyCQjJ">new weekend sale</a> includes every model of the <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb">5th generation iPad Air for up to &#36;150 off</a>, with multiple all-time low prices. These deals are available to all shoppers and do not require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPad-Air-150-Off-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1304" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933761" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air, you can get this tablet for <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.99. Best Buy has every color on sale at this record low price, which we last tracked back in January.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"><strong>&#36;599.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;749.99. You'll again find this model on sale in all colors, and it's another all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, there are cellular discounts as well during this sale, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"><strong>&#36;599.99</strong></a> for the 64GB cellular iPad Air and rising to <a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a> for the 256GB cellular iPad Air. Both of these are again &#36;150 discounts and all-time low prices on the iPad Air, and available in every color at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB cellular) for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (256GB cellular) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the iPad Air, Best Buy has great markdowns on the 9th generation iPad, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/best-buy-10th-gen-ipad/">10th generation iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/macbook-air-pro-low-prices/">MacBook Pro</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/15-inch-macbook-air-best-ever-prices/">MacBook Air</a>, all of which we've covered in articles this week.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/best-buy-has-every-ipad-air/">Every iPad Air Hits All-Time Low Price in Best Buy&#039;s New Sale, Available From &#36;449.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/every-ipad-air-hits-all-time-low-price-in-best-buys-new-sale-available-from-449-99.2419205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Could Take Four Generations to Reach &#039;Ideal Form&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/apple-vision-pro-fourth-generation-ideal/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-could-take-four-generations-to-reach-ideal-form.2419188/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2024 06:48:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/apple-vision-pro-fourth-generation-ideal/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Realizing the Apple Vision Pro headset's "ideal form" could take four successive generations of the device, some people in Apple's Vision Products Group believe. That's according to well-connected <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-at-Steve-Jobs-Theater.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898794" /><br/>
Writing in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-02-11/apple-vision-pro-review-3-499-headset-will-eventually-replace-the-ipad-lshk59z1">Power On</a> newsletter, Gurman says the feeling amongst some of the team working on Apple's headset is that there is much work to do before the device can be considered refined enough for customers to use on a day-to-day basis.   <br/>
<br/>
While it's not clear what Apple's development team consider to be the device's "ideal form," it's easy enough to take cues from some early adopters, whose issues with the first-generation device have extended to both the hardware and the software. <br/>
<br/>
Many Vision Pro users feel the headset itself is too heavy and unwieldy for extended use, making generational miniaturization a crucial touchstone for improvement. Other criticisms have included poor battery life, not enough dedicated apps, and a preponderance of bugs in visionOS.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple's team can resolve those issues over four generations – similar to the progression of the iPhone, iPad and Apple Watch – Gurman's take is that the Vision Pro could eventually replace the iPad. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has had "mixed results" in attempting to position the iPad as more of a Mac replacement, Gurman says. Despite Apple's efforts to make it a multitasking device with features like Stage Manager, the iPad has struggled to become a true productivity workhorse like the Mac, and now sits in a limbo amongst Apple's other offerings. "The device lost its original purpose and has become a more confusing piece of Apple's product portfolio," writes Gurman. <br/>
<br/>
As for Vision Pro, which starts at &#36;3,500, "it's going to take some hardware upgrades, a slew of software updates, and far better support from app developers and content makers to actually make the headset the iPad replacement that it's capable of being," adds Gurman. "Until then, the Vision Pro is essentially a prototype — just one where you have to pay Apple for the privilege of testing it out."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/11/apple-vision-pro-fourth-generation-ideal/">Apple Vision Pro Could Take Four Generations to Reach &#039;Ideal Form&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-could-take-four-generations-to-reach-ideal-form.2419188/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Investigating &#039;Ghost Touches&#039; Issue Affecting Some Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-touch-screen-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-investigating-ghost-touches-issue-affecting-some-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches.2419114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 10:54:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-touch-screen-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Authorized Service Providers</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In an <a href="https://twitter.com/StellaFudge/status/1756365322301423616">internal memo</a> shared with Apple Authorized Service Providers this week, Apple said it is "aware of" and "investigating" a touch-related issue affecting some Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 displays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-9-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913380" /><br/>
"Some customers may report their Apple Watch Series 9 or Apple Watch Ultra 2 is experiencing false touches on their display," reads Apple's memo, obtained by <em>MacRumors</em>. Apple said some customers may describe the issue as "ghost" touches.<br/>
<br/>
The issue may cause the screen on affected Apple Watch models to "jump erratically" or exhibit other unexpected behavior, without any user interaction, according to Apple. The memo said the issue can also result in an Apple Watch starting a phone call unintentionally, and prevent users from entering the device's passcode.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recommends that customers keep their Apple Watch's software up to date, suggesting that the company is hopeful it will be able to address the issue in a future watchOS update. Apple did not say how widespread the issue is, or provide a timeframe for a potential fix. It is unclear if defective hardware is a contributing factor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has instructed technicians not to repair affected Apple Watch models while it investigates. In the meantime, technicians are told to ask customers who are experiencing this issue to force restart their Apple Watch by holding down the Digital Crown and the side button at the same time for at least 10 seconds, until the Apple logo appears.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models were released in September 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aasp/">Apple Authorized Service Providers</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-touch-screen-issue/">Apple Investigating &#039;Ghost Touches&#039; Issue Affecting Some Series 9 and Ultra 2 Watches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-investigating-ghost-touches-issue-affecting-some-series-9-and-ultra-2-watches.2419114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Vision Pro Launch Recap, iOS 17.4 Beta Features, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-launch-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-launch-recap-ios-17-4-beta-features-and-more.2419093/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-launch-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro has been out for a week, so regular users are starting to get settled in with the new device and sharing their thoughts on it while teardown experts have been digging into the hardware.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/top-stories-10feb2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935854" /><br/>
Beyond all the news surrounding Apple's long-anticipated headset, this week also saw more progress on iOS 17.4 and related operating system updates expected to launch next month, fresh iPhone 16 rumors, and more, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Apps to Check Out</h2><br/>
Following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-unboxing/">launch of Apple's new Vision Pro headset</a> on Friday, we shared an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/">in-depth list of apps optimized for the visionOS operating system</a>, from both larger and smaller developers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Vision-Pro-Apps-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934149" /><br/>
Apple announced that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-vision-pro-over-600-native-apps/">over 600 apps have been optimized for visionOS</a> so far, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/">our list highlights many notable ones</a>, while we've also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/top-10-vision-pro-apps/">shared a video looking at ten of our favorites</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro is also compatible with more than one million iPad and iPhone apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iFixit Shares Apple Vision Pro Teardown</h2><br/>
Repair website iFixit recently shared <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/ifixit-apple-vision-pro-teardown/">written and video teardowns of the Apple Vision Pro</a>, providing a closer look inside the headset. The headset is an engineering feat, with an array of cameras, sensors, fans, and many other precisely-arranged components.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iFixit-Vision-Pro-Teardown.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934613" /><br/>
iFixit also shared some technical details about the Vision Pro's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/ifixit-vision-pro-displays-and-repairability/">internal and external displays, battery pack, repairability, and more</a> in a separate video.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17.4 Beta: All the New Features</h2><br/>
Apple last month confirmed that iOS 17.4 will be released at some point in March. The upcoming software update includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">several new features and changes for the iPhone</a>, as outlined in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-beta-features/">our list</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932462" /><br/>
Key new features include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">major App Store changes in the EU</a>, Apple Podcasts transcripts, SharePlay for the HomePod, and new emoji. The update also prepares for the launch of next-generation CarPlay later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug/">released iOS 17.3.1 with a text-related bug fix</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Testing Slim Camera Bump Design for Base iPhone 16</h2><br/>
The standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models launching later this year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">could be equipped with a slim, vertical, pill-shaped rear camera bump</a>, according to leaked schematics.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Colors-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935282" /><br/>
The return to vertically-aligned rear camera lenses would allow for spatial video recording on the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus. The feature is currently exclusive to the Pro models in the iPhone 15 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Now Selling Refurbished 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/apple-refurbished-14-inch-m3-macbook-pro/">added the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the standard M3 chip to its online refurbished store</a> for the first time since the laptop was released in November. Prices are discounted by around 15%.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-bb-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924141" /><br/>
Apple's certified refurbished products are nearly indistinguishable from brand new models, in our view, so they can be an attractive choice for customers who are looking for a discount directly from the company.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The MacRumors Show: One Week With Apple Vision Pro ft. Quinn Nelson</h2><br/>
On <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">this week's episode of <em>The MacRumors Show</em> podcast</a>, special guest Quinn Nelson of Snazzy Labs joined Dan and Hartley to discuss what it's been like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">using the Apple Vision Pro</a> over the past week since its launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/The-MacRumors-Show-Quinn-Nelson-Talks-Vision-Pro-Thumb-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935826" /><br/>
<em>The MacRumors Show</em> now has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so be sure to subscribe for the latest episodes. The show is also available through your preferred podcast app.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/feb-8-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/10/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-launch-recap/">Top Stories: Apple Vision Pro Launch Recap, iOS 17.4 Beta Features, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-vision-pro-launch-recap-ios-17-4-beta-features-and-more.2419093/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Settle Trade Secret Lawsuit With SoC Startup Rivos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/apple-settles-rivos-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-settle-trade-secret-lawsuit-with-soc-startup-rivos.2419053/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 15:29:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/apple-settles-rivos-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has reached an agreement with Rivos, the SoC company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/02/apple-sues-rivos-trade-secret-theft/">that it sued in 2022</a> for theft of trade secrets, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-09/apple-is-settling-chip-secrets-theft-case-against-startup-rivos">Bloomberg</a></em>. Rivos will submit to a forensic examination of its systems to remove any confidential Apple information.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-silicon-1-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1422" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924673" /><br/>
Rivos hired more than 40 employees from Apple, including several former high-ranking engineers, leading Apple to file a lawsuit in May 2022. Apple accused Rivos of poaching employees and stealing chip trade secrets via those employees. Rivos is designing SoCs that would compete with Apple's A-series and M-series chips.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, at least two engineers hired by Rivos took "gigabytes of sensitive SoC specifications and design files" during their last few days at Apple. The employees used USB drives and AirDrop to transfer sensitive Apple material to their own personal devices, and allegedly stole presentations on unreleased SoCs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple asked for an injunction against the employees that joined Rivos to prevent them from continuing to leak sensitive data, and it sought compensation for the loss caused by trade secret misappropriation and Rivos' "unjust enrichment" at Apple's expense. Apple wanted a "reasonable royalty rate" from Rivos on future products, and had requested a jury trial.<br/>
<br/>
Rivos and Apple are aiming to finalize their settlement by March 15, and are working through the remediation process.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/apple-settles-rivos-lawsuit/">Apple to Settle Trade Secret Lawsuit With SoC Startup Rivos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-settle-trade-secret-lawsuit-with-soc-startup-rivos.2419053/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top 10 Vision Pro Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/top-10-vision-pro-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-10-vision-pro-apps.2419041/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 12:24:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/top-10-vision-pro-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Vision Pro launched with its own dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and last Friday, there were more than 600 Vision Pro-optimized apps available for download. We thought we'd pull out 10 of the best apps to check out on Vision Pro, both for day-to-day use and for showing off the capabilities of the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/AeSK-Ilmu38" title="10 Killer Apple Vision Pro Apps!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spatial-cam/id6477200179?platform=appleVisionPro"><strong>Spatial Cam</strong></a> (Free) - With Spatial Cam, you can watch the camera feed from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> on your Vision Pro. The app lets you connect to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and then you can view the feed from afar, which is ideal for keeping an eye on kids and pets. Using this as a window in your workspace is useful for when you're fully immersed in a Vision Pro experience.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juno-for-youtube/id6476961640">Juno for YouTube</a></strong> (&#36;4.99) - There's no official YouTube app for the Vision Pro, so Juno from developer Christian Selig is a good alternative. It offers a better Vision Pro interface than the Safari web interface, and provides quick access controls for creating a home theater experience. Juno is not without its bugs, however, and it does not remove YouTube ads.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/crouton-recipe-manager/id1461650987?platform=appleVisionPro">Crouton</a></strong> (Free, in-app purchases) - Crouton is a recipe management app that lets you save recipes from websites, recipe books, and more, saving them in an easy-to-browse interface. You can get step-by-step cooking instructions that you can follow while wearing the Vision Pro and add timers for different meal components. The app does say not to cook while wearing Vision Pro, but there are a lot of handy cooking tools if you want to break the rules.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/blackbox-for-vision/id6458588937">Blackbox</a></strong> (&#36;19.99) - Blackbox is a puzzle game where you manipulate orbs, bubbles, and other objects to explore different visuals and sounds on Vision Pro. It is one of the more unique experiences on Apple's headset. The game is under active development and new puzzles will be added over time.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spatial-symphony/id6476616491">Spatial Symphony</a></strong> (Free, &#36;6.99 for Pro)- Spatial Symphony gives you a way to visually interact with and create music. You can sculpt sounds by moving your hands to adjust pitch, volume, and more.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nowplaying-music-trivia/id1596487035?platform=appleVisionPro"><strong>NowPlaying</strong></a> (Free, in-app purchases) - You can connect NowPlaying to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> to get a more immersive, visual listening experience. The app provides album artwork, lyrics, facts and trivia about what you're listening to, and song displays so you can watch your music while it plays.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/synth-riders/id6473729300">SynthRiders</a></strong> (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>) - SynthRiders is a rhythm game where the idea is to match the color on your hands with the balls coming at you, keeping up with the rhythm. It's similar to Beat Saber and other games like that.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/floatnotes/id6476990428">FloatNotes</a></strong> (Free) - FloatNotes is a free app that lets you put little sticky notes anywhere in your workspace.</li><br/>
 	<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/shortcut-buttons/id6476515513"><strong>Shortcut Buttons</strong></a> (&#36;7.99) - With Shortcut Buttons, you can create Shortcut buttons that can be put anywhere and launched with a tap.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pga-tour-vision/id6471858717">PGA Tour Vision</a></strong> - Golf fans can see a model of select holes on the PGA Tour, with the models able to be rotated and explored in-depth. There's also a leaderboard, videos to watch, shot tracking, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
We have even more great Vision Pro apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/">in our Vision Pro app guide</a>, but if you have a favorite Vision Pro app, let us know what it is in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/top-10-vision-pro-apps/">Top 10 Vision Pro Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-10-vision-pro-apps.2419041/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a Custom Apple Pencil 2 From ColorWare</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-apple-pencil/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-custom-apple-pencil-2-from-colorware.2419025/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 10:00:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-apple-pencil/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://www.colorware.com/">ColorWare</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1466-colorware-apple-number-2-pencil.aspx?c=variant-15y">a custom Apple Pencil 2</a> that's been painted to look like an actual number 2 pencil.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/colorware-apple-2-pencil-1.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1536" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935830" /><br/>
ColorWare is a company that makes custom-painted Apple products and accessories, and ordering from ColorWare is essentially the only way to get a non-standard color for AirPods, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, the Magic Mouse, and AirTags.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/colorware-apple-2-pencil-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935831" /><br/>
Occasionally, ColorWare comes out with super fun special edition products, such as the new <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1466-colorware-apple-number-2-pencil.aspx?c=variant-15y">ColorWare Apple Number 2 Pencil</a>. This is an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2 that has a black tip, yellow body, painted-on eraser, and other detailing for a faithful rendering of a number 2 pencil.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/colorware-apple-2-pencil-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935832" /><br/>
ColorWare is making a limited number of the Apple Number 2 Pencils, and they're priced at &#36;215. That's an &#36;86 premium over the &#36;129 price tag, but the extra cost is worth it for a unique design that will make your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> stand out. To get the pencil-like effect, ColorWare has combined matte, metallic, and glossy paints for the pencil, and it comes in a special edition box.<br/>
<br/>
ColorWare has been designing and selling custom-painted devices for more than two decades, and it has perfected the steps needed for a gorgeous, durable finish. ColorWare uses a multi-step coating process that includes a primer, the application of a proprietary color formula, and an X2 liquid plastic coating that protects the color. All ColorWare products are warrantied for 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/colorware-apple-2-pencil-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935833" /><br/>
The Apple Number 2 Pencil is set to ship out from ColorWare in March, and two lucky <em>MacRumors</em> readers will be among the first to get them. To enter to win our giveaway, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/Vz0dx/colorware-giveaway" rel="nofollow">ColorWare Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (February 9) at 09:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 09:00 a.m. Pacific Time on February 16. The winners will be picked randomly on or shortly after February 16 and will be contacted by email. The winners will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before new winners are chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-apple-pencil/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a Custom Apple Pencil 2 From ColorWare</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-custom-apple-pencil-2-from-colorware.2419025/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: One Week With Apple Vision Pro ft. Quinn Nelson</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-apple-vision-pro-ft-quinn-nelson.2419023/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 09:14:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/one-week-with-apple-vision-pro-ft-quinn-nelson-snazzy-labs/id1602394741?i=1000644778180">The MacRumors Show</a>, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@snazzy">Snazzy Labs</a>' Quinn Nelson joins us to talk about the first week using Apple's long-awaited Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HRpqWpAHBXE?si=KFaZVrW4_0XwAm62" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Now that they each have one, Quinn and Dan discuss whether the Vision Pro meets their expectations. A significant portion of our dialogue is dedicated to the technical aspects of the Vision Pro, including its display quality, brightness, and the challenges users might face with hand gestures and text selection. The conversation progresses to evaluate the device's text sharpness, its implications for productivity, and how comfortable it feels with the two headband options.<br/>
<br/>
An interesting part of our discussion compares the Vision Pro with other VR headsets in the market. We highlight the distinct features of the Vision Pro that set it apart, especially its distortion correction capabilities and suitability for productivity tasks, contrasting it with the Meta Quest's gaming prowess. We also explore the potential for third-party headbands, future customization, and design possibilities, emphasizing Apple's unique position in the VR landscape and its differing approach from rivals.<br/>
<br/>
We ponder the coexistence of Apple and Meta within the VR space, acknowledging the competition but also recognizing the distinctive strengths and target audiences each company caters to. This leads to a broader discussion about the challenges current VR headsets face, such as eye strain, and the optimistic outlook for technological improvements over time that could mitigate these issues.<br/>
<br/>
A considerable part of our discussion tackles the technicalities and challenges surrounding Personas and face scanning with the Vision Pro, including the influence of factors like face shape, hair, and lighting conditions on the accuracy of these features. Quinn also shares insights on the integration of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> apps with the Vision Pro, highlighting how this has transformed his workflow in certain instances and the potential it unlocks for productivity.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the mix of frustrations and amazement the Vision Pro has brought, we come to a consensus acknowledging the exciting possibilities the device offers for the future of VR and productivity, considering whether or not we would recommend Apple's headset to others.<br/>
<br/>
See more of Quinn's work over on his YouTube channel, <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@snazzy">Snazzy Labs</a>, and follow him on X <a href="https://twitter.com/SnazzyLabs">@SnazzyLabs</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's potential March event to unveil new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; and Mac models, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> as the "biggest" ever <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> software update.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">The MacRumors Show: One Week With Apple Vision Pro ft. Quinn Nelson</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-apple-vision-pro-ft-quinn-nelson.2419023/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sketchy Rumor Says iOS 18 Will Have visionOS-Inspired Design Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/ios-18-visionos-design-elements-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-says-ios-18-will-have-visionos-inspired-design-changes.2419020/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 08:32:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/ios-18-visionos-design-elements-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>The Verifier</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 will feature visionOS-inspired design elements, according to a rumor shared this week by <a href="https://theverifier.co.il/62189/exclusive-apple-ios-18-visionos/">Israeli website <em>The Verifier</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-design.jpeg" alt="" width="1800" height="1012" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935810" /><br/>
For example, the report claims that the Apple TV app on iPadOS 18 will feature the same translucent navigation bar that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/">introduced in the tvOS 17.2 version of the app</a> last year. The design of this menu draws similarities to visionOS, the operating system that runs on Apple's new Vision Pro headset, which launched in the U.S. last week.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also plans to redesign various other system menus and built-in apps on iOS 18, including Safari, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-tv-app-redesign.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918880" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple TV app menu bar on tvOS 17.2</em></div><br/>
We consider this rumor to be "sketchy" because <em>The Verifier</em> has a <a href="https://appletrack.com/the-verifier/">mixed track record</a> with Apple rumors over the years.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will introduce iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC in June, and the first beta should be available shortly after the announcement. The update will be released to all users in September alongside the iPhone 16 lineup. For more details about the upcoming software update, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theverifier-co-il/">The Verifier</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/ios-18-visionos-design-elements-rumor/">Sketchy Rumor Says iOS 18 Will Have visionOS-Inspired Design Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sketchy-rumor-says-ios-18-will-have-visionos-inspired-design-changes.2419020/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get &#36;300 Off Apple&#039;s 15-Inch MacBook Air With Multiple Best-Ever Prices Starting at &#36;999</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/15-inch-macbook-air-best-ever-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-300-off-apples-15-inch-macbook-air-with-multiple-best-ever-prices-starting-at-999.2419012/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 07:14:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/15-inch-macbook-air-best-ever-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's M2 15-inch MacBook Air is available for an all-time low price today at Best Buy, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model. You can get this deal in all four color options, and you don't need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to see this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898579" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The notebooks have an estimated delivery date around February 13, although those dates could change depending on your location. This is a match of the record low price on the 15-inch MacBook Air, and it's only about the second time we've tracked this sale in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For more storage, Best Buy has the 512GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. At &#36;300 off, this is the best price we've ever seen on this model of the MacBook Air, and it's available in all colors as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/15-inch-macbook-air-best-ever-prices/">Get &#36;300 Off Apple&#039;s 15-Inch MacBook Air With Multiple Best-Ever Prices Starting at &#36;999</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-300-off-apples-15-inch-macbook-air-with-multiple-best-ever-prices-starting-at-999.2419012/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Every iPhone 16 Rumor We&#039;ve Covered So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far.2419007/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 06:23:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With much of the tech industry's focus recently taken up by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple's Vision Pro</a> headset, you'd be forgiven for thinking that iPhone rumors have been few and far between over the last few months. Fortunately, that's not the case. Rumors and leaks about the iPhone 16 series continue to surface, and taken together, Apple's next-generation 2024 smartphone lineup looks like it could turn out to be a major upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
To bring you up to speed, we've summarized below the biggest iPhone 16 rumors we've covered so far here on <em>MacRumors</em>. For more details, follow the links, or dive into our dedicated roundups for both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, which are expected to arrive in September.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    1. Larger Displays</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Biggest Ever iPhones</span><br><br/>
This year's iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are rumored to be getting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">bigger display sizes</a>, increasing to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. For comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively. The new display sizes would be the largest ever for the iPhone.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    2. Vertical Camera Layout</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
Apple's iPhone 16 base models will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">vertical camera arrangement</a> with a pill-shaped raised surface, instead of a diagonal camera arrangement like the iPhone 15. The new camera bump features two separate camera rings for the Wide and Ultrawide cameras. The vertical camera layout is expected to enable Spatial Video recording, which is currently limited to the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
3. Battery Changes</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">All iPhone 16 Models</span><br><br/>
One rumor suggests the ‌iPhone 16‌ and iPhone 16 Pro Max will feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/some-iphone-16s-to-feature-bigger-batteries/">larger batteries</a> than their predecessors, but the ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus may have reduced capacity. The iPhone 16 is said to have a 6% increase over the iPhone 15, with the iPhone 16 Pro Max gaining a 5% increase. In contrast, the iPhone 16 Plus is rumored to have a 9% reduction in capacity. On the other hand, Apple could also potentially use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/25/iphone-15-hybrid-lens-rumor/">stacked battery technology</a> to increase energy density and prolong lifespan. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
4. Capture Button</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">New Camera Capabilities</span><br><br/>
All iPhone 16 models will have a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">Capture Button</a>" dedicated to triggering image or video capture. The button will add features like the ability to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus on a subject with a light press, and activate a recording with a more forceful press. The Capture Button will be located on the bottom right side of the ‌iPhone 16, and will take the place of the mmWave antenna on U.S. ‌iPhone‌ models, with the antenna relocating to the left side of the device below the volume and Action buttons.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
5. Ultra Wide Lens Upgrade</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro & iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro models are expected to feature an upgraded <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera lens</a>, which should allow it to capture more light, resulting in improved photos when shooting in 0.5× mode, especially in low-light environments. This also means that iPhone 16 Pro models should be able to shoot 48-megapixel ProRAW photos in Ultra Wide mode. These photos retain more detail in the image file for more editing flexibility, and can be printed at large sizes.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
5. Super Telephoto Camera</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro Max could be the first to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/18/iphone-16-pro-max-super-telephoto-camera/">super telephoto periscope camera</a> for dramatically increased optical zoom. "Super" or "ultra" telephoto usually describes cameras with a focal length of over 300mm. The current telephoto lens is equivalent to a 77mm lens, so if accurate, there could be a notable increase in zoom capabilities. Super telephoto cameras are often used for sports and wild animal photography, but the extremely soft backgrounds they create also make them useful for portrait photography, providing there is enough distance between the subject and the photographer.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
6. Faster Wi-Fi Support</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Wi-Fi 6E & Wi-Fi 7</span><br><br/>
Apple's 2024 iPhone Pro models are expected to get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">Wi-Fi 7 in the Pro models</a>, enabling data transfer over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously. This should result in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. With technologies such as 4K QAM, Wi-Fi 7 is  also expected to offer peak data transfer speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E. Meanwhile, the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">rumored to support Wi-Fi 6E</a>, which works with the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
7. New AXX Series Chips</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">A17 & A18 Pro Variants</span><br><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">next-generation A18 Pro chip</a> is expected to be manufactured with TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, known as N3E. All four iPhone 16 models will be equipped with A18-branded chips, according to one rumor. Meanwhile, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/">another rumor</a> counter-claims that the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus will have A17 chips made using a different manufacturing process to the A17 Pro in the iPhone 15 Pro. The ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌'s A17 Pro chip is fabricated using TSMC's N3B process, but Apple reportedly plans to switch to the lower-cost N3E process for next year's standard A17 chip designed for the ‌iPhone 16‌ and ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
7. 5G Qualcomm Modem</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro & iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
Apple is expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">Qualcomm's latest Snapdragon X75 modem</a> in this year's Pro and Pro Max models. The Snapdragon X75 includes improved carrier aggregation and other technology advancements for faster 5G download and upload speeds compared to the X70, which is used in iPhone 15 models. The modem's combined mmWave and sub-6GHz 5G transceiver also takes up 25% less circuit board space, and is said to use up to 20% less power. The standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus are expected to retain the Snapdragon X70 modem.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
8. Tetraprism Lens</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro</span><br><br/>
Both iPhone 16 Pro models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expected to feature 5x optical zoom</a>, which is currently exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro Max. Apple's tetraprism lens system has a "folded" design that allows it to fit inside the smartphone, enabling up to 5x optical zoom and up to 25x digital zoom. In contrast, the current smaller iPhone 15 Pro is limited to up to 3x optical zoom, which is in line with the iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
10. Micro-Lens Technology</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">More Efficient OLED</span><br><br/>
Apple is said to be weighing up the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">use of micro-lens technology</a> to maintain or increase the brightness of OLED displays on next year's iPhone 16 models while potentially reducing their power consumption. MLA works by using a uniform pattern of billions of lenses inside the panel that reduces internal reflections. These lenses turn the path of light reflected backwards from the inside of the panel towards the screen, which can serve either to increase perceived brightness while maintaining the same level of power consumption, or maintain brightness levels while consuming less power compared to conventional OLED panels at the same luminance.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
11. Action Button</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro models include an Action Button, and in 2024, the Action Button is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">expanded to the standard iPhone 16 models</a>. The Action Button used across the iPhone 16 lineup will be identical to the iPhone 15 Pro Action Button. The Action button, which replaces the traditional mute switch, can perform multiple functions such as activating the Flashlight, turning on the Camera, launching a Shortcut, enabling or disabling a Focus mode, using Translate, turning on/off Silent Mode, and more.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
12. Generative AI</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Large Language Models</span><br><br/>
With iOS 18, Apple is rumored to be introducing new features powered by large language models (LLMs), although additional cutting-edge generative AI features could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">limited to the iPhone 16 models</a>. Apple is developing a large array of features that use generative AI, including a smarter version of Siri, improved interactions between Siri and the Messages app, auto-generated Apple Music playlists, integration with productivity apps for AI-assisted content creation, and more. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
13. Upgraded Microphone</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Enhanced Siri</span><br><br/>
Apple is said to be planning a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/">significant upgrade</a> to the iPhone 16 microphone to improve the new AI-enhanced Siri experience. Apple's Siri AI ambitions will heavily rely on improved voice input processing, and the new mic is expected to offer significantly enhanced signal-to-noise ratio.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
14. New Thermal Design</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Reduced Heat</span><br><br/>
Apple is rumored to be working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/">graphene thermal system</a> for the ‌iPhone 16‌ lineup, while the ‌iPhone 16‌ Pro models could add metal battery casings to reduce overheating. Graphene has high thermal conductivity, surpassing that of copper, which is currently used in iPhone heat-sinks. Apple has been filing patents related to using graphene for thermal management for some time. The move could be in response to widely encountered overheating issues experienced with the iPhone 15 Pro, which Apple addressed through a software update.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
15. Expanded Storage</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Both iPhone 16 Pro Models</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be available with double the maximum storage capacity as the iPhone 15 Pro models, increasing from 1TB to 2TB, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/iphone-16-pro-2tb-option-rumor/">according to one rumor</a>. The move is said to be a result of Apple's switch to higher-density Quad-Level Cell (QLC) NAND flash for higher storage models. Apple's use of QLC NAND could allow Apple to fit more storage into a smaller space and it is less expensive than Triple-Level Cell (TLC) NAND, which current iPhones use. On the downside, QLC has comparatively slower read and write speeds.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
15. Increased Memory</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
Apple's iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models have been rumored to both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">feature 8GB of RAM</a>, an increase over the 6GB of RAM in the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus. More working memory should equate to improved performance for multitasking on the iPhone.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far/">Every iPhone 16 Rumor We&#039;ve Covered So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/every-iphone-16-rumor-weve-covered-so-far.2419007/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;The Joe Rogan Experience&#039; Returns to Apple Podcasts After 3-Year Hiatus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/joe-rogan-experience-apple-podcasts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-joe-rogan-experience-returns-to-apple-podcasts-after-3-year-hiatus.2418999/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 03:22:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/joe-rogan-experience-apple-podcasts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Podcasts</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/05/20/spotify-signs-up-the-joe-rogan-experience-podcast/">three-year absence</a>, the hugely popular and controversial podcast <em>The Joe Rogan Experience</em> is back on Apple Podcasts after Spotify gave up exclusivity as part of a multiyear deal renewal with Rogan.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/05/elon-musk-joe-rogan.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="825" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-742668" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>(Image credit: POWERFULJRE/YOUTUBE)</em></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/joerogan/status/1755735654225334432?s=20">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter), Rogan on Thursday said that "the podcast is now officially back on @apple. We should be back on @youtube with full episodes in the coming weeks."<br/>
<br/>
Under the new deal, which is said to be worth up to &#36;250 million, Rogan's show will be available on other content platforms, including Apple Podcasts, Amazon Music, and YouTube. The move is part of Spotify's revised strategy to forego exclusive streaming rights in favor of broader distribution.<br/>
<br/>
As part of the renewed deal, first reported by <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/business/media/joe-rogan-podcast-spotify-deal-28eb5f74">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>, Spotify will handle distribution and ad sales for the podcast. Rogan will receive a guaranteed minimum fee from Spotify as well as a cut of advertising revenue.<br/>
<br/>
"For more than three years, <em>The Joe Rogan Experience</em> has consistently been the No. 1 podcast across the globe," Spotify said when it announced the renewed deal last week. That accords with Edison Research's Q3 2023 survey of most listened-to podcasts, in which <em>The Joe Rogan Experience</em> ranked number 1 for the period. It was also the second most listened-to podcast for women 13 and older in the U.S., according to Edison.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The podcast is now officially back on <a href="https://twitter.com/Apple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@apple</a><br>We should be back on <a href="https://twitter.com/YouTube?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@youtube</a> with full episodes in the coming weeks. Shoutout to <a href="https://twitter.com/Spotify?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@spotify</a> for absolutely being the coolest and smartest people I’ve ever had the pleasure of being in partnership with. I’m very excited the podcast… <a href="https://t.co/lf9vpPtpLU">pic.twitter.com/lf9vpPtpLU</a></p>&mdash; Joe Rogan (@joerogan) <a href="https://twitter.com/joerogan/status/1755735654225334432?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 8, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Since launching in December 2009, Rogan's podcast has involved candid and varied discussions on topics like politics, health, and society. In recent years it has gained notoriety through Rogan's practice of inviting guests that hold extreme or unconventional views. The show has also faced significant criticism for spreading misinformation and giving a platform to divisive figures.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/joe-rogan-experience-apple-podcasts/">&#039;The Joe Rogan Experience&#039; Returns to Apple Podcasts After 3-Year Hiatus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-joe-rogan-experience-returns-to-apple-podcasts-after-3-year-hiatus.2418999/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Starts Letting Developers Add Alternative App Marketplaces to App Store Connect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/app-store-connect-alternative-app-marketplaces/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-starts-letting-developers-add-alternative-app-marketplaces-to-app-store-connect.2418959/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 14:17:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/app-store-connect-alternative-app-marketplaces/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		<category>App Store Connect</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[EU developers can now add alternative app marketplaces to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> Connect, <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/releases/">Apple said today</a>. Apple is also accepting submissions for the Notarization process, which is required for all apps that will be distributed through alternative marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
Apple is making these changes to &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect ahead of the launch of iOS 17.4, an update that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">overhauls the app ecosystem in the European Union</a>. Alternative app marketplaces are special iOS apps that can be downloaded onto an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from a website or a web browser, serving as an alternative to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. App marketplaces are able to distribute iOS apps, giving developers a way to sell their apps without using the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Both alternative marketplaces and apps that are added to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; through one of the marketplaces are checked over by Apple to prevent malware, viruses, and similar malicious content.<br/>
<br/>
To add an alternative app marketplace or submit an app for Notarization, developers must <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=e59yuu15">agree to Apple's new business terms</a>. The business terms include a Core Technology Fee that requires app marketplaces to pay .50 euros per install, and apps to pay the same fee after 1 million installs.<br/>
<br/>
With alternative app marketplaces able to be added to &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Connect, marketplace distribution and marketplace apps can be set up, and TestFlight can be used to beta test new features.<br/>
<br/>
TestFlight also supports apps that use alternative browser engines and alternative payments through third-party payment providers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store-connect/">App Store Connect</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/app-store-connect-alternative-app-marketplaces/">Apple Starts Letting Developers Add Alternative App Marketplaces to App Store Connect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-starts-letting-developers-add-alternative-app-marketplaces-to-app-store-connect.2418959/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing Improved Vision Pro Personas in visionOS 1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/testing-personas-visionos-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-improved-vision-pro-personas-in-visionos-1-1.2418951/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 13:14:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/testing-personas-visionos-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is currently testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1, the first major update to the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; operating system that runs on the Vision Pro. &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 updates Personas, and multiple reports suggest the software makes Personas look better than before. We thought we'd take a closer look at Personas in &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1, comparing the update to the prior &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.0.2 software.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xEixxDkYXlo" title="Apple Vision Pro Persona FIXED in visionOS 1.1?" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Personas are a key feature on the Vision Pro, representing the user in video calls on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, Zoom, and other platforms. Personas are a digital representation of the Vision Pro wearer, and are captured using the headset itself. With the Vision Pro, the wearer takes a 3D facial scan that captures their facial structure, expressions, hand movements, and more. Apple describes a Persona as an "authentic spatial representation" of a person.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released Personas in a beta capacity, and it's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/31/apple-vision-pro-personas-deeply-weird/">not hard to see why</a> with the Personas that have been shared on the initial versions of the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; software. Reviewers have called personas "deeply weird," "deep in the uncanny valley," "ridiculous," and "frightening."<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1, Personas have more natural looking eyes, skin tone improvements, and more detail that adds realism, though Apple's scanning feature still struggles with hair.<br/>
<br/>
Most Personas are noticeably better with the 1.1 update, but Apple still needs to do a lot of work to eliminate the otherworldly, unnatural vibe that the virtual representations give off. &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 is available to developers in beta right now, and it will likely see a launch in March alongside iOS 17.4.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds Contact Key Verification, support for resetting the headset without a computer, and support for mobile device management.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/testing-personas-visionos-1-1/">Testing Improved Vision Pro Personas in visionOS 1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-improved-vision-pro-personas-in-visionos-1-1.2418951/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tesla App Gains Ultra Wideband Support to Improve Phone Keys</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/tesla-app-ultra-wideband/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tesla-app-gains-ultra-wideband-support-to-improve-phone-keys.2418945/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 12:53:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/tesla-app-ultra-wideband/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Tesla</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The latest Tesla software adds Ultra Wideband support (UWB) to improve the function of the built-in Phone Key feature in the Tesla app (via <em><a href="https://teslanorth.com/2024/02/08/tesla-phone-key-iphone-ultra-wideband/">Tesla North</a></em>). Tesla owners can use Phone Key to lock and unlock their vehicles without a physical key.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/tesla-red-orange-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1560" height="827" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-776244" /><br/>
Ultra Wideband support provides more precise tracking capabilities than Bluetooth, which means the Phone Key feature will better recognize when an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> is near a vehicle to unlock/lock it at the appropriate time. From the release notes:<br/>
<blockquote>Ultrawide band (UWB) technology is now available for Phone Key. So your vehicle and Phone Key can communicate with greater accuracy to more responsively lock, unlock, and open Automatic Doors.</blockquote><br/>
Tesla owners will need both a vehicle that supports Ultra Wideband and an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; with Ultra Wideband to take advantage of the new capabilities. Enabling the updated UWB key requires going to the Phone Key section of the Tesla app (which must be upgraded to version 4.29.5) and following the upgrade steps.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tesla/">Tesla</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/tesla-app-ultra-wideband/">Tesla App Gains Ultra Wideband Support to Improve Phone Keys</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tesla-app-gains-ultra-wideband-support-to-improve-phone-keys.2418945/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.3.1 With Fix for Text Overlapping Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-1-with-fix-for-text-overlapping-bug.2418933/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:53:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3.1, a minor update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that came out last September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3.1 comes a few weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3/">release of macOS Sonoma 14.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
The ‌‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj;‌ 14.3‌.1 update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update addresses a frustrating &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; bug that could cause text to get randomly replaced while typing. There have been <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-text-typing-bug-where-text-gets-randomly-replaced.2407661/">multiple complaints about the issue</a>, which affected web pages and apps like Mail and Messages.<br/>
<br/>
The problem has persisted for several months, and has been an issue through multiple versions of Sonoma.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-1/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.3.1 With Fix for Text Overlapping Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-1-with-fix-for-text-overlapping-bug.2418933/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases watchOS 10.3.1 With Bug Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-1-with-bug-fixes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-1-with-bug-fixes.2418931/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:34:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-1-with-bug-fixes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.3.1, a minor update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/apple-releases-watchos-10/">released in September</a>. watchOS 10.3.1 comes a few weeks after the launch of watchOS 10.3, an update that brought a new watch face.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌.3.1 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General &amp; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the watchOS 10.3.1 update adds unspecified "improvements and bug fixes."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-1-with-bug-fixes/">Apple Releases watchOS 10.3.1 With Bug Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-3-1-with-bug-fixes.2418931/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.3.1 With Fix for Text Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug.2418927/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 10:25:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.3.1 and iPadOS 17.3.1, minor updates for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and iPadOS operating systems that were released in September 2023. iOS 17.3.1 and iPadOS 17.3.1 comes a few weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-ios-17-3/">Apple released iOS 17.3</a> with Stolen Device Protection.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-17.3.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935028" /><br/>
iOS 17.3.1 and iPadOS 17.3.1 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings > General > Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's release notes, the update includes a fix for a bug that could cause text to unexpectedly duplicate or overlap while typing.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug/">Apple Releases iOS 17.3.1 With Fix for Text Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-3-1-with-fix-for-text-bug.2418927/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Fake LastPass App Sneaks Past Apple&#039;s Review Team</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/fake-lastpass-app-in-apple-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fake-lastpass-app-sneaks-past-apples-review-team.2418924/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:57:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/fake-lastpass-app-in-apple-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>LastPass</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular password management app LastPass <a href="https://blog.lastpass.com/2024/02/warning-fraudulent-app-impersonating-lastpass-currently-available-in-apple-app-store/">is warning customers</a> about a fraudulent app that uses a similar name and icon to attempt to trick LastPass customers into using the fake app instead of the real app (via <em><a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/fake-lastpass-password-manager-spotted-on-apples-app-store/">Bleeping Computer</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/lasspass-fake-password-manager-app.jpg" alt="" width="2838" height="1596" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935681" /><br/>
The "LassPass Password Manager" app was somehow approved by Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> review team, even though it appears to clearly mimic the LastPass app. It doesn't use exactly the same icon and the name is a letter off, but the similarities could confuse some LastPass users.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if the fake LassPass app is attempting to steal login information from users, but it does have options for adding passwords, email accounts, addresses, bank accounts, credit cards, debit cards, and more. It doesn't ask for a LastPass login of any kind, but it is possible that the developer can see information added to the app.<br/>
<br/>
There is also a "PRO" upgrade that costs &#36;1.99 per month, &#36;9.99 per year, or &#36;49.99 for a "lifetime" subscription, so the aim of the app may be collecting subscription money from customers. Either way, LastPass users should be aware of the fake app and should avoid it. At best it is aiming to steal money, and at worst, it is stealing passwords and credit card information.<br/>
<br/>
Clone apps often make their way into the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but the app impersonating LastPass is particularly concerning because it could be accessing sensitive information. It is not clear how an app mimicking one of the most popular password management apps was approved by Apple, and its discovery comes at a critical time for the company.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/phil-schiller-on-risks-of-iphone-app-marketplaces/">promoting the safety and security</a> of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; as it prepares to allow for alternate app marketplaces in the European Union, and allowing a fake password management app onto the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is not a good look.<br/>
<br/>
LastPass contacted Apple to get the clone app removed from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and it was pulled at around 11:00 a.m. Pacific Time on February 8. <br/>
Apple removed the fraudulent LassPass app because it violated the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rule preventing copycat apps. The developer has also been removed from the Apple Developer Program and won't be able to submit future apps. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lastpass/">LastPass</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/fake-lastpass-app-in-apple-app-store/">Fake LastPass App Sneaks Past Apple&#039;s Review Team</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fake-lastpass-app-sneaks-past-apples-review-team.2418924/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Mini Film Promoting Upcoming Apple Music Halftime Show Starring Usher</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-music-usher-mini-film/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-mini-film-promoting-upcoming-apple-music-halftime-show-starring-usher.2418923/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2024 09:17:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-music-usher-mini-film/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to hype the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> Super Bowl Halftime Show that's set to air this weekend, with the company sharing a full mini film for its "Where's Usher?" ad campaign.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Where's Usher? Apple Music Super Bowl LVIII Halftime Show (Official Film)" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bdfh6ZUvwVw" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Yesterday, Apple shared a small teaser of the skit starring Ludacris, Lil Jon, Taraji P. Henson, and Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, but today the full 7-minute spot is available to watch on YouTube. Additional stars show up in the longer version, including Wesley Snipes, J Balvin, Anderson .Paak, Blue Man Group, and Criss Angel.<br/>
<br/>
In the promo, the main trio continue their search for Usher in Las Vegas, ultimately locating him doing an impromptu performance in the Caesars Palace fountain.<br/>
<br/>
Usher will headline the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Halftime Show for Super Bowl LVIII, which takes place at the Allegiant Stadium in Las Vegas on Sunday, February 11.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/apple-music-usher-mini-film/">Apple Shares Mini Film Promoting Upcoming Apple Music Halftime Show Starring Usher</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-mini-film-promoting-upcoming-apple-music-halftime-show-starring-usher.2418923/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
