<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 04:04:22 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music vs. Spotify Buyer&#039;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-vs-spotify-buyers-guide/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-vs-spotify-buyers-guide.2418272/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 00:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-vs-spotify-buyers-guide&#038;post_date=1706958000/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and Spotify overwhelmingly dominate the music streaming space, but the two services offer surprisingly different experiences despite their competitive pricing, so which is best?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Music-vs-Spotify-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-930264" /><br/>
While Spotify has been around for longer than &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, both services are now very widely adopted. &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and Spotify have similar libraries with over 100 million songs, with features like personalized playlists, live lyrics, collaboration, crossfade, and SharePlay support, making it all the more difficult to choose between them. Read on for a detailed comparison to help you choose the music streaming service that's best for you.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>Spotify</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Advanced library management, allowing users to curate a collection of music with a wide range of sorting options</td><br/>
 <td>No "library;" add songs to a playlist of liked tracks instead</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Basic music discovery algorithm</td><br/>
 <td>Advanced music discovery algorithm</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Limited personalization comprising "New Music Mix," "Get Up Mix," "Chill Mix," and a personal radio station</td><br/>
 <td>Personalized mixes including "Release Radar," "Discover Weekly," and "Tastebreakers," in addition to thousands of algorithmic playlists that are tailored to the user</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Emphasis on human-curated playlists, with limited use of algorithmic playlists</td><br/>
 <td>Emphasis on advanced algorithmic playlists</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Occasionally offers exclusive releases from major artists</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Spatial Audio with Dolby Atmos for a virtual surround sound experience with supported songs</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lossless Audio up to 24-bit/192 kHz</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Apple Digital Masters specification</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; 1, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Hits, and &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Country radio with live DJs, interviews, specials and show archive</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>In-app music videos</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>In-app podcasts and audiobooks</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical app based on Primephonic</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Sing karaoke experience</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Limited social sharing options</td><br/>
 <td>Comprehensive social sharing options, such as the ability to see what friends are listening to in real-time</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Replay year-long retrospective experience with limited social media support</td><br/>
 <td>Spotify Wrapped end-of-year retrospective experience with better social media support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Closely integrated with the Apple ecosystem, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, Vision Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, and Apple Fitness+</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available on all Apple devices and Android, as well as some games consoles and TVs</td><br/>
 <td>Available across a wide range of devices, including non-Apple ones, but no support for &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; and Vision Pro</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Known for user-friendly, cross-platform design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Ability to control Spotify on one device from another</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Integration with existing iTunes libraries, allowing users to merge a personal music collection with the streaming library and upload and stream tracks that aren't in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; library</td><br/>
 <td>Ability to play local audio files</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Listen to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; 1, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Hits, or &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Country for free</td><br/>
 <td>Full library access and shuffled playlists with ads for free</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>Individual subscription</strong>: &#36;10.99/month<br/>
<strong>Student subscription</strong>: &#36;5.99/month<br/>
<strong>Family subscription</strong>: &#36;16.99/month</td><br/>
 <td><strong>Individual subscription</strong>: &#36;10.99/month<br/>
<strong>Student subscription</strong>: &#36;5.99/month<br/>
<strong>"Duo" household subscription</strong>: &#36;14.99/month<br/>
<strong>Family subscription</strong>: &#36;16.99/month</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Included in all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundle tiers</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Both &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and Spotify boast extensive music libraries, sophisticated personalization features, and comparable subscription models, but the nuances of their offerings cater to slightly different audiences. When choosing between the services, you should decide which of the two following groups you fall into.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; touts a seamless and feature-rich listening experience for Apple device users, offering particular advantages to those who are heavily embedded in Apple's ecosystem. The service is particularly appealing to audiophiles and those invested in high-quality audio, thanks to features like Lossless Audio and Spatial Audio. &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;'s exclusive content, such as live radio shows and the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Classical app, provides unique value to those seeking more than just a vast music library. &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; is the preferred choice for users who appreciate the convenience of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; integration, conventional library management, the ability to merge their own music library with the streaming service, and who are possibly already subscribed to other Apple services, making the &zwnj;Apple One&zwnj; bundle an attractive proposition.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify, on the other hand, excels in music discovery and social sharing. Its sophisticated algorithms that power features like Discover Weekly and Release Radar are unmatched for surfacing new music tailored to the listener's tastes. Spotify's cross-platform design and compatibility with a wide range of devices make it a versatile option for users with a diverse range of hardware. The service's superior social features, such as the ability to see what friends are listening to in real-time, enrich the music discovery process. Spotify is the go-to choice for users who value these social and discovery aspects highly, as well as those who appreciate the option of a free, ad-supported tier.<br/>
<br/>
Which music streaming service do you prefer and why? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-vs-spotify-buyers-guide/">Apple Music vs. Spotify Buyer&#039;s Guide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-vs-spotify-buyers-guide.2418272/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Use These Bluetooth Accessories With Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-bluetooth-accessories/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-use-these-bluetooth-accessories-with-apple-vision-pro.2418242/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:44:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-bluetooth-accessories&#038;post_date=1706935440/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> supports Bluetooth, Apple said today <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213998">in a support document</a> that there is no guarantee that third-party Bluetooth accessories and devices will be compatible. Apple did, however, provide information on what will work for sure.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/mac-magic-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836750" /><br/>
<h2 id="airpodsbeats">AirPods/Beats</h2><br/>
All current models of AirPods and Beats headphones are able to connect to the Vision Pro. Apple recommends the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with USB-C Charging Case for the best experience because it supports Lossless Audio and ultra-low latency, while older AirPods models do not.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="keyboards">Keyboards</h2><br/>
Most Bluetooth keyboards made by Apple and other manufacturers will work with the Vision Pro. The Vision Pro is not compatible with older Apple keyboards that use removable batteries.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro has a virtual keyboard that can be used, but for anything beyond entering a password or typing a quick message, users will want a Bluetooth keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mice_and_trackpads">Mice and Trackpads</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; does not work with Bluetooth mice at all. It does work with the Apple Magic Trackpad, but older Trackpads with removable batteries are not compatible, nor are trackpads from other manufacturers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="controllers">Controllers</h2><br/>
All Made for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Bluetooth controllers can connect to the Vision Pro, including Xbox and PlayStation controllers. Apple says that any controller that works with iPadOS will work with Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="hearing_devices">Hearing Devices</h2><br/>
Made for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; hearing devices are able to connect to the Vision Pro. Some models by Phonak, IQBud, and Poco are also compatible with the headset.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-bluetooth-accessories/">You Can Use These Bluetooth Accessories With Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-use-these-bluetooth-accessories-with-apple-vision-pro.2418242/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What You Need to Know About Traveling With Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-travel/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-you-need-to-know-about-traveling-with-apple-vision-pro.2418238/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 17:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-travel&#038;post_date=1706933040/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Traveling is perhaps one of the best uses of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset, as it can be used on airplanes and has a specific Travel Mode. Apple today published several support documents that provide some important details on <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214004">traveling with the Vision Pro</a>, activating the built-in Travel Mode, and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214004">storing it</a> when it's not in use.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Travel-Mode.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930973" /><br/>
<h2 id="how_to_travel_with_vision_pro">How to Travel With Vision Pro</h2><br/>
The cover that comes with the Vision Pro should be placed on it to protect the glass before it is packed up, but Apple says users should also make sure there are no loose objects like keys or coins nearby that could scratch the internal displays.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recommends the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; Travel Case, which is &#36;200, a soft padded bag, or a "similar protective solution" to protect the Vision Pro from impacts and "excessive vibration." Apple's Travel Case is rather large, so it might be difficult to bring as a carry-on because of the space that it takes up.<br/>
<br/>
If the Vision Pro won't be used for an extended period, it should be disconnected from the battery, and Apple says that the ZEISS Optical Inserts should be packed separately so they don't accidentally detach.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="how_to_use_vision_pro_in_travel_mode">How to Use Vision Pro in Travel Mode</h2><br/>
Travel Mode is specifically designed for using the Vision Pro while on a flight. It can be activated from the Control Center by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Look up and then tap on the arrow near the top of the display to open Control Center.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the Control Center button to see more options.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the Travel Mode button.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap Turn on Travel Mode to confirm.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Exiting Travel Mode can be done by going back to Control Center and tapping "Turn Off."<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the Vision Pro cannot be set up on an airplane, and also Personas are not available when Travel Mode is turned on.<br/>
<h2 id="travel_mode_tips">Travel Mode Tips</h2><br/>
Apple says that users should follow these guidelines when using Travel Mode:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Remain seated while Travel Mode is on, and remove the Vision Pro before standing up. Features that help you stay aware of your surroundings are disabled when Travel Mode is activated.</li><br/>
 <li>Take off the Vision Pro during taxiing, takeoff, and landing. Also remove it if there is turbulence on the flight.</li><br/>
 <li>Avoid looking out the airplane's windows, because it can impact the Vision Pro's ability to detect your surroundings.</li><br/>
 <li>If content appears tilted or off-center, long-press on the Digital Crown to re-center the view.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="storing_vision_pro">Storing Vision Pro</h2><br/>
If the Vision Pro is not going to be in use for a while, Apple recommends taking these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Attach the cover to the Vision Pro to prevent dust accumulation or damage, but make sure the cover is clean and free of debris first.</li><br/>
 <li>Disconnect the battery.</li><br/>
 <li>Place the Vision Pro on a stable, flat surface with the cover glass facing forward. Do not put the Vision Pro facing downward. Alternatively, place it in the Vision Pro Travel Case.</li><br/>
 <li>The Vision Pro can withstand temperatures ranging from -4ยบ to 113ยบ F. It should not be stored in areas that exceed this range.</li><br/>
 <li>Do not leave the Vision Pro in a car because temperatures in parked cars can get too warm.</li><br/>
 <li>Do not leave the Vision Pro in direct sunlight for any length of time.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure the relative humidity of where the Vision Pro is stored is between 0 percent and 95 percent.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
In day to day usage, Apple also suggests that users put the cover back on the Vision Pro whenever it's not being worn. Apple also warns against placing the Vision Pro with the glass facing downward, and says to put it on the polishing cloth rather than any rough or abrasive surface.<br/>
<br/>
Picking up the Vision Pro should always be done with two hands, and it should never be picked up by the Light Seal or Audio Straps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-travel/">What You Need to Know About Traveling With Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-you-need-to-know-about-traveling-with-apple-vision-pro.2418238/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Not Fitting Well? Here Are Apple&#039;s Tips for Improving It</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-fit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-not-fitting-well-here-are-apples-tips-for-improving-it.2418233/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:26:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-fit&#038;post_date=1706930783/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Fit is the most important aspect of the Vision Pro, because if it's not on your head in the right way, it will feel heavy and uncomfortable, plus the displays might look blurry. Apple today published several support documents on <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117730">getting a good fit</a> with the Vision Pro and what to do if you have <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213953">light leakage</a>, <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214019">eye setup issues</a>, and other problems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Teal-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929939" /><br/>
<h2 id="selecting_a_band">Selecting a Band</h2><br/>
There are two bands for the Vision Pro, the Solo Knit Band and the Dual Loop Band. With either band, the Vision Pro should feel balanced across the cheeks and forehead, and it should be snug but not too tight. A head band that is too tight can cause skin sensitivity, general discomfort, or marks and indentations on the face, but Apple says that some "temporary, light markings" are expected after general usage.<br/>
<br/>
Users should select the band that feels the most comfortable, and then adjust from there.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="solo_knit_band_adjustments">Solo Knit Band Adjustments</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Rotate the Fit Dial counterclockwise and pull the device by the frame away from the face to loosen the band if it's too tight. If it won't loosen enough, you might need a larger size.</li><br/>
 <li>If the band feels too loose, turn it clockwise to tighten it. If it won't tighten more, a different size might be required.</li><br/>
 <li>If you feel pressure on your forehead, raise the Solo Knit Band by pulling it up slightly on the back of the head.</li><br/>
 <li>To fix pressure on the cheeks, lower the Solo Knit Band by pulling it slightly down on the back of the head.</li><br/>
 <li>To relieve pressure across the bridge of the nose, swap to the Light Cushion marked with a + or use the Dual Loop Band.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="dual_loop_band_adjustments">Dual Loop Band Adjustments</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>If the head band is too tight, hold the Vision Pro to your face and loosen the upper and lower straps of the Dual Loop Band with the other hand. Pull the device by the frame away from your face.</li><br/>
 <li>To relieve pressure on the forehead, hold the frame, loosen the lower strap, and tighten the upper strap.</li><br/>
 <li>To relieve pressure on the cheeks, hold the frame, pull down the lower strap, and loosen the upper strap.</li><br/>
 <li>To relieve pressure across the bridge of the nose, swap to the Light Cushion marked with a + or use the Solo Knit Band.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="light_seal_cushion_fit">Light Seal Cushion Fit</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>If your eyelashes brush against the Vision Pro or you get a notification that your eyes are too close, swap to the Light Cushion marked with a +. If that does not fix it, a different Light Seal size might be required.</li><br/>
 <li>If your eyes are too far from the displays, swap to the thinner Light Seal Cushion. If that does not work, a different Light Seal Size might be required.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="realign_displays">Realign Displays</h2><br/>
If you feel pressure on the bridge of your nose and adjustments to the band don't help, Apple suggests using the Realign Displays feature under Settings > Eyes and Hands.<br/>
<br/>
To move the displays slightly away from the nose, press the Top Button to move the displays outward. Press and hold the Digital Crown to move the displays inwards for ideal visual alignment.<br/>
<h2 id="fixing_light_leakage">Fixing Light Leakage</h2><br/>
Apple says to determine whether you're experiencing light leakage, you should use the Vision Pro in both a brightly lit and dimly lit room.<br/>
<br/>
If the Vision Pro experience improves in a dimly lit room, there is a light leakage problem that needs to be addressed by adjusting the fit of the Vision Pro head band or choosing a different Light Seal Cushion.<br/>
<br/>
If the dimly lit room does not improve the experience, Apple says there may be light originating from the display causing some reflections within the optical system.<br/>
<br/>
Some light leakage around the nose is normal.<br/>
<h2 id="tips_for_getting_a_good_fit">Tips for Getting a Good Fit</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple suggests that facial jewelry like nose rings or eyebrow rings should be removed before you put on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>.</li><br/>
 <li>Uneven facial discomfort, such as pressure on the forehead, cheeks, or nose, is an indication that a different Light Seal or Light Seal Cushion might be required. Other signs include light leakage, eyelashes brushing on the display, and alerts about eye position.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure that hair does not get caught in either the band or the cable to avoid tugging.</li><br/>
 <li>The Vision Pro is not designed to be worn by children under the age of 13 and it may not fit.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="solving_eye_setup_issues">Solving Eye Setup Issues</h2><br/>
If the Vision Pro eye setup feature cannot be completed, Apple has several solutions.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Ensure that the fit is correct and follow the directions of any alerts that are shown on the display.</li><br/>
 <li>If you're experiencing issues with eye setup, Apple warns that eyelash extensions and items near the eyes like rhinestones or glitter can cause problems.</li><br/>
 <li>Eyes that are too wet or too dry might impact eye setup.</li><br/>
 <li>Debris on the Vision Pro display or ZEISS Optical Inserts can cause issues.</li><br/>
 <li>Cosmetic contact lenses are not compatible with Vision Pro and need to be removed.</li><br/>
 <li>Hard contact lenses might not work with Vision Pro.</li><br/>
 <li>Medical conditions like eyelid drooping, changes in eye alignment, or uncontrolled eye movements can make it difficult for the Vision Pro to detect your eyes. There are <a href="https://support.apple.com/guide/apple-vision-pro/get-started-with-accessibility-features-tan426c48bdc/visionos">several Accessibility features</a> that can help.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="more_help">More Help</h2><br/>
Apple says that if the fit tips do not help, that users should visit a local <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> to get help. It is important to do this quickly because the exchange process must begin within 14 days of receiving the Vision Pro and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-fit/">Vision Pro Not Fitting Well? Here Are Apple&#039;s Tips for Improving It</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-not-fitting-well-here-are-apples-tips-for-improving-it.2418233/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>App Developers Can Now Sign Up for Consultations on Complicated EU App Ecosystem Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/app-developers-consultations-eu-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-developers-can-now-sign-up-for-consultations-on-complicated-eu-app-ecosystem-changes.2418232/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 16:22:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/app-developers-consultations-eu-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=tr8v670x">this week announced</a> that developers can sign up to meet with an Apple team member to discuss the changes being made to iOS, Safari, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-ios-app-store-safari-changes.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933983" /><br/>
Developers can request a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/events/view/upcoming-events?q=Request%20a%20consultation%20about%20the%20changes%20to%20apps%20distributed%20in%20the%20European%20Union">30-minute online consultation</a> to ask questions and provide feedback about Apple's changes. Topics of discussion include alternative distribution on iOS, alternative payments in the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, linking out to purchases on a webpage, new business terms, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also offering in-person labs in Cork, Ireland for those who are interested in starting an alternative app marketplace.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">making sweeping changes</a> to the app ecosystem in the European Union in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act. Alternative app marketplaces can be used to install apps on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and Apple is supporting alternative payment methods in apps across all of its App Stores.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/app-developers-consultations-eu-changes/">App Developers Can Now Sign Up for Consultations on Complicated EU App Ecosystem Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/app-developers-can-now-sign-up-for-consultations-on-complicated-eu-app-ecosystem-changes.2418232/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Are the Gestures Used to Control Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-gestures/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-the-gestures-used-to-control-vision-pro.2418231/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:38:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-gestures&#038;post_date=1706927921/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of the Vision Pro, Apple published plenty of support documents and tutorials, including an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117741">overview of the gestures</a> used to control the headset. Most people have found the gesture-based control to be intuitive, but for those having difficulty, Apple also has some tips on getting the best experience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-vision-pro-gestures.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934311" /><br/>
<h2 id="vision_pro_gestures">Vision Pro Gestures</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong>Tap Fingers Together</strong> - To select an item on the Vision Pro, look at it and then tap your thumb and index finger together. Apple says this is the equivalent of tapping something on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or clicking something on the Mac.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Pinch and Drag</strong> - Moving items on Vision Pro can be done by looking at an item and then pinching your thumb and index finger together. Pinch and hold while moving the item, and then let go. Pinching and dragging is used for arranging apps, resizing windows, scrolling, and dragging things from one app to another.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Pinch and Flick</strong> - Scrolling through content quickly can be done by pinching your thumb and index finger together and then flicking the wrist up or down in a smooth motion. This gesture is used for moving horizontally through apps in the Home View, scrolling long web pages, and browsing images in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Pinch for Options</strong> - If you pinch and hold on an item in Vision Pro, you can bring up a list of items. Just look at an item, tap your thumb and index finger together, and hold. Once the options appear, you can let go and then tap to select the preferred option.</li><br/>
 <li><strong>Touch</strong> - There are elements in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> that can be interacted with directly with the fingers. The virtual keyboard is one such example, as typing can be done by touching on the keys with one finger on each hand.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="gesture_tips">Gesture Tips</h2><br/>
For the best experience with Vision Pro, Apple recommends using it in a well-lit room, without long sleeves or large jewelry, and with your hands visible.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Make sure to use Vision Pro in a well-lit area and ensure that the front of the device is clean and free of smudges so that the outward-facing cameras can see your hands.</li><br/>
 <li>Keep your hands resting comfortably in your lap - there is no need to hold your arm up.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure your hands are visible and not hidden under a desk or blanket.</li><br/>
 <li>Gloves, long sleeves, and large jewelry that covers a significant part or all of the hand can interfere with Vision Pro gesture tracking.</li><br/>
 <li>Don't cross your hands or cover up your gesturing hand with your other hand.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are also a range of Accessibility features that can be used for improving the Vision Pro experience in certain cases, with details available on <a href="https://support.apple.com/guide/apple-vision-pro/get-started-with-accessibility-features-tan426c48bdc/visionos">Apple's support website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-gestures/">These Are the Gestures Used to Control Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-the-gestures-used-to-control-vision-pro.2418231/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Provides Tips For Making Your Persona Look Better</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-persona-tips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-tips-for-making-your-persona-look-better.2418224/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 15:06:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-persona-tips&#038;post_date=1706926018/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple designed the Vision Pro to use a "Persona" or a digital representation of the wearer in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, Zoom, and other video apps. Apple says that the Persona is meant to be a "dynamic, natural representation" of the user's face, but many people have found it to be anything but natural.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/dan-persona-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934314" /><br/>
In fact, many reviewers found the Personas to be creepy, weird, and off-putting because of the uncanny valley experience, and that may be why Apple has only released Personas in a beta capacity. Apple today provided instructions on setting up a Persona, complete with tips on how to get the best result.<br/>
<br/>
You can watch <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan set up a Persona below, but it's basically as simple as tapping on Persona in Settings and following the instructions. Making a Persona uses the Vision Pro's camera and captures the user's face and facial expressions.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Cnvhrc5UEY" title="Apple Vision Pro: Unboxing &amp; Hands-On (It&#39;s INCREDIBLE)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Here's what Apple says Vision Pro owners can do to make the best Persona:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Take your time getting ready. Capture will not start until the Vision Pro is at eye level.</li><br/>
 <li>Use front-facing, even lighting. Do not have bright windows or lamps behind or beside you. The Vision Pro may prompt you to adjust lighting.</li><br/>
 <li>Ensure your face is well-lit with no strong shadows.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure your hair is not covering your face.</li><br/>
 <li>Use a simple background and stay away from nearby objects like chair backs and lamps.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure there are no people behind you.</li><br/>
 <li>Make sure the Vision Pro is held horizontally at eye level throughout the capture.</li><br/>
 <li>When asked to smile, make as large and natural a smile as you can.</li><br/>
 <li>If you're not able to perform one of the expressions, such as raising an eyebrow or smiling with teeth, double clicking on the Digital Crown will skip the expression.</li><br/>
 <li>Hats, earrings, AirPods, and other items might not be captured fully. They will need to be removed and the Persona will need to be redone if they don't look right.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If your Persona does not come out as expected, you can redo the process and change variables until it looks better. Note that glasses cannot be captured, and must be added afterward through Apple's pre-selected styles.<br/>
<br/>
Different lighting options can be applied to a Persona, including Natural, Studio, or Contour. There are also settings to adjust the temperature and brightness of the Persona.<br/>
<br/>
When you capture your Persona, Apple is also capturing your eyes for the EyeSight feature that shows the wearer's eyes when other people are nearby.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-persona-tips/">Apple Provides Tips For Making Your Persona Look Better</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-provides-tips-for-making-your-persona-look-better.2418224/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling &#36;300 Developer Strap for Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-selling-vision-pro-developer-strap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-300-developer-strap-for-vision-pro.2418217/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 14:10:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-selling-vision-pro-developer-strap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Through its Developer website, Apple is offering a &#36;300 "Developer Strap" for the Vision Pro, which provides a USB-C connection between the headset and a Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-developer-strap.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1404" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934307" /><br/>
Apple says that the Developer Strap is helpful for "accelerating the development of graphics-intensive apps and games." It is designed to provide the same audio experience as the standard Right Audio Strap, so it can be used for both development and testing.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <a href="https://daringfireball.net/linked/2024/02/02/vision-pro-developer-strap"><em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber</a>, the Developer Strap is only available to developers who are logged in to a paid U.S. Apple Developer account.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier today, we shared images of the Developer Strap in Apple's documentation. Apple will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-developer-strap-diagnostics-mode/">use the accessory for diagnostics</a> in Apple retail locations.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-selling-vision-pro-developer-strap/">Apple Now Selling &#36;300 Developer Strap for Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-300-developer-strap-for-vision-pro.2418217/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook Compares Vision Pro &#039;Moment&#039; to iPhone and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/tim-cook-on-vision-pro-moment/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-compares-vision-pro-moment-to-iphone-and-mac.2418214/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:38:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/tim-cook-on-vision-pro-moment/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> today sent out a memo to employees, thanking them for their work on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset that was introduced today. In the memo, which was shared by <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-02/apple-fans-line-up-for-headset-as-spatial-computing-era-begins">Bloomberg</a></em>, Cook compared the Vision Pro to the Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Apple Watch, and said that it is joining Apple's "pantheon of groundbreaking products" that have both "defined Apple" and "redefined technology as we know it."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898552" /><br/>
Cook visited <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> Fifth Avenue in New York for the Vision Pro launch, and he said it was "incredible" to watch people try out the Vision Pro for the first time and see the "impossible become possible."<br/>
<br/>
According to Cook, this is "just the beginning" of spatial computing and the impact that Apple will make with the Vision Pro. Apple believes that "incredible opportunities" are still ahead.<br/>
<blockquote>Today we launched Apple Vision Pro, introducing an entirely new era of spatial computing. Moments like this should make us all pause -- to celebrate what we've achieved and reflect on the amazing potential that still lies ahead.<br/>
<br/>
This morning I was with our team at Apple Fifth Avenue, where the excitement for this moment was palpable. It's an incredible thing to watch people experience Apple Vision Pro for the very first time. The impossible becomes possible right before their eyes, and often they don't have the words to describe the experience. It really is a technology you have to see -- and see through -- to believe. And it was truly a gift to hear customers share their amazement, their emotion, and their dreams for this incredible device we've created. The whole experience reaffirmed the magnitude of this moment, as well as our Retail teams' vital role in delivering this unprecedented technology to the world.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Vision Pro brings together thousands of innovations to create a product that's like nothing the world has ever seen before. It's an extraordinary achievement, and as so many of you can attest, it has been years in the making. Apple Vision Pro is a reality thanks to you -- thanks to your commitment, your passion, and your contributions to the special culture that drives innovation at Apple. I especially want to thank all of the teams that have been dedicated to this project, who poured in countless hours over many years to yet again push the boundaries of what is possible.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, for us, the most important thing about Apple Vision Pro is how it enriches our customers' lives -- strengthening connection, unlocking potential, and empowering people to accomplish things that simply wouldn't be possible any other way. It's profoundly moving to think of people reliving their most treasured memories, or even introducing a loved one to a relative they never had the chance to meet. It's exhilarating to imagine the unbelievable new entertainment experiences our customers will discover, and the innovative apps our amazing developers will create. It's exciting to think of everything this unlocks for industries the world over, and of the incredible opportunities that still lie ahead. Because with spatial computing, this is just the beginning of the impact we can make.<br/>
<br/>
Two weeks ago we celebrated the 40th anniversary of the Mac, a revolutionary device that transformed the world and laid the foundation for decades of innovation. When we shared iPod with the world, we put a thousand songs in our customers' pockets overnight. I remember the day we launched iPhone. We knew we had something special, but none of us could have foreseen its profound impact on our everyday lives. Then came iPad, a magical sheet of glass that becomes anything you want it to be, fostering new forms of connection and creativity for millions of people. With Apple Watch, there isn't a day that goes by I don't get a note from a user about its lifesaving impact. And now with today's launch, Apple Vision Pro joins the pantheon of groundbreaking products that have defined Apple and redefined technology as we know it.<br/>
<br/>
It's not every day we have a moment like this one. Thank you for all you've done to make it possible.</blockquote><br/>
Cook also did a quick interview with Good Morning America this morning, where he further explained the impact he thinks the Vision Pro will have. "The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; introduced us to mobile computing, the Mac introduced us to personal computing, this is the first spatial computer," he said. "People are going to interact with it in different ways."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Tim Cook talks new Apple Vision Pro" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Fd5wv3hrd3s" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
"A company only has a few of these," Cook continued. "Most companies have none. We've had the Mac, the iPod, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the Apple Watch, and now the Vision Pro. It's one of those moments."<br/>
<br/>
On the price, Cook went on to explain that it's "tomorrow's technology today," and that it's packed with 5,000 patents. "We think we priced it for the right value today," said Cook.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; is available at U.S. Apple Stores as of today, and some retail locations do have stock available for walk-in purchases. The device is priced starting at &#36;3,500.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/tim-cook-on-vision-pro-moment/">Apple CEO Tim Cook Compares Vision Pro &#039;Moment&#039; to iPhone and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-compares-vision-pro-moment-to-iphone-and-mac.2418214/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Developer Strap and Diagnostics Mode Revealed in More Detail</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-developer-strap-diagnostics-mode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pros-developer-strap-and-diagnostics-mode-revealed-in-more-detail.2418210/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 13:21:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-developer-strap-diagnostics-mode/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Code discovered by <em>MacRumors</em> reveals a clearer look at how Apple stores will support Vision Pro headsets that are in need of servicing or support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/vision-pro-developer-strap-diagnostics.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934278" /><br/>
Back in June, Apple published its "Platform State Of The Union" video for developers, and multiple times throughout that video, a Vision Pro with a mysterious USB-C adapter could be seen, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/09/vision-pro-usb-c-adapter/">leading to speculation as to what it could be</a>. <br/>
<br/>
A recent update to one of Apple's diagnostic tools has shed new light on this by providing a new look at the "developer strap" which was first referenced in iOS 17.0 developer beta 1. The tool, which has a model number of A2776, is designed for use by Apple retail stores when interfacing with a malfunctioning Vision Pro. Interestingly, developers who received the Vision Pro developer kit last year were also provided access to this strap.<br/>
<br/>
Code from the diagnostic tools also reveals more information on steps Apple retail stores can take to enter diagnostics mode on a malfunctioning Vision Pro to perform a restore: <br/>
<br/>
<ol><li>Remove the right audio strap and install the developer strap onto the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>.</li><br/>
<li>Start up the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; to Diagnostics Mode.<br/>
     โ Press and hold down the Digital Crown.<br/>
     โยAttach the battery cable while holding the Digital Crown.<br/>
     โ Continue holding the Digital Crown for 8 to 10 seconds until the Apple logo appears.</li><br/>
<li>Plug the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; into this computer using a USB-C cable.</li></ol><br/>
With &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; officially launching today and Apple publishing a wealth of information about the new device, make sure to keep tabs on all of our coverage for the latest on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-launch-day/">what Apple CEO Tim Cook calls "the era of spatial computing."</a><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-developer-strap-diagnostics-mode/">Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Developer Strap and Diagnostics Mode Revealed in More Detail</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pros-developer-strap-and-diagnostics-mode-revealed-in-more-detail.2418210/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the Apple Vision Pro: Unboxing, Initial Thoughts and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-unboxing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-apple-vision-pro-unboxing-initial-thoughts-and-more.2418206/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:41:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-unboxing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's first major new product category in almost a decade launched today, with the Vision Pro now in the hands of consumers in the United States. We picked up a Vision Pro this morning, and spent the day testing it out and filming our first impressions.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3Cnvhrc5UEY" title="Apple Vision Pro: Unboxing &amp; Hands-On (It&#39;s INCREDIBLE)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Fit appointments at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> are useful because we've already heard of several situations where the initial &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; readings were off in terms of fit. If you're experiencing an issue with light leakage or comfort, Apple employees can get you a new Light Seal or help you adjust the straps to get the headset working the right way.<br/>
<br/>
At over 1.3 pounds, the Vision Pro is undeniably heavy, but the weight is distributed well with the right fit. It can get heavy to wear over time, but you'll mostly notice the weight when you take it off and feel the relief of not having 1.3 pounds on your face. We've had some light leaking in around the nose even with a solid fit, but the displays seem to work well enough even with that little bit of light.<br/>
<br/>
Putting on the Vision Pro for the first time is absolutely a "holy crap" moment because it's such a different experience, especially with the demo that &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; employees provide. The immersive content is mind blowing, especially when digging in to your own panoramas and spatial videos.<br/>
<br/>
Navigation is intuitive for the most part, but the virtual keyboard is kind of a miss. You can enter text one character at a time and that's fine, but you're going to want a Bluetooth keyboard for any extensive writing. Poking at the keyboard to type feels the most natural, but you can also look at the letters and pinch.<br/>
<br/>
The built-in speakers are great and do an awesome job with spatial audio, but be warned that people around you can hear what's going on so you might want to wear AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
Anything you're seeing in the real world is being relayed through passthrough cameras, so if you're not in the best lighting, you're not going to have the best view. Passthrough video quality can be hit or miss for this reason.<br/>
<br/>
Have you had a chance to try out the Vision Pro? Let us know in the comments below. Apple's retail stores are holding demos all weekend long, and starting Monday, you can book an appointment to get a demonstration if you don't have a Vision Pro yourself.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-unboxing/">Hands-On With the Apple Vision Pro: Unboxing, Initial Thoughts and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-apple-vision-pro-unboxing-initial-thoughts-and-more.2418206/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-pro-grid-studio/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2418202/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 12:04:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-pro-grid-studio/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">with GRID Studio</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> from GRID Studio. If you're not familiar with GRID Studio, it is a company <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/collections/all">that makes art</a> out of old, discarded Apple products, saving them from landfills.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934263" /><br/>
GRID Studio takes vintage devices and disassembles them, laying out each component in a careful arrangement that is augmented with interesting facts and details about a device. The result is artwork that reflects a part of Apple's history, making GRID's products the perfect gift for an Apple enthusiast.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen_02.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934264" /><br/>
The GRID 1, for example, features <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">Apple's first ever iPhone</a>, and it is perhaps the most important device in Apple's history. The &#36;399 GRID 1 has all of the components from the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, ranging from the curved aluminum shell to the 2-megapixel rear camera components.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; came well before A-series chips, so the GRID 1 includes the main board with the Samsung CPU and PowerVR GPU that Apple used for the device, as well as the 30-pin connector used for charging at the time and the Home Button, which was just a button in the days before <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>. Each component is labeled and laid out logically, making for an interesting exploration into Apple's first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen_01.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934265" /><br/>
GRID even includes a diagram of what the first version of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s software looked like, with classic apps like Calculator, Text, Phone, Mail, Safari, and YouTube, along with a classic quote from Steve Jobs.<br/>
<br/>
As time goes on, the original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is harder to find, so this is one of GRID's rarer pieces. The company says that there are very limited quantities of the GRID 1 left due to the difficulty of sourcing the first-generation &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. It is worth noting that some of the devices used may have minor scuffs and scratches due to the fact that GRID is using vintage hardware.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Grid-1st-gen_03.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934267" /><br/>
The GRID 1 measures in at 13x13x1.8 inches, and it has a simple black frame that allows it to fit in anywhere in the home. The GRID 1 and other GRID pieces can be <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">purchased from the GRID Studio website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
GRID Studio has provided us with a much newer &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/mxbxs/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (February 2) at 12:00 p.m. Pacific Time through 12:00 p.m. Pacific Time on February 9. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after February 9 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-pro-grid-studio/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2418202/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Don&#039;t Lose Your &#36;3,500 Apple Vision Pro, You Can&#039;t Track Its Location</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-lacks-find-my-tracking/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dont-lose-your-3-500-apple-vision-pro-you-cant-track-its-location.2418198/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:47:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-lacks-find-my-tracking/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you buy a shiny new Vision Pro, be extra careful not to lose it. Unlike the iPhone and many other Apple devices, the headset lacks Find My location tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Travel-Mode.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930973" /><br/>
In a new <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214043">support document</a>, Apple has confirmed that a Vision Pro's location cannot be viewed in the Find My app on another Apple device, or on iCloud.com. Of the Find My family of features, the Vision Pro only supports Activation Lock, which ensures that a thief cannot erase or freshly set up the headset unless they know the owner's Apple ID and password.<br/>
<br/>
"When you turn on Find My, you protect your Vision Pro with Activation Lock โ but you can't use another Apple device or the web to find Vision Pro on a map, play a sound to help find it, turn on Lost Mode, or remotely erase it," says Apple.<br/>
<br/>
While it's nice to know that a thief cannot easily erase your Vision Pro and set it up with their own Apple ID, the inability to track its location in the Find My app is a noteworthy omission for a headset that starts at &#36;3,499. It ultimately means that if you lose your Vision Pro, you could be simply out of luck beyond filing a police report. Unlike for the iPhone, there is no AppleCare+ theft and loss plan available for the Vision Pro at this time.<br/>
<br/>
While many people will primarily use the Vision Pro at home as an entertainment device, which will greatly reduce the risk of the headset being stolen, Apple does promote using the Vision Pro on an airplane and other settings away from home. The headset could be especially attractive to thieves given how expensive it is.<br/>
<br/>
It's unclear why the Vision Pro does not support Find My location tracking, but the headset lacking a built-in battery and GPS could be contributing factors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Use an AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/vision-pro-case-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931669" /><br/>
One option for tracking the location of your Vision Pro is to purchase <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-releases-vision-pro-accessories/">Apple's travel case</a> and place an AirTag in it, and it is likely that accessory makers will come up with solutions for attaching an AirTag directly to the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro owners can also ensure that Activation Lock is turned on by opening the Settings app, selecting Find My, and selecting Find My Vision Pro.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-lacks-find-my-tracking/">Don&#039;t Lose Your &#36;3,500 Apple Vision Pro, You Can&#039;t Track Its Location</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dont-lose-your-3-500-apple-vision-pro-you-cant-track-its-location.2418198/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: iPad Air Drops as Low as &#36;449.99, Plus Record Lows on MacBook Air, MagSafe Duo, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-2-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-ipad-air-drops-as-low-as-449-99-plus-record-lows-on-macbook-air-magsafe-duo-and-more.2418196/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 11:24:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-2-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week we saw a diverse bunch of deals, with everything from Apple's iPad Air and MacBook Air getting all-time low discounts to notable price drops on non-Apple devices. This includes a massive &#36;600 discount on Samsung's popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor, as well as ongoing markdowns on Anker's best Apple accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0007.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847997" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-air-pink-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934208" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;150 off 5th gen iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/31/best-buy-ipad-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB cellular) for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (256GB cellular) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has every 5th generation iPad Air model on sale this week, taking &#36;150 off these tablets with numerous all-time low prices. This discount brings the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet down to &#36;449.99, marking a new record low price for this iPad Air.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/viewfinity-feb-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934207" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;600 off the Samsung ViewFinity S9 5K monitor</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-999/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;600 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's popular 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor got a major discount this week, and it's still available today. You can get this display for &#36;999.99, a &#36;600 markdown on its normal price and a match for the best-ever price on this monitor. You can also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-999/">find a few more monitor deals</a> in our original post.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/anker-feb-pink.png" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934206" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy two, save 15% on Anker accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagnetic-sale%3Fref%3DnaviMenu">Anker</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/ankers-new-sale-has-magsafe/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fcollections%2Fmagnetic-sale%3Fref%3DnaviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY 2, SAVE 15%</div>Anker MagGo Accessory Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;55 OFF</div>Power Station 60,000 mAh for &#36;114.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker hosted a notable sale this week, and many of the highlights of the sale are still available at a discount. This sale is primarily focused on a buy two, save 15 percent discount for MagSafe-compatible "MagGo" accessories, but there are a few standalone discounts as well. Deals on this sale can be found on Anker's website and on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of standalone deals, you'll find the Power Station 60,000 mAh for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.ZX3GY19NGK88_1704725533960"><strong>&#36;114.99</strong></a> (&#36;55 off) and 3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube for <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fy1811%3Fvariant%3D42206465327254%26collections_magnetic-sale%3Dundefined%26Sort_by%3DRecommended"><strong>&#36;134.95</strong></a> (&#36;15 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/15in-mba-pink-feb-.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934205" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;300 off 15-inch MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy kicked off the week with major discounts on the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, with &#36;300 off both the 256GB and 512GB models. These deals are available to everyone and do not require a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MagSafe Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/magsafe-duo-pink-feb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934204" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on MagSafe Duo Charger and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">Woot</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/woot-discounts-magsafe-duo/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot hosted a big Apple accessory sale this week, the highlight of which is the MagSafe Duo Charger for just &#36;79.99, an all-time low price at &#36;49 off. You'll also find the Siri Remote, Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock, and more on sale.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-2-2-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: iPad Air Drops as Low as &#36;449.99, Plus Record Lows on MacBook Air, MagSafe Duo, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-ipad-air-drops-as-low-as-449-99-plus-record-lows-on-macbook-air-magsafe-duo-and-more.2418196/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Apps to Check Out</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-apps-to-check-out.2418189/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 10:32:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list&#038;post_date=1706909528/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Vision Pro is available today with a whole new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and developers large and small have created apps optimized for the spatial computing device. Optimized apps are those that take advantage of the immersive capabilities offered by the Vision Pro, but users will also find that many <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> apps can operate on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Vision-Pro-Apps-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934149" /><br/>
We've rounded up some of the 600+ apps that are offering native <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> support for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; for those who have a new Vision Pro and are looking for new content to download.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="weather">Weather</h2><br/>
There are quite a few popular weather apps that are making the transition to the Vision Pro &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, and these are good picks if you're looking to outfit your virtual workspace with a window that provides insight into the outside conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="carrot_weather">CARROT Weather</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/apple-store/id961390574">CARROT Weather</a> has a visionOS-optimized interface with a translucent window that can be put anywhere into the space around you. It has all of the features that you might expect from CARROT Weather on other platforms, including favorites, sunset/sunrise times, a 10-day forecast, air quality, current weather conditions, hourly forecast, and more. There's also a 3D globe that you can interact with to explore weather patterns in a new way.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-4.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933472" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933470" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/shorts-or-pants/id1538716652">Shorts or Pants</a></strong> - Shorts or Pants is a weather app that has customizable themes and cards for temperature, air quality, humidity, precipitation, UV index and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mercury-weather/id1621800675">Mercury Weather</a></strong> - Mercury Weather offers a selection of interactive mini weather windows that can be placed anywhere in the environment.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/seasons-immersive-weather/id6468994506">Seasons</a></strong> - Seasons is an immersive weather app that was designed for the Vision Pro. It uses spatial audio technology and it has 34 immersive weather atmospheres that users can experience. The app also offers minute, hour, and day-level forecasts along with other weather information.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="productivity">Productivity</h2><br/>
Microsoft is offering several Vision Pro-optimized apps, including Excel, PowerPoint, Word, and Teams, plus there are all kinds of to-do apps, calendars, and other options for your Vision Pro setup.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="microsofts_apps">Microsoft's Apps</h3><br/>
Microsoft has <a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-blog/announcing-microsoft-365-apps-available-on-apple-vision-pro/ba-p/4042505">designed Vision Pro versions</a> of <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-teams/id1113153706">Teams</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-word/id586447913">Word</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-excel/id586683407">Excel</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-powerpoint/id586449534">PowerPoint</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-outlook/id951937596">Outlook</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-onenote/id410395246">OneNote</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-loop/id1637682491">Loop</a>. All of the apps have a visionOS-optimized interface with translucency to allow work content to blend in with the background, and the windows for the apps can be placed anywhere in virtual space.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro lets users practice their PowerPoint presentations as if presenting to an audience, while Excel has tools for graphing complex formulas, charts, and tables and for visualizing data. Word has a focus mode for blocking out distractions, and Teams uses the Vision Pro Persona feature.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="fantastical">Fantastical</h3><br/>
Popular calendar app Fantastical has been redesigned for the Vision Pro, featuring a visionOS-optimized interface that can be placed anywhere in the virtual space around you. It has all of the Fantastical bells and whistles that users are familiar with, plus multiple window support and other &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; features. Fantastical is free to use, with a subscription available to unlock more options. Existing subscribers will have access to all of the premium features in the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; app. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing Fantastical for Apple Vision Pro" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ccsMSGVBoxQ" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="things_3">Things 3</h3><br/>
Popular task management app <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/things-3-for-vision/id6475688586">Things 3</a> has a new interface designed for Vision Pro, which can be used across different environments. Multiple Things windows can be opened up and placed around you to create a customized workspace, and the interface can be navigated using eye and hand gestures. The app syncs with the Mac, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and Apple Watch versions of Things, and it works with a wireless keyboard. The app is available for a one-time purchase of &#36;30.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/things-3-vision-pro.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934000" /><br/>
<h3 id="box">Box</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/box-the-content-cloud/id290853822">Cloud storage service Box</a> has created an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> app that supports viewing and manipulating 3D objects, collaboration, design optimization, videos and animations, and more. Box says that retailers can use Vision Pro to decide on window design proposals, manufacturers can view 3D renderings, and educational institutions can engage in virtual learning experiences with 3D models of complex concepts.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Box for Apple Vision Pro" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BFPg3A5N0HQ" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/flowriter-writers-retreat/id6470159510">Flowriter</a> allows you to generate any location using AI, creating an immersive background that can be used as a backdrop for writing. The app provides custom cutouts so important items like a desk and keyboard remain visible, while everything else is shut out for concentration purposes. Files can be easily exported to a Mac, as can the generated backgrounds. The app is priced at &#36;9.99 per month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/flowriter-app-visionos.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="750" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934001" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/parcel/id375589283"><strong>Parcel</strong></a> - Delivery tracking app Parcel is available on the Vision Pro with a visionOS-optimized interface for package tracking.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/airmail-your-mail-with-you/id993160329"><strong>Airmail</strong></a> - Popular mail app Airmail is available on &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;, so Airmail users can view their mail on Vision Pro in an optimized interface with window translucency and gesture support.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/omniplan-4/id1460319993">OmniPlan 4</a></strong> - OmniPlan 4 for Vision Pro brings the app's familiar interface into a spatial environment.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/remindercal-reminders-to-cal/id1662218674"><strong>ReminderCal 3</strong></a> - ReminderCal 3 brings the ReminderCal interface to Vision Pro, but it has been redesigned with a native look and interface. With ReminderCal 3, Reminders can be synced to the calendar, with everything done offline.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/focus-productivity-timer/id975017240">Focus</a></strong> - Focus is a Pomodoro time management app that brings a Pomodoro timer into your virtual space for task management and tracking work goals.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/sรถka-bucket-lists-made-easy/id6446223795"><strong>Sรถka</strong></a> - Sรถka is an app for creating and tracking bucket lists and goals. It uses AI to generate suggestions.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/de/app/planny-tagesplaner/id1515324201?mt=8">Planny</a></strong> - Planny is a simple day planning app with a visionOS-optimized interface.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/focused-work-pomodoro-timer/id1523968394">Focused Work</a></strong> - Focused Work is a Pomodoro timer app for setting up timed Focus sessions to get work done.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/email-me-notes-in-one-tap/id1090744587">Email Me</a></strong> - Email Me is an app that lets you email a note to yourself so you do not forget to complete a task.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/runestone-editor/id1548193893">Runestone</a></strong> - Runestone is a plain text editor for the Vision Pro. It supports over 25 programming languages, and has syntax highlighting, line numbers, custom themes, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/chronicling/id6445992145">Chronicling</a></strong> - Chronicling is designed to allow you to track and visualize anything, from habits and chores to moods, medications, events, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spark-mail-ai-email-inbox/id997102246">Spark</a></strong> - Readdle's popular email app Spark is available on the Vision Pro with a spatial-optimized experience. Emails can be drafted in an immersive, interactive environment and read in large windows.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/numerics-business-dashboards/id875319874">Numerics</a></strong> - Numerics is a dashboard app for tracking and sharing KPIs. It can unify metrics from a range of different tools into shareable dashboards that provide a 360-degree view of business performance.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/finalist/id6447014685">Finalist Daily Planner</a></strong> - Finalist Daily Planner integrates calendar events, Reminders, weather, and more for simple planning, plus it includes a notepad.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="utilities">Utilities</h2><br/>
The Vision Pro is shipping with a number of utility apps, so you will be able to do everything from use a calculator to keep track of a budget on the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="juno">Juno</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/juno-for-youtube/id6476961640">Juno for YouTube</a> lets users watch YouTube in a &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; interface without having to resort to Safari. YouTube is not making a Vision Pro app, so Juno is an alternative that offers native controls, resizing, aspect ratio detection, and more. It is priced at &#36;4.99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/juno-youtube.jpeg" alt="" width="2732" height="1868" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934029" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pcalc/id284666222">Pcalc</a></strong> - Popular calculator app Pcalc has been ported over to the Vision Pro and it allows users to place a calculator anywhere in their workspace.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://www.jig.space">JigSpace</a></strong> - JigSpace is an app that lets users create and view 3D presentations and view them in augmented reality.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/calcboard-spatial-calculator/id6476637607">Calc Board</a></strong> - Calc Board is a spatial calculator that provides a calculator that can be used with hand gestures with calculations shown on a separate display as an equation is written out.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/cardpointers-for-credit-cards/id1472875808"><strong>CardPointers</strong></a> - Aimed at helping people with credit cards save money by earning points and cash back. The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; version updates while a user shops in Safari, showing which cards will earn the most points at checkout.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bills-to-budget/id1636872963">Bills to Budget</a></strong> - A money management and budgeting app that lets you see your spending on an expandable &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; app window.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/plant-daddy-water-reminders/id1497476884">Plant Daddy</a></strong> - Lets you keep track of your plants and send reminders when it's time to water. Plant windows in &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; can be arranged in virtual space, and you can, for example, set the window to be in the same area as your plants.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/timely-the-spatial-clock/id6476117550?uo=2">Timely: Spatial Clock</a></strong> - Timely is a simple app that allows Vision Pro users to add a clock anywhere in their workspace.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/la-terminal-ssh-client/id1629902861">La Terminal</a></strong> - La Terminal is a Vision Pro app for those who prefer to use the command line. It has Command Search and AI Assistance, along with CPU and memory use visualizations. There are different themes and backgrounds that users can choose from for a customized look.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/locked-notes-access/id6469049274?platform=appleVisionPro">Locked Notes: Access</a></strong> - Access is an app that lets you store passwords, bank accounts, secure notes, credit cards and other information with data synced via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a>. It integrates with the Passwords feature on Apple devices.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/submanager/id1632853914?uo=4">SubManager</a></strong> - SubManager is a subscription management app that lets users track their subscriptions in one spot and get a heads up when a subscription is about to renew.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/visual-countdown-timer/id1576155611">Visual</a></strong> - Visual is a countdown timer that allows users to add a timer to a virtual workspace.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/tldr-ai/id6449050657">TLDR AI</a></strong> - Shows a summary of any article on the web and provides key points. It's also able to summarize any URL link or text pasted into it.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/alpenglow-sunset-prediction/id978589174">Alpenglow</a></strong> - Alpenglow is an app that allows users to view sunrise, sunset, and magic hour times for any location for photo shoot planning. It also provides predictions on whether a sunrise or sunset will be colorful or lackluster.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/tizipizi-time-zone-converter/id6449408612?platform=appleVisionPro">Tizipizi</a></strong> - Tizipizi is a time zone management app for converting time zones and scheduling meetings across the world. It has a reference clock, time sharing support, clock themes, meeting planning tools, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="lifestyle_fitness_and_cooking">Lifestyle, Fitness, and Cooking</h2><br/>
Lifestyle apps run the gamut from meditation to room planning, and everything in between. There are quite a few apps that are aimed at relaxation, as well as some for cooking and working out.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="crouton">Crouton</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/crouton-recipe-manager/id1461650987">Recipe app Crouton</a> allows you to choose a recipe and follow along while you're cooking. A size guide lets you visualize the size of the dish, you can create meal planning card stacks to add them to a quick weekly meal plan, and there is an option for placing timers around the kitchen while you're cooking to keep an eye on what you're making in AR.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/crouton-visionos-app.jpg" alt="" width="1023" height="575" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933997" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/odio-spatial-soundscapes/id1556016869">Odio</a></strong> - Odio offers immersive AR soundscapes that are designed to help users focus on work or relax. The app includes spatial audio ornaments that serve as a focal point for an immersive auditory experience.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spatial-sprinkles/id6476932945"><strong>Sprinkles</strong></a> - Sprinkles is a super simple app that creates confetti showers and lets users operate a confetti cannon.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/project-alleycat/id1483333906"><strong>Project Alleycat</strong></a> - Project Alleycat is a Vision Pro app that allows users to walk through the alleys in Tewkesbury, a medieval English town. The app includes guides on the history of Tewkesbury as well.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/resolve-spatial-bim-app/id6476718767">Resolve</a></strong> - Resolve is an enterprise app for Vision Pro that lets those who design, build, and operate buildings to review data on the headset. With Resolve, users can walk through buildings and explore designs before construction begins.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/smartgym-gym-home-workouts/id922744883?ls=1">SmartGym</a></strong> - SmartGym for Vision Pro lets users set up routines and exercises, learn proper technique, and monitor their fitness progress.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/animant-spatial-memories/id6452913494">Animant</a></strong> - Allows you to take a panorama to create a background, scan key objects, and animate the movement of the models in your space. It is a way of creating AR memories.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/healium-mobile/id1403144098?platform=appleVisionPro">Healium</a></strong> - Healium is a mindfulness app that offers immersive experiences designed to reduce stress and anxiety.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/ambre-recipe-organizer/id1102236212">Ambre</a></strong> - Recipe manager app Ambre allows users to open up ingredients and recipe instructions in different windows, with the windows able to be placed around the kitchen in an appropriate spot.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/elysian-fields-vision-relax/id6476831214">Elysian Fields</a></strong> - Elysian Fields is a meditation app that combines soothing sounds with high-quality visuals.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nuits-white-noise-soundscapes/id1667217062">Nuits</a></strong> - Nuits offers soothing sounds and backgrounds with animated miniatures. It can be used as a Pomodoro timer or to cut out background noise for better sleep and concentration.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="entertainment">Entertainment</h2><br/>
The entertainment category may have the most apps available on day one, with companies like Disney+ and Max developing custom experiences. There are also movie tracking apps, interactive sports apps, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="disney+">Disney+</h3><br/>
The Disney+ app for Vision Pro allows users to watch Disney+ content in four environments created by Disney, such as the Avengers Tower and Tatooine. Each of the environments includes animations and sounds that are designed to make the space feel alive, plus there are easter eggs from movies to find.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Disney-Plus-Vision-Pro-1.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930910" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/max-stream-hbo-tv-movies/id1666653815">Max</a></strong> - The Max app features themed environments such as the Iron Throne room and Red Keep from the House of the Dragons show.</li><br/>
 <li>Amazon Prime Video</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/imax/id1537376352">IMAX</a></strong> - The IMAX app has a selection of 2D and 3D content, such as the Deep Sky documentary.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/nba-live-games-scores/id484672289">NBA</a></strong> - The NBA app on Vision Pro allows basketball fans to stream up to five broadcasts live or on demand, as well as watch real-time player and team stats.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://www.pgatour.com/article/news/latest/2024/02/01/pga-tour-vision-experience-new-spatial-app-apple-vision-pro-february-2-reality-application-immersive?webview=1">PGA TOUR Vision</a></strong> - This app uses real-time shot tracking layered on top of 3D models of real golf courses to bring the tour to life in a user's space.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mubi-stream-great-cinema/id626148774?platform=appleVisionPro"><strong>MUBI</strong></a> - MUBI content can be watched on the native MUBI app for Vision Pro.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/crunchyroll/id329913454?platform=appleVisionPro">Crunchyroll</a></strong> - Crunchyroll has a Vision Pro-optimized interface with options to customize watchlists and stream anime.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/play-save-videos-watch-later/id1596506190">Play</a></strong> - Play lets you bookmark and organize videos from streaming services, YouTube, and more to create playlists of content.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/film-noir-for-trakt-just-watch/id1528417240">FilmNoir</a></strong> - FilmNoir lets users track their favorite movies and TV shows, creating watch lists and a viewing history.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sequel-media-tracker/id1630746993?platform=appleVisionPro">Sequel</a></strong> - Sequel lets you keep track of movies you want to watch, games you want to play, and books you want to read all in one place.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="communication">Communication</h2><br/>
Popular video conferencing app Zoom has native Vision Pro support, and there are also a couple of GIF apps for finding and creating GIFs to share on social media.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/zoom-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933387" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/zoom-one-platform-to-connect/id546505307">Zoom</a></strong> - The Zoom app features a scalable interface that can be viewed in the real world or on a virtual backdrop. It supports Personas, much like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>. Later this year, the app will support 3D file sharing and Team Chat integration.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/gif-video-maker-blue-cap-co/id1625715926">GIF Editor</a></strong> - Allows you to create and combine GIFs and effects for use on social media.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/gh/app/heypster-gif-5/id1571127299">Heypster</a></strong> - Heypster is an app that lets you search for GIFs to react with on social media.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="audio">Audio</h2><br/>
There are a range of audio apps that merge sound creation with gestures for a unique, immersive experience.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="djay">djay</h3><br/>
Popular DJ software and music mixing app djay is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/djay-dj-app-ai-mixer/id450527929">available on the Apple Vision Pro</a>. The app has been redesigned entirely for the Vision Pro, offering a spatial interface and gesture-based controls for an immersive way to create new mixes. There are 3D turntables to interact with, dynamic light shows that accompany music, visual audio scrubbing, and fun extras like a disco ball that can be placed anywhere. Djay now integrates with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> as well, a feature available across all of Apple's platforms.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing djay for Apple Vision Pro - featuring integration with Apple Music" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ZIFdgQ1Rzn8" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/audio-vision/id6475745854">Audio Vision</a></strong> - Audio Vision is an audio analysis app that provides real-time spectrum analysis and a visualization of frequency distribution. It also includes waveform visualization for better comprehension of song and sound composition.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/id149515200">Longplay</a></strong> - Longplay is a music app that puts your albums on a massive, curved wall so you can see everything in your library.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/spatial-symphony/id6476616491">Spatial Symphony</a></strong> - Spatial Symphony is a music app that allows users to create, manipulate, and explore sound using hand gestures. Users can select from a range of preset sounds and sculpt sound by moving their hands.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nowplaying-music-trivia/id1596487035">NowPlaying</a></strong> NowPlaying has a SongDisplay feature that uses the Vision Pro microphone to identify music from any source, plus it provides interesting details about songs, albums, and artists.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://software.moogmusic.com/">Animoog Galaxy</a></strong> - Animoog Galaxy is a music production app that combines generative visuals and audio with a user's existing environment. It has a range of synthesizer controls and 120 professionally designed presets for full design sound capabilities.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/amazevr-concerts/id6474842602">AmazeVR Concerts</a></strong> - This app provides spatial interactive music performances, with concerts priced at &#36;13. There are performances from Zara Larsson, T-Pain, and UPSAHL, with more coming.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="art_and_design">Art and Design</h2><br/>
<ul><li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/art-projector-da-vinci-eye/id6467633766">Da Vinci Eye</a></strong> - Da Vinci Eye is an app that can project an image on to any small or medium-sized surface so that you can trace it to make art. The app is designed to help users get better at drawing, painting, and other crafts. There's also a Mural Maker feature for creating large-scale art pieces.</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://tool.planner5d.com/applevisionpro"><strong>Planner 5D</strong></a> - Planner 5D is an interior design and home improvement app that lets users view 3D design projects, customize interior items and surfaces, explore 360-degree renders and panoramas, and create designs with hundreds of catalog items.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/livesurface-vision/id6474254673">LiveSurface</a></strong> - LiveSurface lets users place their art, photos, sculptures, and illustrations onto objects in the real world.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bento-craft-marketing-assets/id6468541457">Bento Craft</a></strong> - Allows developers to create marketing images for their apps that can be used on social media, websites, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/de/app/scavengar-easy-ar-creation/id1438349207">Scenery</a></strong> - Scenery is a spatial computing creation and storytelling tool that allows creators to build multi-sensory immersive experiences without code.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="education">Education</h2><br/>
Education apps are some of the most interesting right now, with apps offering everything from an exploration of the night sky to an inside look at the heart.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="sky_guide">Sky Guide</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sky-guide/id576588894">Sky Guide</a> has been redesigned for the Vision Pro, offering a series of experiences for users such as an auroral storm and a historic meteor shower, plus there are views of the sky in wavelengths not visible to the naked eye. Users can explore deep space with zoom binoculars and pull constellations from the sky to interact with them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/skyguide-visionos-app.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934006" /><br/>
<h3 id="complete_heartx">Complete HeartX</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/complete-heartx/id6450795770">Complete HeartX</a> has photorealistic models of the heart. Gestures can be used to explore the heart from any angle, and there are details on cardiac conditions and how those conditions affect the structure and function of the heart.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionos-heart-app.jpg" alt="" width="3296" height="1854" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934007" /><br/>
<h3 id="school_assistant">School Assistant</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/school-assistant-planner/id1465687472">School Assistant</a> is a planner app for students, allowing them to track homework, tests, class times, and more. It has a native &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; design with translucency for windows, and as it is designed for students, it is totally free to download and use.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/school-assistant-visionos.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933998" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://www.foreflight.com/">Voyager</a></strong> - Voyager combines satellite imagery, high-resolution terrain, and live traffic data to provide a 3D airport exploration experience. Airports are shown in 3D on top of a floating disk that can be viewed from any angle.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/insight-heart/id1280845473?platform=appleVisionPro">Insight Heart</a></strong> - Insight Heart provides a close-up interactive look at the human heart.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/cellwalk/id1627776848?uo=2">CellWalk</a></strong> - CellWalk takes users inside the processes of life with guided lessons, an inside look into a bacteria cell, and more.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/night-sky/id475772902?platform=appleVisionPro">Night Sky</a></strong> - Night Sky is a personal planetarium app. Users can explore planets, stars, constellations, and more. The app is able to identify stars and planets that are in the sky above, and the planets and constellations can be interacted with using hand gestures.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/schooly/id1524435833">Schooly</a></strong> - Schooly is an app for managing schoolwork and classes. It can be used for tracking assignments, getting reminders when work is due, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/subjects-school-planner/id1619679435?platform=appleVisionPro">Subjects</a></strong> - Subjects is an app for keeping tabs on homework, grades, and class schedules.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="travel">Travel</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/uy/app/pines-tent-rv-camping-guide/id6469646997">Pines</a></strong> - Pines has information on more than 2,500 camping spots in the U.S., and the Vision Pro makes it easier to find and explore new spots.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pack-repeat-packing-lists/id6473901846">Pack, Repeat</a></strong> - Pack, Repeat is an app that is designed to help users pack for a trip. It has a customizable checklist of all the items that a person might need, so that nothing is left behind.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="shopping">Shopping</h2><br/>
Lowe's, Zillow, and other companies have designed interactive apps that bring shopping into the living room.<br/>
<h3 id="zillow">Zillow</h3><br/>
Zillow has a <a href="https://www.zillowgroup.com/news/how-to-get-the-best-out-of-the-zillow-immerse-app/">useful new "Immerse" app</a> for Vision Pro that offers realistic, immersive virtual tours of houses that are for sale. The listings offer a 3D panoramic view of every room, from ceiling to floor.<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Zillow Immerse App Demo" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aEzTl0sOCTc" width="1280" height="720" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="lowes">Lowe's</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lowes-unveils-lowes-style-studio-for-apple-vision-pro-302050735.html?tc=eml_cleartime">Lowe's app for Vision Pro</a> lets users create a dream kitchen, customizing an interactive, 3D kitchen scene. There are designer-curated styles and also customization options with hundreds of real-world materials, fixtures, and appliances.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionos-lowes-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933999" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/j-crew-virtual-closet/id6473550031">J.Crew</a></strong> - The J.Crew Virtual Closet app offers live consultations and helps users explore looks in a spatial environment using a mannequin that can be dressed in J.Crew outfits.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/wayfair-decorify/id6472541408">Wayfair Decorify</a></strong> - Wayfair's Decorify app lets users browse through items and view them in their spaces.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/ca/app/facades/id6443868157?platform=appleVisionPro">Facades</a></strong> - Michael Steeber's Facades app that's focused on Apple's retail stores is available on Vision Pro. Users can explore all of Apple's 500+ stores, track stores they've visited, favorite stores, and see changes to stores over time.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="games">Games</h2><br/>
There are quite a few games available on the Vision Pro, many of which have Vision Pro-optimized interfaces that incorporate gesture-based gameplay. Many apps that are not Vision Pro optimized will also still run on the device and can be played using a Bluetooth controller.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="wisp_world">Wisp World</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/wisp-world/id6476198961">Wisp World</a> lets Vision Pro users befriend a little forest spirit that's meant to live on your desk. It can be used alongside other apps, adding a digital friend to your workspace.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YH2fk7y44is" title="Wisp for Apple Vision Pro" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Over time, the spirit's habitat will evolve as you talk to it and bond with it, and there are soothing interactions and sounds. Wisp World features lore from Liquid City's mobile game Overbeast, so fans of that game will enjoy the app.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="blackbox">Blackbox</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/blackbox-for-vision/id6458588937">Puzzle game Blackbox</a>, priced at &#36;20, tasks players with solving a series of bubble puzzles that float in the air before them. As with Blackbox on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, there are unique ways to conquer the puzzles, such as moving in a certain way, using sound, and more. Development on the game will continue throughout the year, and content updates will be available for free.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5LShA47LhIc" title="Blackbox for Vision" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="loรณna">Loรณna</h3><br/>
<a href="https://loona.vision/">Loรณna</a> is a spatial puzzle game where players assemble 3D dioramas to create animated scenes that come to life. The game is described as a relaxing puzzle with intuitive mechanics that take advantage of the Vision Pro's gesture controls. The game is free to download, but unlocking the full version requires a &#36;19.99 in-app purchase.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/loona-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934168" /><br/>
<h3 id="what_the_golf">What the Golf?</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/what-the-golf/id1415190483?ign-itscg=30200ADM">What the Golf?</a> for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; brings a golf course into the user's surroundings, and the idea is to play a round of gof with horses, cars, houses, planets, and others. It is similar to the What the Golf? game for iOS, but designed for a spatial environment.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="WHAT THE GOLF? - Apple Vision Pro Launch Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LaJ5yzmlNYs" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<h3 id="super_fruit_ninja">Super Fruit Ninja</h3><br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/super-fruit-ninja/id6450550849">Super Fruit Ninja</a> combines familiar gameplay with spatial computing. Players can slice and dice pineapples and watermelons by jabbing at them, send bombs away by pushing them, and fire shuriken into fruit with their palms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Vision-Pro-Super-Fruit-Ninja.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933935" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/game-room/id1642897935">Game Room</a></strong> - Game Room offers realistic recreations of classic tabletop games like Chess, Hearts, Yacht, Sea Battle, and Solitaire with gesture-based gameplay. Games can be played solo or against others from around the world.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/skatrix-pro/id6475421760">Skatrix Pro</a></strong> - In Skatrix Pro, spatial hand gestures can be used with a 3D joystick to control a skateboarder and perform physics-based tricks.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stitch/id1581052096?platform=appleVisionPro">Stitch</a></strong> - Stitch is a puzzle game where players fill in each level by stitching on an embroidery hoop. The Vision Pro version features a more interactive gameplay environment with a realistic embroidery engine.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/illustrated/id1597761942?platform=appleVisionPro">Illustrated</a></strong> - Illustrated is a puzzle game that features illustrations from famous artists around the world.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lego-builders-journey/id1441636691">LEGO Builder's Journey</a></strong> - With LEGO Builder's Journey, virtual LEGO bricks can be used to solve puzzles. This is a story-based app where users progress by figuring out how to solve each puzzle.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/synth-riders/id6473729300">Synth Riders</a></strong> - Synth Riders is an immersive rhythm game that tasks players with catching notes and dodging obstacles to the beet of the music. There are more than 70 soundtracks, and options for full immersion or gameplay in the user's room.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/puzzling-places/id6473639841">Puzzling Places</a></strong> - Puzzling Places is a 3D jigsaw puzzle game where users put together photorealistic miniatures of real places.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/crosscraft-custom-crosswords/id6472669260">CrossCraft</a></strong> - CrossCraft is an app that lets users create their own crossword puzzles for friends and family members.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mahjong-space/id6474938032">Mahjong Space</a></strong> - Mahjong Space is a multiplayer spatial Mahjong game that can be set up on a real physical tabletop or in a floating window for multitasking while playing.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://tiny-fins.com/">TinyFins</a></strong> - In TinyFins, users guide a school of fish through rings using their hands while avoiding sharks and pufferfish.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mtg-scanner-lions-eye/id1546754798?ign-itscg=30200&amp;ign-itsct=apps_box">Lion's Eye</a></strong> - Lion's Eye isn't quite a game itself, but it is game adjacent. It is a Magic: The Gathering collection manager and deck builder.</li><br/>
 <li><strong><a href="https://itunes.apple.com/app/apple-store/id6472619150">Ploppy Pairs</a> and <a href="https://itunes.apple.com/app/apple-store/id6472882190">Where is Ploppy</a></strong> - Ploppy Pairs is a simple game where users match cards together using SharePlay during a &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; call. Where is Ploppy sends a slew of objects into the space around the user, and the user is asked to find a specific object. The game supports VoiceOver and an aural navigation system to help players that are visually impaired find the cards.</li><br/>
<li><strong><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/void-x/id1622479769?platform=appleVisionPro">Void-X</a></strong> - Void-X is an arcade shoot 'em up game with a retro aesthetic and room-wide effects on Vision Pro.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="popular_apps_not_on_vision_pro">Popular Apps Not on Vision Pro</h2><br/>
Several popular apps do not plan to offer Vision Pro compatibility. These companies have also disabled the feature that would allow the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; versions of their app to be used on Vision Pro.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Netflix</li><br/>
 <li>Spotify</li><br/>
 <li>YouTube</li><br/>
 <li>Facebook</li><br/>
 <li>WhatsApp</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="more_apps">More Apps</h2><br/>
Find a favorite Vision Pro app that we don't have on our list? Let us know in the comments below!<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/">Apple Vision Pro Apps to Check Out</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-apps-to-check-out.2418189/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s How to Let Someone Else Try Your Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-vision-pro-guest-mode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-to-let-someone-else-try-your-apple-vision-pro.2418178/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:07:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-vision-pro-guest-mode&#038;post_date=1706904445/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, you're undoubtedly going to get requests from friends and family members who want to give it a try. The headset is primarily designed for a single user because of the customized fit of the Light Seal, but Apple planned for demos with a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117742">built-in Guest Mode</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
Apple warns that guests might not be able to get an optimal fit, but <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/117730">Apple recommends</a> having the person test both the Solo Knit and Dual Loop Bands. Apple suggests that guests should have their own personalized Light Seal, but Light Seals are priced at &#36;200, so that's quite a steep add-on cost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O-OTFLEmF5Q" title="How to share your Apple Vision Pro with Guest User | Apple Support" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Guests can try Vision Pro with a customizable Guest User section. Apple says that to limit access to apps, a passcode should be set. Apps that you don't want the guest to use should be closed, and apps you want to demo should be opened.<br/>
<h2>How to Start a Guest User Session</h2><br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open the Control Center by looking up and tapping the down button at the top of the view.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on the Control Center button to open up more options.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on the Guest User button.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap Allowed Apps under the Guest User window. Select from Open Apps Only to limit access, or All Apps &amp; Data for unrestricted access.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on the back button, and then tap on Start. You'll get a notification that you have five minutes to hand the headset over to the guest user. If you don't hand it over within five minutes, Guest User turns off and the Vision Pro locks.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Apple says that if you tap on View Mirroring while in the Control Center, you can see what your guest is seeing on Vision Pro on one of your other Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
You will need to walk your guest through using Vision Pro, and they may need to press and hold on the Digital Crown until the displays align and a green checkmark appears. A hand and eye setup will follow so the Vision Pro responds appropriately.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to End a Guest User Session</h2><br/>
To end a Guest User session, the guest simply needs to remove the Vision Pro. The next time you wear your Vision Pro, it will return to your personal hand and eye settings.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Guest User Options</h2><br/>
During a Vision Pro Guest session, a guest can access all apps and data or just the apps you've allowed. Any open app will have full access, so if you open <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, they can see your images, or in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, they can listen to your content.<br/>
<br/>
Guests will not have access to your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, Persona, or Wallet &amp; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Guests do have access to a selection of settings such as accessibility, an option to redo eye and hand setup, and an option to learn more about the Guest User experience.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-vision-pro-guest-mode/">Here&#039;s How to Let Someone Else Try Your Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-how-to-let-someone-else-try-your-apple-vision-pro.2418178/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: March Apple Event Rumors and iOS 18&#039;s &#039;Biggest&#039; Ever Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors-and-ios-18s-biggest-ever-update.2418177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 09:03:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/march-apple-event-rumors-and-ios-18s-biggest-ever-update/id1602394741?i=1000643961912">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's potential March event to unveil <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">new iPad and Mac models</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/">"biggest" ever</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> software update, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/apple-vision-pro/">first reviews</a> of the Vision Pro headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z2o4HR10xrs?si=gZNSDA7DN88IRpQQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We explore the major products Apple is expected to unveil in March, including a new 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> model, redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> Pros with OLED displays, and refreshed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models featuring the M3 chip, as well as some of the rumored accessories due to arrive at the same time, such as an all-new, "laptop-like" Magic Keyboard for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>. We consider whether Apple will opt for a fully fledged event, or a simple series of press releases to announce these updates. We also discuss &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, musing about some of the potential redesigns and improvements that could be in store for the software update.<br/>
<br/>
Following the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/apple-vision-pro/">first reviews</a> of Apple's Vision Pro headset, we dissect the varying reactions to the device, examining its form factor, user experience, and the unique approach Apple has taken to mitigate the traditionally insular experience of VR/AR headsets. We address some of the limitations currently faced by headsets, such as the absence of a direct touch experience, the market's apparent skepticism towards the device, and where it could go next.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now <strong>exclusively</strong> on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/the-macrumors-show-the-macs-40th-birthday/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-macintosh-turns-40/">40th anniversary of the Macintosh</a>, some of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/netflix-wont-offer-vision-pro-app-at-launch/">latest controversy</a> surrounding apps for the Vision Pro headset, and the news of Apple's vehicle project yet again being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/">scaled back</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors/">The MacRumors Show: March Apple Event Rumors and iOS 18&#039;s &#039;Biggest&#039; Ever Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-march-apple-event-rumors-and-ios-18s-biggest-ever-update.2418177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Details What to Do If Vision Pro Causes Visual Discomfort, Motion Sickness and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-visual-discomfort/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-details-what-to-do-if-vision-pro-causes-visual-discomfort-motion-sickness-and-more.2418174/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:46:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-visual-discomfort/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the launch of the Vision Pro, Apple has published a number of support documents on how to use the device and what to do if motion sickness or discomfort is experienced when wearing the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Orange-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929937" /><br/>
<h2>Visual Discomfort</h2><br/>
Vision Pro users who <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213946">experience visual discomfort</a> such as blurry vision, double vision, dry eyes, watery eyes, light sensitivity, and eye strain should stop using Vision Pro and wait for symptoms to resolve.<br/>
<br/>
To minimize visual discomfort, Apple says that a good fit is essential, with pressure balanced across the nose and cheeks and the proper alignment set up. Vision Pro should be used in short increments of time to start with, and Apple recommends regular breaks every 20 to 30 minutes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also says that keeping the head upright rather than tilted to one side or another and sitting upright while watching 3D movies, immersive media, or spatial video can help.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Alignment</h2><br/>
Vision Pro was designed to "accommodate a range" of inter-pupillary distances, but Apple says that some people who fall outside of this range could experience visual discomfort using the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Safety Recommendations</h2><br/>
Apple recommends that people <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/vision-pro-medical-conditions/">with certain conditions</a> use caution when using Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The headset <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213944">should be used</a> in a "controlled" indoor or outdoor space that is free of obstacles that could be tripped over or hit with hands. Apple warns that doorknobs and cabinets could catch the power cable and cause it to disconnect.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro should not be used in extreme temperatures, rain, fog, or moisture of any kind, and water damage is not covered under the warranty. Vision Pro should also be used in a well-lit area for the best experience, as low-light conditions can increase the risk of object collisions. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Battery</h2><br/>
The Vision Pro battery should be kept in a well-ventilated area so that it does not get excessively warm.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Motion Sickness</h2><br/>
A "small number of people" <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213934">may experience motion sickness</a> when using Vision Pro. Symptoms include dizziness, nausea, decreased awareness, upset stomach, increased salivation, headache, fatigue, and sweating. Apple says that it can take up to 30 minutes for symptoms to start.<br/>
<br/>
Those experiencing motion sickness should stop using the headset, and should not use Vision Pro while on an airplane. Using the device for short increments of time and with less immersive experiences can help.<br/>
<br/>
To minimize motion sickness, Apple says that users should reduce head motion and move the head and neck as little as possible. Apple also recommends reducing visual motion by decreasing window sizes, reducing the level of immersion, and turning on the Reduce Motion setting in the Accessibility section of Settings.<br/>
<br/>
High motion experiences like Apple Immersive Media should also be avoided by those who get motion sick, as should spatial video with a lot of movement.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-visual-discomfort/">Apple Details What to Do If Vision Pro Causes Visual Discomfort, Motion Sickness and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-details-what-to-do-if-vision-pro-causes-visual-discomfort-motion-sickness-and-more.2418174/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Vision Pro Performance Could Be Reduced in Some Situations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-battery-management-system/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-vision-pro-performance-could-be-reduced-in-some-situations.2418173/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:31:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-battery-management-system/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Like the iPhone, the Vision Pro has an always-on battery management system that could lead to reduced performance in certain situations, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-chips.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898904" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213955">support document</a> published today, Apple said Vision Pro users could notice impacts such as longer app launch times, lower frame rates, reduced wireless speeds, screen dimming, or lower speaker volume in situations where the Vision Pro is low on battery, has a chemically aged battery, or is in a peak-power state.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's full explanation:<blockquote>Apple Vision Pro has built-in software and hardware systems that help reduce performance impacts that may be noticed in certain conditions such as a battery with a low state of charge, a high peak power situation, or a chemically aged battery. The system is automatic, always-on, and works to provide the best possible performance. Power needs are dynamically monitored, and performance is managed to address these needs in real time. The system allows Apple Vision Pro to balance and reduce performance impacts as much as possible. The user may or may not notice effects on device, which may be temporary. Depending on the device battery state and the tasks that your Apple Vision Pro is handling, some examples of these effects may include longer app launch times, lower frame rates, reduced wireless data throughput, screen dimming, or lower speaker volume.</blockquote>Apple introduced a similar system on older iPhone models back in 2017, but it failed to mention the system in its iOS release notes at the time, leading to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-slowdown/">major controversy</a>. Apple eventually <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/06/apple-starts-iphone-batterygate-payouts/">agreed to pay up to &#36;500 million</a> to settle a class action lawsuit that accused the company of "secretly throttling" some iPhone models.<br/>
<br/>
Nowadays, the system is considered by many to be a helpful feature that ensures smooth performance and prevents unexpected shutdowns.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-battery-management-system/">Apple Says Vision Pro Performance Could Be Reduced in Some Situations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-vision-pro-performance-could-be-reduced-in-some-situations.2418173/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains How to Clean Vision Pro Headset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset.2418172/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2024 08:23:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a detailed <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213964">support document</a> explaining how to clean the Vision Pro headset and all of its accompanying components.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-929938" /><br/>
Apple warns that disinfectants like isopropyl alcohol, Windex, and Clorox should not be used to clean the Vision Pro. Instead, users should simply use a dry or slightly damp cloth.<br/>
<br/>
To clean the cover glass of the Vision Pro, Apple simply encourages use of a clean, dry microfiber cloth like the polishing cloth included with the headset. If necessary, users can also spray ZEISS cleaning fluid on the cloth before wiping the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple warns that its polishing cloth may attract particles that could scratch the Vision Pro if it is stored loose in a backpack, handbag, or pockets, and suggests that it should be stored in a clean bag. The polishing cloth can be machine washed and dried, or washed by hand, as needed to ensure it is clean enough to wipe the headset.<br/>
<br/>
To clean the inner displays, Apple says that users should first put the Vision Pro's cover on and put the headset on a level surface. Then, wipe the optical displays with a microfiber cloth, using ZEISS cleaning spray if required.<br/>
<br/>
ZEISS Optical Inserts should be removed from the Vision Pro before cleaning them. They can be cleaned with ZEISS Lens Wipes, ZEISS Cleaning Spray, or lukewarm water, and should be fully dry before being reattached to the headset.<br/>
<br/>
Users should use a lint-free cloth, soft bristle brush, or non-tacky tape to remove debris stuck to the curtain around the displays. Stains in this area can be removed by rubbing them with a damp cloth, but care should be taken to avoid getting the displays wet.<br/>
<br/>
To clean the Light Seal, Light Seal Cushion, head bands, and cover, users can use fragrance-free unscented dish soap, but cleaning wipes, disinfectant wipes, and laundry detergent should be avoided. 5 tsp (25 ml) of fragrance-free dish soap should be mixed into two cups (500 ml) of warm water in a clean container, before submersing the Light Seal, Light Seal Cushion, head band, or cover into the liquid and gently rubbing the surface for around two minutes. The item should then be removed and rinsed under running water while compressing it to remove any excess soap, before leaving it to dry at room temperature. It should not be used until it is completely dry. <br/>
<br/>
The Audio Straps should be cleaned with a lint-free cloth. It can be lightly dampened with water and hypoallergenic soap, as long as the microphone, speakers, power connector, head band connector, and aluminum lid are avoided. It should be dried with a cloth before being attached to the main system. The speaker meshes can be cleaned with a dry cotton swab.<br/>
<br/>
The battery can be cleaned with a damp lint-free cloth once it is disconnected, avoiding getting any moisture near the power cable connector. To clean the power cable itself, a cloth dampened with soapy water can be used. It should be left to dry overnight before using it again with the Vision Pro.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset/">Apple Explains How to Clean Vision Pro Headset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset.2418172/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
