<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 12:02:33 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: All the Rumors and Known Features So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/ios-18-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-all-the-rumors-and-known-features-so-far.2411801/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 06:50:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/ios-18-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 is still over seven months away from being announced, but there are already a few rumors and expectations for the software update. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909207" /><br/>
iOS 18 should be announced at Apple's annual developers conference WWDC next June, and released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September. Below, we recap all of the rumors and information pertaining to the update so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>"Major New Features"</h2><br/>
In his newsletter this month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">iOS 18 could be a "relatively groundbreaking" update</a> with "major new features and designs," although he did not share many specific details. Gurman added that Apple's senior management has internally described its upcoming operating systems as "ambitious and compelling."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smarter Siri</h2><br/>
Gurman said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">iOS 18 will feature generative AI technology</a> that "should improve how both Siri and the Messages app can field questions and auto-complete sentences." He said Apple has explored new generative AI features for other apps across its platforms, including Apple Music, Pages, Keynote, and Xcode.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The Information</em> reported that Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">incorporate large language models into Siri</a> to let users automate complex tasks, a feature that would involve deeper integration with the Shortcuts app. The report said this feature is expected to be released in an iPhone software update coming next year, which could be iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
Generative AI surged in popularity last year when OpenAI released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/chatgpt-app-voice-chat-free-to-all/">ChatGPT</a>, a chatbot that can respond to questions and other prompts. Google and Microsoft released similar chatbots earlier this year, as more companies race into the space. The chatbots are trained on large language models, allowing them to respond like a human.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has publicly confirmed its interest in generative AI, and it has mentioned the technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/02/apple-seeking-generative-ai-engineers-for-ar-vr/">in job listings</a> posted on its website in recent months.<br/>
<br/>
"We've been working on generative AI for years and have done a lot of research," said Apple CEO Tim Cook, in an <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/davidphelan/2023/09/29/apples-tim-cook-talks-about-ai-apps-vision-pro-and-iphone-gaming/">interview with <em>Forbes</em></a> in September. "And we're going to approach it really thoughtfully and think about it deeply, because we're fully aware of the not-good uses that it can have, and the issues around bias and hallucination and so forth."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Improved Texting With Android Users</h2><br/>
Earlier this month, Apple announced that it will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">finally support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS</a> in the Messages app on the iPhone starting "later next year," so it will likely be an iOS 18 feature based on this timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
RCS support should result in several improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging between iPhones and Android devices</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li><br/>
 <li>Improved encryption compared to SMS</li><br/>
</ul>These features are already available for iPhone-to-iPhone conversations with blue bubbles, via iMessage, and many of the features are also available in third-party messaging apps, such as WhatsApp and Telegram. RCS support on the iPhone will extend the features to green bubbles in the built-in Messages app, providing for a much better iPhone/Android messaging experience compared to the current SMS standard.<br/>
<br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">guide about Apple implementing RCS on the iPhone</a> for additional details.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/ios-18-rumors/">iOS 18: All the Rumors and Known Features So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-all-the-rumors-and-known-features-so-far.2411801/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Max 2 Launch Next Year: What to Expect (and What to Hope For)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect-and-what-to-hope-for.2411790/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:50:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AirPods Max are the oldest current-generation AirPods product still in Apple's lineup. It's been almost three years since Apple launched AirPods Max in December 2020, and only recently have we begun hearing rumors about Apple's plans for a new-generation model next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Dark-Red-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877636" /><br/>
According to well-connected <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman, Apple will introduce a new version of the AirPods Max in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/29/gurman-usb-c-airpods-max-late-2024/">late 2024</a>. Here's what we expect from the new version of Apple's premium over-ear headphones, followed by some potential features that we hope to see but are still unconfirmed for AirPods Max 2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2024 AirPods Max: What to Expect</h2><br/>
<h3>USB-C</h3><br/>
According to Gurman, Apple will replace the Lightning port found on the current-generation AirPods Max for a USB-C port. This will ensure the headphones comply with European regulations, and will bring consistency across the company's AirPods lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/USB-C-Over-Lightning-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-817486" /><br/>
This of course means AirPods Max 2 will come supplied with a USB-C to USB-C charging cable, rather than a Lightning to USB-C cable. Apple will also need to offer a USB-C to 3.5mm audio accessory cable so that users can plug AirPods Max 2 into 3.5mm audio ports.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Bluetooth 5.3</h3><br/>
The Bluetooth 5.3 specification can already be found in the AirPods Pro 2, the iPhone 15 lineup, and the latest Apple Watch models. It is also supported by all Mac models released in 2023. Therefore it's almost inevitable that the second-generation ‌AirPods Max‌ will similarly feature the latest Bluetooth standard. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/airpods-max-lifestyle.jpg" alt="" width="980" height="653" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800612" /><br/>
Bluetooth 5.3 includes enhancements that can improve the reliability of the wireless connection as well as energy efficiency. The specification also includes LE Audio, but Apple does not appear to have implemented support for LE Audio in its devices yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>New Colors</h3><br/>
Apple will offer second-generation AirPods Max in fresh colors, according to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/29/gurman-usb-c-airpods-max-late-2024/">October 2023</a> <em>Bloomberg</em> report. Although what those colors might be is currently unknown.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/AirPods-Max-2022-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="2808" height="1579" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-845479" /><br/>
AirPods Max are currently available in Space Gray, Silver, Green, Sky Blue, and Pink, although interchangeable ear cushions allow for many color combinations. Apple sells standalone ear cushions for &#36;69 per pair.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2024 AirPods Max: What to Hope For</h2><br/>
The latest rumors suggest that no other major changes are expected for the AirPods Max 2, although Apple's plans could always change between now and when they are released in late 2024. Here are the improvements and changes that we hope Apple ultimately includes.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>H2 Chip</h2><br/>
It would seem reasonable for AirPods Max 2 to feature the H2 chip, Apple's custom silicon chip designed specifically for earbuds and headphones. The H2 chip enables improved computational audio to enhance sound quality on the current-generation ‌AirPods Pro‌ and improves battery life with better energy efficiency. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/10/airpods-pro-h2-chip.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866128" /><br/>
Despite the H2 chip's introduction with the AirPods Pro, Gurman's latest report suggests Apple currently does not plan to include the technology in the AirPods Max 2, which would also deprive the headphones of H2-specific features like Adaptive Audio, Personalized Volume, and improved noise cancelation and battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>U2 Chip and Precision Finding</h3><br/>
Apple's U2 Ultra Wideband chip can be found in the latest iPhone 15 series, Apple Watch Series 9 and the Apple Watch Ultra 2, and allows for Precision Finding in the Find My app. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/precision-finding-airtag-design-session.jpeg" alt="" width="1800" height="1012" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-803337" /><br/>
The current ‌AirPods Max‌ feature basic support for ‌Find My‌, but do not even feature the previous generation U1 chip. For Apple to add a U2 chip to AirPods Max 2 would therefore enable a much more precise way to locate the headphones when they are nearby.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Redesigned Smart Case</h3><br/>
When Apple unveiled the &#36;549 ‌AirPods Max‌, the included Smart Case stirred up plenty of online chatter for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/23/apple-questionable-design-decisions/">odd appearance and poor overall protection</a> when compared to the traditional hard cases that come with other premium headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/airpods-max-smart-case-video.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="903" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-775618" /><br/>
Apple's much-lampooned case birthed an avalanche of memes, which have irreverently compared it to all sorts of things, from handbags to lingerie, and even body parts. There are no rumors that Apple plans to redesign the case, although one Apple patent describes how a future model could come with a case that offers a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/05/apple-patent-airpods-max-case-design/">more traditional portable housing</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/">AirPods Max 2 Launch Next Year: What to Expect (and What to Hope For)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect-and-what-to-hope-for.2411790/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Proton Drive Encrypted Cloud Storage App Now Available for Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/proton-drive-cloud-storage-app-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/proton-drive-encrypted-cloud-storage-app-now-available-for-mac.2411789/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 04:30:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/proton-drive-cloud-storage-app-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>Proton</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Swiss-based privacy startup Proton today <a href="https://proton.me/blog/proton-drive-mac-app">announced</a> the availability of its end-to-end encrypted cloud storage service for Mac users with the launch of its macOS app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macos-proton-drive.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923807" /><br/>
<a href="https://proton.me/drive/download">Proton Drive</a> lets users sync files between Mac and the cloud, access files offline, and free up space on local drives. Unlike iCloud, all data (including metadata) is end-to-end encrypted by default, so that no-one – not even Proton – can see the files.<br/>
<br/>
Files in Proton Drive are synced on-demand, meaning they don't take up space on the local computer until they are needed. Meanwhile, files and folders saved in the Proton Drive folder automatically sync online to Proton Drive, and any changes made locally are mirrored across all other devices linked to the Proton account. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-advanced-data-protection-icloud/">How to Enable End-to-End Encryption for iCloud Backups</a></li></ul><br/>
When files and folders are downloaded for offline access, Proton Drive syncs changes when an internet connection next becomes available. Users can also access and restore previous versions of files via the web interface. It's worth noting that only files stored in the Proton Drive folder are synced, but Proton says it is working to enable synchronization for any local folder.<br/>
<br/>
Additional Proton Drive options can be found in the app's menu bar item, including one-click sync pausing, sync status, quick access to Proton Drive, and service support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macos-proton-drive-window.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923808" /><br/>
Web access to Proton Drive arrived last September, followed by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/07/proton-drive-ios-app-encrypted-cloud-storage/">native mobile apps in December</a> and a Windows app in July. The arrival of the Mac app means Proton Drive is now available on all major platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Proton Drive offers users 1GB of storage for free, with additional paid plans available starting at &#36;4/month for 200GB of storage, including additional features such as the ability to automatically store previous versions of a file for up to 10 years. Black Friday deals are currently available on the <a href="https://proton.me/drive/black-friday">company's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/proton/">Proton</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/23/proton-drive-cloud-storage-app-mac/">Proton Drive Encrypted Cloud Storage App Now Available for Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/proton-drive-encrypted-cloud-storage-app-now-available-for-mac.2411789/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Black Friday Deals Available Already: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/apple-black-friday-now-wednesday-2023/</link>
		<comments></comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 14:47:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/apple-black-friday-now-wednesday-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're just one day away from Black Friday, and prices keep dropping on some of Apple's most popular products and accessories, including AirPods, iPad, MacBook, and much more. Of course, there's no guarantee that better prices won't appear later in the holiday season, but if you want to shop right now these are the best deals currently available on each product.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/General-Black-Friday-Deals-2022-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874255" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Specifically, in this article we're sharing all of the Apple products that currently have all-time low prices, or discounts that are at least very close to their record-low prices. Beyond Apple, we're also taking a look at notable accessories for Apple products as well as some of the season's best gifts, including LEGO sets. Every deal shared below is available to purchase right now. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Table of Contents</h2><br/>
You can use the links below to jump directly to the section you're shopping for today.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="#homepod">HomePod</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#airpods">AirPods</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#iphone">iPhone</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#ipad">iPad</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#mac">Mac</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#apple_watch">Apple Watch</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#accessories">Accessories</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#more_black_friday_sales">More Black Friday Sales</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#our_black_friday_guides">Our Black Friday Guides</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For more Black Friday deals, particularly including current and upcoming sales from third-party accessory makers, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="homepod">HomePod</h2><br/>
<h3 id="homepod_2nd_gen">HomePod (2nd Gen)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/homepod-candycanes-1.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922530" /><br/>
<br/>
B&H Photo has been the only retailer with a consistent discount on Apple's second generation HomePod. Right now, you can get it in both colors for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. While not a huge markdown, this continues to be the best price we've ever tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>HomePod (Gen 2) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><h2 id="airpods">AirPods</h2><br/>
<h3 id="airpods_2">AirPods 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922536" /><br/>
<br/>
We originally tracked the AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00 at Amazon in early November, but that sale quickly expired. For now, you can get the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This version of the AirPods is perfect for anyone on your holiday shopping list who may be asking for a simple and reliable pair of wireless earbuds, particularly at this insanely low price tag. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_3">AirPods 3</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-3-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922535" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;139.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. These are upgraded in a few ways from the AirPods 2, with spatial audio, Adaptive EQ, force sensor controls, sweat and water resistance, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_pro_2">AirPods Pro 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-pro-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922534" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the Pro lineup, Amazon has the AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) at their all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_max">AirPods Max</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-max-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922533" /><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the high-end AirPods Max are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;549.00. Discounts on the AirPods Max have been rare over the past few months, so this one is a second-best price on the over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone">iPhone</h2><br/>
<h3 id="att">AT&T</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922708" /><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fdeals%2F">AT&T</a> quite a few sales and offers for multiple iPhone 15 devices, including up to &#36;1,000 off the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-max.html">iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> with an eligible smartphone trade-in. Models with lower storage capacities can be purchased at no cost thanks to these discounts, and of course you'll need to purchase the new smartphone on a qualifying installment agreement. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get up to &#36;830 off the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15.html">iPhone 15</a> or <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-plus.html">iPhone 15 Plus</a> as well, with the same stipulations as the Pro devices. Both offers will be delivered via monthly bill credits, starting within three bills after trade-in is completed. It'll be applied in equal amounts over the term of your installment agreement.<br/>
<br/>
For the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max offer, you'll need to trade in a device with a value of &#36;230 or higher to get the full &#36;1,000 off markdown. You'll get up to &#36;830 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;130 to &#36;229 and up to &#36;350 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;35 to &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
For older iPhone models, AT&T is offering the 128GB <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-14.html">iPhone 14 at &#36;10.99/month</a> with no trade-in required. Similarly, the iPhone 14 Pro is available at &#36;15/month with no trade-in required. For these, all you'll need is to purchase the smartphones on an installment plan and pick or upgrade to an eligible unlimited plan.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T is also taking <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fwearables%2F">&#36;300 off any Apple Watch</a> when you purchase two at the same time. Like smartphone plans, you'll have to buy two Apple Watches on an installment plan, add at least one new line, and activate both on your wireless plan. Afterwards, you'll get up to &#36;300 in bill credits over 36 months.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="verizon">Verizon</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-15-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922707" /><br/>
At <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a>, you can get a special bundle offer if you're interested in purchasing the new <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F">iPhone 15 Pro</a> this holiday season. When you do pick up the new smartphone with a new line on an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan, Verizon will reward you with an Apple TV 4K (64GB) and six months of Apple One at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE APPLE TV 4K</div>iPhone 15 Pro at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, you can purchase <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple%2F">higher storage iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max models</a>, but at that point you'll be paying a little extra. The Apple TV 4K promotion requires a smarpthone purchase on an eligible plan and ends on November 15, while the Apple One six month promotion requires a line subscribed to an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan.<br/>
<br/>
For last year's models, you can <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus%2F">get four iPhone 14 Plus devices for free</a> along with four lines on Unlimited Welcome at &#36;120/month. A new line on any 5G Unlimited plan is required per smartphone. You can also stack this with Verizon's current tablet and smartwatch promotions, which offer up to &#36;279.99 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
Verizon is also a great place to buy stocking stuffers for techies during the holiday season with its abundant <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14048362?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fdeals%2Fproducts%2F">accessory sales</a>. Right now it has up to &#36;50 off Anker speakers, 30% off Nimble chargers, 20% off Apple Watch bands, and 20% off Mophie chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="visible">Visible</h3><br/>
Verizon's <a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909">Visible</a> brand has &#36;10 off its premium Visible+ service, now priced at &#36;35/month with the promo code 35FOR6 used at checkout. This promotion will last for six months, and after it ends it will return to the regular price of &#36;45/month for the Visible+ service.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF/MONTH</div>Visible+ Cellular Plan</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Visible offers all of the latest smartphones, including iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models. When you join Visible, you'll save up to &#36;240 via monthly bill credits on your account. You'll need to join Visible on a new line of service, purchase a new device, and select the Visible+ plan.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="t-mobile">T-Mobile</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519">T-Mobile</a> is providing up to &#36;1,000 off the new iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Next plan. You can get up to &#36;830 off these devices when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Plus plan.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The carrier also has a wide variety of previous generation iPhones at a discount. This includes the iPhone 13 and iPhone SE at no extra cost when purchased on select cellular plans and trading in eligible devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad">iPad</h2><br/>
<h3 id="9th_gen_ipad">9th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-1-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922714" /><br/>
<br/>
We've been tracking a great all-time low discount on the ninth generation iPad since Prime Day, and the deal is still around in November. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;229.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. At this record low price, the iPad is a perfect entry-level tablet for a kid or family member who doesn't need the tablet for work-intensive projects.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;229.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="10th_gen_ipad">10th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922713" /><br/>
<br/>
The upgraded iPad from 2022 also has a great discount on Amazon right now, with the 64GB Wi-Fi model on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. This model comes with a bigger 10.9-inch Liquid Retina display, A14 Bionic chip for a performance boost, Wi-Fi 6, and more.<br/>
<br/>
This beats the sale from earlier in the month by &#36;50 and is a new all-time low price on the iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="6th_gen_ipad_mini">6th Gen iPad Mini</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-mini-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922712" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 8.3-inch iPad mini 6 is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This iPad mini has an 8.3-inch Liquid Retina display, A15 Bionic chip, USB-C, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="5th_gen_ipad_air">5th Gen iPad Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-air-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922711" /><br/>
<br/>
Switching to iPad Air models, the 2022 64GB Wi-Fi tablet has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;599.00. That's a solid all-time low price on this model, and you can also find a few other storage configurations at record lows this time around. Note that for the majority of colors, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon to see these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JH3XS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac">Mac</h2><br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m1_macbook_air">13-inch M1 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-m1-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922931" /><br/>
<br/>
The M1 MacBook Air has returned to its steep discounted price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a> for the 256GB model, down from &#36;999.00. This is a great deal and perfect computer for anyone who needs an Apple notebook for simple email and internet browsing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m2_macbook_air">13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/m2-macbook-air-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922930" /><br/>
<br/>
At Best Buy, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,099.00. This deal is only available for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, and it's an all-time low price. You'll find a similar record low deal on the <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sc246Dch">512GB model</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="15-inch_m2_macbook_air">15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-gingerbread-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922720" /><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for the all-time low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is also available for the record low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both have all colors on sale, and they're only available at these prices for My Best Buy Plus/Total members.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's latest MacBook Air model is a great option with numerous pro-level features without the price tag. For a deep dive into all the similarities and differences between each line, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide/">read our buyer's guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_macbook_pro">M3 MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922719" /><br/>
<br/>
There are a few notable discounts on the new M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy and Amazon this week, including savings on the 14-inch and 16-inch models. These are some of the first big discounts on the M3 MacBook Pro, and you can get up to &#36;200 off these notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
For the 14-inch models at Best Buy below, note that the prices reflect My Best Buy Plus/Total member savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sZ0jMbvh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3, 512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s09UEdeF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s1XidD9X"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;2,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_imac">M3 iMac</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/imac-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922718" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is offering record low prices on the just-released M3 iMac, with prices as low as &#36;1,234.05 for the 8-Core GPU, 256GB model. In total, these sales represent up to &#36;100 off the new M3 iMac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5HSYSS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;65 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-Core GPU, 256GB) for &#36;1,234.05</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch">Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_9">Apple Watch Series 9</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922717" /><br/>
<br/>
Some of the best Black Friday Apple Watch deals are focused on the new Series 9 models. You can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">41mm GPS device for &#36;329.00</a> at Amazon, down from &#36;399.00. This &#36;70 discount is a new all-time low price on the 2023 smartwatch. Likewise, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">45mm GPS is down to &#36;359.00</a> at Amazon, another &#36;70 markdown and record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for cellular models, there are a few deals to discover. Amazon has the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">41mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;429.00</a>, as well as the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">45mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;459.00</a>. Both of these are &#36;70 discounts and more all-time low prices for the smartwatch lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;429.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;459.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_ultra_2">Apple Watch Ultra 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ultra-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922928" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few models of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for the all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX59RZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;729.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. This one requires you to clip an on-page coupon, and once you do you'll drop the price of the Ultra 2 down to its new record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX59RZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;729.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_se">Apple Watch SE</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-se-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923276" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want a cheaper Apple Watch, Amazon has the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This one was at &#36;189.00 just last week, so this is yet another record low price for the 2022 Apple Watch SE, and you'll find multiple best-ever prices across the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;179.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;209.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<h3 id="iphone_15_cases">iPhone 15 Cases</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/finewoven-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922725" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking nearly 30 percent off the new FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus this week. Not every color is discounted, but those that are have prices as low as <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;33.60</strong></a> for these brand new accessories, down from &#36;59.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;27 OFF</div>iPhone 15 FineWoven Case for &#36;33.60</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWV2WZW%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;12 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case for &#36;47.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="magsafe_chargers">MagSafe Chargers</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/magsafe-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922724" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Woot and Amazon, you can get a few of Apple's best wireless and MagSafe chargers for all-time low prices. This includes the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;29.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00 and the Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"><strong>&#36;34.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00. Amazon has the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
These are great stocking stuffer present ideas for the holiday season, and all the Woot accessories are in new condition.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;29.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;44 OFF</div>Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for &#36;34.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h3 id="siri_remote">Siri Remote</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/siri-remote-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922723" /><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking to replace or upgrade your Siri Remote, Woot has the second generation model with Lightning at its lowest-ever price of <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"><strong>&#36;44.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;59.00. Like other Woot Apple accessory sales going on right now, this one is in new condition and has a one year Apple limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>Siri Remote (Lightning) for &#36;44.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="keyboards">Keyboards</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/keyboard-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922722" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is discounting the Magic Keyboard Folio to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This keyboard works with the 10th generation iPad, and Amazon's new sale price is now the steepest discount we've ever tracked for this accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard Folio for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you have an 11-inch iPad Pro, you can match it with the 11-inch iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;299.00. This one is available in both White and Black colors, and it's another best-ever price. This sale has been fluctuating in price, so if you don't see it available, be sure to check back again soon.<br/>
<br/>
The only downside is Amazon's current shipping estimate, which has a generous one to four week estimate for shipping. This still guarantees a delivery by Christmas, so if you're looking to buy it as a present and want to take advantage of this solid discount, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;120 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (11-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;179.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09322LR1R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (12.9-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="apple_pencil_2">Apple Pencil 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/apple-pencil-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874814" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;82.00 this Black Friday, down from &#36;129.00. This is a new record low price on the accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;47 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;82.00</div></a></div><h3 id="airtag">AirTag</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airtag-candycane-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874368" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.99 this week, down from &#36;99.00. This is nearly a match of the all-time low price on this model. If you want just one AirTag, Amazon has the AirTag 1-Pack for &#36;23.99, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag (4-Pack) for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0933BVK6T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>AirTag (1-Pack) for &#36;23.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<h3 id="lego">LEGO</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/lego-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923233" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Atari-Building-Adults-Pieces%2Fdp%2FB0BBJM1XDY%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1">Atari (Icons)</a> - &#36;191.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Clamshell-Collectible-Featuring-Sebastian%2Fdp%2FB0BSR9HFJB%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fcrid%3D3RFU7NP7P43PK%26keywords%3Dlego%2Blittle%2Bmermaid%26qid%3D1700604597%26sprefix%3Dlego%2Blittle%2Bmermaid%252Caps%252C112%26sr%3D8-1">Little Mermaid Royal Clamshell (Disney)</a> - &#36;111.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Disney-Celebration-Building-Creative%2Fdp%2FB0BLJ2ZB3H%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1">Up House (Disney)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Building-Project-Beautiful-Display%2Fdp%2FB08HVXZW8X%2Fref%3Dsr_1_9_mod_primary_new">Bonsai Tree (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Orchid-Building-Adults-Display%2Fdp%2FB09Q4L157D%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa">Orchid (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Succulents-Building-Adults-Display%2Fdp%2FB09Q4GWMZQ%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa">Succulents (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Wildflower-Artificial-Anniversary-Collection%2Fdp%2FB0BGQL5B3Q%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2_sspa">Wildflower Bouquet (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="more_black_friday_sales">More Black Friday Sales</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/sonos-black-friday-sale-2023/">Sonos</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/samsung-black-friday/">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/best-buy-reveals-black-friday/">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/walmart-black-friday-plans/">Walmart</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/">Anker</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="our_black_friday_guides">Our Black Friday Guides</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">The Best Black Friday AirPods Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">The Best Black Friday iPhone Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">The Best Black Friday iPad Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">The Best Black Friday HomePod Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">The Best Black Friday Apple Watch Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals/">The Best Black Friday MacBook Deals</a></li></ul> We've been tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/apple-black-friday-now-wednesday-2023/">Apple Black Friday Deals Available Already: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sunbird Shuts Down iMessage App for Android Over Security Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/sunbird-shuts-down-android-imessage-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sunbird-shuts-down-imessage-app-for-android-over-security-concerns.2411730/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 11:13:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/sunbird-shuts-down-android-imessage-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Android</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>Nothing</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sunbirdapp.com">Sunbird</a>, an app that is designed to deliver iMessages to Android devices, has been temporarily shut down due to security concerns. Sunbird this week <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Sunbird/comments/17yf44h/can_someone_repost_sunbird_notification_from_today/">sent out a notification</a> to users letting them know about the shutdown (via <em><a href="https://9to5google.com/2023/11/21/sunbird-shut-down-android-security-concerns/">9to5Google</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/sunbird-app.jpg" alt="" width="1970" height="1108" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923715" /><br/>
Sunbird said that it was investigating security issues that had been raised by the Nothing Chats iMessage app, and shortly after, told users that Sunbird usage had been paused. "We will update you when we are ready to proceed," read the notification.<br/>
<br/>
The Sunbird app was first introduced in late 2022, and it has been limited to customers that signed up for the waitlist. The Sunbird website describes the app as unifying "the world's most popular messaging apps" into a single app, with support for iMessage, SMS/MMS, Facebook Messenger, and WhatsApp.<br/>
<br/>
Using Sunbird on an Android device allowed Android users to send messages to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users that were delivered as iMessage "blue bubbles" rather than green text messages. The app claimed to have end-to-end encryption and confidential messaging for these Android to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; conversations, but those claims have been in question, leading to the pause in service.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, Sunbird <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility/">teamed up with smartphone manufacturer Nothing</a> to launch "Nothing Chats," a messaging app that promised iMessage compatibility. The high-profile announcement led to a deep dive into how Nothing Chats worked and how Sunbird, as the backbone for the feature, functioned.<br/>
<br/>
The Nothing Chats app required users to log in with their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, one of many red flags raised over Sunbird's security. <a href="https://texts.blog/2023/11/18/sunbird-security/"><em>Text.com</em></a> looked into how Sunbird works, and found that it is sending a user's &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; credentials to a Sunbird server, where those credentials are authenticated using a virtual machine running macOS. &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; credentials were being sent over HTTP, which is unencrypted.<br/>
<br/>
Nothing ended up pulling the Nothing Chats app from the Google Play Store less than 24 hours after it was announced, but Sunbird insisted that its service was secure and that &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; credentials and messages were "encrypted at all times." This turned out to be inaccurate, and there are vulnerabilities that could allow an attacker to intercept all Sunbird messages and media attachments. Sunbird employees also had direct access to a platform that stored message contents, contact information, and attachment URLs. <em><a href="https://9to5google.com/2023/11/21/sunbird-shut-down-android-security-concerns/">9to5Google</a></em> discovered that Sunbird is storing more than 630,000 media files like images, videos, and PDFs from its users.<br/>
<br/>
Texts.com ended up releasing a <a href="https://github.com/batuhan/sunbird-poc/tree/main">proof-of-concept app</a> demonstrating how easy it was for iMessage conversations sent through Sunbird and Nothing Chats to be intercepted and viewed because the content was being sent in plain text.<br/>
<br/>
Nothing said that the Nothing Chats app has been pulled "until further notice" as it works with Sunbird to "fix several bugs," but Sunbird has been quiet about the situation aside from the notification sent out to users. As <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2023/11/nothings-imessage-app-was-a-security-catastrophe-taken-down-in-24-hours/">Ars Technica</a></em> points out, Sunbird's initial response to the security concerns does not seem to have come from "a competent developer," raising questions about Sunbird's ability to address the security problems.<br/>
<br/>
Existing Sunbird and Nothing Chats users are advised to change their &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; passwords, remove the apps, <a href="https://twitter.com/batuhan/status/1725985096463724838">and follow additional steps</a> to remove their data. If the apps are reinstated, it is recommended that users do not download them.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/android/">Android</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nothing/">Nothing</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/sunbird-shuts-down-android-imessage-app/">Sunbird Shuts Down iMessage App for Android Over Security Concerns</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sunbird-shuts-down-imessage-app-for-android-over-security-concerns.2411730/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Black Friday Sale Introduces Huge Discounts on MacBooks, TVs, LEGO Sets, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/best-buy-black-friday-sale-wednesday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-black-friday-sale-introduces-huge-discounts-on-macbooks-tvs-lego-sets-and-more.2411714/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:53:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/best-buy-black-friday-sale-wednesday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's <a href="https://howl.me/ck3ASx7u9vB">Black Friday event</a> keeps adding new deals every day, and it includes the best prices we've ever tracked on Apple's entire line of MacBook Air and MacBook Pro computers. Additionally, we're seeing great deals on TVs, audio equipment, smart home products, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923671" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total members will be able to shop exclusive deals during this time, and save even more compared to non-members. This includes those all-time low prices on MacBook Air and MacBook Pro notebooks. You can <a href="https://howl.me/ck0EWogYi7m"><strong>sign up for these memberships</strong></a> on Best Buy's website, and prices start at &#36;49.99/year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck3ASx7u9vB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Best Buy Black Friday Event</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are plenty of deals beyond electronics in Best Buy's sale, including <a href="https://howl.me/ck3B6z6AXFB">low prices on LEGO sets</a> and up to 45 percent off major appliances. For the latter category, Best Buy has <a href="https://howl.me/ck3B5XT1Rha">up to &#36;1,490 in savings on select French door refrigerators</a>, as well as up to &#36;200 in Best Buy e-gift cards with qualifying purchases.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923674" /><br/>
<br/>
Remember that for many of the deals seen below, you'll need to have a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership in order to see these record low prices. If you don't have a membership, Best Buy's discounts still offer solid second-best prices this week.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2JNVcOlvx">13-inch M1 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> for &#36;749.99 (&#36;249 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy">13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> for &#36;899.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2JTmfhKJS">13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB)</a> for &#36;1,199.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ">15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB)</a> for &#36;999.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU">15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB)</a> for &#36;1,199.00 (&#36;300 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923678" /><br/>
<br/>
Similar to the MacBook Air, the best MacBook Pro deals on Best Buy will require you to have a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership. If you don't, you can still net solid second-best prices on these brand new 2023 computers.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J5s7YV3A">14-inch 8-Core M3/512GB</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,599.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J4wxoIRg">14-inch 8-Core M3/1TB</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,799.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J1zgtu9i">14-inch 11-Core M3 Pro/512GB</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;1,999.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J2hhxLv5">14-inch 12-Core M3 Pro/1TB</a> - &#36;2,199.00, down from &#36;2,399.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J3yeuKxf">14-inch 14-Core M3 Max/1TB</a> - &#36;2,949.00, down from &#36;3,199.00 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2J96pslQT">16-inch 12-Core M3 Pro/18GB RAM/512GB</a> - &#36;2,249.00, down from &#36;2,499.00 (&#36;250 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck2Ka1oWkCW">16-inch 12-Core M3 Pro/36GB RAM/512GB</a> - &#36;2,649.00, down from &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;250 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/tvs-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923680" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0EZNrRGkg">TCL 40-inch S-Class 1080p Smart TV with Fire TV</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BnaSOPqN">LG 65-inch LED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E0KC17zf">LG 48-inch Class A2 Series OLED Smart TV</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E1y2bnRl">Samsung 75-inch Class TU690T Crystal 4K Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;579.99, down from &#36;749.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E2vxgpnW">LG 86-inch Class UR7800 Series LED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BoaZNrLh">Samsung 65-inch OLED 4K UHD TV</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E3qCGZKD">Samsung 77-inch Class S89C OLED 4K UHD Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;3,599.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Video Games</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ps5-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923681" /><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should note that the Xbox Series X deal listed below is aimed at My Best Buy Plus/Total members, and at &#36;100 off it marks the lowest we've ever seen this console go down to. If you don't have an account, you can still get a solid &#36;50 off the Xbox.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BWT6T84V">Halo Infinite</a> - &#36;14.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BUQUrS11">Mario + Rabbids Sparks of Hope</a> - &#36;14.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BVCkJY3u">Star Wars Jedi: Survivor</a> - &#36;34.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BTGUHARK">Hogwarts Legacy</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BWkQoMm2">Final Fantasy XVI</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BQX1ZFOr">Xbox Wireless Controller</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BQtCHGXI">PS5 DualSense Wireless Controller</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BODf5yvN">Xbox Series X 1TB Console</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E9SazKdl">PlayStation 5 Console Marvel's Spider-Man 2 Bundle</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;559.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Computers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/computers-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923682" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E4YyH4SH">Lenovo Ideapad 15.6-inch Touch Laptop</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E6EIOZzh">HP Victus 15.6-inch R5 Gaming Laptop</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E7tbh9Pm">HP Envy 2-in-1 14-inch Touch-Screen Laptop</a> - &#36;749.99, down from &#36;1,079.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/monitors-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923685" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BxogbUUG">LG 24-inch FreeSync Monitor</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;169.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BydkL05p">HP 27-inch Monitor with Adjustable Height</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;269.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3ByXzM3nZ">Samsung Odyssey Neo G7 43-inch Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E8I85m59">LG 45-inch OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Audio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/audio-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923686" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E5RV0RNW">Samsung A Series 2.1ch Dolby & DTS and Soundbar</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3Bz2F8Yfy">Beats Studio Pro</a> - &#36;169.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0FaWEYIyf">Bose QuietComfort 45 Noise Cancelling Over-the-Ear Headphones</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BCouNscy">Bose Smart Soundbar 900</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;749.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BBqQRZZL">Sonos Arc</a> - &#36;719.20, down from &#36;899.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smart Home</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ring-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923687" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3B08DxDnh">TP-Link Tapo Smart Plug Mini with Matter (3-Pack)</a> - &#36;22.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BYdKuoba">Echo Show 5</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0Fcfj5lH8">Ring Video Doorbell</a> - &#36;54.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BYTc9kd2">Nest Hub Max</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BZwxKC0E">Nest Learning Smart Thermostat</a> - &#36;179.99, down from &#36;249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0FcYe8Cu6">Arlo Pro 4 Spotlight Camera Security Bundle</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3B0gt55Ed">Eero Pro Mesh Wi-Fi System</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;549.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>LEGO</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/lego-best-buy-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923690" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BEksZ9pZ">Ford Mustang Shelby GT500 (Technic)</a> - &#36;37.49, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BFbdX2lG">Orchid (Botanical Collection)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BFLMsZzM">Succulents (Botanical Collection)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BDwDHKFP">Wildflower Bouquet (Botanical Collection)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BGk9OSix">Up House (Disney)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BJbfJBeQ">The Child (Star Wars)</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BL400wdv">BD-1 (Star Wars)</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BK2UC94R">Vespa 125 (Icons)</a> - &#36;84.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BJSw9ScD">Medieval Blacksmith (Ideas)</a> - &#36;169.99, down from &#36;179.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3BG32qfLg">NASA Space Shuttle Discovery (Icons)</a> - &#36;179.95, down from &#36;199.95</li></ul> You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/best-buy-black-friday-sale-wednesday/">Best Buy Black Friday Sale Introduces Huge Discounts on MacBooks, TVs, LEGO Sets, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-black-friday-sale-introduces-huge-discounts-on-macbooks-tvs-lego-sets-and-more.2411714/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Trials New Option to Turn Off Personalized Recommendations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/spotify-trials-disable-personal-recommendations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-trials-new-option-to-turn-off-personalized-recommendations.2411711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 07:14:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/spotify-trials-disable-personal-recommendations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify is trialing a new ability for users to turn off their personalized recommendations, according to beta code unearthed by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" /><br/>
Depending on how it works, the new option could conceivably allow users to prevent songs played on their account on behalf of other listeners from affecting their personalized recommendations. Either way, it is likely to be welcomed by Spotify users who aren't entirely satisfied with the success rate of the service's algorithms in matching new songs to their listening tastes.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify's recommendation system combines a number of machine learning and AI-driven methods. The service's algorithm analyzes listening history, favorite genres, and the time of day that users listen to music, and bases its personal recommendations on these parameters. This process is combined with content-based filtering, which analyzes the audio of a song that a user interacts with, and takes into account characteristics like time signature, key, and tempo to recommend new songs with similar characteristics.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify's recommendations system also uses something called collaborative filtering. For example, if two users have similar music tastes, Spotify might recommend songs one user has listened to but the other hasn't. However, this can end up with Spotify recommending more popular items more often than lesser known songs, resulting in an "echo chamber" effect, and for new users with no listening history it is next to useless.<br/>
<br/>
It's not clear when the new option to turn off personal recommendations will appear for Spotify users, or whether the trial is region-specific. Spotify simply says it is "evaluating the ability," and thanks users for trying it out to help make Spotify better.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-music-listening-history-focus-filter/">How to Stop Your Kids From Ruining Your Apple Music Recommendations</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple is introducing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-music-listening-history-focus-filter/">similar function</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers in iOS 17.2, in the form of an additional Focus filter that can automatically turns off a user's ‌&zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;‌ listening history. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-iphone-features-december-ios-update/">substantial software update</a> is expected to land on iPhones in December.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/spotify-trials-disable-personal-recommendations/">Spotify Trials New Option to Turn Off Personalized Recommendations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-trials-new-option-to-turn-off-personalized-recommendations.2411711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explores iPhone &#039;Privacy Screens&#039;, Macs With Adjustable Viewing Angles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/iphone-privacy-screens-adjustable-viewing-angles/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explores-iphone-privacy-screens-macs-with-adjustable-viewing-angles.2411700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:56:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/iphone-privacy-screens-adjustable-viewing-angles/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Patent</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this year, <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/apple-iphone-security-theft-passcode-data-privacya-basic-iphone-feature-helps-criminals-steal-your-digital-life-cbf14b1a">The Wall Street Journal</a></em> published an in-depth report highlighting instances of thieves watching <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners enter their passcode before stealing the device in order to gain access to the device, data, and money.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/appleprivacyad-cleaned.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="872" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833885" /><br/>
With knowledge of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s passcode, a thief can easily reset the victim's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> password in the Settings app, even if <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> is enabled. It also allows a thief to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, send Apple Cash, and access banking apps using passwords stored in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain. <br/>
<br/>
"We sympathize with users who have had this experience and we take all attacks on our users very seriously, no matter how rare," said Apple in response to the report. "We will continue to advance the protections to help keep user accounts secure." <br/>
<br/>
Apple did not provide any specific details about any next steps it might take to increase security, but there are indications that Apple may be seeking a hardware solution to scupper the scourge of so-called "shoulder surfers." <br/>
<br/>
Current displays on Apple devices provide a 170-degree field of view, making it easier for others to glance at your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac screen. To counter this, two new patents by Apple propose innovative solutions to restrict screen visibility to just the user.<br/>
<br/>
The first patent, "<a href="https://image-ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/11822103">Privacy Films for Curved Displays</a>," introduces a special screen covering that limits light emission to a single direction. <br/>
<br/>
Positioned directly in front of the screen, the user is witness to the display's full quality and optimal brightness. However, onlookers attempting to peek from even a slight angle to the left or right of this position are not so lucky, and see either a completely obscured view or, more likely, a blurred image.<br/>
<br/>
The second patent, "<a href="https://image-ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/11822165">Displays with Adjustable Angles of View</a>," is designed for flat screens, and describes how a user could adjust a Mac's viewing angle in real-time to act as a filter. <br/>
<br/>
In one embodiment, the user is able to control the screen's polarization using an array of adjustable louvres, effectively limiting visibility from side-on viewing angles and increasing the privacy of onscreen content. The patent also describes how a liquid crystal element could be used that restricts the visibility of certain colors when the screen is not viewed directly. <br/>
<br/>
As with any filed patent, the technology is unlikely to appear in any product soon, if at all, but it does offer an interesting look at how Apple is considering ways to overcome privacy issues when users access their devices in public spaces.<br/>
<br/>
Until such a time, users can adopt best practices for their own smartphone privacy, such as switching from a four-digit passcode to an alphanumeric passcode, which is more difficult for thieves to spy on. This can be done in the Settings app under &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; & Passcode → Change Passcode.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/23/11/21/apple-working-on-privacy-tech-to-make-shoulder-surfing-iphone-screens-harder">AppleInsider</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent/">Patent</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/iphone-privacy-screens-adjustable-viewing-angles/">Apple Explores iPhone &#039;Privacy Screens&#039;, Macs With Adjustable Viewing Angles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explores-iphone-privacy-screens-macs-with-adjustable-viewing-angles.2411700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Touch ID Will Not Return on iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/touch-id-will-not-return-on-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-touch-id-will-not-return-on-iphone-16.2411699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 05:46:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/touch-id-will-not-return-on-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Touch ID</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup will not see the return of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> fingerprint authentication technology, a new report claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Touch-ID-Fingerprint-Sensor-Under-Display-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-888291" /><br/>
The information comes from an <a href="https://weibo.com/u/1833340431">integrated circuit expert</a> on Weibo with a track record for sharing information about Apple's plans. In a new post, they explained that most of the equipment originally used to manufacture the chips required for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s version of &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; has apparently now been permanently shut down, with the only remaining units used for the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, suggesting that Apple has no plans to resurrect &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; as a method to authenticate on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the immediate future. It is also worth pointing out that there are no noteworthy rumors about the return of Apple's fingerprint scanning technology for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup that are still dependable.<br/>
<br/>
Reports suggest that the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/13/iphone-se-4-to-feature-action-button-and-more/">will feature Face ID</a>, replacing the last &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model that still features &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj;. Even so, rumors persist that Apple is working on under-display fingerprint technology that could debut <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/09/apple-researching-under-screen-touch-id/">around 2026</a> – the same time frame that the company is ostensibly planning to move <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> under the display of the device.<br/>
<br/>
The Weibo source was first to report that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> would retain the A15 Bionic chip, with the A16 being exclusive to the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ Pro models. They recently said that the chip designed for the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌ Plus will be made using a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/">distinct manufacturing process</a>, differing fundamentally from the A17 Pro chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, to reduce production costs. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/touch-id-will-not-return-on-iphone-16/">Report: Touch ID Will Not Return on iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-touch-id-will-not-return-on-iphone-16.2411699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT iPhone App&#039;s Voice Chat Feature Now Free to All Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/chatgpt-app-voice-chat-free-to-all/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-iphone-apps-voice-chat-feature-now-free-to-all-users.2411692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 03:38:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/chatgpt-app-voice-chat-free-to-all/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI has announced that the voice chats feature in its <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/chatgpt/id6448311069">official ChatGPT app for iPhone and iPad</a> is now available for everyone to use, no subscription required.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/chatgpt-for-iphone-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896306" /><br/>
OpenAI introduced voice chats in its ChatGPT app back in September. The feature gives users the option of speaking conversationally with the chat bot instead of typing, but it was previously only available to Plus and Enterprise subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
Tuesday's <a href="https://x.com/gdb/status/1727067288740970877?s=20">announcement</a> by OpenAI co-founder Greg Brockman changes all that, and ChatGPT Voice has now rolled out for all free users on iOS and Android.<br/>
<br/>
OpenAI's ChatGPT has long been accessible <a href="https://openai.com/">on the web</a> and has previously been made available on iOS through multiple third-party apps, many of which are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/25/chatgpt-scam-apps-mac-app-store/">little better than scam apps</a>, but the legitimate app gives users a safe way to use ChatGPT on the go.<br/>
<br/>
For those unfamiliar with ChatGPT, it is an AI-based chatbot that uses generative artificial intelligence to answer questions and provide advice on all manner of subjects. History is synced across devices, so you can see your ChatGPT interactions both on the web and on iOS devices, and it integrates the Whisper speech recognition system.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ChatGPT Voice rolled out for all free users. Give it a try — totally changes the ChatGPT experience: <a href="https://t.co/DgzqLlDNYF">https://t.co/DgzqLlDNYF</a></p>&mdash; Greg Brockman (@gdb) <a href="https://twitter.com/gdb/status/1727067288740970877?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 21, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
In case you hadn't heard, it's been a tumultuous few days at OpenAI. Sam Altman, the CEO of OpenAI, was initally ousted from his position as CEO last Friday, shocking the company's investors and employees, who were informed via an internal message and the company's blog post​​. The dismissal was apparently due to internal disagreements over the direction of OpenAI​.<br/>
<br/>
Almost all of the staff at OpenAI threatened to resign if Altman was not reinstated. Then things took a turn on Wednesday morning when OpenAI <a href="https://x.com/OpenAI/status/1727206187077370115?s=20">reached an agreement</a> for Altman to return as CEO. This return is coupled with the establishment of a new board featuring Bret Taylor, formerly co-CEO of Salesforce, as chair, and Larry Summers, former U.S. Treasury Secretary. <br/>
<br/>
Microsoft, a financial backer of OpenAI, welcomed the changes. "We believe this is a first essential step on a path to more stable, well-informed, and effective governance," said Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella in a <a href="https://x.com/satyanadella/status/1727207661547233721?s=20">post on X</a>, formerly Twitter.<br/>
<br/>
"I'm looking forward to returning to OpenAI," said Altman in an <a href="https://twitter.com/sama/status/1727207458324848883">earlier post</a>.<br/>
<br/>
An OpenAI account is required to use the ChatGPT app, and it can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/openai-chatgpt/id6448311069">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/22/chatgpt-app-voice-chat-free-to-all/">ChatGPT iPhone App&#039;s Voice Chat Feature Now Free to All Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-iphone-apps-voice-chat-feature-now-free-to-all-users.2411692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Breaking Down Apple&#039;s 2024 Adoption of Rich Communication Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/breaking-down-apples-2024-adoption-of-rich-communication-services.2411654/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 13:44:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs&#038;post_date=1700613840/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in mid-November announced that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">it will adopt Rich Communication Services (RCS) in 2024</a>, upgrading messaging standards for non-iMessage conversations. Apple's news came as a shock because Google had been aggressively pushing Apple to implement RCS for multiple years, but Apple hadn't budged.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
This guide explains everything that you need to know about RCS, including how it works, how you'll use it on Apple devices, why Apple decided to adopt it now, and the benefits that you can expect to see when support is added.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs_explained">RCS Explained</h2><br/>
Rich Communication Services, or RCS, is a communication protocol developed by the GSM Association and championed by Google. As a communication protocol, RCS is used by smartphone manufacturers and carriers to deliver text-based messages, images, and videos between devices. It's basically what will power the text messages that you send to people with your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and other Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
RCS is a replacement for SMS (Short Messaging Service) and MMS (Multimedia Messaging Service), both of which are used for data sharing over cellular networks. RCS combines the features of SMS and MMS, and adds additional functionality. It will be what allows you to send texts to people who don't have iPhones for iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs_features">RCS Features</h2><br/>
There are a number of benefits to RCS compared to the prior MMS and SMS features. Much of the improvements will be seen in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Android chats because for conversations between Apple device owners, iMessage will continue to be the default.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Support for higher resolution photos and videos.</li><br/>
 <li>Support for larger file sizes and file sharing.</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages.</li><br/>
 <li>Cross-platform emoji reactions.</li><br/>
 <li>Real-time typing indicators.</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts.</li><br/>
 <li>Ability to send messages over cellular or Wi-Fi (SMS is cellular only). There is no cost to send an RCS message over Wi-Fi.</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats.</li><br/>
 <li>Better security. Google's version of RCS has end-to-end encryption, which Apple does not intend to use. Apple will instead work with the GSMA to develop a more secure form of encryption that is baked natively into RCS.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="rcs_vs_smsmms">RCS vs SMS/MMS</h2><br/>
SMS or Short Messaging Service is supported by almost all mobile phones, and it is designed to allow you to send text messages from device to device. It is accompanied by the Mobile Messaging Service extension that supports photos, videos, and longer text messages. Both of these standards have been around for more than two decades and have fallen behind more modern chat apps in terms of features.<br/>
<br/>
RCS is essentially a modernized version of SMS/MMS that carriers and smart phone manufacturers started adopting right around a decade ago, but it has taken time for it to be supported and not all companies have added support (such as Apple), so the more universal (and more limited) SMS/MMS standards have stuck around too.<br/>
<br/>
Perhaps one of the biggest changes is the way that SMS/MMS and RCS work. SMS and MMS are carrier supported and require a cellular connection to function. RCS is supported by carriers, but RCS messages can be sent over a cellular or Wi-Fi connection, similar to iMessages, so there's no specific cellular connection requirement.<br/>
<br/>
RCS is in fact much more like WhatsApp, iMessage, Messenger, and similar chat apps, but baked into a smartphone's default text messaging app. It supports features that SMS/MMS do not, like typing indicators, high-resolution images, file transfers, and video calls.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs_and_imessage">RCS and iMessage</h2><br/>
RCS works alongside iMessage, and it does not replace iMessage. For &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; conversations and texts on any Apple device to another Apple device, iMessage will be the default.<br/>
<br/>
After RCS support is implemented, if you turn off iMessage on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it will likely default to RCS on supported devices as that will be the text messaging standard for non-iMessage communications.<br/>
<br/>
iMessage will continue to function exactly as it does now with no change for communications between Apple device users.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="what_rcs_means_for_iphone_users">What RCS Means for iPhone Users</h2><br/>
If you have friends or family members that have an Android device, you'll see an improvement in some of the frustrations that come with cross-platform messaging.<br/>
<br/>
Group texts between Android and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will be less buggy, and there won't be the same limitations on photo and video size that can cause media not to send. The tapback reactions that you use on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will have an emoji reaction equivalent on Android, so tapbacks won't be quite as confusing to your Android using friends.<br/>
<br/>
Read receipts and typing indicators will be available for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to Android communications and won't just be limited to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; iMessages when RCS rolls out.<br/>
<br/>
In general, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; owners and those with other Apple devices don't need to think about RCS or worry about it. It's a change that's going to happen in the background with no user interaction required. Communication is not changing between iPhones, and between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users, messaging will be the same, but improved in terms of reliability.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs_and_android">RCS and Android</h2><br/>
Text conversations with Android users are the primary way &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will experience RCS when it comes out. RCS will only be available when all participants in the conversation have a device and a carrier that support it, but that should encompass most Android users in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
Android devices have had RCS for some time as Google and Samsung have supported it for several years and were pushing Apple to adopt it.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, sharing photos and videos with Android users can be tricky for an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user, and sometimes photos and videos are too large or won't deliver. There are also often issues with group conversations between Android and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users, both in terms of supported features and stability.<br/>
<br/>
Talking to an Android user should be less of a hassle than it is now when RCS rolls out because features like emoji reactions will be supported, there will be typing indicators, and files and images should not fail to send.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="green_bubbles_vs._blue_bubbles">Green Bubbles vs. Blue Bubbles</h2><br/>
While it will be less frustrating to communicate with "green bubble" people on an Apple device, chat bubble colors are not changing.<br/>
<br/>
iMessage conversations will continue to be denoted with blue chat bubbles, and RCS messages will continue to be green, the same as SMS/MMS messages are now. Note that SMS and MMS aren't going away. They'll continue to be available on networks that don't support RCS and in situations where RCS is unavailable.<br/>
<br/>
RCS requires all of the devices participating in a conversation to have support for the feature, and the network needs to support it too. So if you happen to message someone who uses a carrier that doesn't support RCS or who has RCS turned off, it will fall back to SMS.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a_note_on_encryption">A Note on Encryption</h2><br/>
Google's implementation of RCS for Google Messages supports end-to-end encryption on Android devices, but it is worth noting that Apple is adopting the RCS Universal Profile created by the GSM Association and not a version of RCS modified by Google. RCS messages will be more secure, but won't be end-to-end encrypted as iMessage conversations are, at least not until updates are made to the standard.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that it plans to work with the GSM Association on further improvements for RCS, including better encryption.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="rcs_worldwide">RCS Worldwide</h2><br/>
Google, Samsung, and all U.S. carriers have adopted RCS, but in some countries, local carriers will need to add support before RCS between iPhones and other devices will be functional.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="why_is_apple_supporting_rcs_now">Why Is Apple Supporting RCS Now?</h2><br/>
Google has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/09/android-website-rcs-apple/">practically begging Apple</a> to implement support for RCS since 2022, launching a website, starting a social media campaign, filming ads, and setting up billboards all with the aim of convincing Apple to support the messaging standard.<br/>
<br/>
In September 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that adopting RCS was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/tim-cook-on-ios-rcs-buy-your-mom-an-iphone/">not a priority for Apple</a>. "I don't hear our users asking that we put a lot of energy into that at this point," he said. So what's changed? It isn't entirely clear, but regulatory issues have likely played a factor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is facing scrutiny over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, iMessage, and other proprietary technologies in several countries around the world, so by adopting a universal messaging standard, Apple is showing a willingness to support device interoperability.<br/>
<br/>
In the European Union, legislators are developing laws that would require Apple to make changes to iMessage to make it available on other platforms so that iMessage users aren't locked in to Apple devices. With RCS, iMessage will have fewer benefits that are unavailable cross-platform, and closer feature parity will be available on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="when_will_apple_adopt_rcs">When Will Apple Adopt RCS?</h2><br/>
Apple said that it plans to adopt RCS "later next year," which means at some point in 2024. The "later" wording suggests that it could come more toward the end of the year, perhaps in iOS 18, but that is not confirmed as of yet.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">Breaking Down Apple&#039;s 2024 Adoption of Rich Communication Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/breaking-down-apples-2024-adoption-of-rich-communication-services.2411654/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos to Launch &#36;400+ Headphones and Set-Top Box, Competing with Apple Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/sonos-headphones-set-top-box/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-to-launch-400-headphones-and-set-top-box-competing-with-apple-devices.2411635/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 10:49:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/sonos-headphones-set-top-box/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Popular speaker company Sonos</a> is planning to enter several new product markets that will see it competing with Apple devices, according to a new report from <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-21/sonos-plans-400-500-headphones-tv-set-top-box-video-roam-2-new-sound-bar">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airpods-max-cyber.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-875245" /><br/>
Upcoming over-ear headphones will take on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, which Apple has not yet updated. Sonos plans to offer the headphones in black and white, and features will include voice control navigation and synchronization with Sonos speakers, soundbars, and subwoofers. Sonos plans to price its over-ear headphones at &#36;400 to &#36;500, which is in line with the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; as well as over-ear headphones from companies like Sony and Bose.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s report suggests that Sonos isn't aiming to introduce a more technical feature set than Apple provides, with the company instead focusing on customization and fine-tuning sound with a "Passport" app. Sonos has been working on the headphones for several years, and they are set to be available as early as April 2024. In the future, the company may also develop a set of earbuds that would be similar to the AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
In late 2024 or 2025, Sonos will introduce a set-top streaming box akin to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. The device will serve as a hub for Sonos audio equipment with support for Dolby Atmos and Dolby Vision, and it will offer apps and streaming services much like existing set-top boxes.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos is developing an Android-based operating system for the set-top box, expected to be priced somewhere between &#36;150 and &#36;200. Talks are being conducted with cable companies about possible live television offerings, and Sonos may even create its own video service.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos is developing new amplifiers and in-ceiling speakers for professional installers, a version of the Era 100 speakers for businesses, and a high-end TV sound bar that will be an update to the Arc. For consumers, Sonos is developing a new version of the Sub that will sync with the planned set-top box, along with an updated Roam speaker.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Sonos CEO Patrick Spence confirmed that Sonos is planning to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/">enter a new product category</a> that will "complement" current Sonos devices and that will "delight customers and drive immediate revenue." Sonos expects to generate more than &#36;100 million from new products in 2024.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/sonos-headphones-set-top-box/">Sonos to Launch &#36;400+ Headphones and Set-Top Box, Competing with Apple Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-to-launch-400-headphones-and-set-top-box-competing-with-apple-devices.2411635/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Heartwarming &#039;Fuzzy Feelings&#039; Holiday Ad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-fuzzy-feelings-holiday-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-heartwarming-fuzzy-feelings-holiday-ad.2411625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:18:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-fuzzy-feelings-holiday-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared its annual holiday-themed ad, which is titled "Fuzzy Feelings." This year, the mini film focuses on an animator who is working on a holiday-themed video in the spare moments she has off from her office job.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Fuzzy Feelings Apple Holiday Film" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/LMH5-IHrras" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The stop motion video stars her curmudgeonly boss, who is shown chastising her for being late, giving her last minute work, and generally being miserable. She finds an outlet in depicting him in uncomfortable situations, such as being shocked by Christmas lights or covered by snow while standing out on the street.<br/>
<br/>
After her seemingly horrible boss hands out handmade holiday gifts, she sees another side of him, and changes her animation to something much more positive.<blockquote>Creativity has the power to change the way we see each other, and the world. Sometimes, seeing things through a new lens can make all the difference. You make the holidays.</blockquote>Apple shares a unique holiday ad each year, and these ads often win awards. Apple accompanied the video with a behind-the-scenes look at how it was filmed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Fuzzy Feelings: Behind the Scenes Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zDVQ3he7lVA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
According to Apple, it was created using an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max and then edited on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-fuzzy-feelings-holiday-ad/">Apple Shares Heartwarming &#039;Fuzzy Feelings&#039; Holiday Ad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-heartwarming-fuzzy-feelings-holiday-ad.2411625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Expands Black Friday Sale With Big Discounts on Monitors, Smartphones, Fridges, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/samsung-expands-black-friday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-expands-black-friday-sale-with-big-discounts-on-monitors-smartphones-fridges-and-more.2411622/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:44:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/samsung-expands-black-friday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has expanded its <a href="https://howl.me/ck3cNcgXTyo">Black Friday sale</a> with new discounts across smartphones, smartwatches, tablets, computers, and home appliances. This is in addition to the deals we've been tracking on Samsung's best TVs and monitors, like the Smart Monitor M8 and ViewFinity S9 5K Display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-best-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923404" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Right now, both of these have all-time low prices on Amazon. The Smart Monitor M8 is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> (&#36;300 off) and the ViewFinity S9 5K Display is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSAMSUNG-ViewFinity-Thunderbolt-DisplayPort-LS27C900PANXZA%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2Fref%3Dsr_1_3%3Fcrid%3D2UE1OI1RNSBZ3%26keywords%3Dsamsung%2Bviewfinity%2Bs9%26qid%3D1700578795%26sprefix%3Dsamsung%2Bviewfinity%252Caps%252C133%26sr%3D8-3"><strong>&#36;1,265.31</strong></a> (&#36;334 off). The latter deal has been fluctuating on Amazon, so if it does disappear, Samsung has a solid second-best offer at <a href="https://howl.me/ck3bAoFu1ed">&#36;1,299.99</a> for the next few days.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck3cNcgXTyo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Samsung Black Friday</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung is encouraging users to shop through the Shop Samsung mobile app this season, which has some exclusive deals and deep discounts on smartphones, smartwatches, and mobile accessories. Clicking any of the Samsung links in this post while on mobile should give you the option to install the app.<br/>
<br/>
Other than monitors and TVs, we're also now tracking quite a few deals on refrigerators, tablets, and computers below. These sale prices will be live for this week only, so be sure to check out Samsung's event before the best prices of the year disappear.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smart-monitor-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923411" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Smart Monitor M8</a> - &#36;399.99 at Amazon, down from &#36;699.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bAoFu1ed">ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tF40hlZ8">27-inch Odyssey G32A Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;179.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tFfAKEc2">34-inch ViewFinity S50GC Monitor</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tEtLSIa0">49-inch Odyssey G9 QLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tDoV18FW">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/the-frame-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923410" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tOGqagCf">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tJBTe3BC">The Frame QLED 4K TV</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000, starting at just &#36;549.99 for 32-inch</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tNGTQwIP">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,500.00, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tKrmpTeJ">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,799.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tLk05pDX">55-inch OLED TV</a> - &#36;1,899.99, down from &#36;2,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tL5nOtB2">85-inch Neo QLED 8K TV</a> - &#36;5,499.99, down from &#36;7,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tPlYX1Pr">S-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;899.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tMHeYe4E">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;1,899.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Refrigerators</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/fridge-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923409" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bEJD0D8M">Bespoke Side-by-Side Fridge with Beverage Center</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;2,314.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bK4pflLh">Large Capacity 3-Door Fridge with AutoFill Water Pitcher</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;2,423.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bGNJbhW5">Bespoke 3-Door French Door Fridge with Beverage Center</a> - &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;3,114.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bJgrsA7u">Bespoke 4-Door French Door Fridge</a> - &#36;1,999.00, down from &#36;3,114.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bFYM0t73">Bespoke 4-Door Flex Fridge with Family Hub</a> - &#36;3,099.00, down from &#36;5,114.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smartphones</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/smartphone-samsung.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923408" /><br/>
If you're shopping for a Samsung smartphone this week, there are extra cash discounts to be found on these devices when shopping via the Shop Samsung mobile app, beyond the trade-in bonus offers listed below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bP336HUQ">Galaxy S23 Ultra</a> - Get up to &#36;800 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bScBfKwa">Galaxy S23</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bRePchi9">Galaxy S23+</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bS9XCBv7">Galaxy Z Fold5</a> - Get a free storage upgrade and up to &#36;1,000 instant trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bTLe6f99">Galaxy Z Flip5</a> - Get up to &#36;600 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bUDQL4eU">Galaxy S23 FE</a> - Get up to &#36;400 instant trade-in credit with an eligible phone trade-in</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smartwatches</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Blue-Gradient.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923412" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b1V5tta3">Galaxy Watch6</a> - &#36;229.99, down from &#36;299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b0F2zDo6">Galaxy Watch6 Classic</a> - &#36;319.99, down from &#36;399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b2LyTQlI">Galaxy Watch5 Pro</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;449.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Earbuds</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-earbuds.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923407" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b470zj6i">Galaxy Buds FE</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b4wDOGNP">Galaxy Buds2</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3b3WAwsgE">Galaxy Buds2 Pro</a> - &#36;159.99, down from &#36;229.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Computers & Tablets</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-tablets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923406" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bZxvOKFk">Galaxy Book3 Pro 360</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,899.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bYSZQfan">Galaxy Book3 Ultra</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;2,399.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bXD80QQL">Galaxy Tab S9 FE</a> - Get &#36;50 off and up to &#36;350 instant trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck3bWuaccbI">Galaxy Tab S9 Ultra</a> - Get a free storage upgrade and up to &#36;700 instant trade-in credit</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/samsung-expands-black-friday/">Samsung Expands Black Friday Sale With Big Discounts on Monitors, Smartphones, Fridges, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-expands-black-friday-sale-with-big-discounts-on-monitors-smartphones-fridges-and-more.2411622/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins Selling Refurbished AirPods Pro 2 With Lightning Case in Select Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-refurbished-airpods-pro-2-lightning-case/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-airpods-pro-2-with-lightning-case-in-select-countries.2411611/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 07:00:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-refurbished-airpods-pro-2-lightning-case/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in recent days began selling refurbished second-generation AirPods Pro for the first time in select European countries, <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">including the U.K.</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/at/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Austria</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/be-fr/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Belgium</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Germany</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/ie/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Ireland</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/nl/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">the Netherlands</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/pl/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Poland</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/ch-de/shop/refurbished/accessories/airpods">Switzerland</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862208" /><br/>
Importantly, these are the second-generation AirPods Pro with a Lightning/MagSafe charging case, originally released in November 2022. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">updated the second-generation AirPods Pro</a> with a USB-C/MagSafe charging case and a few other changes in September 2023, but those are not yet available on Apple's refurbished store.<br/>
<br/>
The refurbished AirPods Pro are discounted by approximately 15% compared to original pricing. Apple says all of its refurbished products undergo "full functionality testing" and are "put through a thorough cleaning process and inspection."<br/>
<br/>
Keep in mind that there are often better deals available from third-party resellers, although deals in European countries can be harder to find. In the U.S., brand new AirPods Pro with a USB-C charging case are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/19/black-friday-deals-airpods-2-2/">currently on sale for &#36;189.99 on Amazon</a>, so U.S. customers should avoid purchasing these refurbished ones once available there.<br/>
<br/>
Apple began selling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/04/apple-refurbished-airpods-3/">refurbished third-generation AirPods</a> earlier this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-refurbished-airpods-pro-2-lightning-case/">Apple Begins Selling Refurbished AirPods Pro 2 With Lightning Case in Select Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-airpods-pro-2-with-lightning-case-in-select-countries.2411611/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE Keeps Dropping in Price For Black Friday, Now Down to Just &#36;179</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-watch-se-black-friday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-keeps-dropping-in-price-for-black-friday-now-down-to-just-179.2411605/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 06:26:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-watch-se-black-friday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 2022 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE has further dropped in price on Amazon today, down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2F5NJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.00</strong></a>, from its original price of &#36;249.00. This beats the price we tracked over the weekend by &#36;10 and is a new all-time low price on the second-generation wearable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-se-gold.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923362" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of color options, you'll find three Aluminum Cases at this price: <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2F5NJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Starlight Aluminum with Starlight Sport Loop</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Silver Aluminum with Winter Blue Sport Loop</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Midnight Aluminum with Midnight Sport Loop</a>. Delivery windows start at around November 22 and go through November 26 for most United States residences.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;179.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
More than just the 40mm GPS model is on sale, as you can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE at a new all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3GRK2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;209.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;279.00. This is again beating the weekend's deal by &#36;10 and is the best price currently available online for the wearable.<br/>
<br/>
In terms of colors, the same three Aluminum Cases are available at this price: <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Starlight Aluminum with Starlight Sport Loop</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3GRK2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Silver Aluminum with Winter Blue Sport Loop</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Midnight Aluminum with Midnight Sport Loop</a>. Delivery dates are the same as well, ranging between November 22 and November 26.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;209.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for cellular devices, those prices haven't changed, but they're still at record lows. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7PF7V%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">40mm Cellular is priced at &#36;239.00</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCHR51%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">44mm Cellular is priced at &#36;269.00</a>, both of which are &#36;60 off and available in multiple colors.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-watch-se-black-friday/">Apple Watch SE Keeps Dropping in Price For Black Friday, Now Down to Just &#36;179</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-keeps-dropping-in-price-for-black-friday-now-down-to-just-179.2411605/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Succession Plans &#039;Very Detailed&#039;, Says Tim Cook</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-ceo-succession-plan-tim-cook/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-succession-plans-very-detailed-says-tim-cook.2411594/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 04:45:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-ceo-succession-plan-tim-cook/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> has revealed that Apple has "very detailed" succession plans in place for when the time comes to replace him as chief executive of the company, but he also said he has no intention of going anywhere just yet.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JXQYO8poXC8?si=LA8kqQMWr6vpopXF" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In a 45-minute interview for the BBC Sounds podcast <em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JXQYO8poXC8">Dua Lipa: At Your Service</a></em> hosted by singer Dua Lipa, Cook admitted that he does not know how long he will remain at Apple. <br/>
<br/>
"I love it," he said, reflecting back on 25 years at the company. "I can't envision my life without being there, so I'll be there for a while." However, when asked if there was any succession plan at Apple, Cook continued: <br/>
<blockquote>"We're a company that believes in working on succession plans, so we have very detailed succession plans. Because something unpredictable can always happen. I could step off the wrong curb tomorrow. Hopefully that doesn't happen, I pray that it doesn't."<br/>
<br/>
Dua Lipa: "Are you able to say who is in line for succession?"<br/>
<br/>
"I can't say that, but I would say that my job is to prepare several people for the ability to succeed, and I really want the person to come from within Apple, the next CEO. So that's my role: That there's several for the board to pick from."</blockquote>In the broad-ranging interview, the Apple CEO described a day in the life of &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj;, and shared his experience growing up in a blue-collar family in Alabama, and the arc of his career that ultimately brought him to Apple. <br/>
<br/>
The 63-year-old also discussed Apple's environmental sustainability efforts, as well as his thoughts on the excessive use of smartphones, the value of collaboration and equal representation, philanthropy, and the promise and perils of AI, generative AI, and the "life-changing" potential of large language models. You can watch the full interview on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JXQYO8poXC8">YouTube</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/apple-ceo-succession-plan-tim-cook/">Apple CEO Succession Plans &#039;Very Detailed&#039;, Says Tim Cook</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-succession-plans-very-detailed-says-tim-cook.2411594/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Gains Email Address Verification for Authenticating Accounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/whatsapp-email-verification-authenticate-account/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-gains-email-address-verification-for-authenticating-accounts.2411581/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 02:05:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/whatsapp-email-verification-authenticate-account/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		<category>WABetaInfo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp has started allowing users to authenticate their account on a device with an email address as an alternative to using a phone number, for times when cellular coverage is poor. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
The new option to link an account to an email address does not replace SMS verification via a six-pin code, and opening a WhatsApp account still requires the user to provide a number. But with email verification, existing users now also have the means to authenticate their account on a device with an internet connection even if their cellular service is unavailable. <br/>
<br/>
Spotted by <a href="https://wabetainfo.com/whatsapp-for-ios-23-24-70-whats-new/">WABetaInfo</a>, the new feature is rolling out today as part of version 23.24.70 of WhatsApp for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. To use email verification in the updated app, tap the Settings tab, choose Account, then select Email Address.<br/>
<br/>
WhatsApp has also been working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/25/whatsapp-usernames-in-development/">username feature</a> that could potentially provide people on the messaging service with an additional layer of privacy when communicating with others. <br/>
<br/>
The username feature is still in development, so it's too early to tell how they will work when they are rolled out, but it could be that the platform intends to let users reach other people by entering a username instead of a phone number, similar to Telegram. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wabetainfo/">WABetaInfo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/21/whatsapp-email-verification-authenticate-account/">WhatsApp Gains Email Address Verification for Authenticating Accounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-gains-email-address-verification-for-authenticating-accounts.2411581/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Again Rumored to Include Tetraprism Telephoto Lens With 5X Optical Zoom</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-telephoto-lens-tetraprism/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-again-rumored-to-include-tetraprism-telephoto-lens-with-5x-optical-zoom.2411568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 18:09:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-telephoto-lens-tetraprism/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Both the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max will include Apple's tetraprism Telephoto lens with improved zoom capabilities, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/大立光潛望鏡鏡頭良率-獲利顯著提升-為2024年潛望鏡相機顯著成長的主要受益者-largans-periscope-lens-yield-profitability-improves-6b94601b5710">reiterated today</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPhone-16-Cameras-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919420" /><br/>
Apple introduced a new tetraprism lens system for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max, enabling 5x optical zoom for the first time. The camera technology was not added to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, marking one of the first times that Apple has added camera technology to one Pro device and not the other.<br/>
<br/>
The limitation was rumored to be because of space constraints, with only the Pro Max able to accommodate the hardware, but yield may have also been a factor. According to Kuo, when lens supplier Largan was producing the tetraprism hardware for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max in the third quarter of 2023, production yield was at just 40 percent. Yield has now improved to 70 percent or more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning to increase the size of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro to 6.3 inches, up from 6.1 inches, which will allow for more space for camera hardware. With the size increase and the yield improvement, Apple has addressed the factors that likely kept the tetraprism lens limited to the larger Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It is not yet clear if Apple has plans to make improvements to the tetraprism lens in 2024. One rumor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/18/iphone-16-pro-max-super-telephoto-camera/">has suggested</a> Apple is working on a "super telephoto camera" with a much longer focal length, but we've heard little about it at this point.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-telephoto-lens-tetraprism/">iPhone 16 Pro Again Rumored to Include Tetraprism Telephoto Lens With 5X Optical Zoom</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-again-rumored-to-include-tetraprism-telephoto-lens-with-5x-optical-zoom.2411568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Black Friday Deals Available Now: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/apple-black-friday-now-monday-2023/</link>
		<comments></comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 15:01:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/apple-black-friday-now-monday-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're now just two days away from Black Friday, and we're tracking the best prices of all-time on multiple Apple products, including AirPods, iPad, MacBook, iPhone, and more. Of course, there's no guarantee that better prices won't appear later in the holiday season, but if you want to shop right now these are the best deals currently available on each product.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/General-Black-Friday-Deals-2022-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874255" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Specifically, in this article we're sharing all of the Apple products that currently have all-time low prices, or discounts that are at least very close to their record-low prices. Every deal shared below is available to purchase right now, and <strong>you can use the links below to jump directly to the section you're shopping for today.</strong><br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="#homepod">HomePod</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#airpods">AirPods</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#iphone">iPhone</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#ipad">iPad</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#mac">Mac</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#apple_watch">Apple Watch</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#accessories">Accessories</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#more_black_friday_sales">More Black Friday Sales</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#our_black_friday_guides">Our Black Friday Guides</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
For more Black Friday deals, particularly including current and upcoming sales from third-party accessory makers, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="homepod">HomePod</h2><br/>
<h3 id="homepod_2nd_gen">HomePod (2nd Gen)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/homepod-candycanes-1.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922530" /><br/>
<br/>
B&H Photo has been the only retailer with a consistent discount on Apple's second generation HomePod. Right now, you can get it in both colors for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. While not a huge markdown, this continues to be the best price we've ever tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>HomePod (Gen 2) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><h2 id="airpods">AirPods</h2><br/>
<h3 id="airpods_2">AirPods 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922536" /><br/>
<br/>
We originally tracked the AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00 at Amazon in early November, but that sale quickly expired. For now, you can get the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This version of the AirPods is perfect for anyone on your holiday shopping list who may be asking for a simple and reliable pair of wireless earbuds, particularly at this insanely low price tag. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_3">AirPods 3</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-3-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922535" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;139.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. These are upgraded in a few ways from the AirPods 2, with spatial audio, Adaptive EQ, force sensor controls, sweat and water resistance, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_pro_2">AirPods Pro 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-pro-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922534" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the Pro lineup, Verizon has the AirPods Pro 2 (Lightning) for <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation%2F"><strong>&#36;184.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. Amazon also has the AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) at their all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;64 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (Lightning) for &#36;184.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_max">AirPods Max</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-max-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922533" /><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the high-end AirPods Max are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;549.00. Discounts on the AirPods Max have been rare over the past few months, so this one is a second-best price on the over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone">iPhone</h2><br/>
<h3 id="att">AT&T</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922708" /><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fdeals%2F">AT&T</a> quite a few sales and offers for multiple iPhone 15 devices, including up to &#36;1,000 off the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-max.html">iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> with an eligible smartphone trade-in. Models with lower storage capacities can be purchased at no cost thanks to these discounts, and of course you'll need to purchase the new smartphone on a qualifying installment agreement. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get up to &#36;830 off the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15.html">iPhone 15</a> or <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-plus.html">iPhone 15 Plus</a> as well, with the same stipulations as the Pro devices. Both offers will be delivered via monthly bill credits, starting within three bills after trade-in is completed. It'll be applied in equal amounts over the term of your installment agreement.<br/>
<br/>
For the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max offer, you'll need to trade in a device with a value of &#36;230 or higher to get the full &#36;1,000 off markdown. You'll get up to &#36;830 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;130 to &#36;229 and up to &#36;350 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;35 to &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
For older iPhone models, AT&T is offering the 128GB <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-14.html">iPhone 14 at &#36;10.99/month</a> with no trade-in required. Similarly, the iPhone 14 Pro is available at &#36;15/month with no trade-in required. For these, all you'll need is to purchase the smartphones on an installment plan and pick or upgrade to an eligible unlimited plan.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T is also taking <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fwearables%2F">&#36;300 off any Apple Watch</a> when you purchase two at the same time. Like smartphone plans, you'll have to buy two Apple Watches on an installment plan, add at least one new line, and activate both on your wireless plan. Afterwards, you'll get up to &#36;300 in bill credits over 36 months.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="verizon">Verizon</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-15-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922707" /><br/>
At <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a>, you can get a special bundle offer if you're interested in purchasing the new <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F">iPhone 15 Pro</a> this holiday season. When you do pick up the new smartphone with a new line on an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan, Verizon will reward you with an Apple TV 4K (64GB) and six months of Apple One at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE APPLE TV 4K</div>iPhone 15 Pro at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, you can purchase <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple%2F">higher storage iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max models</a>, but at that point you'll be paying a little extra. The Apple TV 4K promotion requires a smarpthone purchase on an eligible plan and ends on November 15, while the Apple One six month promotion requires a line subscribed to an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan.<br/>
<br/>
For last year's models, you can <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus%2F">get four iPhone 14 Plus devices for free</a> along with four lines on Unlimited Welcome at &#36;120/month. A new line on any 5G Unlimited plan is required per smartphone. You can also stack this with Verizon's current tablet and smartwatch promotions, which offer up to &#36;279.99 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
Verizon is also a great place to buy stocking stuffers for techies during the holiday season with its abundant <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14048362?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fdeals%2Fproducts%2F">accessory sales</a>. Right now it has up to &#36;50 off Anker speakers, 30% off Nimble chargers, 20% off Apple Watch bands, and 20% off Mophie chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="visible">Visible</h3><br/>
Verizon's <a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909">Visible</a> brand has &#36;10 off its premium Visible+ service, now priced at &#36;35/month with the promo code 35FOR6 used at checkout. This promotion will last for six months, and after it ends it will return to the regular price of &#36;45/month for the Visible+ service.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF/MONTH</div>Visible+ Cellular Plan</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Visible offers all of the latest smartphones, including iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models. When you join Visible, you'll save up to &#36;240 via monthly bill credits on your account. You'll need to join Visible on a new line of service, purchase a new device, and select the Visible+ plan.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="t-mobile">T-Mobile</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519">T-Mobile</a> is providing up to &#36;1,000 off the new iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Next plan. You can get up to &#36;830 off these devices when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Plus plan.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The carrier also has a wide variety of previous generation iPhones at a discount. This includes the iPhone 13 and iPhone SE at no extra cost when purchased on select cellular plans and trading in eligible devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad">iPad</h2><br/>
<h3 id="9th_gen_ipad">9th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-1-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922714" /><br/>
<br/>
We've been tracking a great all-time low discount on the ninth generation iPad since Prime Day, and the deal is still around in November. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;229.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. At this record low price, the iPad is a perfect entry-level tablet for a kid or family member who doesn't need the tablet for work-intensive projects.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;229.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="10th_gen_ipad">10th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922713" /><br/>
<br/>
The upgraded iPad from 2022 also has a great discount on Amazon right now, with the 64GB Wi-Fi model on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. This model comes with a bigger 10.9-inch Liquid Retina display, A14 Bionic chip for a performance boost, Wi-Fi 6, and more.<br/>
<br/>
This beats the sale from earlier in the month by &#36;50 and is a new all-time low price on the iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="6th_gen_ipad_mini">6th Gen iPad Mini</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-mini-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922712" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 8.3-inch iPad mini 6 is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This iPad mini has an 8.3-inch Liquid Retina display, A15 Bionic chip, USB-C, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="5th_gen_ipad_air">5th Gen iPad Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-air-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922711" /><br/>
<br/>
Switching to iPad Air models, the 2022 64GB Wi-Fi tablet has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;599.00. That's a solid all-time low price on this model, and you can also find a few other storage configurations at record lows this time around. Note that for the majority of colors, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon to see these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JH3XS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac">Mac</h2><br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m1_macbook_air">13-inch M1 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-m1-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922931" /><br/>
<br/>
The M1 MacBook Air has returned to its steep discounted price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a> for the 256GB model, down from &#36;999.00. This is a great deal and perfect computer for anyone who needs an Apple notebook for simple email and internet browsing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m2_macbook_air">13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/m2-macbook-air-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922930" /><br/>
<br/>
At Best Buy, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,099.00. This deal is only available for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, and it's an all-time low price. You'll find a similar record low deal on the <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sc246Dch">512GB model</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="15-inch_m2_macbook_air">15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-gingerbread-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922720" /><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for the all-time low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is also available for the record low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both have all colors on sale, and they're only available at these prices for My Best Buy Plus/Total members.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's latest MacBook Air model is a great option with numerous pro-level features without the price tag. For a deep dive into all the similarities and differences between each line, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide/">read our buyer's guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_macbook_pro">M3 MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922719" /><br/>
<br/>
There are a few notable discounts on the new M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy and Amazon this week, including savings on the 14-inch and 16-inch models. These are some of the first big discounts on the M3 MacBook Pro, and you can get up to &#36;200 off these notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
For the 14-inch models at Best Buy below, note that the prices reflect My Best Buy Plus/Total member savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sZ0jMbvh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3, 512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s09UEdeF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s1XidD9X"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;2,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_imac">M3 iMac</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/imac-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922718" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is offering record low prices on the just-released M3 iMac, with prices as low as &#36;1,249.00 for the 8-Core GPU, 256GB model. In total, these sales represent up to &#36;100 off the new M3 iMac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5HSYSS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-Core GPU, 256GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch">Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_9">Apple Watch Series 9</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922717" /><br/>
<br/>
Some of the best Black Friday Apple Watch deals are focused on the new Series 9 models. You can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">41mm GPS device for &#36;329.00</a> at Amazon, down from &#36;399.00. This &#36;70 discount is a new all-time low price on the 2023 smartwatch. Likewise, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">45mm GPS is down to &#36;359.00</a> at Amazon, another &#36;70 markdown and record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for cellular models, there are a few deals to discover. Amazon has the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">41mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;429.00</a>, as well as the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">45mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;459.00</a>. Both of these are &#36;70 discounts and more all-time low prices for the smartwatch lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;429.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;459.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_ultra_2">Apple Watch Ultra 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ultra-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922928" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has a few models of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for the all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX59RZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;739.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. This sale was more expansive last week and now only a handful of Ultra 2 models are at this record low price, so if you're interested make sure to take a look at the deal before it's gone.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX59RZ8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;739.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_se">Apple Watch SE</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-se-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923276" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want a cheaper Apple Watch, Amazon has the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This one was at &#36;189.00 just last week, so this is yet another record low price for the 2022 Apple Watch SE, and you'll find multiple best-ever prices across the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;179.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;209.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<h3 id="iphone_15_cases">iPhone 15 Cases</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/finewoven-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922725" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking nearly 30 percent off the new FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus this week. Not every color is discounted, but those that are have prices as low as <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;29.04</strong></a> for these brand new accessories, down from &#36;59.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>iPhone 15 FineWoven Case for &#36;29.04</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWV2WZW%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;12 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case for &#36;47.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="magsafe_chargers">MagSafe Chargers</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/magsafe-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922724" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Woot and Amazon, you can get a few of Apple's best wireless and MagSafe chargers for all-time low prices. This includes the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;29.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00 and the Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"><strong>&#36;34.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00. Amazon has the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
These are great stocking stuffer present ideas for the holiday season, and all the Woot accessories are in new condition.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;29.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;44 OFF</div>Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for &#36;34.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h3 id="siri_remote">Siri Remote</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/siri-remote-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922723" /><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking to replace or upgrade your Siri Remote, Woot has the second generation model with Lightning at its lowest-ever price of <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"><strong>&#36;44.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;59.00. Like other Woot Apple accessory sales going on right now, this one is in new condition and has a one year Apple limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>Siri Remote (Lightning) for &#36;44.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="keyboards">Keyboards</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/keyboard-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922722" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is discounting the Magic Keyboard Folio to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This keyboard works with the 10th generation iPad, and Amazon's new sale price is now the steepest discount we've ever tracked for this accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard Folio for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you have an 11-inch iPad Pro, you can match it with the 11-inch iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;299.00. This one is available in both White and Black colors, and it's another best-ever price. This sale has been fluctuating in price, so if you don't see it available, be sure to check back again soon.<br/>
<br/>
The only downside is Amazon's current shipping estimate, which has a generous one to four week estimate for shipping. This still guarantees a delivery by Christmas, so if you're looking to buy it as a present and want to take advantage of this solid discount, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (11-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09322LR1R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (12.9-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="apple_pencil_2">Apple Pencil 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/apple-pencil-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874814" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00 this Black Friday, down from &#36;129.00. Compared to previous sales, this is a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><h3 id="airtag">AirTag</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airtag-candycane-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874368" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.99 this week, down from &#36;99.00. This is nearly a match of the all-time low price on this model. If you want just one AirTag, Amazon has the AirTag 1-Pack for &#36;23.99, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag (4-Pack) for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0933BVK6T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>AirTag (1-Pack) for &#36;23.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="miscellaneous">Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<h3 id="lego">LEGO</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/lego-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923233" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Marvel-Spider-Man-Building-Pieces%2Fdp%2FB0979GDCDT%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2">Daily Bugle (Marvel)</a> - &#36;300.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Atari-Building-Adults-Pieces%2Fdp%2FB0BBJM1XDY%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1">Atari (Icons)</a> - &#36;191.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Clamshell-Collectible-Featuring-Sebastian%2Fdp%2FB0BSR9HFJB%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fcrid%3D3RFU7NP7P43PK%26keywords%3Dlego%2Blittle%2Bmermaid%26qid%3D1700604597%26sprefix%3Dlego%2Blittle%2Bmermaid%252Caps%252C112%26sr%3D8-1">Little Mermaid Royal Clamshell (Disney)</a> - &#36;111.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Disney-Celebration-Building-Creative%2Fdp%2FB0BLJ2ZB3H%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fcrid%3D2XPQIMWHMWLYE%26keywords%3Dlego%2Bup%2Bhouse%26qid%3D1700604651%26sprefix%3Dlego%2Bup%2Bhouse%252Caps%252C105%26sr%3D8-1">Up House (Disney)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Building-Project-Beautiful-Display%2Fdp%2FB08HVXZW8X%2Fref%3Dsr_1_9_mod_primary_new">Bonsai Tree (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;37.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Orchid-Building-Adults-Display%2Fdp%2FB09Q4L157D%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa">Orchid (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Succulents-Building-Adults-Display%2Fdp%2FB09Q4GWMZQ%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1_sspa">Succulents (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;39.99, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FLEGO-Wildflower-Artificial-Anniversary-Collection%2Fdp%2FB0BGQL5B3Q%2Fref%3Dsr_1_2_sspa">Wildflower Bouquet (Botanicals)</a> - &#36;47.99, down from &#36;59.99</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="more_black_friday_sales">More Black Friday Sales</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/sonos-black-friday-sale-2023/">Sonos</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/samsung-black-friday/">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/best-buy-reveals-black-friday/">Best Buy</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/walmart-black-friday-plans/">Walmart</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/">Anker</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="our_black_friday_guides">Our Black Friday Guides</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">The Best Black Friday AirPods Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">The Best Black Friday iPhone Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">The Best Black Friday iPad Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">The Best Black Friday HomePod Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">The Best Black Friday Apple Watch Deals</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals/">The Best Black Friday MacBook Deals</a></li></ul> We've been tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/apple-black-friday-now-monday-2023/">Apple Black Friday Deals Available Now: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
