<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 04:04:14 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>England&#039;s NHS App Gains Digital Prescription Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/nhs-app-gains-digital-prescriptions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/englands-nhs-app-gains-digital-prescription-services.2417843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 02:56:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/nhs-app-gains-digital-prescriptions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>England</category>
		<category>Health</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/nhs-app/id1388411277">NHS App</a> users in England can now collect medication from a pharmacy without having to contact a GP or health center to get a paper prescription, according to <a href="https://digital.nhs.uk/services/nhs-app">NHS Digital</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/nhs-digital-prescription.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933486" /><br/>
From today, patients in England can use the NHS App to view all their prescription details, order repeat prescriptions, and generate a barcode for medication collection. The barcode replaces the traditional paper slip given by doctors.<br/>
<br/>
The national rollout follows a successful pilot in late 2023. Since then, over 1 million patients have used the app to view their prescriptions. Health Secretary Victoria Atkins told the <em><a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-68133276">BBC</a></em> the update would "ease pressures on our hardworking pharmacists and GPs - freeing up valuable time for patients and helping to cut waiting lists."<br/>
<br/>
The new functionality allows patients to see the medication prescribed, the prescription type (repeat or one-off), and who the prescribing professional is. Patients who don't have a nominated pharmacy can generate a prescription barcode for collection. The app also now shows average local hospital waiting times for elective treatment, such as hip replacements.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Accessing Digital Prescriptions in the NHS App</h2><br/>
<ol><li>Tap <strong>your health</strong> at the bottom of the screen</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>view and manage prescriptions</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Select <strong>Your approved prescriptions</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the green button on the prescription you want to view.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/how-to-nhs-app-digital-prescriptions.jpg" alt="nhs app" width="1284" height="841" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933487" /><br/>
NHS Digital says future developments for the service are now being explored, including prescription tracking to tell patients when medications are ready for collection. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/07/03/nhs-mobile-app-book-doctor-appointments/">Announced in 2018</a>, the NHS Digital app allows more than 33 million registered users to view their health record from their GP and manage hospital appointments. The NHS app is available on iOS devices <a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/nhs-app/id1388411277">through the App Store</a>, as well as on <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nhs.online.nhsonline&hl=en&gl=US">Android phones via Google Play</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/england/">England</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/health/">Health</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/nhs-app-gains-digital-prescriptions/">England&#039;s NHS App Gains Digital Prescription Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/englands-nhs-app-gains-digital-prescription-services.2417843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Warns Proposed UK Law Could &#039;Secretly Veto&#039; Global User Protections</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-warns-proposed-uk-law-could-secretly-veto-global-user-protections.2417840/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 01:13:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Security</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is "deeply concerned" that proposed changes to British surveillance legislation could give the U.K. government unprecedented powers to secretly prevent software updates from being released in any other country (via <em><a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-68128177">BBC News</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-regent-street-hires.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-863362" /><br/>
The UK government is planning to update the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA), which came into effect in 2016 and allows the British Home Office to outlaw certain encrypted services by issuing something called a Technical Capability Notice (TCN).<br/>
<br/>
Dubbed by critics as a "Snooper's Charter," the <a href="https://researchbriefings.files.parliament.uk/documents/LLN-2023-0042/LLN-2023-0042.pdf">updated Act of Parliament</a> could also allow the Home Office to decline security and privacy updates without telling the public.<br/>
<br/>
The bill proposes changes including:<br/>
<ul><li>Creating a new condition for the use of internet connection records to aid "target detection."</li><br/>
<li>Introducing an alternative, less stringent regulatory regime for the retention and examination of bulk personal datasets where individuals have little or no<br/>
expectation of privacy (such as publicly available online telephone directories).</li><br/>
<li>A new notification requirement which can be issued to selected<br/>
telecommunications operators requiring them to inform the government of<br/>
proposed changes to their products or services that could negatively impact the current ability of agencies to lawfully access data.</li></ul><br/>
Apple opposes the requirement to inform the Home Office of any changes to product security features before they are released, the requirement for non-U.K.-based companies to comply with changes that would affect their product globally, and having to take action immediately if requested to disable or block a feature without review or an appeals process.<br/>
<blockquote>"We're deeply concerned the proposed amendments to the Investigatory Powers Act (IPA) now before Parliament place users' privacy and security at risk," said Apple in a statement.<br/>
<br/>
"It's an unprecedented overreach by the government and, if enacted, the UK could attempt to secretly veto new user protections globally preventing us from ever offering them to customers."</blockquote>In a July 2023 letter to the Home Office, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/20/apple-threatens-to-pull-facetime-and-imessage-uk/">argued</a> that the proposed changes "would suppress innovation, stifle commerce, and — when combined with purported extraterritorial application — make the Home Office the de facto global arbiter of what level of data security and encryption are permissible." <br/>
<br/>
The company also said it would consider pulling services such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and iMessage from the U.K. rather than compromise future security. <br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, civil liberties groups including Big Brother Watch, Liberty, Open Rights Group and Privacy International, issued a joint briefing opposing aspects of the bill.<br/>
<br/>
The groups said the proposed changed could "force technology companies, including those based overseas, to inform the government of any plans to improve security or privacy measures on their platforms so that the government can consider serving a notice to prevent such changes."<br/>
<br/>
"This would be effectively transforming private companies into arms of the surveillance state and eroding the security of devices and the internet," the groups added.<br/>
<br/>
The proposed changes will be debated in the House of Lords on Tuesday.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-security/">Apple Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-deeply-concerned-uk-surveillance-law/">Apple Warns Proposed UK Law Could &#039;Secretly Veto&#039; Global User Protections</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-warns-proposed-uk-law-could-secretly-veto-global-user-protections.2417840/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CARROT Weather Coming to Apple Vision Pro With Interactive 3D Globe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/carrot-weather-for-apple-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/carrot-weather-coming-to-apple-vision-pro-with-interactive-3d-globe.2417819/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 17:58:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/carrot-weather-for-apple-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/carrot-weather-alerts-radar/id961390574">CARROT Weather</a> today announced that its app will be available on the Apple Vision Pro on Friday, complete with its signature snarky forecasts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-4.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933472" /><br/>
The popular iPhone weather app has been redesigned for visionOS, with information like the current temperature, hourly and daily forecasts, sunrise and sunset times, Moon phases, air quality, and more displayed at a glance.<br/>
<br/>
On the Vision Pro, CARROT Weather has added an interactive 3D globe that shows temperatures, wind speeds, and precipitation intensity around the world. The app's developer Brian Mueller described the globe as the "marquee feature" of the app, and said that "it's just really cool being able to look at a globe floating in your living room."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-1.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933469" /><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933470" /><br/>
Users can also interact with the snarky AI-powered character CARROT and play mini-games via the "ornament" at the bottom of the app's window.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/CARROT-Weather-Vision-Pro-3.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933471" /><br/>
Apple Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">launches on Friday</a>, and CARROT Weather said its visionOS app will be available in the App Store around 7 a.m. Pacific Time on that day. A subscription is required to access all of the app's features, with pricing in the U.S. ranging from &#36;4.99 to &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;19.99 to &#36;59.99 per year depending on the tier selected.<br/>
<br/>
CARROT Weather will be one of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/21/apple-vision-pro-third-party-apps/">over 250 apps with native visionOS support</a> on day one. Vision Pro is also compatible with over a million iPad and iPhone apps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/carrot-weather-for-apple-vision-pro/">CARROT Weather Coming to Apple Vision Pro With Interactive 3D Globe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/carrot-weather-coming-to-apple-vision-pro-with-interactive-3d-globe.2417819/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Zoom Shows Off Immersive New Vision Pro App With Personas, 3D Object Sharing and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/zoom-vision-pro-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/zoom-shows-off-immersive-new-vision-pro-app-with-personas-3d-object-sharing-and-more.2417815/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 16:22:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/zoom-vision-pro-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>Zoom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the launch of the Vision Pro just days away, popular video collaboration service Zoom <a href="https://news.zoom.us/zoom-launches-new-app-for-apple-vision-pro-to-make-hybrid-collaboration-more-immersive/">announced a Vision Pro app</a> that is set to come out on Friday, February 2. The Zoom app for Vision Pro is meant to blur the lines of in-person and remote meetings to help teams feel more connected with one another.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/zoom-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933387" /><br/>
The Zoom app will work on the "infinite canvas" of the Vision Pro, with the scalable interface able to be viewed in the real world or with a virtual backdrop. The app supports Personas, which are a spatial representation of the user in Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
A Persona is created by using the cameras on the Vision Pro, and it serves as a stand-in for the user during video calls. Personas look like the user, and are able to gesture, speak, and react based on the facial and hand movements of the Vision Pro wearer.<br/>
<br/>
With these features, Zoom users can expect to "feel like they are in the same room as their colleagues and customers" without the need for anything but the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Later in the spring, the Zoom app will add support for sharing 3D files, with the files able to "come to life" on the Vision Pro. Team Chat integration is coming as well, and users will eventually be able to pin up to five Zoom participants anywhere in their physical space.<br/>
<br/>
Pinned users will have their backgrounds removed, adding to the feel of multiple people being in the same room.<br/>
<br/>
Zoom will be available from the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/zoom/">Zoom</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/zoom-vision-pro-app/">Zoom Shows Off Immersive New Vision Pro App With Personas, 3D Object Sharing and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/zoom-shows-off-immersive-new-vision-pro-app-with-personas-3d-object-sharing-and-more.2417815/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Has Sold Approximately 200,000 Vision Pro Headsets</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-vision-pro-headset-sales/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-sold-approximately-200-000-vision-pro-headsets.2417811/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 15:17:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-vision-pro-headset-sales/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has sold upwards of 200,000 Vision Pro headsets, <em>MacRumors</em> has learned from a source with knowledge of Apple's sales numbers. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-now-available-for-pre-order/">began accepting pre-orders</a> for the Vision Pro on January 19, so the headset has been available for purchase in the U.S. for 10 days.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929938" /><br/>
Last Monday, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> claimed that Apple had sold an estimated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-already-sold-up-to-180000-vision-pros/">160,000 to 180,000 Vision Pro units</a> during the pre-order weekend for the device, so sales may have slowed somewhat since then.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro headsets for launch day home delivery sold out within hours of pre-orders launching, and in-store pickup options followed shortly after, so it is no surprise that interest in the headset has started to wane somewhat after the initial rush of orders.<br/>
<br/>
Media reviews for the Vision Pro are set to go live on Tuesday, and that could push more sales, plus there will likely be an uptick in purchases after actual consumers begin sharing hands-on experiences.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo has warned that demand for the Vision Pro could taper off quickly because of the niche market for the device. The headset is priced at &#36;3,500, which puts it out of range of many consumers. Rumors have suggested that Apple is prepared for a limited number of sales, due both to the high price of the Vision Pro and difficulty producing it.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce around half a million Vision Pro headsets, but whether it will sell that many remains to be seen.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-vision-pro-headset-sales/">Apple Has Sold Approximately 200,000 Vision Pro Headsets</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-has-sold-approximately-200-000-vision-pro-headsets.2417811/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.4 Beta Adds Stopwatch Live Activity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/ios-17-4-stopwatch-live-activity/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-stopwatch-live-activity.2417796/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 11:34:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/ios-17-4-stopwatch-live-activity/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 17.4 introduces a small but useful change for the Clock app's Stopwatch function, adding the timer to Apple's Live Activities feature. When activated through the Clock app, the Stopwatch will now show up both in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> and on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ios-17-4-stopwatch.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933379" /><br/>
The &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj; shows a small to-the-second timer, and the Lock Screen shows the full Stopwatch timer when the screen is being looked at. Pressing into the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj; shows options for pausing the Stopwatch or starting a new lap, with these controls also on the Lock Screen. After the Stopwatch is paused, swiping on it from the Lock Screen or tapping on the "X" in &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj; will clear it.<br/>
<br/>
Timers have worked with Live Activities since the feature launched with iOS 16, but the Stopwatch could only be viewed in the Clock app. The addition of Live Activities support will prevent users from activating the timer and then forgetting about it.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(<a href="https://twitter.com/hiddecollee7?lang=en">Thanks, Hidde</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/ios-17-4-stopwatch-live-activity/">iOS 17.4 Beta Adds Stopwatch Live Activity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-4-beta-adds-stopwatch-live-activity.2417796/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 17.4 Code References Mysterious homeOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-17-4-code-references-mysterious-homeos.2417794/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:57:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Code discovered by <i>MacRumors</i> in the first beta of tvOS 17.4 suggests that Apple's work on "homeOS" is continuing behind the scenes. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/homeOS2.jpg" alt="" width="1366" height="768" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801940" /><br/>
Back in June 2021, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/11/03/apple-refers-to-homeos-job-listings/">listed two job postings</a> that mentioned homeOS, but deleted the term when it was noticed by the media. We've seen no sign of homeOS since, except for in the first tvOS 17.4 beta.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's 2018 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> ran a modified version of iOS 11 when it launched, but Apple transitioned to using the tvOS platform for the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with the release of &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; Software 13.4. As part of its effort to develop an expanded smart home presence, Apple could eventually combine the tvOS and &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software in the future, potentially rebranding it as homeOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is actively working on a new smart home display that would compete with the Echo Show, Meta Portal, and Google Nest Hub, according to <i>Bloomberg's</i> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. The smart home display is said to have an iPad-like design and a camera for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls, and it is likely meant to mount to the wall and serve as a central console for smart home products. The device could also feature HomePod-like speakers, and if the product sees a release, it could be part of Apple's &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; lineup. <br/>
<br/>
There have also been rumors of a next-generation version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/27/touchscreen-homepod-everything-we-know/">HomePod with a display</a> at the top of the device, and this product could come out as early as 2024. homeOS could refer to either the iPad-like home hub in the works, or the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a display, but it is also possible that it is neither of these.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/shareplay-music-control-homepod-apple-tv/">A SharePlay feature for the HomePod</a> added in tvOS 17.4 beta 1 further hints at Apple's work on a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a screen. The update adds a QR code to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> app on the TV, which can be scanned by others to start a SharePlay session right on the device. A &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a display could feature a similar function.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 17.4 is expected to see a public release in March alongside iOS 17.4, and the timing is close to when Apple sometimes holds a spring event. We've heard rumors of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> refresh coming in late March, so given the homeOS mention in tvOS 17.4 and a possible upcoming event, we may not have too long to wait before learning more about Apple's homeOS plans.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/">tvOS 17.4 Code References Mysterious homeOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-17-4-code-references-mysterious-homeos.2417794/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Not Working For Some Users [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-music-not-working-for-some-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-not-working-for-some-users-update-fixed.2417793/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:43:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-music-not-working-for-some-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> service is malfunctioning for some users at the current time due to an ongoing outage that started at 1:20 p.m. Eastern Time. The "Home" or "Listen Now" tab is not loading in &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, and songs will not play.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/apple-music.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="734" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-813608" /><br/>
On Mac, some tracks are providing an error message about the song being unavailable, and the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app is continually skipping through playlists trying to find a functional song. On <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, tapping play or selecting a song simply does not work. <br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">Apple's system status page</a>, &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; and the iTunes Store are both down. Apple says that users may be experiencing "intermittent issues" with the services.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> Apple says that the issue has been fixed as of 1:47 p.m. Eastern Time.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-music-not-working-for-some-users/">Apple Music Not Working For Some Users [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-not-working-for-some-users-update-fixed.2417793/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-1-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2417787/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:12:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-1-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="hhttps://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-watchos-10-3/">release of watchOS 10.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.4‌ update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.4 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 includes new emoji characters such as a lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-1-to-developers/">Apple Seeds First Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2417787/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-1-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers.2417784/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 10:11:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-1-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/22/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3/">release of macOS Sonoma 14.3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 introduces some of the features in the iOS 17.4 beta, such as new emoji characters. We don't know what Mac-specific features are included, but if we find anything new in the beta, we'll update this article. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-1-to-developers/">Apple Seeds First Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers.2417784/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Camera Comparison: Samsung S24 Ultra vs iPhone 15 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsung-s24-ultra-vs-iphone-15-pro-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-samsung-s24-ultra-vs-iphone-15-pro-max.2417776/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:21:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsung-s24-ultra-vs-iphone-15-pro-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung came out with its 2024 flagship smartphone lineup in January, with the new devices competing directly with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max. Samsung's high-end S24 Ultra adopts some Apple-like features like a titanium chassis and a 5X zoom lens, but it also has standout additions that set it apart. We have an S24 Ultra, and thought we'd see how one main feature compares to the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max -- the camera.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NBg8g-DVHho" title="iPhone 15 Pro Max vs Samsung Galaxy S24 Ultra Camera Comparison!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Galaxy S24 Ultra has a 200-megapixel wide-angle camera (Apple's Wide lens is 50 megapixels), a 12-megapixel ultra wide camera (equal to Apple's), a 10-megapixel 3x telephoto lens, and a 50-megapixel 5x telephoto lens (Apple has a single 12-megapixel Telephoto lens). A higher pixel count equates to a higher resolution for printing and cropping in, but it doesn't necessarily make for better images because the size of the sensor is more important.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-1x-Keybank.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933352" /><br/>
In the sample images, you'll see that there's not too much of a difference between the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max and the S24 Ultra. The S24 Ultra is a little bit more saturated and the highlights are brightened, so the S24 images can look brighter in straight from the camera comparisons. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> images tend to be sharper for the most part, but Samsung's algorithm works well for night mode images.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-25x-keybank-s24.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933353" /><br/>
Samsung primarily focused on AI this year, so the S24 Ultra camera is almost identical to the S23 Ultra camera, but the telephoto lens is a major difference. Samsung ditched its 10x telephoto lens and opted instead for a 5x telephoto lens that more closely matches the 5x telephoto lens on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Telephoto images are close to the same, but in Portrait mode, Samsung's photos come out crisper.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-s24-street.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933354" /><br/>
There are two telephoto lenses in Samsung's smartphone, so it supports up to 10x optical zoom, and Samsung has long had the edge when it comes to digital zoom. The S24 Ultra can zoom in up to 100x, and while the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s digital zoom is good, it's not able to zoom in to that level.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-portrait-1x.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933355" /><br/>
On the topic of AI, Samsung added some AI-supported features for post processing. You can use generative fill to remove objects from images and change the crop, cut down on noise with remastering, add slow motion to any video, and record with both the front and rear-facing cameras at the same time. We may see camera-related AI additions on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models or in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, but for now, Samsung has the edge when it comes to fun AI-based tools.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-rock-hall-low-light.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933356" /><br/>
No smartphone is able to measure up to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; when it comes to video quality because of its stabilization and resolution, but the Galaxy S24 Ultra is the closest competitor, and it has an edge when it comes to microphone quality. The S24 Ultra's microphone has great noise isolation and clarity, and the Cinematic mode looks nice, though Samsung's Cinematic mode overdoes it on the blur. 4K video is supported at 30 and 60fps, but not 24fps, which is problematic for those who want to shoot high-quality 24fps video. On &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, there is a setting for recording 4K video at 24fps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-sign-5x-portrait-low-light.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933357" /><br/>
As smartphone cameras get better and better, it gets more difficult to distinguish which smartphone takes superior images. Both the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max and the Galaxy Ultra S24 take excellent quality pictures, and it's impossible to pick an overall winner. We think these cameras are about on par.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/samsung-galaxy-24-uw-keybank.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933358" /><br/>
Samsung and Apple are using different algorithms and processing for image capture and to make pictures look sharper in lower light, so you'll see some differences in brightness, white balance, saturation, and similar parameters, and "better" becomes a matter of preference.<br/>
<br/>
Which images do you prefer? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsung-s24-ultra-vs-iphone-15-pro-max/">Camera Comparison: Samsung S24 Ultra vs iPhone 15 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-samsung-s24-ultra-vs-iphone-15-pro-max.2417776/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some iPhone Users Unable to View Latest App Store Reviews</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/iphone-app-store-reviews-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-users-unable-to-view-latest-app-store-reviews.2417773/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 08:12:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/iphone-app-store-reviews-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For the past few weeks, some iPhone users have been unable to view the latest app reviews left by customers in the App Store. Specifically, affected users are only able to read reviews submitted up until January 16 this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/app-store-awards-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876046" /><br/>
It's unclear how widespread this issue is, but it seems to be very inconsistent, with recent reviews showing for some users and not for others depending on the app. We were able to reproduce the issue on iPhones in the U.S. and Canada, but not on an iPhone the U.K., while the Mac App Store does not appear to be affected whatsoever.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-TikTok-Review.jpg" alt="" width="1179" height="582" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933343" /><br/>
The issue was mentioned last week in a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/comments/19fk55c/is_it_me_or_have_there_not_been_any_new_ios_app/">Reddit post</a> spotted by Jeff Johnson, developer of the popular <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stopthemadness-pro/id6471380298">web browser extension StopTheMadness</a> for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac. Johnson said he could see a review for his app submitted on January 20 in the App Store Connect developer tool, but he could not see it on the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
Hopefully this glitch in the App Store matrix is fixed soon.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/iphone-app-store-reviews-issue/">Some iPhone Users Unable to View Latest App Store Reviews</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-users-unable-to-view-latest-app-store-reviews.2417773/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung&#039;s ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor Hits All-Time Low &#36;999 Price (&#36;600 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-999/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-hits-all-time-low-999-price-600-off.2417767/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 07:40:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-999/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has a <a href="https://howl.me/clq2oxlzaSU">new sale on computer monitors</a> this week, including a match of the all-time low price on the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor. You can get this display for <a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"><strong>&#36;999.99</strong></a> on Samsung's website, down from &#36;1,599.99.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/samsung-viewfinity-s9.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903406" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is a massive &#36;600 discount on the Smart Monitor, which features a matte 5K display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4. The monitor is a good (and cheaper) alternative to Apple's Studio Display. The last time we tracked this deal was in early December, so if you've been waiting for a solid markdown on the Samsung display, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clq17ynFNDS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;600 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the ViewFinity display sale, Samsung has a few other monitor discounts right now. One of the steepest is on the 49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor, which is &#36;500 off at &#36;1,299.99 during this discount event. You can find more of these sales in the list below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvFa7EZd3">34-inch ViewFinity Monitor</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvB7Tvgrn">34-inch ViewFinity Curved Monitor</a> - &#36;699.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clq2e77z0lE">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvDxh9PFu">57-inch Odyssey Mini-LED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clwvCVqsFVX">55-inch Odyssey Ark Mini-LED Curved Gaming Screen</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-999/">Samsung&#039;s ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor Hits All-Time Low &#36;999 Price (&#36;600 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsungs-viewfinity-s9-5k-smart-monitor-hits-all-time-low-999-price-600-off.2417767/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;300 Off 15-Inch MacBook Air With Multiple All-Time Low Prices Starting at &#36;999 [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-300-off-15-inch-macbook-air-with-multiple-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-999-updated.2417758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 06:34:14 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's M2 15-inch MacBook Air has returned to an all-time low price today at Best Buy, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model. You can get this deal in all four color options, and you don't need a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership to see this deal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898576" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The notebooks have an estimated delivery between February 5 and February 8, although those dates could change depending on your location. This is a match of the record low price on the 15-inch MacBook Air, and it's a deal we haven't tracked since the holiday season.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvUhPbHPL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For more storage, Best Buy has the 512GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. At &#36;300 off, this is the best price we've ever seen on this model of the MacBook Air, and it's available in all colors as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clwvVizVdRk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> This article originally highlighted deals from Amazon on the MacBook Air, but those sales quickly expired. All links have been replaced with Best Buy links, which should have more stock on the notebooks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/amazon-15-inch-macbook-air/">Best Buy Takes &#36;300 Off 15-Inch MacBook Air With Multiple All-Time Low Prices Starting at &#36;999 [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-300-off-15-inch-macbook-air-with-multiple-all-time-low-prices-starting-at-999-updated.2417758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta Hopes Apple Vision Pro Will &#039;Reinvigorate&#039; Headset Space</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/meta-optimistic-vision-pro-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-hopes-apple-vision-pro-will-reinvigorate-headset-space.2417752/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 04:56:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/meta-optimistic-vision-pro-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Wall Street Journal</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta is "optimistic" that the launch of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> will help reinvigorate the headset market and drive more users towards its Quest devices, according to <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/personal-tech/meta-facebook-vr-quest-war-apple-1a09ae0b">Wall Street Journal</a></em> report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3.jpg" alt="" width="1385" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914163" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Meta Quest 3</em></div><br/>
Formerly known as Facebook, Meta in 2021 changed its name in part to communicate its vision of a future "metaverse" in which people don its headsets and interact with each other in a completely virtual reality. <br/>
<br/>
Three years on and after pouring &#36;50 billion into investment, Meta's Quest devices barely count as 1% of the social media company's revenue, and the metaverse remains a largely nebulous concept that has so far failed to capture the imagination of customers.<br/>
<br/>
But with the February 2 launch of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; just days away, executives at Meta are viewing Apple's entry into the market as a potential validation of CEO Mark Zuckerberg’s AR/VR gamble that could draw more consumers into the headset space, according to sources who spoke to <em>WSJ</em>. <br/>
<br/>
Meta employees "see the Quest and its software ecosystem emerging as a primary alternative to Apple in the space, filling the role played by Google's Android in smartphones," claims the report.<br/>
<br/>
Meta is hoping that software makers will be inspired to develop apps that increasingly draw users into the space, enabling more people to experience the new virtual environments, with the company's sub-&#36;500 Quest devices offering a more affordable alternative to Apple's high-end &#36;3,499 headset.<br/>
<br/>
Executives at Meta have also reportedly been influenced by Apple's concept of spatial computing, which emphasizes mixed reality by overlaying virtual images onto real-world surroundings. Apple unveiled the Vision Pro in June 2023, and in the meantime Meta has been "increasingly focusing on mixed reality," claims <em>WSJ</em>'s sources.<br/>
<blockquote>In addition, some developers are simplifying their apps and favor Apple’s design that allows wearers to use their eyes and fingers to control or manipulate what they see. Meta’s Quest primarily relies on the use of controllers for games or applications, although it can work with finger gestures.</blockquote>Notably, Apple has shunned Meta's digital reality vision at every opportunity. For example, Apple VP of global marketing Greg Joswiak has said that "metaverse" is a word he will never use. Similarly, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> was quoted in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/30/apple-ceo-tim-cook-on-the-metaverse/">2022</a> as saying he's "not sure the average person can tell you what the metaverse is."<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/meta-optimistic-vision-pro-launch/">Meta Hopes Apple Vision Pro Will &#039;Reinvigorate&#039; Headset Space</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-hopes-apple-vision-pro-will-reinvigorate-headset-space.2417752/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Shazam Now Identifies Songs in Other Apps When Using Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/shazam-identifies-songs-other-apps-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/shazam-now-identifies-songs-in-other-apps-when-using-headphones.2417744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 03:21:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/shazam-identifies-songs-other-apps-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Shazam</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple-owned Shazam has released an updated version of the app with a new feature that can identify songs from other apps while you're listening using headphones.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/shazam-for-mac.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-857861" /><br/>
Shazam has been able to recognize songs from other apps for some time, but if headphones were connected to your iPhone, the feature wouldn't work, until now. The latest version of the app, v17.3, fixes that limitation.<br/>
<br/>
The feature works when wired or bluetooth headphones are connected, and they don't have to be Apple-made accessories, so third-party headphones are also supported.<br/>
<br/>
To use the feature, open the Shazam app, check for the headphone icon to confirm your headphones are connected, and then you'll be able to start recognizing music around you or within apps like TikTok, Instagram, and YouTube.  <br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/09/24/apple-shazam-acquisition-finalized/">acquired</a> Shazam in 2018, and has been gradually bringing the app into closer alignment with ‌Apple Music‌ ever since, offering trials to the streaming service through the app and the ability to sync Shazams directly to ‌Apple Music‌. <br/>
<br/>
Shazam can be downloaded from the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/shazam-music-discovery/id284993459">App Store for free</a>. It can be accessed through the Control Center on ‌‌iPhone‌‌ and ‌‌iPad‌‌, through ‌Siri‌ commands, or on the Mac, as well as via widgets. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/shazam/">Shazam</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/shazam-identifies-songs-other-apps-headphones/">Shazam Now Identifies Songs in Other Apps When Using Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/shazam-now-identifies-songs-in-other-apps-when-using-headphones.2417744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Arc Search for iPhone Merges AI and Web Search in a Browser App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/arc-search-for-iphone-merges-ai-and-web-search-in-a-browser-app.2417739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 02:47:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Browser Company has released a new iPhone app called <a href="https://arc.net/blog/arc-search">Arc Search</a> that aims to reimagine the online search experience by using artificial experience to present web results in a more easily digestible, curated presentation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/arc-search-app.jpg" alt="" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933281" /><br/>
The app follows the company's <a href="https://arc.net">Arc Browser</a> for Mac, and could be described as an AI chat bot with web access (think <a href="https://www.perplexity.ai">perplexity.ai</a>), wrapped in a clean, minimalist browser interface that quickly builds webpages on the fly based on your search query.<br/>
<br/>
The app opens with a search bar and keyboard, and its main AI-powered feature, "Browse for me," reads at least six websites and returns key information about the search query in a neatly presented webpage. <br/>
<br/>
For example, when searching "How to change a car tyre," Arc Search creates a page with sections including steps for changing the tyre, safety precautions, necessary tools, positioning the car, and fitting the spare wheel, with links for further reading. <br/>
<br/>
While Arc Search webpages don't always cite sources, the app does feature a "Dive Deeper" section at the bottom of the page so users can check whether the information that is being delivered to them is credible.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from the "Search for me" feature, which is powered by large-language models from OpenAI and others, users can opt to search with more traditional services like Google, Bing, DuckDuckGo, and Ecosia.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, there's a reader mode for clearing cruft from websites, along with the ability to bookmark pages. To keep things tidy, Arc Search also archives tabs after a user-defined period, and blocks GDPR  banners and ads/trackers automatically. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">a little Sunday surprise for you...<br><br>meet <a href="https://twitter.com/browsercompany?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@browsercompany</a>&#39;s 2nd product:<br><br>&#x1f50d;Arc Search&#x1f50e;<br><br>it&#39;s a default browser for your iPhone<br>...that BROWSES FOR YOU<br><br>the origin story is a bit unusual so I wanted to give you the full backstory: <a href="https://t.co/pkVQJYN0QQ">pic.twitter.com/pkVQJYN0QQ</a></p>&mdash; Josh Miller (@joshm) <a href="https://twitter.com/joshm/status/1751734580124787028?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 28, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Arc Search is available for free on the App Store [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/arc-search/id6472513080">Direct Link</a>] and requires iOS 16 or later, while Arc Browser for Mac can be downloaded from the <a href="https://arc.net">company's website</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/">Arc Search for iPhone Merges AI and Web Search in a Browser App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/arc-search-for-iphone-merges-ai-and-web-search-in-a-browser-app.2417739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple VP of Hardware Engineering for Home Devices Leaving Company After 25 Years</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-hardware-engineer-leaving-25-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vp-of-hardware-engineering-for-home-devices-leaving-company-after-25-years.2417735/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 01:16:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-hardware-engineer-leaving-25-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[DJ Novotney, one of Apple's top hardware engineering architects, is leaving Apple for Rivian Automotive, <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-28/apple-home-devices-car-veteran-exits-for-top-rivian-product-role?srnd=technology-vp">Bloomberg</a></em> reported over the weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/HomePod-G4-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793597" /><br/>
Novotney has worked at Apple for 25 years and been highly influential in the development of the iPod and iPhone over multiple generations of the hardware. He also helped lead development of the iPad and bring the Apple Watch to market, according to the report's sources at Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Novotney was also involved in "Project Titan," the company's stalled attempt to develop an autonomous electric vehicle. Most recently he was the senior executive in charge of developing future home devices, with a special focus on robotics and AI. Apple is said to have explored a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/12/homepod-ipad-with-robotic-arm/">high-end HomePod speaker</a> that could include an iPad connected via a robotic arm that tracks and follows users around a room.<br/>
<br/>
Novotney will become senior VP of vehicle programs at Rivian, which makes electric SUVs and pickup trucks. The executive informed colleagues of his exit on Friday, according to the report.<br/>
<blockquote>"Great products are what we do best and I have been so very lucky along the way to be part of so many amazing teams that developed everything from iPod, iPhone, iPad, Watch and so many more," Novotney wrote in a memo to colleagues that was seen by Bloomberg. "Apple has been my life, but now is the time for me to move on and help bring to life a new set of products."</blockquote>Several senior Apple executives are leaving or have left the company in recent years. Notable figures among them include Tang Tan, Apple's VP of product design for the iPhone and Apple Watch, who is joining Jony Ive's LoveFrom design firm next month, and hardware technologies leader Steve Hotelling, who left Apple last year. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/apple-hardware-engineer-leaving-25-years/">Apple VP of Hardware Engineering for Home Devices Leaving Company After 25 Years</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vp-of-hardware-engineering-for-home-devices-leaving-company-after-25-years.2417735/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says &#039;Hello&#039; to Vision Pro in New Ad as Headset Nears Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/hello-apple-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-hello-to-vision-pro-in-new-ad-as-headset-nears-launch.2417710/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 14:55:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/hello-apple-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today promoted the Vision Pro in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IY4x85zqoJM">new video ad</a> shared on its YouTube channel, ahead of the headset launching in the U.S. this Friday, February 2.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IY4x85zqoJM?si=gRv7yO_X-LDL8uER" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The ad demonstrates wearing the Vision Pro and navigating the visionOS operating system. <br/>
<br/>
"Apple Vision Pro is here," the video description says. "Now, digital content blends seamlessly with your physical space. You can do the things you love in ways never before possible."<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <a href="https://twitter.com/DylanMcD8/status/1751752668081795286">Dylan McDonald</a>, this ad is a shorter and slightly modified version of a video that Apple originally showed at the end of its WWDC keynote last June, shortly after introducing the Vision Pro. It aired during today's NFL playoff games.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/hello-apple-vision-pro/">Apple Says &#039;Hello&#039; to Vision Pro in New Ad as Headset Nears Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-hello-to-vision-pro-in-new-ad-as-headset-nears-launch.2417710/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Potentially &#039;Biggest&#039; Software Update in iPhone&#039;s History</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-potentially-biggest-software-update-in-iphones-history.2417674/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2024 06:17:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has big plans for iOS 18, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-28/apple-eu-changes-sideloading-third-party-app-stores-are-future-of-the-iphone-lrxjzbg6"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909207" /><br/>
In the subscriber-only Q&A section of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-28/apple-eu-changes-sideloading-third-party-app-stores-are-future-of-the-iphone-lrxjzbg6"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, Gurman said iOS 18 has the potential to be the "biggest" software update in the iPhone's history.<br/>
<br/>
"I'm told that the new operating system is seen within the company as one of the biggest iOS updates — if not the biggest — in the company's history," he wrote.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said he plans to share more details about specific iOS 18 features and changes that are planned in the future, but we already know about two new features that are likely to be included in the update, as outlined below.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 will be released in September, and the first beta for developers will come out during Apple's annual developers conference WWDC in June.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>RCS Support</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
In November 2023, Apple announced that it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS</a> in the Messages app on the iPhone starting "later" in 2024, so it will likely be an iOS 18 feature based on that timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
RCS support should result in the following improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging between iPhones and Android devices</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li><br/>
 <li>Improved encryption compared to SMS</li><br/>
</ul>These modern features are already available for iPhone-to-iPhone conversations with blue bubbles, via iMessage, and many of the features are also available in third-party messaging apps, such as WhatsApp and Telegram. RCS support on the iPhone will extend the features to green bubbles in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smarter Siri</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
Gurman expects <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">iOS 18 to feature generative AI technology</a> that "should improve how both Siri and the Messages app can field questions and auto-complete sentences." He said Apple has also explored generative AI features for other apps across its platforms, including Apple Music, Pages, Keynote, and Xcode.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The Information</em> reported that Apple plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">incorporate large language models into Siri</a> to let users automate complex tasks, a feature that would involve deeper integration with the Shortcuts app. The report said this feature is expected to be released in an iPhone software update coming in 2024, which would likely be iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Generative AI surged in popularity in 2022 when OpenAI released ChatGPT, a chatbot that can respond to questions and other prompts. Google and Microsoft released similar chatbots last year, as more companies race into the space. The chatbots are trained on large language models, allowing them to respond like a human.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/ios-18-big-expectations/">iOS 18 Potentially &#039;Biggest&#039; Software Update in iPhone&#039;s History</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-potentially-biggest-software-update-in-iphones-history.2417674/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
