<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 16:11:21 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro: Here&#039;s Everything You Get in the Box</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-everything-included-in-box/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-heres-everything-you-get-in-the-box.2415931/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 15:17:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-everything-included-in-box/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">announced</a> the launch date of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, its much-touted spatial computing device. The mixed reality headset starts at &#36;3,499 and will go on sale in the U.S. on Friday, February 2, with availability in Canada and the United Kingdom expected to follow later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band.jpeg" alt="" width="1640" height="1060" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929483" /><br/>
Apple has not yet revealed all the details about the device's configuration options ahead of pre-orders, which start on Friday, January 19, but we do know what is included in the box with every &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>Vision Pro Headset</strong>: The headset is the primary component of the Vision Pro system, featuring advanced eye and hand-tracking technology via cameras, ultra high-resolution displays for each eye, speakers on either side, and an EyeSight front-facing screen. The headset comes with a minimum of 256GB of onboard storage for applications and media.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Solo Knit Band and Dual Loop Band</strong>: These two types of headband are designed for user comfort and customization. The Solo Knit Band is a single band that wraps around the back of the head, while Apple says the Dual Loop Band features "a pair of adjustable upper and lower straps for a personalized fit."</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Light Seal</strong>: The Light Seal is made of a soft textile and likely comes in a range of shapes and sizes, flexing to conform to the user's face for a precise fit. This accessory helps to block external light, enhancing the immersive experience of the headset.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Two Light Seal Cushions</strong>: These cushions come supplied in two sizes and provide additional comfort and light-blocking capability, ensuring a snug fit around the face to prevent light leakage.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Cover for Front Glass</strong>: The cover protects the headset's front glass when not in use, preventing scratches and damage.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Polishing Cloth</strong>: A soft cloth designed for cleaning the headset's lenses and front glass without causing scratches or damage.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Battery Pack</strong>: An external power source for the headset, ensuring longer usage times and portability. The battery provides 2 hours of general use and 2.5 hours of 2D video playback on a single charge, according to Apple.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>USB-C Power Adapter</strong>: The adapter is used to charge the headset's battery pack, ensuring the device is always ready for use. It also may enable the Vision Pro to be connected to an external power source for longer periods of use than the portable battery allows, although Apple has yet to confirm this.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>USB-C Charging Cable</strong>: A cable for connecting the headset or the battery pack to the USB-C power adapter for charging.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Apple will offer optional optical inserts for users who normally wear glasses, but these are not included in the packaging and will be a separate purchase starting at &#36;99. Apple is partnering with ZEISS to offer the inserts that can be customized to each person's vision requirements. <br/>
<br/>
The inserts attach to the Vision Pro lenses magnetically, allowing for precise viewing and eye tracking. Glasses wearers will need a valid prescription to get the inserts, but Apple cautions that not all prescriptions will be supported. Optical inserts will be available to order online on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to start offering Vision Pro demonstrations at U.S. Apple retail stores on launch day. Apple says that demo times will be offered through the weekend on a first-come, first-served basis, with signups to take place starting at 8:00 a.m. on February 2.<br/>
<br/>
For everything else we know about &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-everything-included-in-box/">Apple Vision Pro: Here&#039;s Everything You Get in the Box</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-heres-everything-you-get-in-the-box.2415931/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: OtterBox Launches New Cases Made From Sustainable Cactus Leather</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-otterbox/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-otterbox-launches-new-cases-made-from-sustainable-cactus-leather.2415926/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:49:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-otterbox/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>OtterBox</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.otterbox.com/">OtterBox</a>, known for its range of protective cases designed for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, today announced the launch of new cases that are made from cactus leather. According to OtterBox, the cases are designed to feel like leather, but are created from the more sustainable and ethical cactus material.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/otterbox-cactus-leather-case.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929892" /><br/>
The soft-touch Symmetry Series Cactus Leather Cases offer the case protection that is typical of an OtterBox accessory. There's a rigid case design with reinforced corners for shock absorption, a raised edge to keep the camera safe, a screen lip to protect the display, and DROP+ protection.<br/>
<br/>
The cactus leather is sourced from the nopal cactus, which is more commonly known as the prickly pear. Producing cactus leather requires less land, water, and resources than producing traditional leather, and when mature prickly pear pads are gathered, the rest of the cactus remains alive and healthy for re-harvesting again in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera was able to see OtterBox's cases in person at CES, and he found the material to be an improvement over Apple's leather alternative, FineWoven.<br/>
<br/>
OtterBox is offering the cases alongside cactus leather Apple Watch band options and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> wallet made from the same material.<br/>
<br/>
The first cactus leather cases will be priced at &#36;60 and will be <a href="https://www.otterbox.com/">available from the OtterBox website</a> starting in Spring 2024.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/otterbox/">OtterBox</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-otterbox/">CES 2024: OtterBox Launches New Cases Made From Sustainable Cactus Leather</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-otterbox-launches-new-cases-made-from-sustainable-cactus-leather.2415926/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Rabbit r1 AI Assistant Wants to Do Tasks for You</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-rabbit-r1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-rabbit-r1-ai-assistant-wants-to-do-tasks-for-you.2415922/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 14:04:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-rabbit-r1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AI startup Rabbit today announced the launch of <a href="https://www.rabbit.tech">the Rabbit r1</a>, a mobile device that's designed to simplify the experience of using a smartphone. The r1 runs rabbit OS, an operating system powered by a Large Action Model (LAM).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/rabbit-r1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929901" /><br/>
The Large Action Model is able to learn how humans use computers, or more specifically, how r1 users take advantage of apps. Rabbit says that the r1 can understand complex user intentions, operate user interfaces, and perform actions on behalf of the user. The OS was trained on data from people interacting with apps, allowing the r1 to do tasks like ordering pizza, booking ride services, playing music, communicating with people, and more, through voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Introducing r1. Watch the keynote. <br><br>Order now: <a href="https://t.co/R3sOtVWoJ5">https://t.co/R3sOtVWoJ5</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CES2024?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CES2024</a> <a href="https://t.co/niUmjFvKvE">pic.twitter.com/niUmjFvKvE</a></p>&mdash; rabbit inc. (@rabbit_hmi) <a href="https://twitter.com/rabbit_hmi/status/1744781083831574824?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 9, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The Rabbit r1 can be interacted with using a push-to-talk button on the side, and it understands natural language requests. There are no apps on the r1, and tasks are performed over the internet.<br/>
<br/>
Designed in partnership with Teenage Engineering, the r1 has a 2.88-inch touch screen, a camera that rotates for capturing photos and videos and taking video calls, a scroll wheel for navigation purposes, and a USB-C port for charging. There is a 1,000mAh battery, and battery life depends on usage. While there is no subscription associated with the Rabbit r1, it does need a SIM card for cellular data.<br/>
<br/>
Users can teach the r1 to perform tasks, including multi-step tasks such as researching a location, booking a hotel, securing restaurant recommendations, and finding activities. Once the r1 has learned a task, it can repeat the action independently. It supposedly can even interact with apps like Photoshop, performing multi-step actions within the software.<br/>
<br/>
The Rabbit r1 needs to be provided with a user's logins for various services in order to complete tasks involving those services. <br/>
<br/>
The Rabbit r1 can be <a href="https://www.rabbit.tech">pre-ordered from the Rabbit website</a> for &#36;200. It is expected to ship to customers in March or April of 2024<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-rabbit-r1/">CES 2024: Rabbit r1 AI Assistant Wants to Do Tasks for You</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-rabbit-r1-ai-assistant-wants-to-do-tasks-for-you.2415922/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-3-to-developers.2415915/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 13:09:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.3 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-beta-2-to-developers/">second tvOS 17.3 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.3 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes. We don't yet know what's included in tvOS 17.3.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't always know what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-3-to-developers.2415915/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024 Day 2: Transparent TVs From LG, OtterBox&#039;s Cactus Leather, Lockly Smart Locks and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-day-2-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-2-transparent-tvs-from-lg-otterboxs-cactus-leather-lockly-smart-locks-and-more.2415910/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:42:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-day-2-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[CES is underway in Las Vegas, and while it's been overshadowed by Apple's Vision Pro launch date announcement, there are still plenty of interesting new products to look at. <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera is at CES to bring us an overview of what's worth checking out.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/TfqEDPHjK5Y" title="CES 2024 Day 2: LG Transparent OLED, Facial Recognition Lock &amp; More!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Day 2 at CES was actually Monday, the day before the show "officially" kicks off and the show floor opens. Vendors were on hand showcasing products in private suites, and the annual Pepcom show took place.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/ces-2024-day-1-recap/">Like Samsung</a>, LG was showing off transparent display technology with the LG Signature OLED T (T for transparent). LG's OLED TV is coming out later this year, and it can transition between transparency and an opaque background for television watching. LG has designed content specifically for the see-through background, and some of it has an almost hologram-like look.<br/>
<br/>
Lockly was showing off a HomeKit-compatible smart lock that uses facial recognition to open the door, while Ember brought its cup warming technology to baby bottles. Aqara showed off an indoor lock with fingerprint detection, and Scosche was on hand to demo the BaseLynx 2.0, its modular charging system for Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
OtterBox has a new environmentally friendly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> case made of cactus leather, Orbi showed off a new Wi-Fi 7 mesh router setup, and GE had an indoor smokeless smoker that uses pellets.<br/>
<br/>
Dan will be wandering the show floor on Tuesday, so make sure to stay tuned to see tomorrow's CES roundup video. We're also covering all kinds of announcements from CES, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">which you can check out at our CES 2024 hub</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-day-2-recap/">CES 2024 Day 2: Transparent TVs From LG, OtterBox&#039;s Cactus Leather, Lockly Smart Locks and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-day-2-transparent-tvs-from-lg-otterboxs-cactus-leather-lockly-smart-locks-and-more.2415910/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Was Missing These 10 Essential Features When Unveiled in 2007</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/original-iphone-missing-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-was-missing-these-10-essential-features-when-unveiled-in-2007.2415906/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 12:26:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/original-iphone-missing-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the 17th anniversary of the late Steve Jobs <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MnrJzXM7a6o">unveiling the original iPhone</a> at the Macworld Expo in San Francisco. While the device was significantly more advanced than any other smartphone on the market at the time, the iPhone was still missing some essential features that we take for granted today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/2007-iPhone.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929882" /><br/>
Below, we've put together a list of 10 hardware and software features that the original iPhone didn't have when it was introduced in January 2007.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Copy and Paste:</strong> It may seem hard to believe, but the ability to copy and paste text was not added to the iPhone until 2009.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Front Camera:</strong> While selfies are now ubiquitous, there was no front camera on the original iPhone. In fact, there was no front camera until the iPhone 4 launched in 2010 with new FaceTime video calling.</li><br/>
<li><strong>App Store:</strong> The original iPhone came with preinstalled apps like Phone, Weather, Notes, Calendar, Photos, and Calculator, but there was no official way to install native third-party apps until the App Store launched in July 2008. Developers were able to offer web-based apps, but they were more limited.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Video Recording:</strong> The original iPhone can only shoot photos, with video recording introduced on the iPhone 3GS in 2009.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Flashlight:</strong> With no LED flash on the original iPhone, there was no built-in flashlight. When the App Store launched, some flashlight apps were released that displayed a white screen at max brightness to mimic a flashlight.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Photo Messages:</strong> The original iPhone supported text messaging via SMS, but there was no ability to send photos. MMS capabilities were introduced with iPhone OS 3.0 in 2009, but only for the iPhone 3G and iPhone 3GS.<br/>
<li><strong>GPS:</strong> While the original iPhone came with a Google Maps app preinstalled, there were no turn-by-turn directions, as the device did not have a GPS. Apple introduced a built-in GPS with the iPhone 3G in 2008.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Home Screen Wallpapers:</strong> It was not possible to set a custom Home Screen wallpaper on the iPhone until iOS 4 was released in 2010, and the software update did not support the original iPhone.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Retina Display:</strong> Introduced on the iPhone 4 in 2010, the Retina display featured four times as many pixels as the original iPhone and was the highest-resolution display for a smartphone ever at the time.</li><br/>
<li><strong>3G:</strong> The original iPhone's cellular connectivity was limited to EDGE (2G).</li></ul><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/original-iphone-missing-features/">iPhone Was Missing These 10 Essential Features When Unveiled in 2007</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-was-missing-these-10-essential-features-when-unveiled-in-2007.2415906/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect the AirTag 2 to Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/airtag-2-release-date-and-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-the-airtag-2-to-launch.2415902/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 11:34:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/airtag-2-release-date-and-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple released its <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-airtag/airtag">AirTag</a> item tracker in April 2021. The accessory has not received any hardware updates since, but there have been rumors about a new model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/airtag-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903337" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about when the second-generation AirTag might be released, as well as potential new features to expect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo and <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman both expect the next AirTag to be released in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
In October 2023, Kuo said mass production of the second-generation AirTag had been postponed from the fourth quarter of 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/airtag-2-postponed-until-2025/">until some point in 2025</a>, but he did not provide a reason for the apparent change in plans.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman echoed this revised timeframe <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-01-07/apple-2024-plans-challenges-gen-ai-vision-pro-china-sales-app-store-changes-lr3k9p8p">in his <em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> last Sunday.<br/>
<br/>
"Apple considered launching its second-generation AirTags in 2024, but I'm now told new versions aren't likely to hit the market until 2025," he wrote.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Features</h2><br/>
Kuo believes the new AirTag will have some kind of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/02/kuo-new-airtag-production-late-2024/">integration with Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset</a>, but he has not shared any specific details.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman expects the new AirTag to feature an upgraded wireless chip, but he did not elaborate on what this would mean. It is possible that the AirTag could be updated with the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip that debuted in all iPhone 15 models last year, which would pave the way for improved location accuracy for item tracking.<br/>
<br/>
No design or price changes have been rumored so far. Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags-2/">AirTag 2 guide</a> for more details.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/airtag-2-release-date-and-features/">When to Expect the AirTag 2 to Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-the-airtag-2-to-launch.2415902/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-ios-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-to-developers.2415892/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:07:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-ios-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the updates available a week after the release of the first <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-ios-17-3-beta-2-to-developers/">iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926334" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iOS-17.3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3 introduces a Stolen Device Protection feature that limits access to your private information in case someone obtains both your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and your passcode. When activated, it requires <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> identity verification to do things like accessing passwords in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> Keychain, turning off Lost Mode, making purchases through Safari with saved payment credentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
There are also features that require verification <em>and</em> have a one-hour delay to access, such as changing an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; passcode, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; passcode, turning off <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a>, and turning off &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj;. More details can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/12/ios-17-3-stolen-device-protection-feature/">found in our article on Stolen Device Protection</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The update also adds <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/11/apple-music-collaborative-playlists-2024/">collaborative Apple Music playlists</a>, a feature that lets <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> subscribers share playlists with others to build shared song lists. Collaborative playlists are simple to use, can be shared with a link, and support emoji reactions.<br/>
<br/>
Last week, Apple pulled the second betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 after the updates caused devices to go into a perpetual boot loop. Apple did not re-release the second betas, but presumably the issue is fixed in the third betas. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release iOS 17.3 later in January.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-ios-17-3-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.3 and iPadOS 17.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-3-and-ipados-17-3-to-developers.2415892/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3-to-developers.2415891/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:06:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.3 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-2/">second macOS Sonoma 14.3 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what features are included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.3, and there were no notable changes discovered in the first two betas, so we may not know what's new until the software comes out and is accompanied by release notes.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-3-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-3-to-developers.2415891/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.3 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-3-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-3-to-developers.2415893/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 10:05:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-3-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.3 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/03/apple-seeds-watchos-10-3-beta-2-to-developers/">second watchOS 10.3 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.3‌ update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.3 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
There's no word yet on the new features that might be included in watchOS 10.3, and no notable new features were found in the first betas. <br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-3-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.3 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-3-to-developers.2415893/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Features 16GB of RAM and Likely Up to 1TB of Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-features-16gb-of-ram-and-likely-up-to-1tb-of-storage.2415888/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:53:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a> headset is equipped with 16GB of unified memory, according to files related to the device in Xcode 15.2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-chips.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898904" /><br/>
Our finding in the latest version of Apple's app development tool confirms a June 2023 report from <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-06-02/apple-wwdc-2023-mixed-reality-headset-ios-17-and-other-products-to-expect"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> that said the Vision Pro would be equipped with 16GB of RAM, and that is also the same amount of memory that was included in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/24/apple-vision-pro-developer-kits-now-available/">Vision Pro development kits</a> distributed by Apple last year.<br/>
<br/>
Xcode 15.2 officially <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-releases-vision-pro-updates-testflight-xcode/">adds support for developing visionOS apps</a>, and Apple is now accepting these apps via App Store Connect.<br/>
<br/>
In a press release this week, Apple reiterated that the Vision Pro will be powered by its M2 chip for "powerful standalone performance," along with an all-new R1 chip that "processes input from 12 cameras, five sensors, and six microphones to ensure that content feels like it is appearing right in front of the user's eyes."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's press release also confirmed that the Vision Pro will start at &#36;3,499 in the U.S. with 256GB of storage, and this wording seems to imply that higher storage capacity options will also be available. It was reported last year that at least some of the Vision Pro developer kits were equipped with 1TB of storage.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to share full tech specs for the Vision Pro, which will be available to pre-order in the U.S. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/apple-announces-february-2-vision-pro-launch/">starting Friday, January 19</a> at 5 a.m. Pacific Time. The headset will launch there a few weeks later, on Friday, February 2. When it first announced the Vision Pro, Apple said the headset would launch in additional countries later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Thanks to <a href="https://twitter.com/DimSartz_">Dimitris Sartzetakis</a>, <a href="https://twitter.com/mbrkhrdt">Michael Burkhardt</a>, and <a href="https://mastodon.social/@stroughtonsmith">Steve Troughton-Smith</a> for assistance.</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-how-much-ram-and-storage/">Apple Vision Pro Features 16GB of RAM and Likely Up to 1TB of Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-features-16gb-of-ram-and-likely-up-to-1tb-of-storage.2415888/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple &#039;Carefully Orchestrating&#039; Vision Pro Reviews With Multiple Meetings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-reviews-multiple-meetings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-carefully-orchestrating-vision-pro-reviews-with-multiple-meetings.2415886/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:45:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-reviews-multiple-meetings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has a detailed plan for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> reviews, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1744774909262483693"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. YouTubers and members of the media selected for reviews will meet with Apple on January 16 for a hands-on experience, with a follow-up meeting to take place on January 23 to go over the device's features a second time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Reviews are set to be published at the end of January, which is just ahead of when Apple plans to launch the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
It is no surprise that Apple plans to have a firm hold on the review process and the experience that reviewers undergo, as it has kept headsets provided to developers similarly locked down.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to begin accepting pre-orders for the Vision Pro on Friday, January 19, ahead of when reviews are published. The Vision Pro will then launch on Friday, February 2, with Apple planning to provide in-store demonstrations starting on that day.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-vision-pro-reviews-multiple-meetings/">Apple &#039;Carefully Orchestrating&#039; Vision Pro Reviews With Multiple Meetings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-carefully-orchestrating-vision-pro-reviews-with-multiple-meetings.2415886/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Satechi Debuts New Qi2 Wireless Charging Stands</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-satechi-qi2-chargers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-satechi-debuts-new-qi2-wireless-charging-stands.2415880/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 09:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-satechi-qi2-chargers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://satechi.net">Satechi</a> today introduced two new Qi2 charging options, including the 3-in-1 Foldable Qi2 Wireless Charging Stand and 2-in-1 Foldable Qi2 Wireless Charging Stand. With next-generation Qi2 charging technology, Satechi's chargers are able to charge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> iPhones at up to 15W, the same as official &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; chargers from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/satechi-3-in-1-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929700" /><br/>
The 3-in-1 stand from Satechi also includes a 5W Apple Watch charger and a 5W wireless charger that's designed for the AirPods, while the 2-in-1 stand has a spot for charging the AirPods. Both chargers feature a vegan leather base, an aluminum housing, and a soft silicone charging puck, and they are able to fold down for travel when not in use.<br/>
<br/>
Satechi's 3-in-1 stand is able to provide fast-charging capabilities for the Apple Watch Series 7 and later, plus it comes with a 45W USB-C power adapter. Qi2 uses the same magnetic power profile as &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, so these stands work like &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; stands without the 7.5W limitation of the prior Qi standard.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/satechi-2-in-1-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929701" /><br/>
The 3-in-1 Foldable Qi2 Wireless Charging Stand will be priced at &#36;130, while the 2-in-1 Foldable Qi2 Wireless Charging Stand will be priced at &#36;80. Both chargers are <a href="https://satechi.net">set to launch</a> in the second quarter of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Satechi today also announced the launch of the SM1 Slim Mechanical Backlit Bluetooth Keyboard, the company's first mechanical keyboard option. It is compatible with the Mac, and it is <a href="https://satechi.net/products/sm1-slim-mechanical-backlit-bluetooth-keyboard">priced at &#36;100</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-satechi-qi2-chargers/">CES 2024: Satechi Debuts New Qi2 Wireless Charging Stands</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-satechi-debuts-new-qi2-wireless-charging-stands.2415880/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Take &#36;249 Off Apple&#039;s 15-Inch MacBook Air With Amazon&#039;s New Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/249-off-15-inch-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/take-249-off-apples-15-inch-macbook-air-with-amazons-new-sale.2415872/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 07:59:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/249-off-15-inch-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a pair of discounts on both models of the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, thanks to a few on-page coupons found on their product pages. Many of the notebooks can be delivered as soon as January 13, although some models do have delayed shipping estimates ranging into late January.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898578" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The 256GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75ZRQLB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,049.99</strong></a> in three colors, down from &#36;1,299.00. There's a hefty on-page coupon worth around &#36;152 that'll net you this second-best price, which is just about &#36;50 higher than the previous record low price we saw over the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C75ZRQLB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For more storage, Amazon has the 512GB 15-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76B7QHC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,249.99</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;1,499.00. You'll again need to clip the on-page coupon in order to see this discount, and this is another second-best price on the MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C76B7QHC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/249-off-15-inch-macbook-air/">Take &#36;249 Off Apple&#039;s 15-Inch MacBook Air With Amazon&#039;s New Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/take-249-off-apples-15-inch-macbook-air-with-amazons-new-sale.2415872/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Amazon Unveils Matter Casting Standard as Interoperable Alternative to AirPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/amazon-unveils-matter-casting/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-amazon-unveils-matter-casting-standard-as-interoperable-alternative-to-airplay.2415868/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 07:10:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/amazon-unveils-matter-casting/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		<category>AirPlay</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today announced Matter Casting, an interoperable rival to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> feature, at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a> (via <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-01-09/amazon-debuts-video-streaming-feature-that-rivals-apple-airplay">Bloomberg</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/echo-show.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-818290" /><br/>
Matter Casting will initially only support streaming content from Amazon's Prime Video app to Echo Show devices, but the feature will support Fire TV in the coming months. Later in the year, it will work across a range of other video services, including Plex, Starz, Pluto TV, Sling TV, and ZDF.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; allows Apple device users to wirelessly stream video from an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> or another Mac, as well as stream audio from almost any Apple device to any <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, or compatible third-party speaker. Google has a similar equivalent for its Chromecast devices called Google Cast. Both &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; and Google Cast are proprietary technologies, so Amazon's new feature is designed to be interoperable across platforms.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Google worked with Amazon on the Matter home standard, but they have not yet announced any plans to support Matter Casting and could choose to remain uninvolved. Nevertheless, it is clearly Amazon's wish to make video streaming apps and TV accessories work together more seamlessly, regardless of their platform.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/amazon-unveils-matter-casting/">CES 2024: Amazon Unveils Matter Casting Standard as Interoperable Alternative to AirPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-amazon-unveils-matter-casting-standard-as-interoperable-alternative-to-airplay.2415868/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Nanoleaf Debuts Matter-Enabled Outdoor Lights and New Music Feature, Accepts Pre-Orders for Skylight</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/nanoleaf-ces-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-nanoleaf-debuts-matter-enabled-outdoor-lights-and-new-music-feature-accepts-pre-orders-for-skylight.2415865/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 07:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/nanoleaf-ces-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nanoleaf</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular smart lighting company Nanoleaf today announced the launch of several new Matter-enabled lighting options, including its first outdoor lights. The company is also debuting a new music feature and accepting pre-orders for the Nanoleaf Skylight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/nanoleaf-permanent-outdoor-lights.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929046" /><br/>
Nanoleaf's Matter-enabled lights include the Smart Multicolor Lightstrip, the Smart Multicolor Outdoor String Lights, and the Smart Multicolor Permanent Outdoor Lights. The Outdoor String Lights feature large bulbs for decorating a front entryway, patio, or deck, while the permanent lights are designed to be installed under the eaves of a house in lieu of holiday string lights.<br/>
<br/>
The Matter lights from Nanoleaf are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> compatible and can be controlled using the Nanoleaf app, the Home app, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands. They support more than 16 million colors and several shades of white, and can be used with all of the Nanoleaf lighting scenes and app customization features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/nanoleaf-outdoor-light-bulbs.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929047" /><br/>
To go along with the lights, Nanoleaf announced new Orchestrator software for the Nanoleaf Desktop App, which will use real-time music analysis to create light shows that match with the beat. Orchestrator is able to connect directly with the sound source of a computer for a more accurate real-time audio visual experience.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to the Rhythm feature that reacts to sound, Orchestrator is designed to react to music. It can separate beats, melodies, and audio spectrum, timing the light activation to the songs that are playing.<br/>
<br/>
Both the new Matter-enabled lights and the Orchestrator will be available in the spring, but Nanoleaf is accepting pre-orders for the Skylight <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/03/nanoleaf-ces-2023/">first announced at CES 2023</a>. The Skylight is a square-shaped modular ceiling light panel setup that is hardwired and supports up to 100 squares.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/nanoleaf-skylight.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878921" /><br/>
Nanoleaf's Skylight offers millions of color options like other Nanoleaf panels, and it can be controlled via the Nanoleaf app and the Home app. There are special scenes like Gentle Rain and Sun Shower, plus support for the Rhythm Music Visualizer. Each panel offers 1400 lumens of light.<br/>
<br/>
The Nanoleaf Skylight can be <a href="https://nanoleaf.me/en-US/">pre-ordered from the Nanoleaf website</a> for &#36;250 for three panels, with an additional panel expansion pack available for &#36;70.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nanoleaf/">Nanoleaf</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/nanoleaf-ces-2024/">CES 2024: Nanoleaf Debuts Matter-Enabled Outdoor Lights and New Music Feature, Accepts Pre-Orders for Skylight</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-nanoleaf-debuts-matter-enabled-outdoor-lights-and-new-music-feature-accepts-pre-orders-for-skylight.2415865/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Music Classical Expanding to More Countries Later This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-music-classical-expanding-to-more-countries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-expanding-to-more-countries-later-this-month.2415861/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 06:46:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-music-classical-expanding-to-more-countries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>Apple Music Classical</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Music Classical will be available in China, Japan, South Korea, Taiwan, Hong Kong, and Macao starting January 24, according to a <a href="https://twitter.com/AppleClassical/status/1744681071327785163">post from Apple on X</a>, formerly known as Twitter. The app can be pre-ordered now on the App Store in these regions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/apple-music-classical.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890263" /><br/>
Apple Music Classical <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/27/apple-music-classical-begins-rolling-out/">first launched in most other countries last March</a>, offering Apple Music subscribers access to over five million classical music tracks at no additional cost. The app features advanced search functionality, exclusive artwork, extensive metadata, curated listening recommendations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The app is available on the iPhone, iPad, and Android devices. It is built upon Primephonic, a classical music streaming service acquired by Apple in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., a standard Apple Music subscription costs &#36;10.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music-classical/">Apple Music Classical</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/apple-music-classical-expanding-to-more-countries/">Apple Music Classical Expanding to More Countries Later This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-music-classical-expanding-to-more-countries-later-this-month.2415861/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Band Designed for Black Apple Watch Ultra Surfaces Online</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/band-designed-for-black-apple-watch-ultra-surfaces/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/band-designed-for-black-apple-watch-ultra-surfaces-online.2415859/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 06:23:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/band-designed-for-black-apple-watch-ultra-surfaces/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>DongleBookPro</category>
		<category>Prototypes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Images of an Alpine Loop prototype designed for a black Apple Watch Ultra model today surfaced online, supporting rumors that Apple had plans to release a darker version of the device last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/black-apple-watch-ultra-band.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-929756" /><br/>
Prior to the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, multiple rumors <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/01/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-titanium-rumor/">suggested</a> that Apple had plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/31/2023-apple-watch-ultra-new-dark-color/">new darker color option</a> that was originally tested for the previous model but ultimately canceled. When the device was announced in September 2023, it continued to only be available in the same natural titanium color as the first-generation model. <br/>
<br/>
Now, further indication has emerged that Apple had plans to release a darker color option. The latest images, <a href="https://x.com/DongleBookPro/status/1744716821553676298?s=20">shared by "DongleBookPro" on X</a>, show a blue Alpine Loop prototype with an anodized black titanium hook and lugs. The released version of the Alpine Loop has natural titanium trim to match the Apple Watch Ultra's casing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Space Black Apple Watch Ultra Confirmed? <a href="https://t.co/aLjkJGCsg7">pic.twitter.com/aLjkJGCsg7</a></p>&mdash; Dongle (@DongleBookPro) <a href="https://twitter.com/DongleBookPro/status/1744716821553676298?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 9, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple released the blue version of the Alpine Loop alongside the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj;, supporting previous indications that the company had concrete plans to release the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; with a black color option. In November, documents filed with the United States Federal Communications Commission <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/">revealed a black Apple Watch Ultra</a> with a matching dark ceramic back, cementing the validity of earlier rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-ultra-prototype-fcc.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922908" /><br/>
The reason for Apple's decision to cancel the new colorway is unknown, but there is a chance that the company deemed the finish insufficiently durable for a device focused on withstanding extreme challenges. There have not yet been any rumors to suggest that Apple plans to revive the black colorway for the third-generation version of the device, but it could still be a possibility given how far developed the darker finish was for the current model prior to its release.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/donglebookpro/">DongleBookPro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prototypes/">Prototypes</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/band-designed-for-black-apple-watch-ultra-surfaces/">Band Designed for Black Apple Watch Ultra Surfaces Online</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/band-designed-for-black-apple-watch-ultra-surfaces-online.2415859/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>CES 2024: Alogic Launches Innovative &#039;Matrix Ultimate&#039; 3-in-1 Charger and 32-Inch 4K Displays With Optional Touchscreen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-alogic-charger-displays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-alogic-launches-innovative-matrix-ultimate-3-in-1-charger-and-32-inch-4k-displays-with-optional-touchscreen.2415857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 06:08:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-alogic-charger-displays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Alogic</category>
		<category>CES 2024</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[At <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a> this week, accessory company <a href="https://alogic.co/?ref=y2uwzwu">Alogic</a> is launching several new products in the display and charging categories, with both lineups offering some innovative features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-clarity-32-display-matrix-ultimate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929726" /><br/>
First, Alogic's new Matrix lineup will offer an array of wireless chargers and power banks such as the Matrix Ultimate that I've had a chance to try out.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://alogic.co/products/matrix-ultimate-3-in-1-wireless-charger-with-5-000mah-magsafe-power-bank/?ref=y2uwzwu">Matrix Ultimate</a> is a 3-in-1 folding stand with an integrated power bank. In stand mode, it's a fairly typical 3-in-1 charger, with an official <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charging pad for your phone plus an elevated Apple Watch charger on behind the device and a spot on the rear portion of the base for AirPods or another Qi device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-matrix-ultimate-front.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929712" /><br/>
The AirPods charging spot is unfortunately not magnetic, so you'll need to manually ensure your AirPods are properly aligned for charging, but it seems pretty forgiving on the placement and with supported AirPods you can also use the magnetic Apple Watch charger on the stand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-matrix-ultimate-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929713" /><br/>
Beyond being a typical 3-in-1 charger, the Matrix Ultimate has a few tricks up its sleeve. First, the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging pad is actually part of a 5,000 mAh power bank that slides into the stand where it supports the phone and receives fixed power from the base unit. Even in power bank mode, it still supports 15-watt &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging.<br/>
<br/>
The power bank is fairly compact, but it's a little thicker than some other 5,000 mAh options on the market and only the &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; pad portion of it sits flush against the back of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, so it will pop loose from the phone if you press the lower portion of the power bank toward the phone. As a result, this isn't the type of magnetic power bank I would want to leave attached to my phone throughout the day, but for periodic charging while in a fixed location it would be perfectly fine.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-matrix-ultimate-power-bank.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929715" /><br/>
In addition to the removable power bank, the Matrix Ultimate also features a removable Apple Watch charging puck that connects to the body of the stand via USB-C. The puck supports Apple Watch fast charging, and the removable design gives you the flexibility to take just the Apple Watch charger with you depending on what you need. You can then just plug it directly into a power adapter, a computer USB port, or even the USB-C port on the Matrix Ultimate power bank in order to recharge your watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-matrix-ultimate-removables.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929714" /><br/>
The third trick up the Matrix Ultimate's sleeve is that the whole things folds down for travel and can be stored in a felt travel case alongside the provided USB-C to USB-C cable and 30-watt power adapter with folding prongs in the U.S. The whole thing remains a bit on the bulky side due in part to the hardware needed for the removable power bank, but it should still pack easily in most computer bags, backpacks, or suitcases.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-matrix-ultimate-parts.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929716" /><br/>
The Matrix Ultimate is largely constructed of a matte white plastic with a shiny chrome-colored hinge between the stand and base, though this is essentially hidden unless the stand is viewed from the rear. It's <a href="https://alogic.co/products/matrix-ultimate-3-in-1-wireless-charger-with-5-000mah-magsafe-power-bank/?ref=y2uwzwu">priced at &#36;169.99</a> in the U.S. and roughly equivalent amounts in the UK, EU, and Australia. A multi-country model including a 35-watt adapter with plugs for the US, UK, EU, and Australia will be &#36;10 more. Alogic currently has a sale going that knocks 20% off of those prices with coupon code CS20, bringing the U.S. model down to &#36;136.00.<br/>
<br/>
Second, the company is expanding its line of Clarity displays to include a trio of 32-inch models. Just like with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/alogic-clarity-pro-touch-displays/">27-inch Clarity displays</a> released last year, the 32-inch options include a <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery/?ref=y2uwzwu">base model</a>, a <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-pro-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-and-webcam/?ref=y2uwzwu">middle-tier model</a> with a motorized retractable 8-megapixel webcam, and a <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-touch-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-webcam-and-touch-screen/?ref=y2uwzwu">high-end model</a> with both webcam and touchscreen support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-32-clarity-display.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="970" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929717" /><br/>
All three displays offer 4K resolution at 60 Hz, which still looks decent at reasonably scaled desktop sizes, but you won't get the true Retina quality you see on higher-density displays like 27-inch 5K displays and you won't get the benefit of higher refresh rates.<br/>
<br/>
The 32-inch models all provide up to 65-watts of passthrough power via USB-C to keep your laptop charged, which should be sufficient for most users, although the most powerful MacBook Pro models could draw more than that under heavy load.<br/>
<br/>
All three models also have a small USB hub on the rear of the display with a pair of USB-A ports (5 Gbps and 7.5 watts) plus a 3.5mm combo audio jack. If you want or need to use something other than USB-C, the display also include a pair of HDMI 2.1 ports and a DisplayPort 1.4 port<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-32-clarity-display-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929720" /><br/>
The included stand on all Clarity Max models supports tilt and height adjustments, as well as the ability to pivot the display to portrait mode. The display can also be used with 100x100 VESA mounts.<br/>
<br/>
I've had a brief opportunity to try out the high-end Clarity Max Touch model, and my impressions are very similar to those from the corresponding 27-inch model, just with a bigger display. The touchscreen functionality is highly customizable on a per-app basis with the system able to recognize several different gestures, which is fantastic.<br/>
<br/>
I still don't see myself using the touchscreen capabilities (which can be used with fingers or a capacitive stylus, but not an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>) on a full-time basis, but especially in a multi-monitor setup it can be handy to be able to quickly tap on the screen rather than having to move a mouse cursor across multiple displays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-32-clarity-display-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929721" /><br/>
The retractable webcam offers some nice peace of mind, as once it's tucked away you can be sure that it's not being used to surreptitiously monitor you. And at 8 megapixels, it offers solid quality better than many other built-in webcams found on displays, although it doesn't match what you get when using an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; via Continuity Camera.<br/>
<br/>
The stand is a high-quality two-piece aluminum design that provides very good stability and smooth adjustments, plus a passthrough to help with cable management. The display itself is constructed of a silver plastic shell on the back with nearly edge-to-edge glass on front. There are definite black bezels on all four sides under the glass, with the bottom being somewhat wider than the other three.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/alogic-32-clarity-display-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="920" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929722" /><br/>
The base <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery/?ref=y2uwzwu">Clarity Max</a> model is priced at &#36;999.99, while the <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-pro-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-and-webcam/?ref=y2uwzwu">Clarity Max Pro with retractable webcam</a> is priced at &#36;1,199.99, and the top-of-the-line <a href="https://alogic.co/products/clarity-max-touch-32-uhd-4k-monitor-with-usb-c-power-delivery-webcam-and-touch-screen/?ref=y2uwzwu">Clarity Max Touch with webcam and touchscreen capabilities</a> is priced at &#36;1,399.99, but Alogic's sale currently knocks 20% off of those prices with coupon code CS20.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Note: Alogic provided MacRumors with the Clarity Max Touch display and the Matrix Ultimate for the purpose of this hands-on coverage. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Alogic. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</em></small><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alogic/">Alogic</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ces-2024/">CES 2024</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/ces-2024-alogic-charger-displays/">CES 2024: Alogic Launches Innovative &#039;Matrix Ultimate&#039; 3-in-1 Charger and 32-Inch 4K Displays With Optional Touchscreen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ces-2024-alogic-launches-innovative-matrix-ultimate-3-in-1-charger-and-32-inch-4k-displays-with-optional-touchscreen.2415857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Asks Vision Pro Developers to Avoid &#039;VR&#039; Branding and Hints at &#039;Vision&#039; Product Line</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/vision-pro-developers-asked-to-avoid-vr-branding/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-vision-pro-developers-to-avoid-vr-branding-and-hints-at-vision-product-line.2415856/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 05:17:03 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/vision-pro-developers-asked-to-avoid-vr-branding/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is asking developers to avoid mention of "AR" and "VR," as well as the Vision Pro as a generic "headset," when listing their apps on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/visionos-app-preview.jpg" alt="" width="1470" height="827" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-929750" /><br/>
<a href="https://developer.apple.com/visionos/submit/">Apple's developer website</a> now features new requirements for Vision Pro apps (via <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/01/08/apple-visionos-apps-ar-vr/">9to5Mac</a></em>), including how to appropriately list their apps on the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Instructions about how developers should describe their apps include specific prohibition of the terms augmented reality (AR), virtual reality (VR), extended reality (XR), or mixed reality (MR).<br/>
<br/>
Instead, developers should adopt the "spatial computing" phrasing that Apple has touted since the Vision Pro's announcement in June last year. The push is likely part of Apple's continued effort to disassociate the Vision Pro headset from other products in the space from the likes of Meta and forge its own path in the minds of customers.<blockquote><strong>Spatial computing</strong>: Refer to your app as a spatial computing app. Don't describe your app experience as augmented reality (AR), virtual reality (VR), extended reality (XR), or mixed reality (MR).</blockquote>Similarly, Apple requests that app developers do not refer to the Vision Pro generically as a "headset."<blockquote><strong>Apple Vision Pro</strong>: Always typeset Apple Vision Pro as three words with an uppercase A, V, and P followed by lowercase letters. Don't break Apple Vision Pro over two lines. Don't use the article the before Apple Vision Pro. Apple Vision Pro apps are available on the App Store or can be downloaded from the App Store. It's acceptable to say Name of app for Apple Vision Pro when your promotion is focused on features and benefits related to Apple Vision Pro. Don't refer to Apple Vision Pro generically as a "headset." The phrase "Apple Vision Pro" can't be included in your app name, but it can be included in your app description.</blockquote>Apple is also continuing to change mentions of "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>" to "Apple Vision" throughout its beta cycle. For example, Apple now refers to "Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple Vision apps" instead of "Mac, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; apps." Apple's website features a "Vision" product tab instead of a "Vision Pro" tab, but the gradual shift toward "Apple Vision" branding appears to add credence to the idea of Apple building a "Vision" product line.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro is positioned as a high-end device with a &#36;3,499 price tag, but there have been a multitude of rumors about Apple's plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/work-on-multiple-next-gen-vision-pro-headsets/">cheaper headset</a> in the future. Such a device would make sense as an "Apple Vision" headset, just as the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; is to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> is to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/09/vision-pro-developers-asked-to-avoid-vr-branding/">Apple Asks Vision Pro Developers to Avoid &#039;VR&#039; Branding and Hints at &#039;Vision&#039; Product Line</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-vision-pro-developers-to-avoid-vr-branding-and-hints-at-vision-product-line.2415856/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
