<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 20:03:18 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple to Support RCS, iPhone 16 Rumors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/18/top-stories-apple-rcs-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-to-support-rcs-iphone-16-rumors-and-more.2411356/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/18/top-stories-apple-rcs-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Raise your hand if you thought Apple was going to decide to support RCS messaging to enable better communication with green-bubble folks!<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/top-stories-18nov2023.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923044" /><br/>
That was certainly the biggest story of the week, but there was plenty more news including rumors about the timing of app sideloading support for users in the EU, developments coming in iOS 18, and a welcome change in watchOS 10.2 for swapping watch faces. Black Friday sales are also now in full swing, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple to Adopt RCS Messaging Standard for Better Interoperability With Android Devices</h2><br/>
In a bit of shocking news this week, Apple announced that it will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">add support for the Rich Communication Standard (RCS) standard</a> "later next year," allowing for better messaging interoperability with Android devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-rcs-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2776" height="1562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923042" /><br/>
Apple has long resisted adopting the successor to SMS and MMS messaging amid intense pressure from Google and Android device manufacturers, and it's unclear exactly what has changed Apple's mind other than perhaps ongoing pressure from regulators on various aspects of the company's business.<br/>
<br/>
While RCS will remain separate from iMessage, it will bring a number of advancements for communication between Apple and Android users, including enhanced security, higher-resolution photos and videos, audio messages, and much-improved group chats.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Series Rumored to Have These 17 New Features</h2><br/>
It's still only November, but we’ve been hearing about a decent number of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-16-series-16-rumored-new-features/">potential upgrades for next year's flagship iPhone lineup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922680" /><br/>
From bigger displays on the Pro models to camera improvements and more, it looks like 2024 should be a good year for those who are ready to make the jump to a new iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone App Sideloading Coming to Users in the EU in First Half of 2024</h2><br/>
iPhone users in the EU next year will be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/">download apps hosted outside of Apple's official App Store</a> to comply with European regulations, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/federighi-sideloading.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-825519" /><br/>
Writing in the latest subscriber edition of his Power On newsletter, Gurman said Apple will introduce a "highly controlled system" that lets EU users install apps hosted elsewhere. Apple also will reportedly alter Messages and payment apps as part of the changes, likely via a localized iOS 17 update.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Black Friday Deals Available Now: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</h2><br/>
We're less than a week away from Black Friday, but deals have been in full swing since October so we are firmly in holiday shopping season where you can get great deals across Apple products and accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-early-black-friday-deals.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920468" /><br/>
We're <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now/">keeping track of the best deals on Apple products and related accessories</a>, so be sure to check out our ongoing coverage throughout the rest of this month and into December.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AI-Infused iOS 18 Lauded as 'Ambitious and Compelling' by Apple Execs</h2><br/>
Apple internally believes its iOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, and tvOS 18 updates next year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">will be "ambitious and compelling,"</a> thanks to major new software features and designs in the works. That's according to the latest information relayed by <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Siri-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909208" /><br/>
While little is known about the specifics, many of the changes are believed to involve generative AI, including a smarter version of Siri that takes the virtual assistant's integration with the operating systems to a new level.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>watchOS 10.2 Beta Reintroduces Option to Change Apple Watch Faces With a Swipe</h2><br/>
As part of Apple's revamp of the Apple Watch interface with watchOS 10, the company did away with the ability to quickly change watch faces with a simple swipe.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-watch-ultra-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913279" /><br/>
While some users were relieved to no longer find themselves accidentally changing faces, others have been upset that changing faces now requires multiple steps.<br/>
<br/>
With the latest watchOS 10.2 beta seeded this week, Apple is seeking to satisfy both groups, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/watchos-10-2-watch-face-swipe-change/">bringing back the swipe gesture to change watch faces</a> but making it an optional setting. watchOS 10.2 is expected to see a public release next month.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/nov-16-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/18/top-stories-apple-rcs-support/">Top Stories: Apple to Support RCS, iPhone 16 Rumors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-to-support-rcs-iphone-16-rumors-and-more.2411356/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>25 New Things Your iPhone Can Do With Next Month&#039;s iOS 17.2 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-iphone-features-december-ios-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/25-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-with-next-months-ios-17-2-update.2411302/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 14:04:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-iphone-features-december-ios-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple made the first beta of iOS 17.2 available to developers in October. Since then we've seen two more betas, and with each iteration Apple continues to add more new features and changes, many of which users have been anticipating for quite a while. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.2-Everything-New-Your-iPhone-Can-Do-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922959" /><br/>
Below, we've listed 25 new things that are coming to your iPhone when the finalized version is publicly released in December.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>1. Help You Keep a Daily Journal</h2> <br/>
Your iPhone will soon be able to act as your personal journaling companion, thanks to Apple's new Journal app. Apple originally announced it was releasing a Journal app as part of iOS 17, and it's finally coming in iOS 17.2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Journal-App-iOS-17-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918878" /><br/>
The Journal app has a simple, straightforward interface. When you open it up, you're presented with a "+" button, and tapping on it lets you start a new entry. Journal entries are automatically dated, and you can bookmark your favorite ones. Entries can include images, voice recordings, and location tags, so not only will you have the ability to create and maintain a daily journal, you'll be able to easily record your thoughts, experiences, and memories with your iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>2. Set a Journaling Schedule</h2> <br/>
Staying consistent with journaling can be difficult, but your iPhone can make it a lot easier with the new Journal app's scheduling feature, which can be found in Settings ➝ Journal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/journal-schedule.jpg" alt="journal" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922941" /><br/>
The scheduling option isn't just a reminder – it's about building a habit. So whether it's a gentle reminder notification that you need in the morning or a prompt before bed, you can adapt the feature to your personal routine.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>3. Offer Journaling Suggestions</h2> <br/>
When you first open the Journal app, you can decide what information it can pull from your phone for writing suggestions. Options include workout activity, media like podcasts and music, photos, and significant locations. You can control which apps and services appear using the switches in the Settings app under Privacy & Security ➝ Journaling Suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/journal-suggestions.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922984" /><br/>
Here, there are also settings to prefer suggestions with others when you're around your contacts or large groups, and to be discoverable by others to help prioritize the suggestions of other people. If you don't like suggestions in general, you can simply turn them off (Settings ➝ Journal ➝ Skip Journaling Suggestions).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>4. Give Journaling Prompts</h2> <br/>
If you have a serious case of writer's block, iOS 17.2 can offer you entry prompts in the form of "reflections." These reflections are designed to inspire and guide you, providing ideas and topics to explore in each entry.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/journal-prompts.jpg" alt="journal" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922986" /><br/>
The reflections can vary from thought-provoking questions to creative writing cues, and if the one you're offered doesn't get your gears turning, you can tap a button to generate a new one.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>5. Secure Your Journal</h2> <br/>
Privacy and security are paramount when it comes to personal journaling. That's why iOS 17.2 introduces enhanced security features, including encryption and password protection, to safeguard your journal from unauthorized access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/journal-lock.jpg" alt="settings" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922990" /><br/>
The option can be found in the Settings app under Journal ➝ Lock Journal, and it allows you to use your device passcode, Face ID or Touch ID, providing peace of mind every time you record sensitive or personal information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>6. Translate with a Button Press</h2> <br/>
Overcome communication barriers with the new custom Translation option for the Action button in iOS 17.2. With just a button press, your iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max will be able to translate live conversations into multiple languages. The feature should be a boon for travelers, students, and anyone learning a language.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Action-Button-Translate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911022" /><br/>
You can choose which language the speech should be translated into in the Translate app. According to Apple, the translation is not just accurate but also context-aware, ensuring that nuances and colloquialisms are captured effectively.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>7. Show Detailed Weather Forecasts on Home Screen</h2> <br/>
The update includes new Details, Daily Forecast, and Sunrise/Sunset widgets for the Weather widget, providing more of the kind of information that you would normally only find by going into the Weather app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/weather-app-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918889" /><br/>
Details shows information like precipitation chance, UV index, wind speed, and air quality, while Daily Forecast offers the weather for the next few days in a small widget size. Sunrise/Sunset naturally shows the sunrise and sunset times for each day.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>8. Host Collaborative Music Playlists</h2> <br/>
Collaborative playlists in the Music app let you create and share playlists with friends, family, or colleagues, enabling everyone to contribute their favorite tracks. It adds another social dimension to the Music app, and provides a useful way to discover new music and share your musical tastes with others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
In a playlist you have made, just tap on the three-dot icon in the top right of the app, select the Collaborate option and choose Start Collaboration. You'll then be able to create a link to the playlist, and anyone who has access to that link can add to it. You can also invite people to join via QR code, and opt to approve each person that asks to join.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9. Use Stickers as Message Reactions</h2> <br/>
Apple aims to make message reactions in the Messages app more fun and expressive by offering an easier way to use stickers as an alternative to tapback reactions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tapback-reply-sticker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918892" /><br/>
Previously you had to drag a sticker or an emoji from the keyboard onto any message bubble. Now you can simply long press on any chat bubble and tap "Add Sticker," which lets you choose either a sticker or an emoji to apply to the corner of an iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10. Record Spatial Video</h2> <br/>
If you have an iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro Max, iOS 17.2 will allow you to record spatial video for viewing in the Photos app on Apple's forthcoming Vision Pro headset, set to be released in early 2024. (Note that when spatial videos captured with an ‌iPhone‌ are viewed on the ‌iPhone‌, they appear as normal videos.)<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
To enable spatial video recording, go to Settings ➝ Camera ➝ Formats, then toggle on Spatial Video for Apple Vision Pro. Video is recorded at 30 frames per second at 1080p, and one minute of video takes up 130MB of storage space. Apple says that for best results when recording spatial video, the iPhone should be held stable in landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>11. Populate a Favorites Music Playlist</h2> <br/>
Apple is introducing a Favorites Music Playlist in Apple Music that automatically aggregates any songs that you have favorited, ensuring that your most-liked tracks are always at your fingertips.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-favorite-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918891" /><br/>
Since it populates dynamically, it should make it easier to enjoy the music you love while removing some of the hassle of manual curation.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>12. Selectively Turn Off Your Listening History</h2> <br/>
There's a new privacy-centric feature that allows you to selectively turn off your listening history. This means that you can listen to music – or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/apple-music-listening-history-focus-filter/">allow your kids to listen to their stuff on your device</a> – without influencing your future recommendations or shared playlists.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-music-listening-history-focus1.jpg" alt="focus" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920453" /><br/>
It's a useful tool for times when you're exploring new genres or playing music for others, since it ensures that your personal recommendations remain untainted by atypical listening choices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>13. Verify Your iMessage Contacts</h2> <br/>
The security of iMessage has been enhanced with a new feature to verify your contacts. Contact Key Verification adds an extra layer of trust and authenticity to your conversations by displaying a code that verifies you are communicating with the intended person.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
Apple first previewed iMessage Contact Key Verification in December 2022, and said it is designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials. It should help in safeguarding against impersonation and phishing attempts, making iMessage and FaceTime more secure platforms for personal and professional communication.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>14. Sync Additional Message Settings in iCloud</h2> <br/>
iCloud's capabilities now include the synchronization of additional message settings across your Apple devices. A new "Messages in ‌iCloud‌" section in the Settings app shows the total amount of storage that messages are taking up, the number of messages synced to ‌iCloud‌, and the time of the last sync. There's also a "Sync Now" option to force an update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-messages-in-icloud.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918896" /><br/>
Preferences and customizations made in the Messages app on one device will automatically reflect on your other devices signed in to the same iCloud account. Apple previously said that additional settings would be synced through Messages in ‌iCloud‌ in ‌iOS 17‌, like Text Message Forwarding, Send & Receive accounts, and SMS filters across devices, so those additional settings are likely to sync, too.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>15. A New TV App Experience</h2><br/>
Apple is revamping the TV app in iOS 17.2, offering a refreshed and more user-friendly experience. The update focuses on improving navigation and discoverability, making it easier to find your favorite shows and movies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918905" /><br/>
Apple has removed the separate tabs for Movies and TV shows in the Store section of the Apple TV app, with everything now integrated together. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said that Apple also plans to remove the option to purchase TV shows and movies from the iTunes app as part of a TV app redesign.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>16. Improve Reliability of Emergency Alerts</h2><br/>
Apple has improved the reliability of emergency alerts on iPhone. In Settings -> Notifications & Emergency Alerts, there is a new "Local Awareness" option that can be turned on. Apple says that Local Awareness uses your approximate location to improve the timeliness, accuracy, and reliability of emergency alerts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-emergency-local-awareness.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918902" /><br/>
Whether it's severe weather warnings, Amber alerts, or other vital notifications, this setting should increase the probability that important alerts are not missed due to technical issues.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>17. Add More Color to Contact Posters</h2> <br/>
Add a splash of color to your Contact Poster, with a new rainbow-colored text option for your name, allowing you to make it more vibrant and visually appealing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-contact-poster-rainbow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918893" /><br/>
If you want your Contact Poster to stand out from the contacts crowd, this provides another way to do it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>18. Make Your iPhone an AirPlay Receiver</h2> <br/>
The iOS 17.2 update will turn your iPhone into an AirPlay receiver ready for the spatial computing era. A new "AirPlay Receiver" setting allows the upcoming ‌Apple Vision Pro‌ headset to stream or share content to your ‌iPhone‌.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-airplay-handoff.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918898" /><br/>
Earlier this year, Apple said AirPlay‌ would soon work with supported televisions in hotels, allowing users to easily enjoy their favorite content on the TV when traveling. Apple said the capability will be available before the end of the year in select hotels, and it looks as if iOS 17.2 could also be the update that makes it happen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>19. Add More Memoji Customizations</h2> <br/>
The update brings enhanced customization options for Memoji, allowing users to create avatars that are more representative of their personal style and identity.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-memoji-body.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918895" /><br/>
To that end, Apple has added a "Body" section for Memoji where users can customize waist, bust, shoulders, and arms.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>20. Rolling News Event Updates in Real Time</h2> <br/>
The News app now delivers events in real-time with added support for Live Activities, keeping users informed with up-to-the-minute updates on news-related events such as elections.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-apple-news-live-activities.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918899" /><br/>
Live Activities allow iPhone users to stay on top of real-time events right on the Lock Screen on any iPhone model compatible with iOS 17, and in the Dynamic Island on iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>21. Stop Adding Favorited Songs to Your Library</h2> <br/>
A new option included in the update enables you to stop favorited songs (and in many cases whole albums) from being automatically added to your music library. It gives you more control over your music collection by ensuring that only the songs you choose to add are saved.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-17-2-music-add-favorite-songs.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922545" /><br/>
The new toggle can be found in Settings ➝ Music ➝ Add Favorite Songs. If you turn the option off, don't worry – favorited songs will still populate the new Favorites playlist. The option to "Favorite" songs was added in iOS 17.1.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>22. Disable Inline Predictions</h2> <br/>
It's now possible to disable inline predictions when you're entering text into your iPhone. The new "Show Predictions Inline" toggle, found in Settings ➝ General ➝ Keyboard, is likely to be welcomed by those who prefer a more manual typing experience or find inline autocomplete text suggestions distracting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/keyboard-inline-predictions.jpg" alt="" width="1808" height="1017" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922546" /><br/>
The additional toggle also means that you can now turn off inline text predictions without disabling the predictive text that appears above the onscreen keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>23. FaceTime Blocked Contact Warnings</h2> <br/>
iOS 17.2 enhances privacy in FaceTime by introducing warnings for blocked contacts. If a blocked contact tries to reach you via FaceTime, the app now provides a notification, giving you awareness and control over the communication before the call is initiated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/General-Apps-FaceTime.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-832602" /><br/>
Apple provides warnings when joining a call with a blocked contact, or when a blocked contact is joining a call you're already on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>24. Share Your Contact Poster in FaceTime</h2> <br/>
The update adds new options for sharing your Contact Poster through FaceTime and Phone. Previously, the setting was only available for the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/phone-share-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922547" /><br/>
In the settings pages for both apps, "Share Name and Photo" can be toggled off, set to Contacts Only, or set to Always Ask, which prompts you before sharing that information with others.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>25. Expand Sensitive Content Warnings</h2> <br/>
Lastly, Apple's opt-in Sensitive Content Warning feature will work with Contact Posters in both the Contacts and Phone apps, as well as stickers in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Sensitive-Content-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922023" /><br/>
When turned on, the Sensitive Content Warning feature uses on-device machine learning to analyze photos and videos, and blurs photos or videos with any detected nudity before users view them. Apple says it does not receive any indication that nudity was detected, and does not gain access to the photos or videos as a result.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-iphone-features-december-ios-update/">25 New Things Your iPhone Can Do With Next Month&#039;s iOS 17.2 Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/25-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-with-next-months-ios-17-2-update.2411302/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pausing Advertising on X Following Latest Elon Musk Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-pauses-ads-on-x/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pausing-advertising-on-x-following-latest-elon-musk-controversy.2411296/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 12:14:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-pauses-ads-on-x/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		<category>Elon Musk</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is pausing all of its advertising on social network X, formerly known as Twitter, reports <em><a href="https://www.axios.com/2023/11/17/apple-twitter-x-advertising-elon-musk-antisemitism-ads">Axios</a></em>. The decision comes following antisemitic remarks that Musk <a href="https://twitter.com/elonmusk/status/1724908287471272299">made on Wednesday</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
After advertisers fled from X after Musk's takeover of the social network, Apple continued to pay for ad spots, and has been one of the Twitter's largest ad partners. Back in March, Musk <a href="https://deadline.com/2023/03/elon-musk-thanks-apple-disney-advertising-on-twitter-whic-would-have-gone-bankrupt-without-him-1235282055/">thanked Apple</a> for its support, calling the company one of Twitter's "biggest advertisers."<br/>
<br/>
Apple did <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/28/elon-musk-apple-stopped-twitter-ads/">temporarily pause ads</a> on Twitter back in November 2022, which spurred Musk to lash out and ask if Apple hated "free speech." Musk also said that Apple had threatened to remove Twitter from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and said that he would "make an alternative phone" if the social network was ultimately pulled.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/30/elon-musk-tim-cook-meeting-apple-park/">dispute was resolved</a> after Musk met with Cook at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> later that year, after which Musk claimed that Apple had in fact never threatened to remove Twitter from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and that it was a "misunderstanding." Musk ultimately called it a "good conversation," and after that point, Apple "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/03/apple-resumes-twitter-advertising/">fully resumed</a>" advertising. Reports in 2022 suggested Apple was spending more than <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2022-11-28/musk-says-that-apple-has-mostly-stopped-advertising-on-twitter">&#36;100 million per year</a> on Twitter ads.<br/>
<br/>
With Musk's latest comments, and evidence that X is <a href="https://www.mediamatters.org/twitter/musk-endorses-antisemitic-conspiracy-theory-x-has-been-placing-ads-apple-bravo-ibm-oracle">showing Apple ads</a> alongside pro-Hitler content, it is unclear if Apple will be convinced to resume advertising again sometime in the future. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/09/18/tim-cook-says-apple-constantly-weighing-advertising-on-elon-musks-x.html">in September said</a> that Apple is "constantly" evaluating whether Apple should be buying ads on the social network.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is not the only company pulling out of Twitter ads. IBM <a href="https://apnews.com/article/elon-musk-x-antisemitism-twitter-ads-83e68f03e9bf1d261c1a8c55066c4e59">said this week</a> that it is pulling ads, and the European Union also no longer plans to advertise on the social network. The White House earlier today <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/11/17/white-house-blasts-elon-musk-for-promoting-antisemitic-racist-hate.html">condemned Musk's comments</a>, and X employees told <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/11/16/technology/elon-musk-endorses-antisemitic-post-ibm.html">The New York Times</a></em> that it has been fielding calls from other companies upset with Musk.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-pauses-ads-on-x/">Apple Pausing Advertising on X Following Latest Elon Musk Controversy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pausing-advertising-on-x-following-latest-elon-musk-controversy.2411296/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>4 Best Black Friday iPad Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/4-best-black-friday-ipad-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/4-best-black-friday-ipad-deals.2411283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:19:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/4-best-black-friday-ipad-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Even though there's still one week until Black Friday, we're tracking a number of all-time low prices on iPads today. This also includes record lows on iPad accessories like the Magic Keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-red.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923016" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPads</h2><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 9th generation iPad, Amazon has the 64GB Wi-Fi model for &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00. This is a match of the best price we've ever tracked on this iPad, and it's a great entry-level option for kids or family members who don't need a tablet for intensive tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the 10th generation iPad at an all-time low price, and this one is a new deal for Black Friday 2023. The 64GB Wi-Fi model has hit &#36;349.00, down from &#36;449.00, which is &#36;50 below the typical price we've been tracking all year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the iPad Air, Amazon is discounting the 2022 64GB Wi-Fi tablet to &#36;499.99, down from &#36;599.00. It's another best-ever price, and it's one of many iPad Air deals that have appeared for Black Friday. You can also find cellular markdowns on Amazon right now.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JH3XS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There aren't many record low prices on the iPad Pro lineup, but Amazon does have the 128GB Wi-Fi 12.9-inch model for &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,099.00, which remains the best price we've tracked to date.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLF2BRM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>12.9-inch iPad Pro (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><h2>Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK">Apple Pencil (USB-C)</a> - &#36;71.00, down from &#36;79.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil 2</a> - &#36;89.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Magic Keyboard Folio</a> - &#36;169.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">11-inch Magic Keyboard</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09322LR1R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">12.9-inch Magic Keyboard</a> - &#36;249.00, down from &#36;349.00</li></ul> You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/4-best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">4 Best Black Friday iPad Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/4-best-black-friday-ipad-deals.2411283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iOS 18&#039;s AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-ai-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ios-18s-ai-features.2411279/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:54:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-ai-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/ios-18s-major-new-ai-features/id1602394741?i=1000635198080">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the widely rumored array of AI features heading for iOS 18 and Apple's other major software updates in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/NeOs-iR03Fo?si=F3CRMstGZU0sahiI" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Supply chain checks <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-generative-ai-late-2024-jeff-pu/">suggest</a> that Apple is building servers to deliver cloud-based AI in late 2024, as well as locally-processed "edge-AI." The company is reportedly planning to debut a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">"smarter" version of Siri</a> based on its own large language model (LLM) next year that can understand complex questions and auto-complete sentences more effectively, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">integrate with the Shortcuts app</a> for complex multi-step tasks.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to be working on adding AI to as many apps as possible, including features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, such as auto-generated playlists, and productivity apps like Pages and Keynote, where AI could assist with writing or creating slide decks. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup is also rumored to feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">exclusive AI capabilities</a>, and the company is even rumored to be looking into how generative AI could be used to aid <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so head over and subscribe to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show's new YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, <a href="https://pca.st/itunes/1602394741">Pocket Casts</a>, <a href="https://castro.fm/itunes/1602394741">Castro</a>, <a href="https://podcasts.google.com/feed/aHR0cHM6Ly9hdWRpb2Jvb20uY29tL2NoYW5uZWxzLzUwOTYxNDQucnNz">Google Podcasts</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the current state of gaming in Apple's ecosystem with <a href="https://toucharcade.com"><em>TouchArcade</em></a>'s Jared Nelson and Eli Hodapp.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by exciting guests like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/07/the-macrumors-show-wwdc23-recap-andru-edwards-kevin-nether/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/16/the-macrumors-show-quinn-nelson-iphone-15-rumors/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is now on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-ai-features/">The MacRumors Show: iOS 18&#039;s AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ios-18s-ai-features.2411279/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win Custom-Colored AirPods Pro 2 From ColorWare</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-airpod-pro-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-custom-colored-airpods-pro-2-from-colorware.2411278/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 09:38:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-airpod-pro-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		<category>ColorWare</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've <a href="https://www.colorware.com/">teamed up with ColorWare</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a set of <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1405-airpods-pro-2nd-gen-usb-c.aspx?c=variant-142*l02-9ngo*l03-9nit*l04-9njs">custom-painted second-generation AirPods Pro with a USB-C port</a>. Apple in September discontinued the Lightning-based version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 and instead swapped over to USB-C, and ColorWare is already able to make them in unique colors<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923022" /><br/>
ColorWare has been offering custom-painted Apple products and accessories for more than two decades now, and this is <em>the</em> company to go with if you want AirPods or Apple devices in shades that are less boring than Apple's default colors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923023" /><br/>
All of ColorWare's products come in hundreds of unique color combinations, and it customizes AirPods, &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTags</a>, Magic Mouse, and accessories like consoles and controllers from companies like Nintendo, Microsoft, and Sony.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923025" /><br/>
Custom <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1405-airpods-pro-2nd-gen-usb-c.aspx?c=variant-142*l02-9ngo*l03-9nit*l04-9njs">second-generation AirPods Pro 2 with a USB-C port</a> are available from ColorWare for &#36;439, a price that includes colorization for both of the AirPods and the accompanying USB-C <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Charging Case. If you just want to customize the earbuds, that can be done for &#36;389.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-5.jpg" alt="" width="1999" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923026" /><br/>
There's a premium price tag for ordering from ColorWare, but with &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 only available in white, this is the sole way to get AirPods in black, red, blue, orange, or dozens of other colors. With the holidays coming up, custom AirPods are a unique gift you won't find elsewhere.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-6.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923027" /><br/>
ColorWare also has a multi-step coating process that includes a primer, the application of a proprietary color formula, and an X2 liquid plastic coating that protects the color. Custom painting is guaranteed for 12 months.<br/>
<br/>
You can get both solid and metallic paint options from ColorWare, along with gloss and matte finishes depending on personal preference. There are traditional silver, gray, and gold colors that match Apple devices, but colors in every shade of the rainbow are available too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-7.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923028" /><br/>
Each AirPod can be painted the same color as the case, or you can get the case and the earbuds all in different colors, which leads to thousands of color combinations to chose from.<br/>
<br/>
ColorWare even offers custom colors <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1419-colorware-cowpods-pro-pink.aspx?c=variant-14h">like the "CowPods Pro"</a> that features a case with a cow print, or the <a href="https://www.colorware.com/p-1418-colorware-airpods-pro-2nd-gen-supernova.aspx?c=variant-14g">black holographic Supernova set</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/colorware-airpods-pro-usb-c-2.jpg" alt="" width="1999" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923024" /><br/>
To create its custom accessories, ColorWare uses standard second-generation &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; with USB-C case directly from Apple, which means the full AirPods functionality is intact.<br/>
<br/>
We have two sets of custom &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 with USB-C port to give away to <em>MacRumors</em> readers. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winners and send the prizes. You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, <a href="http://www.threads.net/@macrumors/">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/6Fasc/colorware-giveaway" rel="nofollow">ColorWare Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (November 17) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on November 24. The winners will be chosen randomly on or shortly after November 24 and will be contacted by email. The winners will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before new winners are chosen.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/colorware/">ColorWare</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/macrumors-giveaway-colorware-airpod-pro-2/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win Custom-Colored AirPods Pro 2 From ColorWare</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-custom-colored-airpods-pro-2-from-colorware.2411278/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Reveals Black Friday Plans With Sitewide Sales Available Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/best-buy-reveals-black-friday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-reveals-black-friday-plans-with-sitewide-sales-available-now.2411269/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 08:20:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/best-buy-reveals-black-friday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following in the footsteps of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/walmart-black-friday-plans/">Walmart</a>, Best Buy this week detailed its plans for the Black Friday shopping holiday and its schedule looks a lot like other retailers. In terms of sales, <a href="https://howl.me/ck1uKiKojui">Best Buy</a> has the expected list of TVs, appliances, video games, computers, streaming devices, and even some all-time low prices on MacBook Air notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-new-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922694" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Best Buy's Black Friday Schedule</h2><br/>
Best Buy's Black Friday sale officially starts today, November 17, although there have been deals running all month long. The retailer said that these deals will run online and in store through Saturday, November 25. Then shoppers can expect a refresh of deals on Cyber Monday.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>November 17-25: Black Friday sale</li><br/>
<li>November 26-27: Cyber Monday sale</li></ul><br/>
<h2>My Best Buy Membership</h2><br/>
My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total members will be able to shop exclusive deals during this time, and save even more compared to non-members. You can <a href="https://howl.me/ck0EWogYi7m"><strong>sign up for these memberships</strong></a> on Best Buy's website, and prices start at &#36;49.99/year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Deals Available Now</h2><br/>
Shoppers should note that many of the deal prices below reflect My Best Buy Plus/Total exclusive prices, particularly regarding the MacBook Air and MacBook Pro sales. If you're a member, this will net you great Black Friday exclusive discounts sitewide at Best Buy, and any future My Best Buy Plus deals that may appear over the next year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1uKiKojui"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Best Buy Black Friday Event</div></a></div><h3>Apple</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-lights.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922987" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0ENeWZv3b">13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air</a> - &#36;899.00, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ">15-inch M2 MacBook Air</a> - &#36;999.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sZ0jMbvh">14-inch M3 MacBook Pro</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,599.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>TVs</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-tvs.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922993" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0EZNrRGkg">TCL 40-inch S-Class 1080p Smart TV with Fire TV</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E0KC17zf">LG 48-inch Class A2 Series OLED Smart TV</a> - &#36;549.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E1y2bnRl">Samsung 75-inch Class TU690T Crystal 4K Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;579.99, down from &#36;749.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E2vxgpnW">LG 86-inch Class UR7800 Series LED 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,249.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E3qCGZKD">Samsung 77-inch Class S89C OLED 4K UHD Smart Tizen TV</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;3,599.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Computers</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-laptop.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923003" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E4YyH4SH">Lenovo Ideapad 15.6-inch Touch Laptop</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E6EIOZzh">HP Victus 15.6-inch R5 Gaming Laptop</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E7tbh9Pm">HP Envy 2-in-1 14-inch Touch-Screen Laptop</a> - &#36;749.99, down from &#36;1,079.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Monitors</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/lg-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923002" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E8I85m59">LG 45-inch OLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-soundbar.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923001" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E5RV0RNW">Samsung A Series 2.1ch Dolby & DTS and Soundbar</a> - &#36;119.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0FaWEYIyf">Bose QuietComfort 45 Noise Cancelling Over-the-Ear Headphones</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;329.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Video Games</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-ps5.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922999" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0E9SazKdl">PlayStation 5 Console Marvel's Spider-Man 2 Bundle</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;559.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Smart Home</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/best-buy-ring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923000" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0Fcfj5lH8">Ring Video Doorbell</a> - &#36;54.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck0FcYe8Cu6">Arlo Pro 4 Spotlight Camera Security Bundle</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;599.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/best-buy-reveals-black-friday/">Best Buy Reveals Black Friday Plans With Sitewide Sales Available Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-reveals-black-friday-plans-with-sitewide-sales-available-now.2411269/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing to Add Support for Digital Car Keys on MINI Vehicles</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-digital-car-key-mini-vehicles/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-support-for-digital-car-keys-on-mini-vehicles.2411266/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:57:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-digital-car-key-mini-vehicles/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>MINI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is preparing to begin supporting digital car keys in the Wallet app for certain MINI vehicles, allowing owners to lock, unlock, and start their vehicles using a pass stored in the Wallet app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/mini-oled-display.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922995" /><br/>
MINI's parent company BMW was the first manufacturer to launch digital car keys in Wallet back in 2020, but it wasn't until earlier today that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> configuration files were updated to specifically list MINI among supported brands, as spotted by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris.<br/>
<br/>
Several months ago, MINI unveiled its <a href="https://www.mini.com/en_MS/home/new-family/a-digital-quantum-leap.html">next-generation MINI Operating System 9</a>, which includes MINI Digital Key Plus. The feature will support Ultra Wideband on both iOS and Android, allowing the user to access the vehicle without having to remove their phone from their pocket or bag.<br/>
<br/>
MINI Operating System 9 will run on the auto industry's first large circular OLED display known as the MINI Interaction Unit, a customizable 9.4-inch screen mounted prominently in the center of the dashboard with colorful and immersive themes available to help personalize the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
The new MINI Interaction Unit with MINI Operating System 9 and MINI Digital Key Plus recently debuted in the new <a href="https://www.mini.com/en_MS/home/new-family/all-electric-mini-cooper.html">all-electric MINI Cooper</a> and <a href="https://www.mini.com/en_MS/home/new-family/all-electric-mini-countryman.html">MINI Countryman</a>, with both vehicles launching next year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mini/">MINI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-digital-car-key-mini-vehicles/">Apple Preparing to Add Support for Digital Car Keys on MINI Vehicles</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-to-add-support-for-digital-car-keys-on-mini-vehicles.2411266/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Black Friday Sale Introduces Steep Discounts on TVs, Monitors, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/samsung-black-friday/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-black-friday-sale-introduces-steep-discounts-on-tvs-monitors-and-more.2411264/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:53:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/samsung-black-friday/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is joining the collection of retailers kicking off Black Friday sales today, with <a href="https://howl.me/ck1tDFDYO0R">big savings on monitors and TVs</a>. In total, you can get up to 30 percent off sitewide at Samsung this week, with deals on everything from appliances to smartphones as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-the-frame.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922968" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Samsung is encouraging users to shop through the Shop Samsung mobile app this season, which has some exclusive deals on smartphones, smartwatches, and mobile accessories. Prices on TVs and monitors should be the same on the web as they are on the mobile app, however.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tDFDYO0R"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE SALE</div>Samsung Black Friday</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Monitor deals include a new all-time low price on the Smart Monitor M8, which is actually located at Amazon. This new monitor is now down to just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0C3WMX69W%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26smid%3DATVPDKIKX0DER%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, from &#36;699.99, in the Warm White colorway. At Samsung, you'll find savings on even more gaming and computer monitors.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tF40hlZ8">27-inch Odyssey G32A Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;199.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tFfAKEc2">34-inch ViewFinity S50GC Monitor</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tEtLSIa0">49-inch Odyssey G9 QLED Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tDoV18FW">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For TVs, Samsung is offering steep &#36;1,000 markdowns on the popular Frame TV, as well as up to &#36;2,500 other models, including 8K TV sets. There's also a mix of audio equipment on sale, with up to &#36;500 off select soundbars and home theater set-up bundles.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tOGqagCf">85-inch Crystal UHD TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tJBTe3BC">The Frame QLED 4K TV</a> - Save up to &#36;1,000, starting at just &#36;549.99 for 32-inch</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tNGTQwIP">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,500.00, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tKrmpTeJ">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,799.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tLk05pDX">55-inch OLED TV</a> - &#36;1,899.99, down from &#36;2,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tL5nOtB2">85-inch Neo QLED 8K TV</a> - &#36;5,499.99, down from &#36;7,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tPlYX1Pr">S-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;599.99, down from &#36;899.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/ck1tMHeYe4E">Q-Series Wireless Dolby ATMOS Soundbar</a> - &#36;1,399.99, down from &#36;1,899.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/samsung-black-friday/">Samsung Black Friday Sale Introduces Steep Discounts on TVs, Monitors, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-black-friday-sale-introduces-steep-discounts-on-tvs-monitors-and-more.2411264/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Files Legal Challenge Against EU Law as Sideloading Requirement Looms</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu-law-as-sideloading-requirement-looms.2411261/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 07:09:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today filed a legal challenge against the European Union's Digital Markets Act ahead of the impending requirement to enable app sideloading on its devices (via <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/legal/transactional/apple-files-legal-challenge-eus-digital-markets-act-2023-11-17/">Reuters</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
The Digital Markets Act (DMA), which came into effect on November 1, 2022, requires "gatekeeper" companies to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/01/dma-eu-law-could-force-major-changes-apple/">open up their services and platforms</a> to other companies and developers. The DMA will have a significant impact on Apple's platforms and it could result in the company being forced to make major changes to the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>‌, Messages, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, and more. For example, Apple will be obliged to enable users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/">"sideload" apps</a> from outside the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. The company appears to have already put <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/eu-iphone-app-sideloading-coming-2024/">preparations</a> in place to acquiesce to this demand in early 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's new legal case takes issue with specific decisions taken by the European Commission under the DMA, but the exact details of the challenge have not yet been publicized. The case is expected to include an argument against the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; being included on the EU's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">list of gatekeeper platforms</a>, which requires app sideloading to be an option to allow users to avoid the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; if they wish. In a statement at the time, Apple told <em>Bloomberg</em>, "We remain very concerned about the privacy and data security risks the DMA poses for our users." Meta and TikTok have filed similar appeals disputing the European Commission's inclusion of their services.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu/">Apple Files Legal Challenge Against EU Law as Sideloading Requirement Looms</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-files-legal-challenge-against-eu-law-as-sideloading-requirement-looms.2411261/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Black Friday Sale Takes Up to 25% Off Speakers, Soundbars, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/sonos-black-friday-sale-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-black-friday-sale-takes-up-to-25-off-speakers-soundbars-and-more.2411258/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 06:29:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/sonos-black-friday-sale-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday is now just one week away, and numerous retailers have opened up their official Black Friday sales today. This includes <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a>, which is offering up to 20 percent off select home theater products and up to 25 percent off portable speakers for this week only.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/new-sonos-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921988" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Sonos very rarely offers straight cash discounts on individual products, with typical sales throughout the year focusing on bundle sales. For Black Friday, the company is finally back with steep markdowns on numerous products, and you don't need to bundle or enter a code for the savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 25% OFF</div>Sonos Black Friday Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The deal prices listed below will last through Cyber Monday on November 27. There's a good mix of devices on sale, including the popular Arc soundbar for &#36;719 (&#36;180 off), cheaper Ray soundbar for &#36;223 (&#36;56 off), Roam Bluetooth speaker for &#36;134 (&#36;45 off), and more.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Arc Soundbar</a> - &#36;719, down from &#36;899</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/beam">Beam Soundbar</a> - &#36;399, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/ray">Ray Soundbar</a> - &#36;223, down from &#36;279</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sub</a> - &#36;639, down from &#36;799</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub-mini">Sub Mini</a> - &#36;343, down from &#36;429</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam">Roam Speaker</a> - &#36;134, down from &#36;179</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-sl">Roam SL Speaker</a> - &#36;119, down from &#36;159</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Era 100 Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/amp">Amp</a> - &#36;599, down from &#36;699</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/port">Port</a> - &#36;399, down from &#36;449</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're starting your holiday shopping this week, we've got you covered with guides for the best early Black Friday deals for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-macbook-deals/">MacBook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">Apple Watch</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">iPad</a>. We've also been keeping an eye on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now/">best overall Apple deals</a> in the lead-up to November 24. All of these guides will be updated as the month continues, so be sure to bookmark and revisit to stay up-to-date on the best prices for the products you have an eye on.<br/>
<br/>
For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/sonos-black-friday-sale-2023/">Sonos Black Friday Sale Takes Up to 25% Off Speakers, Soundbars, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-black-friday-sale-takes-up-to-25-off-speakers-soundbars-and-more.2411258/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Apple Plans to Bring OLED to Nine New Devices By 2027</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-plans-to-bring-oled-to-nine-new-devices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-plans-to-bring-oled-to-nine-new-devices-by-2027.2411257/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 06:12:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-plans-to-bring-oled-to-nine-new-devices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to bring OLED display technology to nine new devices by 2027, according to a new report from Taiwan's <a href="https://m.etnews.com/20231116000282"><em>ET News</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/Oled-iPads-and-MackBook-Pro-Notch.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1403" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-824300" /><br/>
Following the introduction of OLED displays on both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/ipad-pro-oled-panel-production-in-2024/">next year</a>, Apple reportedly plans to bring the technology to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> in 2026. While the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; will retain a 10.9-inch display, the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s screen will grow from 8.3- to 8.7-inches in size. In 2027, Apple will bring OLED display technology to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-working-on-larger-ipad-air/">rumored 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> model, which is expected to debut with an LCD display <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">early next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple apparently plans to use a low-temperature polycrystalline oxide (LTPO) OLED panel for the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and a single-stack low-temperature polycrystalline silicon (LTPS) panel for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, meaning that ProMotion for refresh rates up to 120Hz will continue to be exclusive to the high-end models. <br/>
<br/>
In 2027, Apple will upgrade the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s OLED panels to a next-generation panel with improved light efficiency via Color Filter on Encapsulation (CoE), which is said to reduce power consumption by around 20%. Use of a color filter could also enable Apple to implement under-display camera technology on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
In 2025, Apple will purportedly bring OLED to the 16-inch MacBook Pro, followed by the 14-inch model in 2026. The 13- and 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models will also transition from LCD to OLED in 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Benefits of OLED include increased brightness, higher contrast ratio, greater color accuracy, and lower power consumption compared to existing models with LCD panels. Apple already uses OLED displays for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch models, with the exception of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>. The report notes that OLED panels are also thinner and lighter than LCDs, which offer particular benefits to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/apple-plans-to-bring-oled-to-nine-new-devices/">Report: Apple Plans to Bring OLED to Nine New Devices By 2027</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-apple-plans-to-bring-oled-to-nine-new-devices-by-2027.2411257/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Black Friday Deals Available Now: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now-airpods-iphone-ipad-and-more.2411255/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 05:31:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now&#038;post_date=1700238697/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're now less than one week away from Black Friday 2023, and discount events have begun in full force across the Internet this weekend. In this article, we're highlighting all of the best deals you can get right now on Apple products and other related accessories, and we'll be updating as prices change and new deals arrive. Of course, there's no guarantee that better prices won't appear later in the season, but anyone who wants to shop early will find the best deals currently available listed below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/General-Black-Friday-Deals-2022-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874255" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Specifically, in this article we're sharing all of the Apple products that currently have all-time low prices, or discounts that are at least very close to their record-low prices. Every deal shared below is available to purchase right now, and <strong>you can use the links below to jump directly to the section you're shopping for today.</strong><br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="#homepod">HomePod</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#airpods">AirPods</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#iphone">iPhone</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#ipad">iPad</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#mac">Mac</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#apple_watch">Apple Watch</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="#accessories">Accessories</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For more Black Friday deals, particularly including current and upcoming sales from third-party accessory makers, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="homepod">HomePod</h2><br/>
<h3 id="homepod_2nd_gen">HomePod (2nd Gen)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/homepod-candycanes-1.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922530" /><br/>
<br/>
B&H Photo has been the only retailer with a consistent discount on Apple's second generation HomePod. Right now, you can get it in both colors for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. While not a huge markdown, this continues to be the best price we've ever tracked.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1746861-REG/apple_mqj73ll_a_homepod_2nd_generation.html/kw/APHOMEPODMN/BI/2696/KBID/3612"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>HomePod (Gen 2) for &#36;279.99</div></a></div><h2 id="airpods">AirPods</h2><br/>
<h3 id="airpods_2">AirPods 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922536" /><br/>
<br/>
We originally tracked the AirPods 2 for &#36;69.00 at Amazon in early November, but that sale quickly expired. For now, you can get the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This version of the AirPods is perfect for anyone on your holiday shopping list who may be asking for a simple and reliable pair of wireless earbuds, particularly at this insanely low price tag. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_3">AirPods 3</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-3-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922535" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;139.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. These are upgraded in a few ways from the AirPods 2, with spatial audio, Adaptive EQ, force sensor controls, sweat and water resistance, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_pro_2">AirPods Pro 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-pro-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922534" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the Pro lineup, Verizon has the AirPods Pro 2 (Lightning) for <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation%2F"><strong>&#36;184.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. We haven't seen a steep discount on the new USB-C model in about a week, so right now this is the most notable AirPods Pro deal. At &#36;64 off, it's still a great deal and an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-airpods-pro-2nd-generation%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;64 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (Lightning) for &#36;184.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="airpods_max">AirPods Max</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-max-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922533" /><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the high-end AirPods Max are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;549.00. Discounts on the AirPods Max have been rare over the past few months, so this one is a second-best price on the over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZD76NP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone">iPhone</h2><br/>
<h3 id="att">AT&T</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922708" /><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fdeals%2F">AT&T</a> quite a few sales and offers for multiple iPhone 15 devices, including up to &#36;1,000 off the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-max.html">iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> with an eligible smartphone trade-in. Models with lower storage capacities can be purchased at no cost thanks to these discounts, and of course you'll need to purchase the new smartphone on a qualifying installment agreement. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Pro at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can get up to &#36;830 off the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15.html">iPhone 15</a> or <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-plus.html">iPhone 15 Plus</a> as well, with the same stipulations as the Pro devices. Both offers will be delivered via monthly bill credits, starting within three bills after trade-in is completed. It'll be applied in equal amounts over the term of your installment agreement.<br/>
<br/>
For the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max offer, you'll need to trade in a device with a value of &#36;230 or higher to get the full &#36;1,000 off markdown. You'll get up to &#36;830 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;130 to &#36;229 and up to &#36;350 in bill credits with a trade-in value of &#36;35 to &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
For older iPhone models, AT&T is offering the 128GB <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-14.html">iPhone 14 at &#36;10.99/month</a> with no trade-in required. Similarly, the iPhone 14 Pro is available at &#36;15/month with no trade-in required. For these, all you'll need is to purchase the smartphones on an installment plan and pick or upgrade to an eligible unlimited plan.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T is also taking <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fwearables%2F">&#36;300 off any Apple Watch</a> when you purchase two at the same time. Like smartphone plans, you'll have to buy two Apple Watches on an installment plan, add at least one new line, and activate both on your wireless plan. Afterwards, you'll get up to &#36;300 in bill credits over 36 months.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="verizon">Verizon</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iphone-15-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922707" /><br/>
At <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F">Verizon</a>, you can get a special bundle offer if you're interested in purchasing the new <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F">iPhone 15 Pro</a> this holiday season. When you do pick up the new smartphone with a new line on an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan, Verizon will reward you with an Apple TV 4K (64GB) and six months of Apple One at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">FREE APPLE TV 4K</div>iPhone 15 Pro at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, you can purchase <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple%2F">higher storage iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max models</a>, but at that point you'll be paying a little extra. The Apple TV 4K promotion requires a smarpthone purchase on an eligible plan and ends on November 15, while the Apple One six month promotion requires a line subscribed to an Unlimited Plus or Unlimited Ultimate plan.<br/>
<br/>
For last year's models, you can <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14067866?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-14-plus%2F">get four iPhone 14 Plus devices for free</a> along with four lines on Unlimited Welcome at &#36;120/month. A new line on any 5G Unlimited plan is required per smartphone. You can also stack this with Verizon's current tablet and smartwatch promotions, which offer up to &#36;279.99 off these devices.<br/>
<br/>
Verizon is also a great place to buy stocking stuffers for techies during the holiday season with its abundant <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-14048362?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fdeals%2Fproducts%2F">accessory sales</a>. Right now it has up to &#36;50 off Anker speakers, 30% off Nimble chargers, 20% off Apple Watch bands, and 20% off Mophie chargers.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="visible">Visible</h3><br/>
Verizon's <a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909">Visible</a> brand has &#36;10 off its premium Visible+ service, now priced at &#36;35/month with the promo code 35FOR6 used at checkout. This promotion will last for six months, and after it ends it will return to the regular price of &#36;45/month for the Visible+ service.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF/MONTH</div>Visible+ Cellular Plan</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Visible offers all of the latest smartphones, including iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models. When you join Visible, you'll save up to &#36;240 via monthly bill credits on your account. You'll need to join Visible on a new line of service, purchase a new device, and select the Visible+ plan.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="t-mobile">T-Mobile</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519">T-Mobile</a> is providing up to &#36;1,000 off the new iPhone 15 or iPhone 15 Pro when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Next plan. You can get up to &#36;830 off these devices when you trade in an eligible device on a Go5G Plus plan.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/cell-phones/brand/apple?icid=MGPO_TMO_P_23HOLIIP15_ACF7436252B5D95636519"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The carrier also has a wide variety of previous generation iPhones at a discount. This includes the iPhone 13 and iPhone SE at no extra cost when purchased on select cellular plans and trading in eligible devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ipad">iPad</h2><br/>
<h3 id="9th_gen_ipad">9th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-1-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922714" /><br/>
<br/>
We've been tracking a great all-time low discount on the ninth generation iPad since Prime Day, and the deal is still around in November. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. At this price, the iPad is a perfect entry-level tablet for a kid or family member who doesn't need the tablet for work-intensive projects.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="10th_gen_ipad">10th Gen iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-2-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922713" /><br/>
<br/>
The upgraded iPad from 2022 also has a great discount on Amazon right now, with the 64GB Wi-Fi model on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. This model comes with a bigger 10.9-inch Liquid Retina display, A14 Bionic chip for a performance boost, Wi-Fi 6, and more.<br/>
<br/>
This beats the sale from earlier in the month by &#36;50 and is a new all-time low price on the iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="6th_gen_ipad_mini">6th Gen iPad Mini</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-mini-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922712" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 8.3-inch iPad mini 6 is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This iPad mini has an 8.3-inch Liquid Retina display, A15 Bionic chip, USB-C, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G983JJS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="5th_gen_ipad_air">5th Gen iPad Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-air-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922711" /><br/>
<br/>
Switching to iPad Air models, the 2022 64GB Wi-Fi tablet has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;599.00. That's a solid all-time low price on this model, and you can also find a few other storage configurations at record lows this time around. Note that for the majority of colors, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon to see these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JH3XS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac">Mac</h2><br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m1_macbook_air">13-inch M1 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-m1-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922931" /><br/>
<br/>
The M1 MacBook Air has returned to its steep discounted price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a> for the 256GB model, down from &#36;999.00. This is a great deal and perfect computer for anyone who needs an Apple notebook for simple email and internet browsing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>M1 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="13-inch_m2_macbook_air">13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/m2-macbook-air-candycane.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922930" /><br/>
<br/>
At Best Buy, you can get the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"><strong>&#36;899.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,099.00. This deal is only available for My Best Buy Plus/Total members, and it's an all-time low price. You'll find a similar record low deal on the <a href="https://howl.me/ck1sc246Dch">512GB model</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sb5g8usy"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="15-inch_m2_macbook_air">15-inch M2 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-gingerbread-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922720" /><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for the all-time low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. The 512GB model is also available for the record low price of <a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. Both have all colors on sale, and they're only available at these prices for My Best Buy Plus/Total members.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's latest MacBook Air model is a great option with numerous pro-level features without the price tag. For a deep dive into all the similarities and differences between each line, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro-buyers-guide/">read our buyer's guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s37bL0vJ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s4Up2SuU"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>15-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_macbook_pro">M3 MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-pro-gingerbread.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922719" /><br/>
<br/>
There are a few notable discounts on the new M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy and Amazon this week, including savings on the 14-inch and 16-inch models. These are some of the first big discounts on the M3 MacBook Pro, and you can get up to &#36;200 off these notebooks.<br/>
<br/>
For the 14-inch models at Best Buy below, note that the prices reflect My Best Buy Plus/Total member savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1sZ0jMbvh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3, 512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s09UEdeF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck1s1XidD9X"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;2,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m3_imac">M3 iMac</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/imac-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922718" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is offering record low prices on the just-released M3 iMac, with prices as low as &#36;1,199.00 for the 8-Core GPU, 256GB model. In total, these sales represent up to &#36;100 off the new M3 iMac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5HSYSS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-Core GPU, 256GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch">Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_series_9">Apple Watch Series 9</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922717" /><br/>
<br/>
Right now, the best early Black Friday Apple Watch deals are focused entirely on the new Series 9 models. You can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">41mm GPS device for &#36;349.00</a> at Amazon, down from &#36;399.00. This &#36;50 discount is a new all-time low price on the 2023 smartwatch. Likewise, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">45mm GPS is down to &#36;379.00</a> at Amazon, another &#36;50 markdown and record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX13ZGM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for cellular models, there are a few deals to discover. Amazon has the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">41mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;449.00</a>, as well as the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">45mm cellular Series 9 model for &#36;479.00</a>. Both of these are &#36;50 discounts and more all-time low prices for the smartwatch lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;479.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_watch_ultra_2">Apple Watch Ultra 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ultra-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922928" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has nearly every model of the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for the all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX4JGWL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;739.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX4JGWL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;739.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<h3 id="iphone_15_cases">iPhone 15 Cases</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/finewoven-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922725" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking nearly 30 percent off the new FineWoven Cases for iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus this week. Not every color is discounted, but those that are have prices as low as <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;23.23</strong></a> for these brand new accessories, down from &#36;59.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You need to clip the on-page coupon and head to checkout to see the deal.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;36 OFF</div>iPhone 15 FineWoven Case for &#36;23.23</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWV2WZW%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;12 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case for &#36;47.20</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="magsafe_chargers">MagSafe Chargers</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/magsafe-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922724" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Woot and Amazon, you can get a few of Apple's best wireless and MagSafe chargers for all-time low prices. This includes the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;29.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00 and the Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"><strong>&#36;34.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;79.00. Amazon has the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
These are great stocking stuffer present ideas for the holiday season, and all the Woot accessories are in new condition.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;29.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_24"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;44 OFF</div>Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock for &#36;34.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h3 id="siri_remote">Siri Remote</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/siri-remote-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922723" /><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking to replace or upgrade your Siri Remote, Woot has the second generation model with Lightning at its lowest-ever price of <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"><strong>&#36;44.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;59.00. Like other Woot Apple accessory sales going on right now, this one is in new condition and has a one year Apple limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-tv-siri-remote-2nd-gen-6%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_3"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>Siri Remote (Lightning) for &#36;44.99</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="keyboards">Keyboards</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/keyboard-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922722" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is discounting the Magic Keyboard Folio to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This keyboard works with the 10th generation iPad, and Amazon's new sale price is now the steepest discount we've ever tracked for this accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard Folio for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you have an 11-inch iPad Pro, you can match it with the 11-inch iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;299.00. This one is available in both White and Black colors, and it's another best-ever price. This sale has been fluctuating in price, so if you don't see it available, be sure to check back again soon.<br/>
<br/>
The only downside is Amazon's current shipping estimate, which has a generous one to four week estimate for shipping. This still guarantees a delivery by Christmas, so if you're looking to buy it as a present and want to take advantage of this solid discount, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (11-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09322LR1R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (12.9-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="apple_pencil_2">Apple Pencil 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/apple-pencil-candycanes.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874814" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00 this Black Friday, down from &#36;129.00. Compared to previous sales, this is a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<h3 id="airtag">AirTag</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/airtag-candycane-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-874368" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;86.88 this week, down from &#36;99.00. We've seen this version of the AirTag go lower in the past, but right now this is the best sale online.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;14 OFF</div>AirTag (4-Pack) for &#36;86.88</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've been tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now/">Apple Black Friday Deals Available Now: AirPods, iPhone, iPad, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-black-friday-deals-available-now-airpods-iphone-ipad-and-more.2411255/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Philips Hue Secure Contact Sensors Gain HomeKit Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/philips-hue-secure-contact-sensors-support-homekit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-secure-contact-sensors-gain-homekit-support.2411248/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 03:55:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/philips-hue-secure-contact-sensors-support-homekit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Philips Hue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Signify has released new Philips Hue Contact Sensor firmware that adds support for Apple HomeKit, reports <em><a href="https://hueblog.com/2023/11/16/hue-secure-contact-sensor-now-compatible-with-homekit/">Hueblog.com</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/hue-secure-contact-sensor.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908248" /><br/>
Previously the indoor sensors could only be controlled through the Philips Hue app's Security Center. Now, after updating to the new firmware (1961076030), they appear in the Home app, where users can use the "open" and "closed" status of the sensors to create automations and control other HomeKit devices that are not connected to the Philips Hue Bridge. <br/>
<br/>
Released in September, the Philips Hue Secure Contact Sensor can be applied to doors, windows, cabinets, and more, sending notifications when the contact sensor is opened or closed. Users can remotely activate an alarm that flashes the lights, sounds a siren, and contacts local authorities, plus there are options for customizing camera settings. <br/>
<br/>
As with Philips Hue Secure cameras, the sensors can be linked to lights to activate them when the sensor is triggered, so they can be used for things like turning on the lights in the bathroom when the door is opened.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us/p/hue-secure-contact-sensor/046677580995">Philips Hue Secure Contact Sensors</a> are priced at &#36;40 for one or &#36;70 for a two-pack, and various mounts and other add-on hardware can be purchased for &#36;15 to &#36;50. More information is available on the <a href="https://www.philips-hue.com/en-us/p/hue-secure-contact-sensor/046677580995">Hue website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/philips-hue/">Philips Hue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/philips-hue-secure-contact-sensors-support-homekit/">Philips Hue Secure Contact Sensors Gain HomeKit Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-secure-contact-sensors-gain-homekit-support.2411248/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Darker Apple Watch Ultra Prototype Shown in FCC Filing Images</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/darker-apple-watch-ultra-prototype-shown-in-fcc-filing-images.2411231/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 01:01:15 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to have originally designed an Apple Watch Ultra with a dark ceramic back, according to documents filed with the United States Federal Communications Commission and spotted by <a href="https://twitter.com/ParrotSWD/status/1725358035004965129">@ParrotSWD</a> on X, formerly Twitter (via <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-ultra-black-ceramic-back/">9to5Mac</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-ultra-prototype-fcc.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922908" /><br/>
When releasing a new device, tech hardware companies must share details with the FCC, which Apple did for the Apple Watch Ultra prior to its release in September 2022.<br/>
<br/>
In the document, Apple appears to have used an Apple Watch Ultra with a darker, almost black ceramic rear case – similar to Apple Watch Series models – and a plastic-looking Action button with no indent. These design attributes did not make it into the final release.<br/>
<br/>
Often in filings of this type, external photos and other sensitive details are subject to a confidentiality clause with an expiry date, so it is likely that the clause in this one recently expired, hence why the images have only just come to light.<br/>
<br/>
Apple currently offers the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, released in September 2023, in the same natural titanium color as the first-generation model. Prior to launch, some rumors <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/01/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-titanium-rumor/">suggested</a> Apple could release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/31/2023-apple-watch-ultra-new-dark-color/">new darker color option</a> that was originally tested for the previous model but ultimately canceled. It didn't happen.  <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/17/new-apple-watch-ultra-black-prototype-images/">Darker Apple Watch Ultra Prototype Shown in FCC Filing Images</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/darker-apple-watch-ultra-prototype-shown-in-fcc-filing-images.2411231/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Announces Plans to Enter Major New Product Category, Likely Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-announces-plans-to-enter-major-new-product-category-likely-headphones.2411202/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 14:59:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Sonos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos</a> today <a href="https://investors.sonos.com/news-and-events/investor-news/latest-news/2023/Sonos-Reports-Fourth-Quarter-and-Fiscal-2023-Results/default.aspx">announced plans</a> to expand into a new "multi-billion dollar" product category in 2024, which is widely believed to be headphones. Sonos CEO Patrick Spence declined to give specific details on the company's plans, but he said that the new product will "complement" current Sonos devices and will "delight customers and drive immediate revenue."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/airpods-max-spring-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-842859" /><br/>
Spence said that Sonos believes it will generate more than &#36;100 million from new products in 2024, and the new product will account for a "large portion" of this revenue in the second half of the year.<br/>
<br/>
There have been rumors for years now that Sonos intends to enter the headphone market with a pair of wireless headphones that could be similar in design to over-ear headphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. Sonos has never confirmed its work on headphones, but a leaked internal memo that was obtained by <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-16/sonos-plans-to-cut-jobs-as-it-prepares-push-into-headphones"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> earlier today confirmed that the company does indeed have a headphone division.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/home">Sonos develops</a> wireless speakers, soundbars, and other home theater devices, so headphones seem to be a logical next step for the company. As Sonos manufactures higher-end devices, the first headphones could perhaps be designed to compete with over-ear headphones from companies like Bose, Sony, Sennheiser, Shure, and Bowers &amp; Wilkins, but Sonos could also target the AirPods market.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2019-01-24/sonos-is-said-to-plan-headphones-in-move-outside-the-home">in 2019</a> said that Sonos was targeting a &#36;300 price point and was focusing on features like audio quality and multi-service interoperability, but it has been several years since new details emerged.<br/>
<br/>
Sonos speakers already compete with Apple's speakers, so a set of heaadphones that serve as an alternative to &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; and Beats would not be a surprise. At this point, little is known about Sonos' plans for the headphones, and there is no specific launch date that has been shared.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonos/">Sonos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/sonos-new-product-category/">Sonos Announces Plans to Enter Major New Product Category, Likely Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-announces-plans-to-enter-major-new-product-category-likely-headphones.2411202/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 Model at All-Time Low Prices for Black Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-model-at-all-time-low-prices-for-black-friday.2411189/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:53:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last week, Amazon introduced the first major discounts on the Apple Watch Series 9. Today, these deals have returned and offer some of the best Black Friday deals around with &#36;50 off nearly every Series 9 device, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a> for the 41mm GPS model, down from &#36;399.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-series-9-black-friday.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921790" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple launched the Series 9 models back in September, and early on the steepest discounts were about &#36;10-15. Amazon's Black Friday deals are blowing those early markdowns out of the water, and they include both GPS and cellular models. This time around, the 41mm GPS device is available in two Aluminum models, as well as in both S/M and M/L fits.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5R8BP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00. It's available in four Aluminum color options, both S/M and M/L fits, and this is another record low price on the smartwatch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXF9R4Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Cellular Apple Watch Series 9 deals are just as abundant on Amazon right now. You can get the 41mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.00</strong></a> and the 45mm Cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;479.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;50 discounts and all-time low prices. You'll find all five Aluminum options on sale at these prices, as well as multiple size options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FM3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T2TM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;479.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anyone shopping for Apple Watch deals should head to our dedicated guide for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-apple-watch-deals/">Best Early Black Friday Apple Watch Deals</a>. Right now, this also includes a record low price on the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE (2022), priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3GRK2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;279.00.<br/>
<br/>
If you're starting your holiday shopping this week, we've got you covered with even more guides for the best early Black Friday deals for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-homepod-deals/">HomePod</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">iPad</a>. We've also been keeping an eye on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/">best overall Apple deals</a> in the lead-up to November 24. All of these guides will be updated as the month continues, so be sure to bookmark and revisit to stay up-to-date on the best prices for the products you have an eye on.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, we're tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories, so it's another good resource for your online holiday shopping.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-watch-series-9-low-prices/">Amazon Has Nearly Every Apple Watch Series 9 Model at All-Time Low Prices for Black Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-has-nearly-every-apple-watch-series-9-model-at-all-time-low-prices-for-black-friday.2411189/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s In-House 5G Modem Work Faces Further Delays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-in-house-5g-modem-work-faces-further-delays.2411187/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 12:24:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to run into troubles in its attempt to develop a 5G modem to replace Qualcomm's 5G modems in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and other products, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-16/apple-project-to-replace-modems-made-by-qualcomm-falls-further-behind-to-2026">reports <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/5G-Modem-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886940" /><br/>
Apple in 2019 acquired the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">majority of Intel's smartphone business</a> and started in on a serious effort to develop its own modem hardware, but the project has suffered multiple setbacks. Apple is still "years away" from creating a chip that is able to perform as well as or better than chips from rival Qualcomm.<br/>
<br/>
The Cupertino company initially wanted to have an in-house modem chip ready to go by 2024, a goal that could not be met, and now Gurman says that Apple is also going to miss an extended spring 2025 launch timeline. As of now, the modem chip launch has been postponed until the end of 2025 or early 2026, and Apple is still planning to introduce the technology in a version of the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Development on a modem chip is said to be in the early stages, and it "may lag behind the competition by years." One version in development does not support faster mmWave technology, and Apple has also run into issues with the Intel code that it has been working with. Rewrites have been required, and adding new features has been causing existing features to break, plus Apple has to be careful not to infringe on Qualcomm patents while developing the chip.<br/>
<br/>
"Why we thought we could take a failed project from Intel and somehow succeed is a mystery," an Apple employee allegedly told Gurman. Apple's hardware technologies group is also said to be "stretched thin" across numerous projects, leading to difficulty resolving bugs. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's dissatisfaction with Qualcomm surfaced in 2017, which is when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">Apple sued Qualcomm</a> for unfairly collecting royalties for technologies it had nothing to do with. Apple was of the opinion that Qualcomm was charging too much for its modem chip technology.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 lineup, Apple was able to opt out of using Qualcomm chips, instead equipping iPhones with chips from Intel, but the relationship between Intel and Apple was short lived. After the launch of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, Apple wanted to continue to use Intel chips for its first 5G iPhones, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models, but Intel could not manufacture 5G chips that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/03/intel-delays-5g-iphone-2020/">were up to Apple's standards</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was instead forced to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">settle its legal dispute</a> with Qualcomm, and all litigation was dropped. The two companies signed a new contract, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/11/apple-extends-deal-with-qualcomm-as-modem-delayed/">extended in September 2023</a>. The latest deal with Qualcomm covers smartphone launches in 2024, 2025, and 2026, and will last through Apple's delayed modem chip development.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple's in-house modem chip has been delayed, the company is continuing development because it is eager to end its expensive deal with Qualcomm. Apple's first modem chip will be a standalone chip, but the company hopes to eventually develop a system-on-a-chip that will also cut out suppliers like Broadcom and give it more control over component development.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-in-house-5g-modem-delays/">Apple&#039;s In-House 5G Modem Work Faces Further Delays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-in-house-5g-modem-work-faces-further-delays.2411187/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Digital Car Key and Ultra Wideband Groups Team Up for Future Apple Car Keys Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/digital-car-key-and-ultra-wideband-groups-team-up-for-future-apple-car-keys-improvements.2411182/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 11:37:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The way vehicles take advantage of new connectivity standards could be improving in the near future, leading to updates on how smartphones like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> control cars.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/01/bmw-car-key-photo.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-778616" /><br/>
This month, the Car Connectivity Consortium (CCC) and the FiRa Consortium that oversees the development of the Ultra-wideband (UWB) standard, <a href="https://carconnectivity.org/car-connectivity-consortium-and-fira-consortium-partner-on-uwb-technology-used-in-the-ccc-digital-key/">announced a partnership</a> for the future development of UWB features used for the CCC Digital Key function.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is a member of both the CCC and FiRa. The CCC's Digital Key specification has been adopted by Apple for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/carkey/">Car Keys</a> feature that allows the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the Apple Watch to unlock compatible vehicles over NFC. Select BMW, Kia, Hyundai, Mercedes, and Genesis vehicles <a href="https://www.apple.com/ios/carplay/available-models/">work with Car Keys</a>, but Apple undoubtedly wants to expand adoption.<br/>
<br/>
The CCC and FiRa Consortiums will work together to "develop and maintain" the UWB technology specifications used for the Digital Key standard that serves as the basis for &zwnj;Car Keys&zwnj; on Apple devices. Apple engineer Jinjing Jiang will oversee the joint effort.<br/>
<br/>
The partnership is expected to encourage broader adoption of UWB technology use in vehicles. As of now, UWB is used for the Digital Key standard to relay how close a user is to their vehicle, allowing a smartphone or wearable to be used for vehicle access or to start the car when at the appropriate range.<br/>
<br/>
Apple uses UWB for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple Watch, and AirTag. UWB enables more precise location awareness and it powers features like Precision Finding for the AirTag.<br/>
<br/>
Along with Apple, CCC members include most vehicle manufacturers like Ford, BMW, GM, Honda, Volkswagen, Mercedes-Benz, and more, while FiRa members include Apple, Google, Qualcomm, Cisco, Samsung, NXP, and more.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/digital-car-key-ultra-wideband-improvements/">Digital Car Key and Ultra Wideband Groups Team Up for Future Apple Car Keys Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/digital-car-key-and-ultra-wideband-groups-team-up-for-future-apple-car-keys-improvements.2411182/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Adopt RCS Messaging Standard for Better Interoperability With Android Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard-for-better-interoperability-with-android-devices.2411170/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 10:08:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>RCS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After years of persuading from Google, Apple plans to adopt the Rich Communication Services (RCS) standard. An Apple spokesperson told <em><a href="https://www.techradar.com/phones/iphone/breaking-apple-will-support-rcs-in-2024">TechRadar</a></em> and <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/16/apple-rcs-coming-to-iphone/">9to5Mac</a></em> that support for RCS will be coming next year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Mz_44PZ-0Js" title="No More Green Bubbles? Apple Officially Announces RCS Support!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
<blockquote>Later next year, we will be adding support for RCS Universal Profile, the standard as currently published by the GSM Association. We believe the RCS Universal Profile will offer a better interoperability experience when compared to SMS or MMS. This will work alongside iMessage, which will continue to be the best and most secure messaging experience for Apple users.</blockquote><br/>
According to Apple, RCS will "work alongside iMessage" and will improve communication between <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android users. iMessage will continue to be the default for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; communication, with RCS serving as a replacement for the existing SMS and MMS standards. SMS and MMS will remain available as a fallback when necessary, though.<br/>
<br/>
Rich Communication Services is a communication protocol adopted by Google. Smartphone makers and carriers worldwide have adopted RCS, but Apple has been resisting its adoption. Google has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/google-ipager-ad-rcs-apple/">pushing Apple to accept RCS</a> through a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/02/google-again-pushes-apple-to-adopt-rcs/">long-running ad campaign</a> involving billboards, a website, social media pressure, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Google has had a "Get the Message" website <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/09/android-website-rcs-apple/">since August 2022</a>, with the site calling on Apple to "fix what's broken" in texts between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users. Earlier this year, even Samsung got into the PR campaign, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/09/samsung-pushes-apple-to-adopt-rcs/">publishing a bizarre ad</a> where "Romeo" with his green bubbles and "Juliet" with her blue bubbles were unable to be together because of Apple's hesitation to adopt RCS.<br/>
<br/>
"Green bubbles and blue bubbles want to be together," read Samsung's ad, which also included the #GetTheMessage hashtag Google used for its social media push.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to MMS and SMS, the standards that Apple uses for text messages, RCS supports higher resolution photos and videos, audio messages, and bigger file sizes. It also adds improved encryption for chats between &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Android users, cross-platform emoji reactions, and more reliability for group chats across different devices.<br/>
<br/>
With RCS, real-time typing indicators, read receipts, better photos and videos, and much improved group chats will be standard on iPhones and Android phones, putting an end to the frustration that some &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users experience when attempting to communicate with Android smartphone owners. Apple claims that while RCS improves security for cross-device messaging, it is not as secure as iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple, RCS will provide users with the option to share their location with others inside text threads over text messages, and like iMessage, RCS will work over Wi-Fi in addition to cellular.<br/>
<br/>
Back in September 2022, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that adopting RCS was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/08/tim-cook-on-ios-rcs-buy-your-mom-an-iphone/">not a priority for Apple</a>. "I don't hear our users asking that we put a lot of energy into that at this point," he said. It is not clear why Apple has changed its stance, but the company is facing regulatory scrutiny over the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, iMessage, and other proprietary technologies in multiple countries, so adopting RCS could be seen as a willingness to work with other companies to improve device interoperability.<br/>
<br/>
The European Union, for example, has been working on legislation that would have required Apple to make changes to iMessage to make it available on other platforms. With RCS, iMessage will no longer have as many benefits that are unavailable cross-platform.<br/>
<br/>
Going forward, Apple plans to work with Google and other Global System for Mobile Communications Association (GSMA) members on further improving RCS. RCS support will be introduced in a software update next year, and carriers will need to implement support for full functionality. In the United States, Verizon, T-Mobile, and AT&amp;T already support RCS.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">Apple to Adopt RCS Messaging Standard for Better Interoperability With Android Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard-for-better-interoperability-with-android-devices.2411170/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
