<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:11:19 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches Sale on Mac App Store Games</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-mac-app-store-game-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-sale-on-mac-app-store-games.2429709/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:09:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-mac-app-store-game-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Mac App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a> games are <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/story/id1750125921">on sale for the next week</a>, with discounts of up to 75 percent off available. Valheim, Death Stranding Director's Cut, and Inscryption are all half price, with several other titles also on sale at even lower prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/mac-app-store-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2359" height="1327" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956487" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>Valheim</strong> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Death Stranding Director's Cut</strong> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Inscryption</strong> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Lies of P</strong> - &#36;41.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Resident Evil Village</strong> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Return to Monkey Island</strong> - &#36;12.99, down from &#36;24.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Disney Dreamlight Valley</strong> - &#36;29.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>GRIS</strong> - &#36;2.99, down from &#36;9.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>SnowRunner</strong> - &#36;14.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Inside</strong> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Disco Elysium: The Final Cut</strong> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;39.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>LUNA The Shadow Dust</strong> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Transport Fever 2</strong> - &#36;17.99, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The discounted games can be purchased from the &zwnj;Mac App Store&zwnj; by following <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/story/id1750125921">this link for story about the sale</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Mac App Store&zwnj; sale will last from June 20 to June 27.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-mac-app-store-game-sale/">Apple Launches Sale on Mac App Store Games</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-sale-on-mac-app-store-games.2429709/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>1Password Launches Recovery Codes and Simplified Sign-In Process</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/1password-launches-recovery-codes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1password-launches-recovery-codes-and-simplified-sign-in-process.2429706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:40:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/1password-launches-recovery-codes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>1Password</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular password management app 1Password <a href="https://blog.1password.com/introducing-1password-recovery-codes/">today announced the launch</a> of two new features that are designed to make the app more user friendly. 1Password is improving the sign-in process on new devices and adding the ability to recover an account when a master password and secret key are lost.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Introducing Recovery Codes" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q8rZxntMlN0" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
With recovery codes, 1Password is providing a failsafe that will let customers back into their accounts in the event that a password is lost. 1Password already provides an Emergency Kit PDF that includes a Secret Key, and users are instructed to keep the Secret Key safe. The Secret Key allows for access to a 1Password account if the master password isn't available, but prior to now, if the Secret Key was also lost, there was no option for account recovery.<br/>
<br/>
1Password users can now log in and generate a recovery code, which can be used to regain access to an account. The company recommends that customers go through the recovery code process immediately, as a recovery code can't be generated after a user is locked out of their 1Password account.<br/>
<br/>
After a recovery code has been created, it can be used at any time to regain access to a 1Password account, though users will need access to the email address associated with their 1Password account.<br/>
<br/>
Generating a recovery code can be done by going to the Manage Accounts section, selecting Sign-in and Recovery, and choosing the "Set up recovery code option." 1Password recommends that recovery codes be stored in a safe and accessible place.<br/>
<br/>
1Password is also testing an updated sign-in experience in a beta capacity, with the new method aimed at making it easier to log in on a new device or through a web browser. When logging in somewhere new, users can now choose the Scan QR Code option from the top left account menu in 1Password and scan a QR code on the new device to log in.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Scan a QR Code to set up 1Password on a new device" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/obqEheFUyis" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
The new sign-in option is available in beta and nightly release channels on 1Password for desktop and TestFlight for iOS. Recovery codes are available to all 1Password users.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/1password/">1Password</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/1password-launches-recovery-codes/">1Password Launches Recovery Codes and Simplified Sign-In Process</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1password-launches-recovery-codes-and-simplified-sign-in-process.2429706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Warped Kart Racers and Cityscapes: Sim Builder Coming to Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-vision-pro-warped-kart-racers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warped-kart-racers-and-cityscapes-sim-builder-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2429702/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 15:15:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-vision-pro-warped-kart-racers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Two new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> games optimized for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-arcade-launches-two-hit-games-on-apple-vision-pro/">are set to launch</a> on the headset, with Warped Kart Racers available today and Cityscapes: Sim Builder coming out on July 3.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-arcade-vision-pro-warped-kart.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956482" /><br/>
Warped Kart Racers is a racing game that features characters from 20th Television animated shows like Family Guy, King of the Hill, American Dad, and Solar Opposites. Players can take control of one of 20 playable characters and race against friends across 16 maps that come from iconic show episodes. There's both a single player campaign and the option for multiplayer matches.<br/>
<br/>
Cityscapes: Sim Builder was the &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; Game of the Year and an Apple Design Award finalist. Players are able to become the mayor of an up and coming city, developing careful, thought out systems to meet the needs of the city's citizens.<br/>
<br/>
Power, clean water, garbage collection, pollution, and road traffic all need to be dealt with, and establishing a thriving city raises the power level and unlocks more city options. The game has a City Pass, which is a monthly event that includes exclusive parks, buildings, and landmarks.<br/>
<br/>
Both Cityscapes: Sim Builder and Warped Kart Racers are available on existing Apple devices through &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj;, but the update will also allow them to be played using the Vision Pro's hand gestures and eye controls. In Warped Kart Racers, players use their hands to steer, drift, and throw objects, and in Cityscapes: Sim Builder, hand movements are used to lay roads and build neighborhoods.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and third-party developers have made several &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games available on the Vision Pro, including Game Room, What the Golf, Super Fruit Ninja, and Crossy Road Stories. Apple is releasing content updates for two Vision Pro games today, including Gibbon: Beyond the Trees and Bloons TD 6+.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; is priced at &#36;6.99 per month and provides access to up to six family members. &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games do not include in-app purchases or other freemium features.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-vision-pro-warped-kart-racers/">Warped Kart Racers and Cityscapes: Sim Builder Coming to Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/warped-kart-racers-and-cityscapes-sim-builder-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2429702/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Satechi Launches Qi2 Wireless Car Charger</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/satechi-qi2-wireless-car-charger/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-qi2-wireless-car-charger.2429698/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:16:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/satechi-qi2-wireless-car-charger/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Satechi today announced the launch of its latest Qi2 product, a car charger that is able to mount to a vehicle's vents. The Qi2 Wireless Car Charger is able to charge a compatible <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W, which is the same speed as an official <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charger.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/satechi-qi2-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956497" /><br/>
Like many of Satechi's products, the Qi2 Wireless Car Charger is made from an aluminum material that is designed to match Apple's devices It comes in a space gray color, with a soft black silicone charging pad available for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. It clips on to a vent with a stabilizing clamp, and includes a 25W car charger and 3.3-foot USB-C cable. The mount is able to swivel, and it can be used in landscape or portrait mode.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 charging speeds are available on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 and later, with Apple adding support for the faster charging through software updates. All of Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; iPhones are now able to charge at the faster Qi2 speeds. As with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will need to be caseless or equipped with a magnetic case.<br/>
<br/>
The Qi2 Wireless Car Charger can be <a href="https://satechi.net/products/qi2-wireless-car-charger">purchased from the Satechi website</a> for &#36;60.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/satechi-qi2-wireless-car-charger/">Satechi Launches Qi2 Wireless Car Charger</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-qi2-wireless-car-charger.2429698/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Apps Can Integrate With Translate App on iOS 17.4 and Later</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-translation-framework/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-apps-can-integrate-with-translate-app-on-ios-17-4-and-later.2429688/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:15:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-translation-framework/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Translate</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10117/">WWDC 2024 coding video</a> last week, Apple highlighted a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/Translation">recently-introduced API</a> that allows developers to offer built-in Translate app capabilities in their own apps on iOS 17.4, iPadOS 17.4, macOS Sonoma, and later.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-17-4-Translate-App-API.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956475" /><br/>
While the iPhone, iPad, and Mac already offer a system-level translation function for highlighted text, websites viewed in Safari, and more, the API provides a convenient solution for user-generated content like reviews. For example, if a user writes a review in Japanese, the text can be quickly translated to other languages.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia enhance the API by allowing translated text to appear in-line within an app, instead of in an overlaid Translate sheet.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Translate-App-API.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956474" /><br/>
Another language-related change on iOS 18 is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10185/">bilingual keyboard support</a>. For example, you can type in English and Korean on the same keyboard without having to manually switch languages, complete with word suggestions in each language.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Multilingual-Keyboard.jpeg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956476" /><br/>
iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia are currently in beta for developers. The software updates will be released later this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-translate/">Apple Translate</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-translation-framework/">iPhone Apps Can Integrate With Translate App on iOS 17.4 and Later</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-apps-can-integrate-with-translate-app-on-ios-17-4-and-later.2429688/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2429685/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:35:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first beta of an upcoming macOS 14.6 update to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its launch. Today's public beta comes a few days after Apple released the initial developer beta. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.5 update to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its launch. The public beta comes a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5/">released the second public beta</a> and a day after Apple seeded the beta to developers. <br/>
<br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
No new Mac features were found in the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.6 developer beta, so it is not clear what might be included. With Apple now working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, development on &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; is beginning to wrap up.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/">Apple Releases First macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2429685/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First Public Beta of iOS 17.6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2429684/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:18:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the first betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to public beta testers, with the betas coming a few days after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-6-beta-1-to-developers/">initial iOS and iPadOS 17.6 developer betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
The new additions Apple promised for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented at this point, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no features were discovered in the developer beta.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple now shifting its focus to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also seeded the first public betas of upcoming watchOS 10.6 and tvOS 17.6 updates. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6/">Apple Releases First Public Beta of iOS 17.6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2429684/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Final Cut Pro Gets Major Update With New Camera App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/final-cut-pro-major-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-gets-major-update-with-new-camera-app.2429683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:16:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/final-cut-pro-major-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/new-versions-of-final-cut-pro-for-ipad-and-mac-available-today/">today released</a> Final Cut Pro 2 for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Final Cut Pro 10.8 for the Mac, two Final Cut Pro updates that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/final-cut-pro-ipad-2/">first announced back in May</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949711" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/final-cut-pro-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; has been updated with new capabilities that are designed for the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models that came out earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
Live Multicam lets users capture up to four different angles of a single scene using connected iPhones and iPads. To make this feature work, Apple has created a Final Cut Camera app that captures video from each of the devices and feeds it into Final Cut Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Users can get a director's view of each connected camera in real time, and the settings can be adjusted from the Final Cut Pro app. There are options for tweaking exposure, focus, white balance, ISO, shutter speed, and zoom to get the perfect shots. Preview clips are passed through to Final Cut Pro and then replaced with full-resolution files so users can quickly move from production to editing.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Camera is available as a standalone app as of today and in addition to feeding footage to Final Cut Pro, it can be used as a video capture app for recording video with precise manual controls.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949712" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/final-cut-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" /><br/>
The updated Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app supports external projects, so users can create or open projects on an external device and import media without taking up &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; storage space. Apple added additional customization options to Final Cut Pro, including 12 color-grading presets, eight basic text titles, 20 soundtracks, and new dynamic backgrounds.<br/>
<br/>
With the M4 chip, final rendering with Final Cut Pro is up to 2x faster, and it supports up to 4x more streams of ProRes RAW than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip. Final Cut for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; works with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro, adding support for barrel roll and squeeze, improving access to and control over tools.<br/>
<br/>
As for Final Cut Pro for the Mac, it includes Enhance Light and Color, an AI feature that improves color, color balance, contrast, and brightness in one step. Smooth Slo-Mo, another new feature, blends frames of video intelligently to provide higher-quality movement.<br/>
<br/>
Final Cut Pro for &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; 2 is available as a free update for existing users, with new users able to purchase it for &#36;4.99 per month or &#36;49 per year. Final Cut Pro for Mac 10.8 is also available as a free update for existing users, with new users able to purchase the software for &#36;299.99. Apple has also released new versions of Compressor and Motion.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/final-cut-pro-major-update/">Final Cut Pro Gets Major Update With New Camera App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/final-cut-pro-gets-major-update-with-new-camera-app.2429683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Introduces Low Prices on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack Card, and Anker Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/amazon-airtag-eufy-anker/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-low-prices-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-card-and-anker-accessories.2429677/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:45:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/amazon-airtag-eufy-anker/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a collection of Bluetooth tracker discounts on Amazon, which include low prices on Apple's AirTag and Eufy's SmartTrack Card accessory. There are also a few Anker discounts on Amazon this week, including portable batteries and charging stations.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirTag</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/airtag-purple-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-916645" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirTag 4 Pack available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;99.00. This is a solid second-best price on the accessory, and just about &#36;5 higher than the all-time low price. As of writing, the AirTag 4 Pack can be delivered as soon as June 22 for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0932QJ2JZ"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/eufy-smarttrack-card.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956422" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want to save more money, Eufy's SmartTrack Card Bluetooth tracker is on sale right now on Amazon. This accessory is designed to fit in your wallet and is priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1718290256476"><strong>&#36;19.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;29.99. The SmartTrack Card is compatible with Apple's Find My app, allowing you to track the device within the app and receive left behind alerts and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1718290256476"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>SmartTrack Card for &#36;19.99</div></a></div><h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/anker-battery-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956426" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to Anker's charging accessories, you can get multiple MagSafe-compatible devices at a discount this week on Amazon, like a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1718896305471">portable battery</a> and a <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1718896354198">wireless charging station</a>. The highlight of the sale is Anker's 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK_1718896414506"><strong>&#36;88.95</strong></a>, down from &#36;149.99. Many of these will require you to clip an on-page coupon before you head to the checkout screen in order to see the sales.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1718896223267">10,000 mAh Power Bank With Built-in USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;35.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;44.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1718896305471">MagGo 10,000 mAh Power Bank with Foldable Stand</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1718896354198">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09VPHVT2Z%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3Y9TDY9TTSHK_1718896414506">24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;88.95, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1718896212698">MagGo 3-in-1 Foldable Charging Stand</a> - &#36;93.49, down from &#36;109.99</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/amazon-airtag-eufy-anker/">Amazon Introduces Low Prices on AirTag, Eufy SmartTrack Card, and Anker Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-introduces-low-prices-on-airtag-eufy-smarttrack-card-and-anker-accessories.2429677/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS 18 Allows Apps to Offer Custom Drawing Tools for Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/ipados-18-custom-apple-pencil-drawing-tools/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-allows-apps-to-offer-custom-drawing-tools-for-apple-pencil.2429675/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:27:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/ipados-18-custom-apple-pencil-drawing-tools/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with iPadOS 18, which will be widely released later this year, iPad apps can offer custom drawing tools for the Apple Pencil.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPadOS-18-Custom-Drawing-Tool-Apple-Pencil.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956430" /><br/>
For example, in a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10214/">WWDC 2024 coding video</a> last week, Apple demonstrated how an app could implement a tool that allows for cat paw prints and other animal-related symbols to be added to a drawing. The custom tools support features on the new Apple Pencil Pro, including the squeeze gesture and barrel roll action.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 and visionOS 2 also support custom drawing tools in apps, but the iPhone and Vision Pro do not support the Apple Pencil. As always, any drawing tool can also be controlled with your finger and other input methods.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPadOS-18-Custom-Drawing-Tool-Apple-Pencil-2.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956431" /><br/>
In addition to custom tools, apps across iPadOS 18, iOS 18, and visionOS 2 are able to change the selection of default drawing tools that appear in the system tool picker. Apple said apps are even able to offer multiple tools of the same type for added convenience, such as two colors of pens or two colors of markers.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18, iOS 18, and visionOS 2 are currently in beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/ipados-18-custom-apple-pencil-drawing-tools/">iPadOS 18 Allows Apps to Offer Custom Drawing Tools for Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-18-allows-apps-to-offer-custom-drawing-tools-for-apple-pencil.2429675/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Beats Solo Buds Available at Select Apple Stores Starting Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/beats-solo-buds-available-at-apple-stores-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-solo-buds-available-at-select-apple-stores-starting-today.2429671/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 06:21:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/beats-solo-buds-available-at-apple-stores-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		<category>Beats Solo Buds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new Beats Solo Buds wireless earbuds are available to purchase at select Apple retail stores and authorized resellers around the world starting today. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/beats-solo-buds-video-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955953" /><br/>
Beats Solo Buds feature a more affordable &#36;79.99 price in the U.S., up to 18 hours of battery life, and a compact USB-C carrying case. However, they lack active noise cancellation, and the carrying case does not have a built-in battery. As a result, the earbuds can only be charged when the case is connected to an external power source.<br/>
<br/>
Beats Solo Buds pre-orders <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/18/beats-solo-buds-orders/">began on Tuesday</a>, ahead of today's launch. The earbuds can be <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUW03LL/A/beats-solo-buds-true-wireless-earbuds-transparent-red">purchased on Apple's online store</a> for delivery, or in-store pickup where available. More details can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">our coverage from a few months ago</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-4-launch/">Beats Solo 4 on-ear headphones</a> also launched this year, and a new version of the discontinued Beats Pill wireless speaker is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/apple-teases-june-25-beats-pill-unveiling/">expected to be announced next week</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats-solo-buds/">Beats Solo Buds</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/beats-solo-buds-available-at-apple-stores-today/">Beats Solo Buds Available at Select Apple Stores Starting Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/beats-solo-buds-available-at-select-apple-stores-starting-today.2429671/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Unveils Stunning Kuala Lumpur Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-unveils-stunning-kuala-lumpur-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-stunning-kuala-lumpur-store.2429668/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 05:17:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-unveils-stunning-kuala-lumpur-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Retail</category>
		<category>Malaysia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/06/apple-the-exchange-trx-opens-saturday-june-22-in-kuala-lumpur/">previewed</a> its first store in Malaysia, Apple The Exchange TRX, located in Kuala Lumpur's Tun Razak Exchange business district.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-trx-exterior.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956347" /><br/>
The architectural design of Apple The Exchange TRX features a three-dimensional layered roof with horizontal glass panels and sun-shading blades. A central glazed oculus brings natural daylight into the interior and contains a dynamic artificial-lighting system that adjusts based on the time of day. The building connects the mall's central atrium to a rooftop park that wraps around the store's upper level.<br/>
<br/>
Inside, a sculptural quartz and glass staircase connects the three levels. The main floor is a floating deck that sits above the primary display area. The Forum, where Today at Apple sessions take place, is located on this floating deck, providing a central location for workshops and events. The upper level, which connects directly to the rooftop park, brings natural light and greenery into the store through a continuous glass facade. The interior features high-quality materials such as natural stone walls, polished stainless-steel columns, light terrazzo floors, and a timber ceiling.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-trx-interior.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956348" /><br/>
Apple The Exchange TRX runs on 100% renewable energy and is carbon neutral, in line with Apple's broader environmental goals. The store contains a Genius Bar, a dedicated Apple Pickup counter, and more than 160 retail employees to help customers.<br/>
<br/>
To celebrate the store's opening, Apple will run a special series of Today at Apple sessions called "Jom Discover," running from June 22 through July 6. These sessions will feature some of Malaysia's most celebrated creators, offering insights into their creative processes and showcasing Apple's products and services. Highlights include a performance by De Fam, workshops on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> photography with Jason smashpop, video editing on Mac with Adam Lobo, productivity on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with Iman Azman, and health and wellness sessions with Nana Mohd focusing on the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple The Exchange TRX opens on Saturday, June 22, at 10 a.m. MYT.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/retail/">Retail</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/malaysia/">Malaysia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-unveils-stunning-kuala-lumpur-store/">Apple Unveils Stunning Kuala Lumpur Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-unveils-stunning-kuala-lumpur-store.2429668/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 Back to School Sale Launches, Up to &#36;150 Gift Card With Mac or iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-back-to-schoo-promotion-launches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-back-to-school-sale-launches-up-to-150-gift-card-with-mac-or-ipad.2429667/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 04:29:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-back-to-schoo-promotion-launches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Education</category>
		<category>Back to School Promotion</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has launched its <a href="https://www.apple.com/us-edu/store">annual Back to School promotion</a> for college students in the United States. This year's promotion offers a free Apple gift card with the purchase of an eligible Mac or iPad. Apple is also offering students 20% off AppleCare+ plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/2022-back-to-school-apple-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2178" height="1224" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851334" /><br/>
Apple is offering a &#36;150 gift card with any new MacBook Air, MacBook Pro, or iMac, and a &#36;100 gift card with the purchase of any new M4 iPad Pro, M2 iPad Air, or Mac mini. The gift card can be used towards purchases of Apple products and accessories, App Store apps, subscriptions to services like Apple Music, iCloud+ storage, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The offer is available through Apple's online education store and at Apple Store locations for students attending or accepted to a higher-education institution, faculty and staff of higher-education institutions, parents purchasing on behalf of an eligible student, employees of a K-12 institution, and select others.<br/>
<br/>
Here are the promotions:<ul><br/>
  <li>iMac (&#36;150 gift card)</li><br/>
  <li>MacBook Air (&#36;150 gift card)</li><br/>
  <li>MacBook Pro (&#36;150 gift card)</li><br/>
  <li>Mac mini (&#36;100 gift card)</li><br/>
  <li>iPad Pro 11-inch / 13-inch, M4 chip (&#36;100 gift card)</li><br/>
  <li>iPad Air 11-inch / 13-inch, M2 chip (&#36;100 gift card)</li><br/>
</ul>The promotion runs through September 30 in the U.S., according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/back-to-school/terms-conditions">Apple's terms and conditions</a>. The free gift card is in addition to Apple's standard educational discounts of around 5% to 10% off most Macs and iPads. The promotion has also gone live in Canada, India, and possibly other countries, and will likely come to Europe and other regions in the coming weeks.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/education/">Education</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/back-to-school-promotion/">Back to School Promotion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-back-to-schoo-promotion-launches/">Apple&#039;s 2024 Back to School Sale Launches, Up to &#36;150 Gift Card With Mac or iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-back-to-school-sale-launches-up-to-150-gift-card-with-mac-or-ipad.2429667/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sequoia Adds iCloud Support for macOS 15 Virtual Machines</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/macos-sequoia-adds-icloud-support-vms/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-adds-icloud-support-for-macos-15-virtual-machines.2429664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 03:39:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/macos-sequoia-adds-icloud-support-vms/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is introducing a notable enhancement to its virtualization framework in macOS Sequoia by enabling Mac users to sign into iCloud within macOS virtual machines (VMs).  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-macOS-Sequoia-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954631" /><br/>
Previously, users could not sign into iCloud on macOS VMs, which limited the framework's utility for developers needing to test iCloud features and for users looking to sync their apps with iCloud. As spotted by <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2024/06/apple-quietly-improves-mac-virtualization-in-macos-15-sequoia/">ArsTechnica</a></em>, macOS Sequoia removes that barrier, provided that both the host and guest operating systems are macOS 15 or newer.<br/>
<br/>
The feature will be available on Apple silicon Macs, but it has some limitations. Developers aiming to run older macOS versions alongside macOS 15 in a VM or those who upgrade VMs from older macOS versions will not be able to sign into iCloud on the VM. Only brand-new VMs created from a macOS 15 install image (an .ipsw file) can utilize iCloud and services related to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/11/apple-id-renamed-to-apple-account/">Apple Account</a> (formerly Apple ID).<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://developer.apple.com/documentation/virtualization/using_icloud_with_macos_virtual_machines">virtualization framework documentation explains</a>: <br/>
<blockquote>"When you create a VM in macOS 15 from a macOS 15 software image Virtualization configures an identity for the VM that it derives from security information in the host's Secure Enclave. Just as individual physical devices have distinct identities based on their Secure Enclaves, this identity is distinct from other VMs."</blockquote>Apple says that if someone moves a VM to a different Mac host and restarts it, the Virtualization framework automatically creates a new identity for the VM using the information from the Secure Enclave of the new Mac host. This identity change requires the person using the VM to re-authenticate to allow iCloud to restart syncing data to the VM.<br/>
<br/>
Both Parallels and VMware offer virtualization software, and Broadcom recently made VMware Fusion <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/vmware-fusion-pro-13-free-personal-use/">free for personal use</a>. macOS Sequoia is currently in developer beta, with a public beta set to arrive in July, followed by a general release in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/macos-sequoia-adds-icloud-support-vms/">macOS Sequoia Adds iCloud Support for macOS 15 Virtual Machines</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sequoia-adds-icloud-support-for-macos-15-virtual-machines.2429664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: How to Lock and Hide iPhone Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-how-to-lock-and-hide-iphone-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-how-to-lock-and-hide-iphone-apps.2429659/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 01:41:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-how-to-lock-and-hide-iphone-apps&#038;post_date=1718883660/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 17, Apple doesn't offer a system-level method for individually locking sensitive apps like Photos behind Face ID. There is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/automatically-lock-iphone-app-opened/">Shortcut action</a> that provides rudimentary protection, but it's not infallible. Thankfully, iOS 18 includes a dedicated option to lock and even hide individual apps even when the iPhone itself is already unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-on-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955605" /><br/>
This is useful because it means you can unlock your iPhone and hand it to someone for them to look at something, knowing they won't be able to open the apps you have locked. If someone using your iPhone tries to open an app that you have manually locked using the method described below, they will see a popup informing them that it can't be accessed without secondary authentication via Face ID (or Touch ID on the iPhone SE). <br/>
<br/>
Notably, if <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-stolen-device-protection/">Stolen Device Protection</a> is active, entering a passcode to unlock an app is not an option, so even if your iPhone is stolen and the thief knows your passcode, they still won't be able to open the app. However, if Stolen Device Protection is not enabled, a passcode prompt appears that can be used to unlock the app after three failed Face ID attempts.<br/>
<br/>
It's worth noting that not all apps can be locked. As things stand in the first iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 betas, Apple does not provide the lock option for non-sensitive apps like Maps, Clock, Calculator, and Stocks. Otherwise, almost every other app can be locked, including third-party apps. Here's how it's done.<br/>
<ol><li>On your Home Screen, press and hold on the icon for the app that you want to lock.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Require Face ID</strong> (or Touch ID).</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Require Face ID</strong> (or Touch ID) to confirm.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/lock-app-ios-18.jpg" alt="safari" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956294" /><br/>
<br/>
Note that you can't use Siri with a locked app, and Spotlight search and any notification previews will not show content from the app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Lock and Hide Apps</h2><br/>
When you lock a third-party app using the above method, you have the option to hide it as well  but at present you cannot hide system apps like Safari or Photos. When enabled, the app icon and name is removed from the Home Screen, and it will not show up in searches, although it may still appear in the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/hide-app-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="2898" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956295" /><br/>
An obscured folder for hidden apps is also created in your App Library, which is accessed by swiping left to the end of your Home Screen pages. However, you will not get app notifications or incoming calls from a hidden third-party app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>How to Unlock and Unhide Apps</h2><br/>
To unlock an app that you previously locked, simply long press on the app's icon and choose the "Don't Require Face ID" option. As long as you have Stolen Device Protection enabled, turning the lock on and off requires a Face ID scan, so it can't be turned off without your knowledge. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/hidden-folder-app-library.jpg" alt="App Library" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956326" /><br/>
To unhide a locked third-party app, swipe through to the App Library and tap the obscured Hidden folder at the bottom. You will be required to perform a Face ID scan to reveal its contents. After that, you can access any hidden apps contained within it. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-how-to-lock-and-hide-iphone-apps/">iOS 18: How to Lock and Hide iPhone Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-how-to-lock-and-hide-iphone-apps.2429659/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Education Store Down in US and Canada, Back to School Offer Expected Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-education-store-down-us-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-education-store-down-in-us-and-canada-back-to-school-offer-expected-soon.2429653/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:48:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-education-store-down-us-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Education</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/us-edu/store">online education store</a> has gone down in the United States and Canada, as Apple prepares to launch its annual Back to School promotion for university students.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-store-down.jpg" alt="" width="1142" height="654" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-852939" /><br/>
Apple's back to school sales provide students with a free Apple gift card when purchasing a Mac or an iPad, and this year's promotion could help Apple push the new M2 iPad Air and M4 iPad Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
Last year, Apple offered U.S. students up to &#36;150 when purchasing a Mac and up to &#36;100 when purchasing an iPad. <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1803484272873099699">According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, Apple will this year again offer up to a &#36;150 gift card with every Mac purchase, and it will additionally shave 20% off the price of AppleCare+. Gift cards will also again be offered with iPad purchases, but Gurman did not state an exact value.<br/>
<br/>
Apple began advertising its Back to School sale on social networks in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/back-to-school-2024-launching-this-week/">early June</a>, with some Instagram users seeing an ad promoting Macs with discounts to college and university students.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/education/">Education</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/20/apple-education-store-down-us-canada/">Apple Education Store Down in US and Canada, Back to School Offer Expected Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-education-store-down-in-us-and-canada-back-to-school-offer-expected-soon.2429653/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;119 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-119/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-119-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2429601/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 08:48:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-119/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Pencil Pro has dropped to a new record low price today on Amazon, and we're also tracking a collection of discounts on the M4 iPad Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-pencil-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956283" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Amazon today has the Apple Pencil Pro for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a>, down from the regular price of &#36;129.00. Although this is only a &#36;10 discount, it's now the lowest price we've tracked on the brand new Apple Pencil Pro among the major online retailers. The Apple Pencil 2 is also at an all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Pencil Pro launched last month alongside the new 2024 iPad lineup, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/09/apple-pencil-pro-features/">new gestures and capabilities</a> into the stylus. The Apple Pencil Pro is compatible with the M4 iPad Pro and the M2 iPad Air, and marks the first update to the Apple Pencil since the Apple Pencil 2 in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m4-ipad-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956285" /><br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
Moving to the iPads, Amazon has all-time low prices on a few models of the 11-inch M4 iPad Pro. Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;944.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and also include one cellular tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;944.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,124.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9KW87%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Cellular</a> - &#36;1,139.00, down from &#36;1,199.00</li></ul><h3>13-inch</h3><br/>
Similar to the 11-inch models, there are three versions of the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro on sale today at Amazon. Prices for these start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,219.00</strong></a> for the 256GB Wi-Fi tablet, but there aren't any cellular models on sale this time around.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,219.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J776JL%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,144.00, down from &#36;2,299.00</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-119/">Apple Pencil Pro Drops to &#36;119 on Amazon Alongside Record Low Prices for M4 iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pencil-pro-drops-to-119-on-amazon-alongside-record-low-prices-for-m4-ipad-pro.2429601/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>watchOS 11 Gets &#039;Check In&#039; Feature That Supports Outdoor Workouts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/watchos-11-supports-workout-check-in/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-gets-check-in-feature-that-supports-outdoor-workouts.2429597/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:47:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/watchos-11-supports-workout-check-in/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in iOS 17 added a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-check-in-feature-ios-messages/">Check In feature to Messages</a> that allows you to let a loved one know when you've made it back home safely. With watchOS 11, Check In is also coming to Apple Watch, but it's not just in the Messages app that you can activate it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/check-in-workout-watchos-11.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956266" /><br/>
Anyone who has used a Garmin watch will probably be familiar with its LiveTrack feature, which creates a real-time view of your location during an activity, so friends and family can keep tabs on your progress. Strava Beacon offers similar functionality, and now with Check In integration, Apple Watch users can let loved ones know they have successfully completed their workout, too.<br/>
<br/>
Like on iPhone, Apple Watch users can start a Check In from Messages in watchOS 11. But the feature also works within the Workout app. When you start a workout, a swipe right reveals a new Check In option. So if you're walking home after dark or heading out for an early morning run, you can notify someone that you've started out, and Check In will let them know when you return home.<br/>
<br/>
If something unexpected happens and you get delayed, Check In will automatically notify your friend that you havent arrived as expected, and tell them your location (if available), the route you took, and your iPhone's battery level and cellular service in case they want to contact you.<br/>
<br/>
There's also a new option in Settings  Workout that lets you turn on Check In Reminders, so Apple Watch can remind you to send a Workout Check In whenever you start an outdoor workout.<br/>
<br/>
Note that watchOS 11 is in developer beta, and some features could always change or be removed before Apple releases the new Apple Watch software to the public in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/watchos-11-supports-workout-check-in/">watchOS 11 Gets &#039;Check In&#039; Feature That Supports Outdoor Workouts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/watchos-11-gets-check-in-feature-that-supports-outdoor-workouts.2429597/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Allows Third-Party Apps to Offer Spatial Video Recording on iPhone 15 Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/ios-18-spatial-video-recording-third-party-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-allows-third-party-apps-to-offer-spatial-video-recording-on-iphone-15-pro.2429596/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 06:40:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/ios-18-spatial-video-recording-third-party-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max models running iOS 17.2 or later <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/record-spatial-video-iphone/">can record spatial video</a> with 3D depth for playback on Apple's Vision Pro headset. While spatial video recording has been limited to Apple's built-in Camera app until this point, third-party camera apps on the App Store can also offer this functionality starting on iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-iphone-15-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911686" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2024/10166/">WWDC 2024 coding session</a> last week, Apple revealed that it has released an API that allows developers to offer spatial video recording in any app. Apple said the API is built into existing camera-related frameworks, making it easy to implement.<br/>
<br/>
When held in landscape orientation, the iPhone 15 Pro's main and ultra wide cameras combine to record spatial video. In addition to the iPhone 16 Pro models, it is likely that spatial video recording will be expanded to the regular iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus, as the rear cameras on those devices are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">rumored to be vertically aligned</a>.<br/>
<br/>
You will need a Vision Pro to see the added depth in spatial videos, as they appear in a normal 2D format when played on an iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 is currently in beta, and it should be released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/ios-18-spatial-video-recording-third-party-apps/">iOS 18 Allows Third-Party Apps to Offer Spatial Video Recording on iPhone 15 Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-allows-third-party-apps-to-offer-spatial-video-recording-on-iphone-15-pro.2429596/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Explains iPhone 15 Pro Requirement for Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-iphone-15-pro-requirement-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-iphone-15-pro-requirement-for-apple-intelligence.2429589/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 04:48:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-iphone-15-pro-requirement-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Daring Fireball</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia, Apple is introducing a new personalized AI experience called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/10/apple-intelligence-generative-personal-ai-unveiled-for-iphone-ipad-and-mac/">Apple Intelligence</a> that uses on-device, generative large-language models to enhance the user experience across iPhone, iPad, and Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-WWDC24-Apple-Intelligence-hero-240610.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954530" /><br/>
These new AI features require Apple's latest iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max models to work, while only Macs and iPads with M1 or later chips will support Apple Intelligence. Since the news came to light, many users have been asking what the reason is for the cut-off.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/14/the-talk-show-live-from-wwdc-2024/">The Talk Show Live From WWDC 2024</a>, <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber put the question to Apple's AI/machine learning head John Giannandrea, marketing chief Greg Joswiak, and software engineering chief Craig Federighi, and this was the response.<br/>
<blockquote>Giannandrea: "So these models, when you run them at run times, it's called inference, and the inference of large language models is incredibly computationally expensive. And so it's a combination of bandwidth in the device, it's the size of the Apple Neural Engine, it's the oomph in the device to actually do these models fast enough to be useful. You could, in theory, run these models on a very old device, but it would be so slow that it would not be useful.<br/>
<br/>
Gruber: "So it's not a scheme to sell new iPhones?"<br/>
<br/>
Joswiak: "No, not at all. Otherwise, we would have been smart enough just to do our most recent iPads and Macs, too, wouldn't we?"</blockquote>Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi said that the company's first move with any new feature is to work out how to bring it back to older devices as far as possible. But when it comes to Apple Intelligence, "This is the hardware that it takes... It's a pretty extraordinary thing to run models of this power on an iPhone," he added.<br/>
<br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro models use the A17 Pro chip, which has a 16-core Neural Engine that's up to 2x faster than the A16 chip found in the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus, performing nearly 35 trillion operations per second. Federighi hinted that RAM is also another aspect of the system that the new AI features require, so it is perhaps no coincidence that all the devices compatible with Apple Intelligence have at least 8GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the cutoff, owners of older iPhones still have plenty to look forward to in Apple's upcoming software update: iOS 18 boasts several new features besides Apple Intelligence, and every iPhone that can run iOS 17 is compatible iOS 18. That includes the iPhone XR from 2018.<br/>
<br/>
If you still want Apple Intelligence in your pocket but don't have an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, you may want to hold out for the iPhone 16 series, which is expected to launch when iOS 18 is released in the fall. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/daringfireball-net/">Daring Fireball</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Caution)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-iphone-15-pro-requirement-apple-intelligence/">Apple Explains iPhone 15 Pro Requirement for Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-explains-iphone-15-pro-requirement-for-apple-intelligence.2429589/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
