<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:03:06 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Oppo Find X7 Ultra</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-find-x7-ultra.2424689/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:46:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Oppo Find X7 Ultra's camera has <a href="https://www.dxomark.com/smartphones/#sort-camera/segments-%5B%22ultra%22%5D/device-Oppo%20Find%20X7%20Ultra">one of the highest rankings</a> on camera site DXOMark, coming in well ahead of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max. For that reason, we thought we'd compare the Oppo Find X7 Ultra to Apple's flagship <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to see how the cameras actually measure up in real life.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="#1 Ranked Camera vs iPhone 15 Pro Max" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vKSvQj8AkLY" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Oppo Find X7 Ultra has a 50-megapixel main lens, a 50-megapixel wide-angle lens, and two 50-megapixel telephoto lenses, one of which is a 3x periscope lens. The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max has a 48-megapixel Main lens with multiple focal lengths, a 12-megapixel Ultra Wide lens, and a 12-megapixel telephoto lens that supports 5x optical zoom. In terms of hardware, the main cameras are similar, but the Oppo has higher resolution options for the telephoto and wide-angle lenses.<br/>
<br/>
We shared a series of photos from each smartphone on our social media channels, without mentioning which one was the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. When we asked which images people liked better, our poll favored the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, but overall, most people liked some images from the Oppo and some images from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. No surprises there, as with high-end smartphones, differences in camera quality can be miniscule. Choosing a favorite often comes down to processing done by each smartphone, and picking an image based on the look comes down to personal preference.<br/>
<br/>
For standard main camera photos taken during the daytime, the images come out almost the same. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can sometimes seem a little more washed out because it loses some of the saturation when raising highlights, while the Oppo tends to be more saturated. &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; images can be brighter, which is preferable to some people, but the Oppo features more vibrant colors in a lot of shots. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sometimes boosts the warmth, and again, that's something that some people prefer.<br/>
<br/>
For night shots, the Oppo images came out better for the most part. The nighttime colors were more true to life, and there were fewer issues with reflections and flare. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; raised the brightness of some areas of nighttime shots just a little too much, though a couple of the low light images came out better because of some of the low light processing features Apple has built into the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
For telephoto images and Portrait images, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; had the edge in terms of focus and color, though the photos were sometimes softer than the Oppo's shots.<br/>
<br/>
Which images do you prefer? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-x7-ultra/">Camera Comparison: iPhone 15 Pro Max vs. Oppo Find X7 Ultra</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/camera-comparison-iphone-15-pro-max-vs-oppo-find-x7-ultra.2424689/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Working to Secure Streaming Rights to FIFA Club World Cup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-secure-streaming-rights-to-fifa-club-world-cup.2424683/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 09:58:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>FIFA</category>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working to secure an exclusive TV deal with soccer governing organization FIFA, reports <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/04/22/business/fifa-apple-tv-deal.html">The New York Times</a></em>. FIFA will launch a revamped version of Club World Cup in 2025, and Apple wants the TV rights. Club World Cup 2025 will feature 32 teams from each of the six confederations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/fifa.jpg" alt="" width="1535" height="863" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947662" /><br/>
An agreement between Apple and FIFA could be announced as soon as this month, and the first tournament will take place in the United States next summer. Apple could be paying around &#36;1 billion, and <em>The New York Times</em> says it is not yet clear if there will be any free-to-air rights. If not, the entire tournament could be available only to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has already shelled out &#36;2.5 billion to secure global broadcasting rights to Major League Soccer. MLS and League Cup games are streamed on &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;, with access priced at &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;99 per season for non-subscribers and &#36;12.99 per month or &#36;79 per season for those who subscribe to &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sees live sports as a way to lure new customers to the &zwnj;Apple TV+&zwnj; streaming service. In addition to the MLS deal, it has also secured a deal with Major League Baseball. Apple negotiated for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/19/apple-quits-nfl-sunday-ticket-negotiations/">NFL Sunday Ticket access</a>, and while that didn't work out, a report from <em><a href="https://theathletic.com/5430093/2024/04/22/nba-tv-rights-amazon-nbc/">The Athletic</a></em> suggests that Apple is still in the running to secure some streaming access to NBA games.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple introduced a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-hands-on/">dedicated Apple Sports app</a> that allows users to get real-time scores and stats for their favorite teams. The app is able to sync with the My Sports experience in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fifa/">FIFA</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-fifa-tournament-rights/">Apple Working to Secure Streaming Rights to FIFA Club World Cup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-working-to-secure-streaming-rights-to-fifa-club-world-cup.2424683/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Acquires French AI Company Specializing in On-Device Processing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-french-ai-company-specializing-in-on-device-processing.2424672/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:01:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>France</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has acquired the Paris-based artificial intelligence startup Datakalab amid its push to deliver on-device AI tools.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Datakalab specializes in algorithm compression and embedded AI systems. The acquisition, finalized on December 17 last year, was quietly conducted but noted in a European Commission filing spotted by French publication <em><a href="https://www.challenges.fr/high-tech/ia-apple-rachete-la-start-up-parisienne-datakalab_890773">Challenges</a></em> (via <em><a href="https://iphonesoft.fr/2024/04/22/apple-rachete-start-up-francaise-datakalab-specialisee-ia-embarquee">iPhoneSoft</a></em>). While the financial details of the transaction remain undisclosed, the move is almost certainly part of Apple's broader strategy to bring more sophisticated AI technology to its devices, such as those expected to be introduced in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The company was established in 2016 by Xavier and Lucas Fischer and made significant strides in AI technology focusing on low-power, high-efficiency deep learning algorithms that function without relying on cloud-based systems. This approach aligns with Apple's oft-touted commitment to user privacy, data security, and reliable performance, as processing data locally minimizes the risk of data breaches and ensures faster processing times. The startup's expertise in compressing neural networks to work effectively on portable devices like smartphones and tablets is likely a key factor in Apple's interest.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> recently reported that Apple's LLM <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">will run entirely on-device</a>, rather than via the cloud like most existing AI services.  Apple's AI tools may be less capable in certain instances than its direct cloud-based rivals, but Gurman suggested that the company could "fill in the gaps" by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">licensing technology from Google</a> and other AI service providers. <br/>
<br/>
Before its acquisition, Datakalab engaged in various high-profile projects, including collaborations with the French government and Disney. The company developed technology capable of analyzing human emotions by facial recognition and visual data, which were later used to monitor audience reactions in real-time during cinema screenings. The first look at Apple's new AI strategy is widely anticipated to arrive alongside previews of its next-generation operating systems at WWDC in early June.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-acquires-french-ai-company/">Apple Acquires French AI Company Specializing in On-Device Processing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-acquires-french-ai-company-specializing-in-on-device-processing.2424672/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Air Stock Running Low Ahead of New Model Introduction</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-model-introduction.2424670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:29:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Retail stock of the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> is starting to dwindle ahead of the widely anticipated arrival of new models early next month, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Air-5-Colors-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1494" height="840" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-941843" /><br/>
Citing sources at multiple retail stores in the latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that inventory levels of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; are diminishing in Apple stores, a typical indicator that new versions are soon to be released. Unlike the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> apparently remains abundantly available, which suggests that Apple might be planning to sell through its current stock even after introducing an upgraded model. Historically, Apple has managed its inventory to align with the release cycles of its products, reducing shipments of older units to make room for the latest offerings. <br/>
<br/>
Expected changes coming to the next-generation &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; include the more powerful <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip and an additional 12.9-inch display size option, while the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is rumored to receive OLED display technology, the M3 chip, and new accessories. The refreshed &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/gurman-new-ipads-first-week-of-may/">expected to be announced</a> during the second week of May.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/ipad-air-stock-running-low/">iPad Air Stock Running Low Ahead of New Model Introduction</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-air-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-model-introduction.2424670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off Every Model of the 13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-every-model-of-the-13-inch-m3-macbook-air.2424669/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 07:24:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today is taking &#36;100 off across the entire 13-inch M3 MacBook Air lineup, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/cl6aWzhUJR0"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> for the 256GB model. For every version of the laptop these are all-time low prices, and they're available in all four colors of Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the entry-level 256GB laptop, Best Buy also has the 8GB RAM/512GB SSD 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2vWqjoI"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a> and the 16GB RAM/512GB SSD model for <a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2V0NjOE"><strong>&#36;1,399.00</strong></a>. Both of these are also &#36;100 discounts and record low prices on the just-released M3 MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6aWzhUJR0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2vWqjoI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB RAM/512GB SSD) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl6a2V0NjOE"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB RAM/512GB SSD) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
These MacBook Air models just launched last month, coming in both 13-inch and 15-inch sizes. Both of the new MacBook Air machines include the M3 chip and focus on internal upgrades. Apple did not change the design of the MacBook Air with the 2024 update, using the same design that was first introduced in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/best-buy-100-off-m3-macbook-air/">Best Buy Takes &#36;100 Off Every Model of the 13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-100-off-every-model-of-the-13-inch-m3-macbook-air.2424669/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Orders Capacitive Button Components Allegedly for iPhone 16</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-orders-capacitive-button-components-allegedly-for-iphone-16.2424660/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 05:08:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Economic Daily News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has ordered a large number of capacitative button components from a Taiwan supplier that are allegedly for use in the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series, claims a new report out of Asia.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/unbox-therapy-15-buttons.jpg" alt="" width="2842" height="1572" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895008" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image credit: Unbox Therapy</em></div><br/>
According to the <em><a href="https://money.udn.com/money/story/11162/7914175">Economic Daily News</a></em>, Advanced Semiconductor Engineering won the order, which is said to include system-in-a-package (SIP) modules that will be used to integrate capcative components with two Taptic Engine motors, one on either side of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The claim in the report is that Apple will replace the existing physical buttons on both sides of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> with capacitive versions that will provide &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; users with haptic feedback. The latter type of button detects pressure and emulates the press of a physical button via a haptic (or Taptic) engine which generates vibrations. <br/>
<br/>
Apple may well have ordered the buttons in preparation for future production plans, but this does not necessarily mean that they are destined for use in this year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. <br/>
<br/>
The earliest known prototypes of the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌ were thought to include haptic power and volume buttons. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/20/iphone-15-haptic-button-overview/">Project Bongo</a>, as it was known internally, was a redesign of the volume and power buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;. However, it was scrapped in 2023 following unresolved technical issues, according to <em>MacRumors</em>' sources. After the cancelation of the Bongo project, Apple moved back to mechanical buttons for the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;‌.<br/>
<br/>
As a result, most rumors suggest that &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have all-mechanical buttons, and this includes the rumored addition of a fourth button. According to <em>The Information</em>, Apple will add a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">Capture Button</a>" to all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, but the button is expected to be mechanical rather than capacitive, and yet it will be able to respond to pressure and touch. <br/>
<br/>
The button will be used for taking photos and videos, and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users will reportedly be able to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus with a light press, and activate a recording with a more forceful press.<br/>
<br/>
Today's report claims the capacitive components will enter volume production in the third quarter of this year, which is unusually late in terms of Apple's typical initial &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production run, so the order may be for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 lineup rather than this year's upcoming models. That said, as we saw with the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;‌ series, things can change fairly far into the process, so watch this space.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/udn-com/">Economic Daily News</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-orders-capactive-butttons-iphone-16/">Apple Orders Capacitive Button Components Allegedly for iPhone 16</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-orders-capacitive-button-components-allegedly-for-iphone-16.2424660/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Customer Interest Dying Down at Some Retail Stores</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down-at-some-retail-stores.2424651/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 02:12:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, Apple's &#36;3,500 spatial computing device, appears to be following a pattern familiar to the AR/VR headset industry – initial enthusiasm giving way to a significant dip in sustained interest and usage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Since its debut in the U.S. in February 2024, excitement for the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; has noticeably cooled, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. Writing in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna">Power On newsletter</a>, Gurman reports a marked decline in the demand for retail demos and sales, based on the Apple Stores he has spoken to:<br/>
<blockquote>Demand for demos is way down. People who do book appointments often don't show up, and sales — at least at some locations — have gone from a couple of units a day to just a handful in a whole week. Apple also has had to step up the marketing on its online homepage. There's a huge promo for the Vision Pro at the top of the website — the most aggressive pitch since the device went on sale in early February.</blockquote>The trend that &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; appears to be following is less likely to be a retail anomaly, and more indicative of a broader issue that has plagued VR technology from its inception: Maintaining user engagement after the initial novelty wears off. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman offers his personal experience of Apple's headset as a microcosm of what he suspects is a wider user trend. His own usage has decreased from daily interactions to just once or twice a week. A significant barrier to more frequent use, he says, is a setup that involves attaching batteries, booting up, and navigating a complex interface, which makes traditional devices like laptops and smartphones more appealing for regular tasks. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman also blames the Vision Pro's lack of a "killer app" and compelling content for further diminishing the headset's appeal. He notes that it feels better suited to solitary activities – say, on a long flight or while working from home – rather than for use in social situations or around co-workers.<br/>
<br/>
It seems Apple still has a considerable task ahead in evolving the Vision Pro into a device that redefines everyday technology use. In the meantime, several bugs that initially plagued <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> have been resolved, although many of Apple's own apps are still not optimized for the device's operating system.<br/>
<br/>
In the last &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; update, Apple added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/testing-vision-pro-spatial-persona/">Spatial Personas</a>, which make it feel like you are in the same virtual room as another Vision Pro user. Spatial Personas can be used for watching movies and TV shows together, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and other video calls, using apps like Freeform, playing games, and more. However, the feature needs other Vision Pro owners to appreciate it, and as Gurman notes, they are still few and far between. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to produce fewer than 400,000 Vision Pro headsets in 2024 due to the complexity of manufacturing, according to analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. However, Apple is said to be already working on a new version of the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; for 2025 that will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">priced more affordably</a>. Meanwhile, the first incarnation of the headset is expected to arrive in additional countries later this year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/">Apple Vision Pro Customer Interest Dying Down at Some Retail Stores</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down-at-some-retail-stores.2424651/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly Stops Production of FineWoven Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-stops-production-of-finewoven-accessories.2424610/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 06:03:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		<category>FineWoven</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has stopped production of FineWoven accessories, according to the Apple leaker and prototype collector known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1782025156292198751">post on X</a> (formerly Twitter), Kosutami explained that Apple has stopped production of FineWoven accessories due to its poor durability. The company may move to another non-leather material for its premium accessories in the future.<br/>
<br/>
Kosutami has revealed accurate information about FineWoven accessories in the past. The leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/09/new-apple-watch-magnetic-band/">unveiled</a> Apple's plans to introduce new Apple Watch bands made of a "woven fabric material" over a month before they debuted, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/finewoven-cases-may-match-new-watch-band/">matching iPhone cases</a>. Kosutami also revealed the very <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/exclusive-first-look-finewoven-apple-watch-band/">first images of FineWoven accessories</a> shortly before the event in which they were officially announced. <em>MacRumors</em> understands the source of this latest information regarding the cessation of production to be the same as these previous FineWoven rumors that were ultimately accurate, so it should be taken seriously until we know more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">stopped selling leather accessories</a> in September last year, replacing them with a more environmentally friendly "FineWoven" material that the company describes as "luxurious and durable microtwill" made from 68% post-consumer recycled polyester. FineWoven <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases are priced at &#36;59, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> Wallets at &#36;59, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> holders at &#36;35, and Apple Watch bands at &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
Accessories made of the material have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">very poorly received by customers</a>, citing poor durability and disappointing quality. FineWoven accessories in new color options were noticeably absent from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/">Apple's spring refresh</a>. If Apple has indeed stopped production of FineWoven accessories, it may be some time before the company's existing stock inventory begins to noticeably deplete. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/finewoven/">FineWoven</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/">Apple Reportedly Stops Production of FineWoven Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-stops-production-of-finewoven-accessories.2424610/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Working on On-Device LLM for Generative AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-working-on-on-device-llm-for-generative-ai-features.2424609/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 05:35:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is developing its own large language model (LLM) that runs on-device to prioritize speed and privacy, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Writing in his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said that Apple's LLM underpins upcoming generative AI features. "All indications" apparently suggests that it will run entirely on-device, rather than via the cloud like most existing AI services.<br/>
<br/>
Since they will run on-device, Apple's AI tools may be less capable in certain instances than its direct cloud-based rivals, but Gurman suggested that the company could "fill in the gaps" by licensing technology from Google and other AI service providers. Last month, Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">reported</a> that Apple was in discussions with Google to integrate its Gemini AI engine into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as part of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. The main advantages of on-device processing will be quicker response times and superior privacy compared to cloud-based solutions. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's marketing strategy for its AI technology will apparently be based around how it can be useful to users' daily lives, rather than its power. Apple's broader AI strategy is expected to be revealed alongside previews of its major software updates at WWDC in June.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">Gurman: Apple Working on On-Device LLM for Generative AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-working-on-on-device-llm-for-generative-ai-features.2424609/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Likely Planning to Skip M3 Mac Mini for M4 Refresh in Late 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini-for-m4-refresh-in-late-2024.2424607/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 05:16:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>M4 Macs</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is likely to skip an M3 version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> in favor of a bigger update with M4 chips toward the end of the year, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Mini-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-946149" /><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-21/apple-aapl-growth-opportunities-southeast-asia-and-africa-lower-end-iphone-lv9itkna?">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that he does not expect Apple to refresh the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with M3 chips. Apple last updated the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chips <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/17/new-m2-m2-pro-mac-mini/">in January 2023</a>. Other new features included two extra Thunderbolt 4 ports and an HDMI 2.1 port for &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro configurations, Wi-Fi 6E support with a compatible router, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously said that Apple is planning to release new &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; models with M4 and M4 Pro chips "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">between the end of 2024 and early 2025</a>." Now, he has clarified that with new Mac minis arriving as soon as the end of the year, there is not sufficient "room for M3 models to come out before then, so it's probably safe to say that those Mac desktops will skip the M3 generation."<br/>
<br/>
Such a move would not be unprecedented since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> skipped the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip entirely, holding off until a bigger performance bump with the M3 chip late last year. With the M4 chip series, the &zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; should get a significant CPU performance improvement compared to the existing models with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series. The M4 chips are also rumored to have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">faster Neural Engine</a> for artificial intelligence tasks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macs/">M4 Macs</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini/">Apple Likely Planning to Skip M3 Mac Mini for M4 Refresh in Late 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-likely-planning-to-skip-m3-mac-mini-for-m4-refresh-in-late-2024.2424607/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>LeBron James Spotted With Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lebron-james-spotted-with-unreleased-beats-pill-speaker.2424590/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:26:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of tonight's NBA playoff game, the Los Angeles Lakers <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lakers/reel/C5_8L_DPjYW/">posted an Instagram reel</a> showing superstar LeBron James arriving at Ball Arena in Denver carrying what appears to be an unreleased version of the Pill speaker from Apple's Beats brand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/lebron-unreleased-beats-pill.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947585" /><br/>
The original Beats Pill was a wireless Bluetooth speaker introduced in 2012 prior to Apple's acquisition of Beats Electronics. It received a few updates in its first several years on the market, with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/10/26/beats-pill-speaker-launches/">final revision being a redesigned Pill+</a> with a Lightning connector introduced under Apple's ownership in 2015.<br/>
<br/>
The Pill+ remained on the market for a number of years in that form before being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">quietly discontinued</a> in early 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Based on today's video, it appears the Pill may soon be making a comeback, as the speaker in James' hand clearly shows a Beats logo and it includes a lanyard that was not present on previous versions of the speaker.<br/>
<br/>
With the direction of Apple's product lineup, a USB-C port for charging appears likely. And given the previous Pill+ was introduced almost nine years ago, there have been significant advances in Bluetooth and other technologies since that time, so this upcoming version is likely to be a significant improvement. Specific details on the speaker, including a release date, however, remain unknown.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">LeBron James Spotted With Unreleased Beats Pill Speaker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lebron-james-spotted-with-unreleased-beats-pill-speaker.2424590/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Big iPad Sale Has &#36;100 Off iPad Mini, iPad Air, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-big-ipad-sale-has-100-off-ipad-mini-ipad-air-and-more.2424564/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:09:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is back with a <a href="https://howl.me/clG8QCkba7O">new sale on Apple iPads</a>, including some of the best prices we've ever seen on iPad, iPad mini, and iPad Air. Additionally, we're still tracking a great deal on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, which is &#36;150 off right now at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/best-buy-blue-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937846" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-best-buy-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938106" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad at <a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a>, which is an all-time low price at &#36;100 off. You'll find every model of the 10th generation iPad on sale at a record low price during this sale. This includes all Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, in all colors.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKavBDVPi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKbvh8PEh"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKduB2Qbr"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clAKdXDXcha"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926944" /><br/>
We're tracking discounts across the entire iPad mini 6 lineup at Best Buy this weekend, including second-best prices for multiple tablets. Prices start at <a href="https://howl.me/cl4ULPxMzsv"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4ULPxMzsv"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UMAu57Lv"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UNaOAqS8"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad mini for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UNMb7NwA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad mini for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><h2>iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/ipad-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930002" /><br/>
Best Buy has the 2022 iPad Air for &#36;100 off every configuration this weekend. These are solid second-best prices across the board, starting at <a href="https://howl.me/cl4UGX1cxXA"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UGX1cxXA"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UHF9fr6R"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UIg9rOk7"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;649.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl4UITHMucB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;799.99</div></a></div><h2>13-inch M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/macbook-air-best-buy.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924749" /><br/>
Every model of the 2022 13-inch MacBook Air is <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI">available for &#36;150 off</a> this weekend at Best Buy. The 256GB model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a> and the 512GB model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"><strong>&#36;1,049.00</strong></a>. These deals beat the previous prices by about &#36;50, and you don't need to be a My Best Buy Plus or Total member to get them.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3gg6L3KI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clP3g2gOdEC"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/best-buys-big-ipad-sale/">Best Buy&#039;s Big iPad Sale Has &#36;100 Off iPad Mini, iPad Air, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-big-ipad-sale-has-100-off-ipad-mini-ipad-air-and-more.2424564/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Nintendo Emulators on App Store, Two New iOS 17 Features, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-nintendo-emulators-on-app-store-two-new-ios-17-features-and-more.2424557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It was a big week for retro gaming fans, as iPhone users are starting to reap the rewards of Apple's recent change to allow retro game emulators on the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/top-stories-20apr2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947573" /><br/>
This week also saw a new iOS 17.5 beta that will support web-based app distribution in the EU, the debut of the first hotels to allow for direct AirPlay streaming to room TVs, a fresh rumor about the impending iPad Air update, and more details on the sequence of Apple's M4-based Mac updates starting later this year, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Delta Game Emulator Now Available From App Store on iPhone</h2><br/>
A few weeks after Apple updated its App Review Guidelines to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allow retro game console emulator apps</a>, the popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">Nintendo emulator Delta is now available in the App Store</a>. Delta can emulate games released for many older Nintendo consoles, including the NES, SNES, Nintendo 64, Nintendo DS, and all Game Boy models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Delta-Emulator-Pokemon-Gen-3-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947545" /><br/>
We published an article explaining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/what-to-know-about-iphone-app-store-emulators/">key facts about emulators in the App Store</a> and the legality of downloading games.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New iOS 17.5 Beta Lets EU iPhone Users Download Apps Directly From Websites</h2><br/>
Starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/">second beta of iOS 17.5</a>, released this week, large developers in the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">can now distribute apps directly on the web</a> instead of through the App Store or an alternative app marketplace.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-EU-iOS-Changes-Orange-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946723" /><br/>
To be eligible for this new Web Distribution feature, Apple says a developer must meet several requirements, including having an app that had more than one million annual installs on iOS in the EU in the prior calendar year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 17's New AirPlay Feature for Hotel Room TVs Begins Rolling Out</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/ios-17-airplay-hotel-feature-now-available/">announced that AirPlay is now available at around 60 hotels</a> operated by IHG Hotels & Resorts in the U.S., Canada, and Mexico.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/IHG-Hotel-AirPlay.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947151" /><br/>
At hotels that offer the feature, guests can scan a unique QR code on their room's TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing them to wirelessly stream content from their iPhone or iPad. For example, they could stream Apple TV+ or Netflix shows, listen to music on Apple Music or Spotify, play games on Apple Arcade, or work out with Apple Fitness+.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 30 Rumored Upgrades Compared</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16 lineup is still months away from being announced, there are already many rumors about the four devices that have been circulating for months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature-Cyan-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935694" /><br/>
If you own an iPhone 15 Pro or Pro Max model, and will be considering upgrading to the iPhone 16 Pro family, check out our new comparison chart that outlines <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">over 30 rumored new features and changes for the iPhone 16 Pro models</a>, and if you're an iPhone 15 or 15 Plus user, we're tracking <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/">over 15 changes expected for the iPhone 16 models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>12.9-Inch iPad Air Now Rumored to Feature Mini-LED Display</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">rumored 12.9-inch iPad Air</a> that is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/28/new-ipad-models-may-launch/">expected to be announced in May</a> will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/12-9-inch-ipad-air-mini-led-display-rumor/">equipped with a mini-LED display</a> like the current 12.9-inch iPad Pro, according to info shared this week by Ross Young, CEO of research firm Display Supply Chain Consultants.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPad-Air-12.9-Inch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2192" height="1233" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917813" /><br/>
The existing 10.9-inch iPad Air is equipped with a standard LCD panel, and the move to mini-LED technology for the 12.9-inch model would provide increased brightness for HDR content, deeper blacks, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Macs Are Expected to Launch in This Order Starting Later This Year</h2><br/>
In his <em>Power On</em> newsletter this week, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman outlined the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">order in which he expects Macs with the M4 family of chips to be released</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945901" /><br/>
Gurman said the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">entire Mac lineup will be updated</a> with the M4 chip or higher-end variants, starting with the MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini between late 2024 and early 2025, followed by the MacBook Air, Mac Studio, and Mac Pro between the spring and end of 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/apr-18-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/top-stories-game-emulators-app-store/">Top Stories: Nintendo Emulators on App Store, Two New iOS 17 Features, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-nintendo-emulators-on-app-store-two-new-ios-17-features-and-more.2424557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announced the 24-Inch iMac Three Years Ago Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today.2424556/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:13:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the three-year anniversary of Apple's announcement of the 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, a transformative redesign featuring the first integration of Apple silicon in the product line.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iMac-24-Apple-Newsroom-Gray-bg.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-930105" /><br/>
Apple unveiled the new 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; on April 20, 2021, almost nine years after the previous &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; redesign debuted. It replaced both the 21.5-inch and the 27-inch Intel iMacs, and represented a recommitment to the long-standing desktop product line.<br/>
<br/>
The highly anticipated redesign offers a much thinner and more compact body compared to its predecessors, available in an array of vibrant colors reminiscent of the original iMacs released in the late 1990s. The 24-inch 4.5K Retina display boasts 11.3 million pixels and support for 1 billion colors.<br/>
<br/>
The new model was not only notable for its updated design but also as the inaugural &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; to incorporate Apple silicon, one of the last Macs to make the transition away from Intel. Apple claimed that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip delivered up to 85% faster CPU performance and up to two-times faster GPU performance compared to the previous 21.5-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; models. The new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; also offered a 1080p <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> HD camera, studio-quality microphones, and a six-speaker sound system, as well as a color-matched Magic Keyboard with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple refreshed the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with the M3 chip, Wi-Fi 6E, and Bluetooth 5.3 in November 2023. Rumors suggest that a larger-screened &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; that could be positioned as an &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">launch in 2025</a>. In June 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that the high-end &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; was a year or two away from launching as work on the device was still in the early stages.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today/">Apple Announced the 24-Inch iMac Three Years Ago Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announced-the-24-inch-imac-three-years-ago-today.2424556/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M4 MacBook Pro Lineup: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-macbook-pro-lineup-what-to-expect.2424533/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:02:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro&#038;post_date=1713574947/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>M4 MacBook Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to refresh the MacBook Pro with M4 chips starting in late 2024, and this guide aggregates everything that we know about Apple's M4 MacBook Pro plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945903" /><br/>
<h2 id="m4_update">M4 Update</h2><br/>
Apple built the M3 chip on a new 3-nanometer process, and we are not expecting a node change for the M4. It too will be a 3-nanometer chip, but Apple supplier TSMC could introduce updates that make it more efficient and faster.<br/>
<br/>
New artificial intelligence capabilities are rumored for Apple's upcoming products, and so the M4 will focus on AI. Apple wants to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">improve performance</a> for AI functionality, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">rumors suggest</a> that the M4 (and the A18 chips for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>) will have an upgraded Neural Engine with "significantly" more cores.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chips all have a 16-core Neural Engine, and Apple has not increased the Neural Engine cores for several years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="entry-level_14-inch_macbook_pro">Entry-Level 14-Inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
With the M3 chip launch last year, Apple did away with the 13-inch MacBook Pro. It's been replaced with the 14-inch MacBook Pro, which Apple now offers with three different chip options.<br/>
<br/>
The entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro has an M3 chip and a &#36;1,599 starting price, and this is the model that will get the standard M4 chip. The current M3 chip has an 8-core CPU and up to a 10-core GPU, and the M4 could be similar.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="higher-end_14-inch_and_16-inch_macbook_pro_models">Higher-End 14-Inch and 16-Inch MacBook Pro Models</h2><br/>
For customers who want a more "pro" machine, the higher-end 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models are set to be refreshed with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips, which are more powerful versions of the faster M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
The current M3 Pro has up to a 12-core CPU and up to an 18-core GPU, while the M3 Max has up to a 16-core CPU and up to a 40-core GPU. CPU and GPU improvements for the M4 Pro and M4 Max aren't yet known.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design_changes">Design Changes?</h2><br/>
There are no rumors of a design change for the MacBook Pro at this time, and we're not quite due for one. Apple last updated the MacBook Pro design in 2021 with the transition to Apple silicon. In recent history, Apple has redesigned the MacBook in 2012, 2016, and 2021, so following that pattern, we'll see the next design tweak in 2025 or 2026.<br/>
<br/>
This year's M-series update will likely be limited to the MacBook Pro's internals.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/14/when-are-m4-macs-launching/">According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, the entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro could get an M4 chip in late 2024, while the timeline for the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro refresh is estimated at late 2024 to early 2025.<br/>
<br/>
We could see the M4, M4 Pro, and M4 Max variants come out all at once like the M3 chip lineup, or Apple could space them out across several months.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 MacBook Pro models came out in October 2023, so a refresh around October 2024 would come at the one-year mark.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/">Apple&#039;s M4 MacBook Pro Lineup: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-macbook-pro-lineup-what-to-expect.2424533/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Now Available on Apple&#039;s Refurbished Store in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-now-available-on-apples-refurbished-store-in-u-s.2424524/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:34:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began selling certified refurbished Apple Watch Ultra 2 models in the U.S. for the first time since the device was released in September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-blorange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911679" /><br/>
As of writing, refurbished Ultra 2 models with the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREG3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-Blue-Ocean-Band">Blue</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREH3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-Orange-Ocean-Band?fnode=c33d6587feda6a2d1b4df893338e0b10c6def7ee3d2db1465e981af4a26e20b29a9c5339994ab02294593ec3968732539fefa1c777bc2e2d0e1bd6aff98bcb1fe958a412ce82bc5f5b2e7389568d2e15">Orange</a>, or <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/FREJ3LW/A/Refurbished-Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-GPS-Cellular-49mm-Titanium-Case-with-White-Ocean-Band?fnode=e5406cc44be0df3204093d631dbb4976cebe18e711d09d02bbce5167a990eea5a25cbe8bf141f71311fff9fcc8eb7773853603822f89ae164ace9014c53293a3a11637451df5bf9098715a484e206991">White Ocean Band</a> are available for &#36;679, compared to &#36;799 brand new.<br/>
<br/>
Like new Ultra 2 models sold directly by Apple in the U.S. currently, we expect that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/apple-website-apple-watch-blood-oxygen-removal/">Blood Oxygen app is deactivated</a> on the refurbished models, due to a legal battle with medical technology company Masimo. Last year, the U.S. International Trade Commission (ITC) <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/10/itc-opposes-apple-watch-sales-ban-pause/">banned Apple</a> from importing and selling Apple Watch models with blood oxygen sensing after it ruled that the feature infringed on Masimo's patents. Apple is appealing the decision, and could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-software/">re-enable the Blood Oxygen app with a watchOS update</a> if it is overturned.<br/>
<br/>
Availability began <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/18/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-begins-rolling-out/">in the U.K. and China</a> earlier this week, and the Blood Oxygen app remains functional outside of the U.S. currently.<br/>
<br/>
There are no refurbished Apple Watch Series 9 models available on Apple's store in the U.S. yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/refurbished-apple-watch-ultra-2-in-us/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Now Available on Apple&#039;s Refurbished Store in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-now-available-on-apples-refurbished-store-in-u-s.2424524/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Pulls WhatsApp, Telegram, Signal, and Threads From App Store in China Following Order</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/apple-pulls-whatsapp-telegram-signal-threads-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-whatsapp-telegram-signal-and-threads-from-app-store-in-china-following-order.2424517/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:20:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/apple-pulls-whatsapp-telegram-signal-threads-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on late Thursday into Friday removed the popular messaging and social media apps WhatsApp, Telegram, Signal, and Threads from its App Store in China at the request of the Chinese government, <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/apple-removes-whatsapp-threads-from-china-app-store-on-government-orders-a0c02100"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em> reported</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Whatsapp-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786421" /><br/>
In a statement shared with several media outlets, Apple said China's national internet regulator ordered the removal of the apps from the App Store in the country due to unspecified "national security concerns." Apple said it is "obligated to follow the laws in the countries where we operate, even when we disagree."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has complied with similar App Store removal orders from the Chinese government in the past for apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/10/20/senators-ask-apple-why-vpn-apps-removed-china/">related to VPNs</a>, news, and more.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/apple-pulls-whatsapp-telegram-signal-threads-china/">Apple Pulls WhatsApp, Telegram, Signal, and Threads From App Store in China Following Order</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pulls-whatsapp-telegram-signal-and-threads-from-app-store-in-china-following-order.2424517/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>European Regulators Will Soon Approve Apple&#039;s Plan to Open Up Tap-to-Pay to Banks and Payment Providers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/eu-regulators-tap-to-pay-approval/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/european-regulators-will-soon-approve-apples-plan-to-open-up-tap-to-pay-to-banks-and-payment-providers.2424513/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 10:04:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/eu-regulators-tap-to-pay-approval/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>NFC</category>
		<category>Europe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of the changes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">introduced in Europe in iOS 17.4</a>, Apple gave third-party payment apps and banks direct access to the NFC chip, allowing for non-Apple Pay tap-to-pay payment options. The European Commission is set to approve Apple's plan to open up tap-and-go mobile payments "as soon as next month," according to <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/apples-offer-open-up-tap-and-go-tech-be-approved-by-eu-next-month-sources-say-2024-04-19/">Reuters</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921515" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
With NFC access, banks and third-party payment apps can offer contactless payments directly on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> without having to use the Wallet app or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. This feature is available in the European Economic Area, and it lets EU users set a default non-Apple wallet app and default contactless payment provider that activates at tap-to-pay terminals or when the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s side button is pressed twice.<br/>
<br/>
The European Economic Area (EEA) is the only area where Apple has opened up NFC access, and developers in other countries cannot access the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s NFC chip for tap-to-pay purposes. Customers will be able to use NFC-enabled apps from their banks and other payment providers with no involvement from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has long limited the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and other Apple devices to &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; payments, which has prevented banks and other financial services from providing their customers with direct contactless payment solutions on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced plans to open NFC payment technology to third-party developers in Europe <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/20/apple-offers-to-open-nfc-in-europe/">in January</a>, and Apple made the change in order to address antitrust charges it was facing from the European Commission (EC). The EC has accused Apple of limiting competition by preventing rival mobile wallets from accessing the NFC chip, and Apple's decision to open it up will prevent fines and other penalties.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nfc/">NFC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/europe/">Europe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/eu-regulators-tap-to-pay-approval/">European Regulators Will Soon Approve Apple&#039;s Plan to Open Up Tap-to-Pay to Banks and Payment Providers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/european-regulators-will-soon-approve-apples-plan-to-open-up-tap-to-pay-to-banks-and-payment-providers.2424513/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: AI Macs With M4 Chips</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/the-macrumors-show-ai-macs-with-m4-chips/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ai-macs-with-m4-chips.2424510/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:31:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/the-macrumors-show-ai-macs-with-m4-chips/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/can-the-humane-ai-pin-replace-your-iphone/id1602394741?i=1000652990381">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the latest AI consumer technology and Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">rumored plans</a> to bring major AI-focused hardware enhancements to the Mac later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oqqMn2FLYus?si=xQySmWmXTqaloZBz" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div> <br/>
We talk through the response to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/humane-ai-pin/">Humane's AI Pin</a> and its widely acknowledged deficiencies, such as its limited utility, subpar camera performance, and steep price point. We also take a look at the Rabbit R1, another AI device that prompts us to question the necessity of such hardware when similar functionalities could potentially be achieved with existing smartphones. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/11/m4-ai-chips-late-2024/">M4-series custom silicon chips</a> starting this year, featuring more powerful Neural Engines with more cores to support AI processes. These chips are likely based on the advancements coming to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup's A18 chip, hinting that iPhone-exclusive AI features could later come to the Mac. <br/>
<br/>
We also touch on the progress of AI tools in video editing software, including recent announcements from Adobe Premiere and DaVinci Resolve which have introduced new AI-driven editing features like generative fill and object removal. Such features could see enhanced performance on next-generation Macs with AI-focused chips. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> is now on <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips going forward:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our chat with Matthew Cassinelli, one of the minds behind Workflow, discuss Apple Shortcuts and potential improvements and AI features coming to the app in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/the-macrumors-show-ai-macs-with-m4-chips/">The MacRumors Show: AI Macs With M4 Chips</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ai-macs-with-m4-chips.2424510/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-april/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2424508/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 09:23:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-april/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with GRID Studio to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win a 256GB <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>. <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">GRID Studio</a> is a company dedicated to taking old, retired Apple devices and giving them new life in the form of art.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/grid-studio-4-03.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947421" /><br/>
To celebrate Earth Day, GRID Studio is hosting a special deal on one of its most popular products, <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/framed-iphone-4">offering the GRID 4</a> for just &#36;99. The GRID 4 features a disassembled <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 4, with all of the components skillfully arranged to give a look back at Apple's history.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4 is one of Apple's most notable designs, because it introduced the first major design update after the original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3G, and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 3GS. It featured an all-new look with squared edges that felt decidedly modern at the time, and it is an aesthetic that Apple returned to starting with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/grid-studio-4-01.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947423" /><br/>
GRID's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4 piece includes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4 internals, ranging from the logic board with Apple A4 chip and PowerVR GPU to the iconic Home button. Components are labeled and arranged in a logical way so you can tell what's what. GRID's art makes a great gift for any Apple enthusiast, and there are many other <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/collections/iphone">disassembled iPhone options</a> ranging from the original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/grid-studio-t-shirt-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947425" /><br/>
In addition to the sale on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 4, GRID is discounting all of its products by 15 percent. GRID customers who spend over &#36;30 this week can get a special <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE-earth-day-eco-tee">Earth Day Eco Tee</a> for just &#36;9.99, with the shirt featuring a recycling logo made up of a ton of tiny Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/grid-studio-t-shirt-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947426" /><br/>
We have one 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; to give away to a <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/lVuri/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (April 19) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on April 26. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after April 26 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-april/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 Pro From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-pro-from-grid-studio.2424508/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
