<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 21:03:18 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini 7</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-2024-ipad-mini-7.2427857/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 15:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7&#038;post_date=1717207020/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>iPad mini 7</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While Apple refreshed the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> in May, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> is still in need of an update. Apple last introduced a new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in September 2021, so it's overdue for an overhaul.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipad-mini-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="1607" height="905" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937844" /><br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple has plans to refresh its smallest tablet in 2024, and this guide highlights all of the rumors we've heard about the device so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="display_and_design">Display and Design</h2><br/>
We haven't heard rumors of design changes for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, which means it will likely feature the same 8.3-inch size and all-display design. The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; has a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> Power Button, which we're also expecting for the new model.<br/>
<br/>
According to a 2023 rumor, Apple will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">make a small tweak</a> to the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s display in an effort to cut down on "jelly scrolling." The screen assembly will be rotated, which is supposed to reduce the effect when using the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in portrait orientation.<br/>
<br/>
Jelly scrolling refers to noticeable lag when scrolling vertically through text-based context like a webpage. Each line appears to tilt downward toward the left of the screen as it passes, which makes it look like one side of the display is responding faster. Apple says that this is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">normal behavior</a> for LCD iPads, but the company still wants to make a change to minimize the effect.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="a-series_chip">A-Series Chip</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; have M-series chips, but we're not expecting the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; to get a Mac chip this year. Instead, Apple is likely to go with the A17 Pro that was used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, or some other A17 variant.<br/>
<br/>
It's also possible that the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will get an A18 chip if it comes after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup, as rumors suggest the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will have chips in the A18 family.<br/>
<br/>
With an A17 Pro or better, the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; would be on par with or faster than the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, but it won't have the speeds of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is overhauling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and iPadOS 18 with a focus on AI, so high powered chips are a must for upcoming devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_colors">New Colors</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is available in space gray, starlight, pink, and purple right now. Apple often refreshes color options with updates, so new colors are a definite possibility. With the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, which the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; often mimics, Apple got rid of pink.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple makes the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; available in the same colors as the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, it could come in space gray, purple, blue, and starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="front_camera">Front Camera</h2><br/>
Apple moved the front-facing camera on the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; to the landscape edge of the device, and it could make the same change for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;. It may make less sense to have a landscape camera on an &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, though, because it's less often used with keyboards.<br/>
<br/>
The camera could get support for HDR 4 and it could have a wider aperture, if it adopts the camera used in the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="connectivity">Connectivity</h2><br/>
Apple has been adding Wi-Fi 6E to each product as it's updated, and it should be the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s turn this year. Wi-Fi 6E will allow the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; to connect to the 6GHz Wi-Fi network on supported routers.<br/>
<br/>
Bluetooth 5.3 is also expected, as that's another update Apple has been making to new devices, and the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; could lose its nano-SIM slot, with Apple opting only for eSIM.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_pencil_pro">Apple Pencil Pro</h2><br/>
The current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; works with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> 2, so the new model will likely support the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro. The &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro has a squeeze gesture, haptic feedback, a gyroscope for barrel roll support, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> integration.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover might also be a new feature, as the current &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; does not support it.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple will likely release a new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; toward the end of the year, likely in September or October. In some years, Apple holds a special October event for Macs and iPads, and we could get that in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
MacBook Pro models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, and the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> could all be refreshed alongside the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="future_ipad_mini_models">Future iPad mini Models</h2><br/>
There are rumors that Apple is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-foldable-2026-could-replace-ipad-mini/">foldable iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">OLED display technology</a> for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, but neither of these updates are expected in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
OLED, a foldable &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, or a foldable OLED &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; are technologies not expected until 2026, 2027, or even later.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s 2024 iPad Mini 7</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-2024-ipad-mini-7.2427857/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Foldable MacBooks: Six Things to Know About Apple&#039;s Future Plans</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/foldable-macbook-rumor-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-macbooks-six-things-to-know-about-apples-future-plans.2427855/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 14:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/foldable-macbook-rumor-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Rumors from multiple reliable sources suggest that Apple is working on a MacBook that has a foldable screen, and it could in fact be Apple's first foldable device, coming before a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. We've rounded up six key features that we've heard about the device so far.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Foldable-Screen-MacBook-Concept-Astropad.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="576" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952144" /><em>Concept by <a href="https://astropad.com/foldable-mac-screen/">Astropad</a></em></div><br/>
<h2>Design</h2><br/>
The all-display design of the foldable MacBook would be distinct from the current MacBook, which has a display and keyboard. It would feature a single large screen that's able to be folded in half.<br/>
<br/>
When unfolded, the MacBook could be used as a monitor when paired with a keyboard and a trackpad or mouse, and when folded, it could serve as a notebook machine. Presumably this kind of design would not have a separate keyboard, instead using an on-screen keyboard with digital keys and haptic feedback for a key-like feel.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Size</h2><br/>
Display research analyst Ross Young claims the foldable MacBook will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">an 18.8-inch display</a>, with Apple aiming to make the screen "as crease-free as possible" when it is unfolded. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has also suggested Apple is planning for a screen around 19 inches.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Display Technology</h2><br/>
Apple has been rumored to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/01/foldable-oled-ipads-and-macbooks-in-development/">working with LG Display</a> to develop a foldable OLED panel, and LG has been developing foldable ultra-thin cover glass for the last several years.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also tested <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/17/kuo-apple-testing-eink-display-foldable-devices/">electronic paper display</a> (EPD) technology that it could use in future foldable devices. EPD could potentially be used in the outer-most display in a foldable device, if Apple goes with some kind of dual display design with an outside and inside screen.<br/>
<br/>
EPD is a form of e-ink technology, which is known for being much more viewable than LED or OLED screens in bright light.<br/>
<br/>
At an 18.8-inch size, the foldable notebook would likely have a 5K or higher resolution.<br/>
<h2>M-Series Chip</h2><br/>
Mass production on foldable display panels for a future MacBook could begin in the fourth quarter of 2025 for a launch in late 2025 or early 2026. That would be timed with the future M5 chip, a successor to the 2024 M4.<br/>
<br/>
We don't know what to expect from the M5, but it is likely to be manufactured on a next-generation 3-nanometer node or even a 2-nanometer node. TSMC is working on 2nm chips, and they're supposed to be ready somewhere around the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/24/apple-tsmc-first-2nm-chips/">second half of 2025</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> and 2nm reference the architecture that TSMC is using for its chips, and a decrease in node size corresponds to a decrease in transistor size, allowing more transistors to fit on a processor. This often results in faster performance and better energy efficiency. Right now, Apple's M4 chips are built on a 3-nanometer mode, much like the M3 chips.<br/>
<h2>Price</h2><br/>
Apple will need to use high-cost components for the foldable MacBook, and Kuo believes it could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/20-inch-foldable-macbook-crease-free-rumor/">almost as expensive</a> as the &#36;3,500 Vision Pro headset when it launches. The 16-inch MacBook Pro currently starts at &#36;2,500, so presumably the larger foldable model would be more expensive than that.<br/>
<h2>Release Date</h2><br/>
If rumors are accurate and Apple is planning to have LG Display begin mass production on a foldable MacBook in the fourth quarter of 2025, the device could launch in 2025 or 2026. Kuo estimates that Apple will ship more than one million units in 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ross Young believes that a foldable MacBook could come <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/31/apple-foldable-notebook-2025/">as soon as 2025</a>, the same timeline suggested by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">analyst Jeff Pu</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors about a foldable MacBook have been all over the place, however, and just two months prior to suggesting a Q4 2025 mass production schedule, Kuo said a foldable MacBook wouldn't come until 2027. It's best not to read too much into launch date rumors at this point, because Apple's plans could change.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/foldable-macbook-rumor-recap/">Foldable MacBooks: Six Things to Know About Apple&#039;s Future Plans</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/foldable-macbooks-six-things-to-know-about-apples-future-plans.2427855/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 and macOS 15 to Feature Refreshed Settings App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-refreshed-settings-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-macos-15-to-feature-refreshed-settings-app.2427850/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 13:22:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-refreshed-settings-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a> updates, Apple plans to streamline the Settings app, <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1796399911526920509"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> confirmed today. He said that while it's not a "huge deal," there are some changes planned.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944196" /><br/>
The Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and the System Settings on Macs will get an updated UI with a "reorganized, cleaner layout" that's simpler to navigate. Search in the Settings app is also set to improve, and that's been a major issue with prior versions of iOS and macOS.<br/>
<br/>
On iOS specifically, searching for an option in the Settings app often returns no results or the wrong result. A search for "Charging Optimization," a setting on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, does not bring up the interface, for example. There are several other smaller settings options that are similarly inaccessible when searching.<br/>
<br/>
Part of the changes planned for &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj; include major updates to Spotlight and search throughout the operating systems, as well as an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/">overhauled version of Siri</a> that is able to control all individual features in apps. Combined, these updates should make it easier to get to some of the more hidden settings on Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
A prior rumor suggested that Apple would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/macos-15-system-settings-design/">overhaul the macOS System Settings app</a>, introducing rearranged menus and app UIs in an update that will be the biggest since the Settings app was refreshed in macOS Ventura. On the Mac, Apple is said to be using an organizational system focused on "priority and overall importance," and the same changes could be made on iOS as well.<br/>
<br/>
The Notifications and Sound categories in System Settings will be moved lower in the list, with General settings moved up under Network settings. Wallpaper and Displays will join General settings, and Privacy and Security will be paired with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> and Password.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also planning to refresh <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-control-center-updates-rumor/">the Control Center</a> on &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and Apple has been testing the changes internally, but specific updates are unclear at this time.<br/>
<br/>
More on the features that are coming to iOS and macOS can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a> roundups, which are updated regularly with all of the new rumors that we've heard.<br/>
<br/>
The 2024 Worldwide Developers Conference keynote is set to take place on Monday, June 10, with Apple unveiling &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;macOS 15&zwnj;, and also iPadOS 18, tvOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2, and watchOS 11.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-refreshed-settings-app/">iOS 18 and macOS 15 to Feature Refreshed Settings App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-and-macos-15-to-feature-refreshed-settings-app.2427850/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iPhone 5s Now Obsolete as iPod Touch 6 Becomes &#039;Vintage&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-says-iphone-5s-now-obsolete/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphone-5s-now-obsolete-as-ipod-touch-6-becomes-vintage.2427839/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 10:30:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-says-iphone-5s-now-obsolete/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today made three changes to its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">vintage and obsolete products list</a>, involving the iPhone 5s, sixth-generation iPod touch, and an older iMac model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-5s-16x9.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952997" /><br/>
First, Apple now considers the iPhone 5s to be an "obsolete" product worldwide, meaning that Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers no longer offer repairs or other hardware service for the device. Apple says it considers a product "obsolete" once seven years have passed since the company last distributed it for sale.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released the iPhone 5s in September 2013, with its key new feature being the Touch ID fingerprint sensor built into the Home button. The device also introduced the A7 chip, which was Apple's first iPhone chip with 64-bit architecture.<br/>
<br/>
Second, the sixth-generation iPod touch and the late 2015 edition of the 21.5-inch iMac with a Retina 4K display are now classified as "vintage" products, as more than five years have passed since the company stopped distributing the devices for sale. Apple Stores and Apple Authorized Service Providers can continue to offer repairs for vintage products for up to two more years, but only if the necessary parts remain available.<br/>
<br/>
The sixth-generation iPod touch was released in 2015, and it was the second-last model of the device. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/10/apple-discontinues-ipod-touch/">discontinued the iPod touch line</a> in 2022.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-says-iphone-5s-now-obsolete/">Apple Says iPhone 5s Now Obsolete as iPod Touch 6 Becomes &#039;Vintage&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-iphone-5s-now-obsolete-as-ipod-touch-6-becomes-vintage.2427839/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad Pro From GRID Studio</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-pro-from-grid-studio.2427835/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:53:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://gridstudio.cc">GRID Studio</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>. For those unfamiliar with GRID Studio, it is a small company that crafts art out of old, discarded Apple products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/grid_frame_studio_1st_iphone_10.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952967" /><br/>
GRID Studio buys and recycles old electronics, taking them apart and arranging each component carefully under a glass frame. Their work turns a hodgepodge of parts into display pieces designed for Apple enthusiasts who want to own a piece of Apple's history.<br/>
<br/>
The &#36;400 <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/iphone-1st-generation">GRID 1</a> is perhaps GRID Studio's most iconic offering, featuring the original Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from 2007. The GRID 1 includes all of the components of the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, complete with labeling and interesting facts like all of GRID's pieces. The original &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s unmistakable housing is displayed next to the button, headphone socket, speaker, logic board, ear piece, and other components, and it's particularly interesting because it was before the days when Apple started making its own chips.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid%C2%AE4s">GRID 4S</a> is an affordable way to get a piece of GRID Studio's art, as it's on sale for &#36;99 this week. The GRID 4S was the final &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that was introduced while Steve Jobs was still alive, and the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> launched without Jobs. The "S" stood for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, and it was the first &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that included the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; personal assistant.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/grid-studio-iphone-4S.jpg" alt="" width="2959" height="1664" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952965" /><br/>
For Mac fans, the &#36;600 <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/products/grid-macbook-air-1st-generation">GRID MacBook Air</a> showcases the first-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> that Apple released, and it is one of GRID Studio's larger pieces at 30 inches by 18.5 inches. At the time, the 2008 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; was marketed world's thinnest notebook computer, and it is definitely one of Apple's most well-known later-stage Macs.<br/>
<br/>
The GRID &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has the machine's display at the top, followed by all of the interior components, and then the keyboard and trackpad combo. The hard drive, fan, network card, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> components are all neatly displayed, and it's a fun look at some vintage components that Apple has long since abandoned.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/grid-studio-macbook-air.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952966" /><br/>
We have an 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; for one <em>MacRumors</em> reader. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/XPT0j/grid-studio-giveaway" rel="nofollow">GRID Studio Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (May 31) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on June 7. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after June 7 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/macrumors-giveaway-grid-studio-ipad-pro/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPad Pro From GRID Studio</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-ipad-pro-from-grid-studio.2427835/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit 10th Gen iPad and M2 iPad Air, Plus Sonos and Anker Discounts</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-31-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-10th-gen-ipad-and-m2-ipad-air-plus-sonos-and-anker-discounts.2427832/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:34:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-31-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some of the best deals of the last week included steep markdowns on Apple-related accessories from companies like Sonos and Anker, but you'll also find discounts on a number of Apple products. This includes new record low prices on the 10th generation iPad and M2 iPad Air, and a sale on the Apple Watch Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0005.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-847995" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipad-pink-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952909" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;49 off the 10th gen iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The best iPad deal we tracked this week was on the 10th generation iPad, which dropped down to just &#36;299.99 for the 64GB Wi-Fi model, from &#36;349.00. These iPads saw their prices cut by &#36;100 earlier in the month, and deals have been coming in fast ever since those price cuts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/sonos-pink-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952908" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to 25% off Sonos products</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 25% OFF</div>Sonos Home Theater Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sonos began its Father's Day sale this week, offering up to 25 percent off select home theater equipment during the event. You'll find deals on the company's most popular devices including the Arc soundbar, Move 2 speaker, Sub (Gen 3) Subwoofer, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-pink-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952907" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on popular accessories from Anker and Eufy</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/memorial-day-deals-2024/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Anker had quite a few discounts as part of its Memorial Day sale earlier this week, and many are still available right now. One highlight of the sale is the best price we've ever seen on the popular <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a>, available for &#36;94.99 for Prime members and with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/memorial-day-deals-2024/">In our original article</a>, you'll also find sales on MagSafe-compatible accessories, Bluetooth speakers, and Eufy's Bluetooth trackers.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;64.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;34.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1716560863385">MagGo Power Bank</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.RULOQRFTA7IW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.RULOQRFTA7IW_1716560980966">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;89.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;184.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659902126">SmartTrack Link 1-Pack</a> - &#36;15.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659917907">SmartTrack Link 2-Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727">SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipad-air-new-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952906" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;80 off the new iPad Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J617D7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/80-off-the-m2-ipad-air/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J617D7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;569.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;754.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon continues to have the best discounts on the new 11-inch and 13-inch M2 iPad Air, with up to &#36;80 in savings on these tablets. A few of these are dwindling in stock as we head into the weekend, so be sure to shop soon if you want to save on Apple's latest iPad Air.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-ultra-pink-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952905" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;85 off the Apple Watch Ultra 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, this week saw Amazon expand its sale on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 with a few new models getting an &#36;85 discount. This is a solid second-best price on the high-end wearable, and only Amazon has the deal.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-31-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Record Low Prices Hit 10th Gen iPad and M2 iPad Air, Plus Sonos and Anker Discounts</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-record-low-prices-hit-10th-gen-ipad-and-m2-ipad-air-plus-sonos-and-anker-discounts.2427832/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: New iOS 18 Rumors Ahead of WWDC 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-18-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-18-rumors-ahead-of-wwdc-2024.2427829/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:18:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-18-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/new-ios-18-leaks-rumors-ahead-of-wwdc-2024/id1602394741?i=1000657420444">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss some of the latest rumors about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, including deeper <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> customization, AI-generated emojis, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/G6-3eNxaCNI?si=aH34d4pRK3bz5vAO" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
With &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is expected to undergo a substantial overhaul with improved natural language processing, enabling more conversational interactions and proactive intelligence. The assistant will apparently understand and perform more complex tasks within apps. These tasks range from moving notes between folders and deleting emails to summarizing articles and recent notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Spotlight search will also allegedly see similar enhancements, integrating deeper with system-wide information to provide more intelligent and relevant results. In Messages, AI will suggest responses and create custom emojis based on message content. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app will incorporate AI-powered retouching tools and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> will offer auto-generated playlists and smoother song transitions.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is also expected to introduce a more customizable &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj;. Users will have the freedom to place app icons anywhere on the grid and change app icon colors.<br/>
<br/>
Safari is expected to gain an Intelligent Search option, summarizing key topics and phrases on web pages, and a new Web Eraser tool, which allows users to remove unwanted portions of websites. The Calculator app will be redesigned to include recent calculations and better unit conversion tools, becoming a universal app for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> will introduce custom routes and topographic maps, enhancing navigation and outdoor activities.<br/>
<br/>
Accessibility is another focus area for &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; with new features like Eye Tracking, which uses the front-facing camera to navigate the interface, and Vehicle Motion Cues, designed to reduce motion sickness. Music Haptics will provide tactile feedback in sync with music, and Vocal Shortcuts will enable users to assign custom phrases for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to execute complex tasks.<br/>
<br/>
The adoption of the Rich Communication Services (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>) standard should improve messaging between iPhones and Android devices with support for higher resolution photos, audio messages, typing indicators, read receipts, and improved group chat functionality. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is expected to be compatible with all iPhones that support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, including models as old as the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS. However, iPadOS 18 may drop support for older models such as the first-generation 10.5-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and the second-generation 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-rumor/">latest rumors</a> about an all new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 "Slim" model, and the newly announced Sonos Ace over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-18-rumors/">The MacRumors Show: New iOS 18 Rumors Ahead of WWDC 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-new-ios-18-rumors-ahead-of-wwdc-2024.2427829/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Exclusive: iOS 18 to Add Text Effects to iMessage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-imessage-text-effects/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/exclusive-ios-18-to-add-text-effects-to-imessage.2427827/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 09:17:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-imessage-text-effects/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to add a new text effects feature to the Messages app on iOS 18, according to multiple sources familiar with the matter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
While it is already possible to send iMessages with bubble effects or full-screen effects, such as invisible ink or confetti, the text effects would allow you to animate individual words within a message. With the Messages app <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">set to gain RCS support</a> on iOS 18, it is possible the text effects will also work with green bubbles.<br/>
<br/>
Our hope is that Apple will also add bold, italics, and underline formatting options alongside the text effects, but we have not confirmed that possibility.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the text effects and RCS support, the Messages app on iOS 18 will reportedly gain an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">AI-powered autocompletion tool</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As a refresher, RCS support will provide an improved messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices compared to the current SMS standard. Just like iMessage, RCS features higher-resolution photos and videos, audio messages, typing indicators, read receipts, the ability to send messages over a Wi-Fi network, and better functionality for group chats.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 is set to be unveiled during the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>, and the first beta should be made available to members of the Apple Developer Program immediately after the presentation. The first public beta of iOS 18 will likely follow in July, and the update should be widely released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-imessage-text-effects/">Exclusive: iOS 18 to Add Text Effects to iMessage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/exclusive-ios-18-to-add-text-effects-to-imessage.2427827/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Two Weeks With the M4 iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/two-week-review-m4-ipad-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-m4-ipad-pro.2427824/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 08:43:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/two-week-review-m4-ipad-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been just over two weeks since the M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> launched, which means it's time for a longer term review of the updated OLED display, AI-focused processor, super thin design, and new accessories that include the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro and Magic Keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qMjlq2XeWNQ?si=loJUAJ9xOnXbM2O8" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The design of the new &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is probably the best overall feature, and the drop in weight and thickness makes a difference whether you're traveling or just using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> around the house. At 5.1mm, the 13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is Apple's thinnest device to date, and a tablet of this size and thickness continues to be impressive. Two weeks on, there's no hint of a "bendgate" thanks to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/14/ipad-pro-structural-design-avoid-bendgate/">the reinforced rib</a> that Apple included under the hood. There's an argument to be made that some people would have preferred a bigger battery to a slimmer design, of course.<br/>
<br/>
Apple moved the front camera to the landscape side of the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, and it's a small but notable change. If you use your &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; with a keyboard in landscape orientation but have had to awkwardly turn it to portrait mode for a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> call, this is a tweak you'll appreciate. It's much more natural than treating the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; like a giant <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s OLED display has no competition. It is by far the best display that Apple has introduced in an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and you won't find a better tablet display available from competing products, either. Apple used tandem OLED technology (basically stacking two OLED displays on top of each other), and the brightness and contrast are unparalleled. Movies look amazing, the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; does well in bright lighting, and the HDR makes images pop.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to the prior-generation &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with mini-LED display, the OLED display is better, but not so much so that it's worth upgrading for that alone. Coming from an LCD, though, the difference is much more notable.<br/>
<br/>
The last &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip is incredibly fast, and the M4 is even quicker, based on benchmarks. You're not going to find much that's going to max out the M4 processor in day to day usage, but you'll see bigger numbers on benchmarking tests comparing the M4 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; to the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;. Editing videos and creating songs in Final Cut Pro and Logic Pro is super fast with the M4, but it was also super fast with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;. Maybe the M4 chip will shine when iPadOS 18 is updated with a slew of new AI features, but for now, it's overkill.<br/>
<br/>
Apple nixed both the Ultra Wide camera and mmWave 5G in this version of the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, and most people probably won't miss these features. Whether a 13-inch tablet needs any kind of rear camera is up in the air, and mmWave 5G speeds are still fairly limited in availability. Sub 6GHz 5G remains, and that's plenty fast enough for downloads, watching streaming content, and playing games.<br/>
<br/>
As for accessories, the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro is basically the same as the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2 but with a couple new tricks. You can squeeze to bring up menus so you don't need to go hunting for settings to do things like change line thickness or color, and there's a barrel roll feature that basically does things like vary line thickness when tilting the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; so it behaves more like a real writing or drawing tool. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> might be the most useful addition so you can track down the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; if it goes missing, and Haptic Feedback is also nice to have.<br/>
<br/>
The Magic Keyboard is way more Mac like thanks to that larger glass trackpad and the aluminum palm rest. The trackpad is more pleasant to use than before, and the function keys are also a big plus for controlling media, changing screen brightness, and more without having to dig into the Settings app or Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
Unsurprisingly, the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; is without a doubt Apple's best &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and it's probably the best tablet on the market. The major downside is the price, with the 11-inch model starting at &#36;999 and the 13-inch model starting at &#36;1299. Those are Mac prices, and while the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s hardware is worth it, it's a lot to pay for the limitations that you're stuck with when using iPadOS. There are workflows out there that work with a tablet, but many people aren't going to be able to replace a Mac with an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
You also have to shell out for the 1TB+ &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; if you want maximum performance, as the 1TB and 2TB models have an extra CPU core (10 cores vs. 9 cores) and 16GB RAM instead of 8GB.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/two-week-review-m4-ipad-pro/">Review: Two Weeks With the M4 iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-two-weeks-with-the-m4-ipad-pro.2427824/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: iOS 18 to Feature &#039;Updates&#039; to Control Center</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-control-center-updates-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-ios-18-to-feature-updates-to-control-center.2427819/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 08:27:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-control-center-updates-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Control Center</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iOS 18 update for the iPhone will include unspecified "updates" to Control Center, according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1796399911526920509"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-18-Control-Center-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952914" /><br/>
If that sounds familiar, it is because Control Center was rumored to be revamped on <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2021/04/07/ios-15-control-center-touch-id-rumor/">both iOS 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/05/ios-17-control-center-changes-rumor/">iOS 17</a>, but neither update ended up introducing any significant changes to the feature, which provides quick access to system functions like Wi-Fi, display brightness, volume, and more. However, both of those rumors proved to be from unreliable sources for Apple leaks, whereas Gurman is a more reputable source.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> has learned that Apple has internally tested a redesigned Control Center for iOS 18, but we cannot confirm if these changes have been finalized.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will unveil iOS 18 during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>, and the first beta should be made available to members of the Apple Developer Program immediately after the presentation. The first public beta of iOS 18 will likely follow in July, and the update should be widely released to all users with a compatible iPhone in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/control-center/">Control Center</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-control-center-updates-rumor/">Gurman: iOS 18 to Feature &#039;Updates&#039; to Control Center</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-ios-18-to-feature-updates-to-control-center.2427819/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro International Launch Likely Scheduled for July</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-vision-pro-international-launch-likely-july/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-international-launch-likely-scheduled-for-july.2427811/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 06:53:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-vision-pro-international-launch-likely-july/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The international launch of Apple's Vision Pro headset could finally occur in July, just over six months after the device was released in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Vision-Pro-Demo.jpeg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-933882" /><br/>
A source familiar with the matter told <em>MacRumors</em> that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> is now scheduled to launch internationally in July. Separately, <em>MacRumors</em> is aware that some Apple Stores in the UK recently received large deliveries on pallets, believed to be couches designed for Vision Pro demos, that staff are not yet allowed to open. Apple Retail Managers in the UK have been told to begin the process of planning to transition the Avenues to facilitate Vision Pro accessories. Further refreshes of in-store visuals are also planned for July.<br/>
<br/>
The international launch of the Vision Pro is likely to fall in the third or fourth week of July. Given this timing, there is a chance that Apple will confirm the date at its WWDC keynote on June 10.<br/>
<br/>
This time frame is later than anticipated by many analysts, such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, who said that Apple was highly likely to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">launch the Vision Pro internationally</a> before WWDC to drive interest in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2. The United Kingdom, Canada, and China are rumored to be the first markets to receive the product outside the United States.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/apple-vision-pro-international-launch-likely-july/">Apple Vision Pro International Launch Likely Scheduled for July</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-international-launch-likely-scheduled-for-july.2427811/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>More Advanced AI Siri Functionality Not Coming to iOS 18 Until 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-advanced-ai-siri-functionality-not-coming-to-ios-18-until-2025.2427773/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:29:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Siri</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a major AI overhaul for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-30/apple-ios-18-siri-ai-update-will-let-users-control-features-in-apps-with-voice"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> says that the update will let &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; control all individual features in apps for the first time, expanding the range of functions the personal assistant can perform.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do things like open specific documents, move a note from one folder to another, delete an email, summarize an article, email a web link, and open a particular news site in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>. Apple plans to use AI to analyze what people are doing on their devices, automatically enabling &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features.<br/>
<br/>
To make this happen, Apple engineers had to rearchitect &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s underlying software with large language models or LLMs, which is also the technology that's been used for chatbots like ChatGPT. Apple has been working on a deal with OpenAI to integrate OpenAI's ChatGPT technology into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, and it is also in talks with Google about incorporating Gemini, but &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality likely relies on Apple's own LLM work.<br/>
<br/>
At launch, the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality will be limited to Apple apps, and &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will only be able to respond to one command at a time. Eventually, Apple wants &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to be able to respond to multiple commands, such as capturing a photo and then sending it to someone in a message.<br/>
<br/>
While the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features will be introduced at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a>, Apple reportedly does not plan to launch them in September when &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; sees an initial release. Instead, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be overhauled in a future &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; update that's set to be introduced in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Basic AI tasks in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will be processed on device, but more advanced capabilities will rely on Apple's cloud servers. Gurman previously said that Apple would power all of the initial &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; features on-device without relying on cloud technology in order to preserve privacy, but rumors have shifted in recent weeks. Part of Apple's new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; technology will include code for determining whether a request can be processed on device or requires Apple's servers. On-device &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; AI capabilities will largely require an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> or later to work, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> or later for iPadOS 18 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/29/ios-18-cloud-ai-features-privacy-protections/">The Information</a></em>, Apple's AI servers will be powered by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Ultra and M4 chips, with Apple planning to use the Secure Enclave to "to help isolate the data being processed on its servers so that it can't be seen by the wider system or Apple." Gurman says that Apple will also provide customers with an "intelligent report" that explains how information is kept safe.<br/>
<br/>
We'll hear all about the AI functionality coming to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; in just over 10 days. &zwnj;WWDC 2024&zwnj; is set to begin on Monday, June 10.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/">More Advanced AI Siri Functionality Not Coming to iOS 18 Until 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-advanced-ai-siri-functionality-not-coming-to-ios-18-until-2025.2427773/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spatial Puzzle Game &#039;Where Cards Fall&#039; Now Available on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spatial-puzzle-game-where-cards-fall-now-available-on-apple-vision-pro.2427771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 13:09:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing to add to its lineup of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> games on the Vision Pro, today adding puzzle game <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/where-cards-fall/id1466331487?platform=vision">Where Cards Fall</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/where-cards-fall-apple-arcade.jpg" alt="" width="1286" height="724" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952862" /><br/>
Where Cards Fall has previously been available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, and Mac, and it won an Apple Design Award back in 2020. A dreamlike spatial puzzle game, Where Cards Fall is a coming-of-age story that tasks players with building houses of cards to bring memories to life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that the game features full 3D depth and immersion, and players can use tactile, accessible controls designed specifically for the Vision Pro. There are more than 50 puzzles to solve using imagination and strategic thinking.<br/>
<br/>
Where Cards Fall is <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-arcade/">part of Apple Arcade</a>, which is priced at &#36;6.99 per month and is also available with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One</a> subscription bundle. For the monthly price, up to six people that are part of a family group can access games, and there are more than 200 titles available. New subscribers can get a three-month trial with the purchase of an Apple device or a one-month trial.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/where-cards-fall-vision-pro/">Spatial Puzzle Game &#039;Where Cards Fall&#039; Now Available on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spatial-puzzle-game-where-cards-fall-now-available-on-apple-vision-pro.2427771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares New Ads Promoting Apple Card</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-ads-promoting-apple-card.2427761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:40:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a trio of short ads designed to promote the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a>, which is Apple's credit card that continues to be limited to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
The Sock, Sweater, and Ladder spots all highlight different &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; features. Sock focuses on the Daily Cash back reward, Sweater demonstrates the option to see past purchases, and Ladder shows the ease of paying an &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; balance through the Wallet app.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Sweater Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ynwBRLN3bms" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Sock Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Jk_29kXLboc" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Card Ladder Apple" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q04S_NkRHGw" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
All three ads feature the tagline "Reboot your credit card" and link to <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-card/">the Apple Card website</a> so that potential customers can get more information.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; has been available in the U.S. since 2019, and it integrates with the Wallet app for easy purchase management. Daily Cash back, which is delivered same-day, is one of the key features. Customers get one percent cash back from standard physical card purchases, two percent for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> purchases, and three percent cash back at select partner stores and Apple retail locations.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-shares-new-apple-card-ads/">Apple Shares New Ads Promoting Apple Card</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-new-ads-promoting-apple-card.2427761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for &#36;714.00 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-714-00-on-amazon.2427758/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 10:24:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has a low price on three models of the Apple Watch Ultra 2, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;714.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. Right now only Amazon has this sale, and it does not require a coupon in order to see the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-watch-ultra-2-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939712" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Models on sale at this price include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Green/Grey Trail Loop (S/M)</a>, the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX94FRH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Blue/Black Trail Loop (S/M)</a>, and the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8Z6W4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Indigo Alpine Loop (Small)</a>. Stock on the Blue/Black Trail Loop has been dwindling this afternoon, but the other two models appear well stocked as of writing.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Although we tracked a steeper discount on the Apple Watch Ultra 2 back in March, that sale was a bit of a fluke and only ever appeared for one model and has never returned. This makes today's discounts at Amazon solid second-best prices on the high-end wearable, and they can be delivered as soon as this weekend for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
There are a few other Apple Watch deals going on right now for anyone interested in cheaper models. You can get the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> and the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-watch-ultra-2-for-714/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Available for &#36;714.00 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-available-for-714-00-on-amazon.2427758/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Brings Tap to Pay on iPhone to Italy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy.2427755/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 09:35:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Italy</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Tap to Pay on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.apple.com/it/newsroom/2024/05/apple-introduces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-italy/">today launched in Italy</a>, allowing individual sellers, major retailers, and small businesses to use the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; as a contactless payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/tap-to-pay-iphone-italy.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952842" /><br/>
Retailers are able to take advantage of the NFC chip in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to accept credit and debit card payments, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> and other digital payment options. Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does not require additional hardware and it replaces hardware-based payment systems such as the Square Reader.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available to payment platforms and payment app developers in Italy. Adyen, myPOS, Nexi, Revolut, Stripe, SumUp, and Viva are all supporting Tap to Pay, and Fabrick, Numia, and Sella will also be adding Tap to Pay integration in the near future. Starting today, Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can be used in all Apple retail stores in Italy as well.<br/>
<blockquote>"Tap to Pay on iPhone has revolutionized the checkout experience in many types of businesses in Europe and other countries, and we are happy to partner with payment platforms to support merchants in Italy by offering them a simple, secure and private way to accept contactless payments via iPhone and a partner-enabled iOS app, without the need for additional devices," said Jennifer Bailey, Vice President of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet at Apple. "Over 4.3 million small and medium-sized companies in Italy have long played a key role in the country's economy and, together with payment platforms, developers and developers of apps and payment networks, we are making it easier than ever for Italian businesses of all sizes to accept contactless payments and continue to grow their business."</blockquote><br/>
When a customer makes a purchase, a merchant that supports Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; can accept payment by having the customer bring their credit card, debit card, prepaid card, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple Watch, or other digital wallet close to the merchant's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. The transaction is completed through NFC, with processing done using the Secure Element for security purposes.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; requires an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS or newer model, and a contactless card or device also needed. Contactless cards from American Express, Global Discover Network, Diners, Mastercard, and Visa will work.<br/>
<br/>
Italy is the 11th country where Tap to Pay on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is available. Apple previously rolled out the feature in the United States, United Kingdom, Canada, Australia, Japan, the Netherlands, Brazil, France, Taiwan, and Ukraine.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/italy/">Italy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy/">Apple Brings Tap to Pay on iPhone to Italy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-brings-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-to-italy.2427755/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Satechi Launches Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station.2427745/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Satechi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Satechi today announced the launch of its latest Mac accessory, the <a href="https://satechi.net/products/thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station">Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</a>. The Docking Station uses DisplayLink software technology to allow a Mac to connect to up to four external monitors, plus it offers 96W power delivery and Thunderbolt 4 transfer speeds.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/satechi-thunderbolt-dock.jpg" alt="" width="1579" height="888" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952797" /><br/>
Made from a space gray aluminum that is meant to match Apple devices, the hub supports up to four extended monitors at 4K/60Hz resolution, or one display at 8K/60Hz. With four displays, two can be connected through Thunderbolt 4 and two through HDMI. Satechi says that this feature is designed to address the single display limit of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a>, and M3 chips. &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, and M3 MacBook Pro models support up to three displays with Satechi's dock, while the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> supports four when in clamshell mode. Machines with Pro and Max chips support up to four displays through the hub.<br/>
<br/>
The hub provides 96W power delivery to the host machine, which is enough to charge even the 16-inch MacBook Pro. Each of the three Thunderbolt 4 downstream ports also offer 15W for charging iPhones, Apple Watches, and other accessories, with two ports able to be used at one time for charging purposes. The Thunderbolt 4 ports facilitate data transfers at speeds up to 40Gb/s, and there are two USB-A ports that support transfer speeds up to 10Gb/s. a UHS-II SD card reader is available as well, and it is capable of transferring up to 312MB/s.<br/>
<br/>
Satechi says the dock supports daisy-chaining up to six devices, providing 32Gb/s native PCIe support for external GPUs and Thunderbolt-based storage devices.<br/>
<br/>
The Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station can be <a href="https://satechi.net/products/thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station">purchased from the Satechi website</a> for &#36;300.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/satechi/">Satechi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/satechi-multi-display-docking-station/">Satechi Launches Thunderbolt 4 Multi-Display Docking Station</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/satechi-launches-thunderbolt-4-multi-display-docking-station.2427745/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Sonos Kicks Off Rare Sale With Up to 25% Off Popular Audio Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-kicks-off-rare-sale-with-up-to-25-off-popular-audio-accessories.2427743/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 07:02:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Sonos today has begun its <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Father's Day sale</a>, offering steep discounts on select home theater audio equipment. This includes record low prices on the Sonos Arc soundbar (&#36;719), as well as various discounted bundles, all of which are rare deals we haven't tracked since earlier in the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/sonos-deals-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934823" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Sonos. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This sale has a good balance between individual Sonos products and bundles that should help elevate your home theater setup with various soundbars, subwoofers, and speakers. Highlights of the event include the <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Sonos Arc for &#36;719</a> (&#36;180 off) and <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sonos Sub Gen 3 for &#36;639</a> (&#36;160 off), which are rarely discounted outside of holiday events like this one. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO 25% OFF</div>Sonos Home Theater Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We've accumulated a few of the devices in the sale below, but be sure to <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">browse this landing page</a> on the Sonos website for everything being discounted.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Speakers and Soundbars</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/roam-sl">Roam SL Portable Speaker</a> - &#36;127, down from &#36;159</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-100">Era 100 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;199, down from &#36;249</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/move-2">Move 2 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;336, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/era-300">Era 300 Smart Speaker</a> - &#36;359, down from &#36;449</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/beam">Beam (Gen 2) Soundbar</a> - &#36;399, down from &#36;499</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/sub">Sub (Gen 3) Subwoofer</a> - &#36;639, down from &#36;799</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc">Arc Soundbar</a> - &#36;719, down from &#36;899</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Bundles</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/arc-mount-set">Arc + Wall Mount Bundle</a> - &#36;798, down from &#36;978</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/multiroom-entertainment-set-arc-and-move-2">Arc + Move 2 Speaker Bundle</a> - &#36;1,055, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/personal-entertainment-set-sonos-ace-arc">Arc + Sonos Ace Headphones Bundle</a> - &#36;1,168, down from &#36;1,348</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/3-1-entertainment-set-beam-sub">Beam + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,038, down from &#36;1,298</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/surround-set-arc-era-100-pair">Arc + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,117, down from &#36;1,397</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/entertainment-set-arc-sub">Arc + Sub Bundle</a> - &#36;1,358, down from &#36;1,698</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/premium-immersive-set-beam-sub-era-100-pair">Beam + Sub + 2x Era 100 Speakers Bundle</a> - &#36;1,436, down from &#36;1,796</li></ul> Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/sonos-rare-discounts/">Sonos Kicks Off Rare Sale With Up to 25% Off Popular Audio Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonos-kicks-off-rare-sale-with-up-to-25-off-popular-audio-accessories.2427743/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Logitech Expands &#039;Designed for Mac&#039; Range With New Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range-with-new-accessories.2427739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 06:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Logitech</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Logitech today introduced a new lineup of Mac accessories, including the latest MX series keyboards and mice, as well as an ergonomic keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Wave-Keys-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951949" /><br/>
The new range comprises the MX Keys S for Mac, MX Keys S Combo for Mac, MX Anywhere 3S for Mac, MX Keys Mini for Mac in Space Gray, and the Ergo Wave Keys for Mac. The products offer dedicated macOS keyboard layouts and colors that complement Apple hardware. <br/>
<br/>
The MX Keys S for Mac features comfortable, precise typing with smart illumination that adjusts to ambient light and hand proximity. The keyboard also includes Smart Actions via the Logi Options+ app, enabling users to automate repetitive tasks and streamline their workflows. The MX Keys S can connect to three different Apple devices simultaneously, allowing for easy switching with the press of a button. It is available in Space Gray and Pale Gray, and incorporates post-consumer recycled plastic in its construction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Keys-S-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951948" /><br/>
The MX Keys S Combo for Mac includes the MX Keys S keyboard, MX Master 3S for Mac mouse, and an MX Palm Rest, designed to provide an integrated solution for high-performance Mac users. The mouse features quiet clicks, a high-precision 8K DPI sensor, and the MagSpeed Electromagnetic wheel for fast, precise scrolling. Both the keyboard and mouse come with customizable options via the Logi Options+ app, allowing for personalized shortcuts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Anywhere-3S-for-Mac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951946" /><br/>
The MX Anywhere 3S for Mac is a compact mouse designed for portability and high performance. It features ultra-fast scrolling, quiet clicks, and an advanced 8K DPI tracking sensor that works on virtually any surface, including glass. The mouse is built to withstand the rigors of mobile work and includes a USB-C quick charging feature, providing up to 70 days of use on a full charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/MX-Keys-Mini-for-Mac-Space-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-951947" /><br/>
The MX Keys Mini for Mac is a minimalist keyboard optimized for Mac users, now available in Space Gray to match Apple devices. It offers smart illumination, precise typing, and software customization that allows users to create app-specific profiles and shortcuts. This keyboard is designed to improve ergonomics by aligning the shoulders and allowing the mouse to be placed closer to the keyboard.<br/>
<br/>
Rounding out the new lineup is the Ergo Wave Keys for Mac, Logitech's first ergonomic keyboard specifically designed for Mac users. It features a unique wave design and a cushioned palm rest, developed by the Logi Ergo Lab to provide day-long comfort. The keyboard is said to promote better posture and reduces strain on the wrists.<br/>
<br/>
Logitech's new Mac accessories will be available globally this month <a href="http://www.logitech.com">via its website</a> and other retailers. The MX Keys S for Mac sells for &#36;109.99, the MX Keys S Combo for Mac costs &#36;199.99, the MX Anywhere 3S for Mac is priced at &#36;79.99, the MX Keys Mini for Mac costs &#36;99.99, and the Wave Keys for Mac costs &#36;59.99.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/logitech/">Logitech</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range/">Logitech Expands &#039;Designed for Mac&#039; Range With New Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/logitech-expands-designed-for-mac-range-with-new-accessories.2427739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>More Details About iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Revealed</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed.2427731/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 05:00:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>AppleInsider</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to introduce new AI features including Smart Replies for messages and a generative retouch tool for photos in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, a new report claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-947754" /><br/>
A new article from <em><a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/05/30/ios-18-project-greymatter-will-use-ai-to-summarize-notifications-articles-and-much-more">AppleInsider</a></em> today revealed some further detail about several of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;'s widely anticipated AI features. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is rumored to receive some major upgrades including:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li><strong>Improved Responses</strong>: Significantly updated response generation capabilities with a new smart response framework that takes into account entities such as people, companies, calendar events, locations, dates, and more.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Enhanced Voices</strong>: "More natural" voices with better text-to-speech functionality.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Cross-Device Media Controls</strong>: Use &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on one device to control playback on another, such as via the Apple Watch for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. This feature is not expected to arrive until later in 2024.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Catch Up</strong>: Users can request an overview of their recent notifications via &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
A range of other AI-powered features are also in the works for specific apps in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Smart Replies</strong>: Allows users to reply to messages and emails with automatically generated text responses.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Transcription and Summarization</strong>: New AI tools for the Notes app allowing users to edit audio in the app, transcribe audio, and summarize text.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Math Notes</strong>: Support for proper mathematical notation in the Notes app with Calculator app integation. Math Notes will allow the Notes app to recognise mathematical equations and come up with solutions and generate graphs.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Keyboard Math Predictions</strong>: Input enhancements for mathematics enabling the completion of complex mathematical expressions when recognised as part of text input, similar to predictive text or inline text completion.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Clean Up</strong>: Remove objects from photos using generative AI. This tool will replace Apple's current "Retouch" feature.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>Generative Playground</strong>: Application that uses generative AI to create and edit images with an iMessage app extension. It is currently designed for Apple's internal test environments only, but indicates that there are plans to allow users to generate images and then share them via iMessage. This could be related to rumored plans to allow users to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">generate custom emojis</a>.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2 will also apparently gain an improved predictive text model thanks to integration with Apple's Transformer LM, as well as a redesigned Voice Commands UI. Updates to the Calendar and Freeform apps, as well as System Settings for macOS, are also said to be planned. Apple's selection of new AI features are expected to be previewed during the company's WWDC keynote on June 10. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/appleinsider-com/">AppleInsider</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed/">More Details About iOS 18&#039;s AI Features Revealed</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/more-details-about-ios-18s-ai-features-revealed.2427731/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
