<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2024 03:02:38 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.2: Everything You Should Know About Image Playground</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-everything-you-should-know-about-image-playground.2440974/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 15:35:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground&#038;post_date=1729906551/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Image Playground</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18.2 includes the first image generation technologies that are coming to Apple Intelligence, including Image Playground. Image Playground is Apple's dedicated image creation app that can build cartoon-like pictures based on text descriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/image-playground-ios-18-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972926" /><br/>
This guide highlights everything that you need to know about Image Playground, from its limitations to where you can use it, and we'll provide updates as Image Playground evolves.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="the_image_playground_app">The Image Playground App</h2><br/>
Updating to iOS 18.2, iPadOS 18.2, or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.2 adds a "Playground" app to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or desktop, denoted by an icon featuring a white cat/dog/bear creature in a 3D style.<br/>
<br/>
Tapping into the app brings up a splash screen with instructions on how to use Image Playground, but it's straightforward. There's a text bar at the bottom that instructs you to "Describe an image."<br/>
<br/>
As soon as you type in a word or phrase, Image Playground starts working on generating an image for you. You can essentially type in anything, like "crocodile wearing a tutu" or "skunk hula hooping on top of an elephant."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-crocodile.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972927" /><br/>
You can modify the result with additional word descriptions, or use one of Apple's suggestions. You'll get several possible images for each description, and you can swipe through them to choose what you want. You can add and remove words and phrases until you refine the generated image to exactly what you want.<br/>
<br/>
Image Playground is very much in beta right now, so Apple is soliciting feedback. There are thumbs up and thumbs down icons you can use to submit feedback. Thumbs up doesn't require additional input, but thumbs down goes to an interface where you can select what's wrong with an image and provide additional written details.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-feedback.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972928" /><br/>
After you've created your ideal image, you can tap on the Done button to save it to your Image Playground library. Items saved in the Image Playground library can be edited again later, deleted, or shared with the standard Share Sheet. There are also built-in tools for copying, sharing, or saving an image during the creation process.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="personalized_images_based_on_people">Personalized Images Based on People</h3><br/>
You can start an Image Playground creation with a person. People that are saved in your People album in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app will show up as an option (yourself included), and you can select a specific photo of a person to use as the base for a new image.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-person.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972929" /><br/>
Each photo of a person will look different because Image Playground is pulling in the specific angle, lighting, and look of a particular image rather than of an aggregate, so you can swipe through to see which image of a person looks the most like them when converted to an animated form.<br/>
<br/>
You are limited to individuals that are saved to your People album, so AI isn't going to understand if you ask for an image of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> or Taylor Swift, but for this use case, you can import a photo.<br/>
<br/>
You can also create a generic look to use as a base using the built-in "Appearance" option in the Person interface. That setting lets you select a skin tone and feature set, which can be refined further with image descriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="image_playground_suggestions">Image Playground Suggestions</h3><br/>
If you don't know where to start with an image creation or you need inspiration for details, Apple has a range of suggestions that you can tap to add to your image.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Image-Playground-Preset-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955046" /><br/>
There are themes like adventure, disco, summer, party, sunset, and fantasy, along with places like city, space, desert, park, prairie, and forest. Apple suggests costumes that include artist, chef, hiker, mage, robot, and superhero, and there are accessories you can select from like sunglasses, beanie, top hat, party hat, and flower crown.<br/>
<br/>
These are just a jumping off point, of course, and you can choose any location or setting and add any objects and accessories you want using text descriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/image-playground-cat.jpg" alt="" width="1024" height="1024" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972925" /><br/>
Suggestions in the Image Playground app aren't contextual, but when you use Image Playground in Messages, you might see suggestions based on what you've been talking about.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="animation_style">Animation Style</h3><br/>
You can't make photorealistic images with Image Playground, and that's by design. Apple doesn't want to generate images that can fool someone, so you're limited to two styles: Animation and Illustration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-styles.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972930" /><br/>
Animation is a 3D-looking style that looks like something out of a Pixar movie, while Illustration is a flatter, 2D image that's simpler.<br/>
<br/>
When Image Playground was first announced in June 2024, Apple said there would be three styles, including Animation, Illustration, and Sketch. It's not clear if sketch is still planned and will be coming at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="base_an_image_on_a_photo">Base an Image on a Photo</h3><br/>
You can take a photo or import a photo from the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app to use as inspiration for an Image Playground creation. If you want an Image Playground image with &zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj;, using a photo is the way to go.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972934" /><br/>
Any photo works to serve as inspiration for a creation, and you can use a photo for the main subject of an image or for the background.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_in_messages">Image Playground in Messages</h2><br/>
You can create images in the Image Playground app and share them in Messages, but you can also do it directly from the Messages app. In a conversation, tap on the "+" button and then choose Image Playground from the list.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960704" /><br/>
The Messages mini app works like the full app. Just type in a description of an image and use the same steps to get it to where you want it. When you're finished, tap on Done, and it'll show up in the send field of your conversation so you can text it to whoever you're conversing with.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="sharing_image_playground_creations">Sharing Image Playground Creations</h2><br/>
To share an Image Playground image in a text message, you can use the built-in Image Playground mini app in Messages, which is the quickest route.<br/>
<br/>
You can also go to the Image Playground library or create a new image in the app and then use the Share Sheet to AirDrop it, send it via Messages, email it, or save it to the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; or Files app. Anything you've saved to &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; can be uploaded to a social media app.<br/>
<br/>
The Share Sheet is like the Share Sheet anywhere else in iOS, so if you have an app like Instagram installed, there is a Share Sheet option to upload an Image Playground creation directly to Instagram. The same goes for other social networks that support the Share Sheet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_limitations">Image Playground Limitations</h2><br/>
Image Playground is in beta right now, and Apple says that users can see unexpected results depending on the descriptors that are used. Sometimes words that seem like they should produce a simple result end up making something unexpectedly odd, such as the banana split images below. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-banana-split.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972932" /><br/>
The AI has some limitations to be aware of, and there are also built-in guardrails that restrict the content that you can create. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="size_and_scope">Size and Scope</h2><br/>
One noticeable limitation involves Image Playground creations that use photos of people. You can only get portrait-style photos that show the top half of a person, with no option for a full-body pose. So if you wanted to generate an image of your friend Eric roller skating, it's hard to depict that activity accurately because Image Playground will only generate a chest-up image.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-playground-people-limitation.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972933" /><br/>
This limitation doesn't apply when generating images of animals and creatures, but it's an issue when you want to depict an activity that needs more than a head and shoulders.<br/>
<br/>
This also impacts images that you might want to generate with a secondary object, like a cat or another person. Image Playground doesn't always do a good job with multiple subjects in a photo at this time. The more descriptors you have, the more it struggles with this kind of thing.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="words">Words</h3><br/>
As with most image generating tools that are available, Image Playground struggles with text. Text tends to be non-sensical.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-2-image-playground-writing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972931" /><br/>
<h3 id="restricted_phrases">Restricted Phrases</h3><br/>
Apple learned some lessons from other tech companies that have introduced image generation tools, and there are plenty of built-in restrictions. When Google <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/21/google-pixel-editing-image-creation-tools/">debuted Pixel Studio</a> in August, people were able to use it to generate images with drugs, alcohol, Nazis, and more, and Apple's not allowing any of that.<br/>
<br/>
When a word isn't allowed, you'll see the following message: "Unable to use that description" with an undo button you can use to remove it.<br/>
<br/>
There are other phrases that Image Playground will kind of ignore. If you use "blood" or "bloody" for example, you'll get a red-tinted background, but no actual blood. You can't use words like murder or dead or their synonyms, and while gun and pistol are okay, AK-47, machine gun, and shotgun are not.<br/>
<br/>
Concepts that could be used to generate a political image are likewise banned. You can't add country-specific flags, or countries like United States, Mexico or Germany. Words related to drugs or drug paraphernalia don't work, and there are a lot of descriptors that Image Playground will just disregard, even if you don't get a message that it's explicitly forbidden.<br/>
<br/>
It's clear that Apple put a lot of work into preventing Image Playground from generating inappropriate images, and the company has made it clear that improvements will be made and that there's still a possibility of unexpected results during the beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="people_requirement">People Requirement</h3><br/>
When Apple Intelligence is having trouble applying a word, it often requires you to select a person to add to your image, even if you didn't want to add a person. It can be frustrating, and you'll need to add the person, change your phrasing, and remove the person to get to what you really meant. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="copyright">Copyright</h3><br/>
Likewise, Apple doesn't allow you to create images of copyrighted characters, so there won't be any option to use Image Playground to create compromising photos of Bluey and Mickey Mouse.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="security">Security</h2><br/>
Image generation for Image Playground is done on-device, so nothing that you're typing in is sent to a cloud server or shared, though it is worth noting that Apple is collecting feedback on it right now.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="availability">Availability</h2><br/>
Image Playground is only available in the iOS 18.2 beta, and the beta is limited to developers at the current time. There is no word yet on when a public beta might be released.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="waitlist">Waitlist</h3><br/>
You need to opt in to a second waitlist to get access to Image Playground and Genmoji in iOS 18.2, with Apple apparently limiting the number of people who can use the features. The wait is longer than the initial wait for opting in to Apple Intelligence, and it has taken 24+ hours in some cases.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="public_launch">Public Launch</h2><br/>
If Apple follows launch timelines from prior years, we could see an iOS 18.2 release sometime in mid-December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">iOS 18.2: Everything You Should Know About Image Playground</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-everything-you-should-know-about-image-playground.2440974/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: M2 MacBook Air Gets Massive &#36;299 Discount Alongside AirPods 4 and Apple Pencil Pro Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-25-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-m2-macbook-air-gets-massive-299-discount-alongside-airpods-4-and-apple-pencil-pro-sales.2440968/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:46:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-25-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week we saw big discounts on a few Apple devices and related accessories, including a new record low price on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. You'll also find great deals on Apple Pencil Pro, Apple Watch Series 10, AirPods 4, and more below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/best-apple-deals-hero-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959384" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-pencil-pro-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972563" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Apple's first party accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/get-the-apple-pencil-pro-for-94/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;35 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;93.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>11-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;259.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;298.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHHJXTC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>2-meter MagSafe Charger for &#36;38.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we tracked a few deals on Apple's Magic Keyboards for iPad, Apple Pencil Pro, AirTag, and the new MagSafe Charger. Some of the most notable discounts include the Apple Pencil Pro which was at &#36;94.99 and has since dropped another &#36;1 to sit just &#36;4 above its all-time low price, plus up to &#36;50 off the M4 Magic Keyboards.<br/>
<br/>
Additionally, you can find some big discounts on <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fapple-iphone-16-cases">Apple's official Silicone and Clear Cases for the iPhone 16</a> at Woot. There's a large selection of these cases down to &#36;34.99 right now, and you can take an additional &#36;10 off with the coupon code APPLEWELCOME through the end of today, Friday, October 25.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/m2-macbook-air-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972561" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;299 off M2 MacBook Air</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C2R8MP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/get-apples-m2-macbook-air-699/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C2R8MP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;699.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;949.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
One of the most notable deals of the week was on the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, available for just &#36;699.99, down from &#36;999.00, and this sale has since expanded to include more colors. Overall, this is a new record low price on the previous generation MacBook Air, and the 512GB model is seeing a similarly steep discount on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/airpods-4-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972562" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;10 off AirPods 4</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/airpods-4-drop-to-119/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7HYG1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 (ANC) for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon took &#36;10 off both models of the AirPods 4 this week, starting at &#36;119.00 for the base model without Active Noise Cancellation. Both deals are still available to purchase today, and right now only Amazon has the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-watch-series-10-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972560" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;33 off Apple Watch Series 10</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-watch-series-10-drops/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHV8NLZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;33 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (42mm GPS) for &#36;365.28</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3WKR6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 10 (46mm GPS) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon hosted a few low prices on the Apple Watch Series 10 this week, with solid markdowns on both the 42mm and 46mm GPS models still available. This includes the 42mm GPS model for the all-time low price of &#36;365.28 in Rose Gold Aluminum, down from &#36;399.00.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/samsung-week-sale-blue.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972559" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Find sitewide deals during Samsung's week-long event</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cnlVGcT3IGL">Samsung</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/samsung-week-long-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVGcT3IGL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Samsung Week Discount Event</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's new discount event features deals on TVs, smartphones, monitors and memory, wearables, appliances, and more. One of the most notable offers during this sale is a bundle deal with Samsung's TVs and monitors. When you <a href="https://howl.me/cnlV16oWQ0u">purchase select gaming monitors</a> at the same time as one of Samsung's OLED S95D TVs, you can save up to &#36;1,075 on your entire order.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Deals Newsletter</h3><br/>
Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our Deals Newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!<br/>
<br/>
<div style="text-align:center;margin-bottom:2em;"><br/>
<form action="http://macrumors.us5.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0&amp;id=eebad02bf4&amp;f_id=00fbede0f0" method="post" id="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" name="mc-embedded-subscribe-form" class="validate" target="_blank" novalidate><input type="email" value="" name="EMAIL" size="30" class="required email" id="mce-EMAIL" placeholder="Enter Email Address"/><div class="response" id="mce-error-response" style="display:none"></div><div class="response" id="mce-success-response" style="display:none"></div><div style="position: absolute; left: -5000px;"><input type="text" name="b_7d0106b433773bd0aef5828e0_eebad02bf4" tabindex="-1" value=""/></div> <input type="submit" value="Subscribe" name="subscribe" id="mc-embedded-subscribe" class="button"/></form></div><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-10-25-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: M2 MacBook Air Gets Massive &#36;299 Discount Alongside AirPods 4 and Apple Pencil Pro Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-m2-macbook-air-gets-massive-299-discount-alongside-airpods-4-and-apple-pencil-pro-sales.2440968/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Bringing Spatial Photo and Video Support to Safari for Vision Pro Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-vision-pro-safari-spatial-photo-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-spatial-photo-and-video-support-to-safari-for-vision-pro-users.2440965/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:29:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-vision-pro-safari-spatial-photo-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Vision Pro users will soon be able to view spatial photos and videos in Safari, according to <a href="https://petapixel.com/2024/10/25/apple-is-adding-spatial-photo-and-video-support-to-safari/"><em>PetaPixel</em></a>. The photography site did an interview with Apple product manager Della Huff and designer Billy Sorrentino, who shared that Apple is bringing spatial photo and spatial video support to Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionos-2-2d-spatial-photos.jpg" alt="" width="1793" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957275" /><br/>
Later this year, web developers will be able to add spatial photos and videos to their websites, which will be viewable in 3D on the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial photos and videos can be captured with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro and Pro Max, as well as all four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models and the Vision Pro itself. Note that spatial photo support for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro is coming in iOS 18.1, set to be released next week. With Vision Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a>, even existing photos can have added depth.<br/>
<br/>
As of right now, spatial photos and videos can only be viewed on Vision Pro when they're sent to you directly via Messages, email, or AirDrop, which makes it difficult to see content from other people. Browser support for spatial videos and photos will let <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users upload their content to websites where anyone with a Vision Pro can see it in 3D.<br/>
<br/>
For those without a Vision Pro, spatial photos and videos will look like standard media embeds. "Once you embedded spatial content, folks who are on Vision Pro are getting spatial and folks who are just looking at it on their laptop see it in two dimensions," Sorrentino told <em>PetaPixel</em>.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word on exactly when spatial photo and video support will be coming to Safari, but it is expected before the end of the year so it could be included in a visionOS 2.2 update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-vision-pro-safari-spatial-photo-video/">Apple Bringing Spatial Photo and Video Support to Safari for Vision Pro Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-bringing-spatial-photo-and-video-support-to-safari-for-vision-pro-users.2440965/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Journey&#039;s NOVA 3-in-1 Qi2 Charging Station Powers Up Your Devices With a Unique Minimalist Design</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/journey-nova-3-in-1-charging-station/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-journeys-nova-3-in-1-qi2-charging-station-powers-up-your-devices-with-a-unique-minimalist-design.2440963/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 11:04:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/journey-nova-3-in-1-charging-station&#038;post_date=1729890254/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Journey</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[3-in-1 charging stations capable of wirelessly powering up an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, an Apple Watch, and AirPods have been popular for years now, although most of them involve relatively straightforward and utilitarian designs. Accessory brand <a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=2017698&u=63177&m=124934&urllink=&afftrack=">Journey</a> is looking to bring a bit more design flair to the category with its new <a href="https://shrsl.com/4q4vd">NOVA 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a>, which will begin shipping next Monday, October 28.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/journey-nova-charger-parts.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972694" /><br/>
The NOVA charging station is available in Wood Grain and Sparkle Grey color options, and I've been testing out a Wood Grain model for a few days to see how it looks and performs.<br/>
<br/>
Overall it features a compact footprint with a vertically oriented design rather than a "tree-style" design used on some competing 3-in-1 chargers. The entire body is made of plastic, but the faux wood grain front can help it fit in depending on your decor. A pair of non-slip strips on the bottom of the charger help keep it in place and protect your surfaces from damage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/journey-nova-charger-devices.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972697" /><br/>
At a little over 400 grams (0.9 pounds), the NOVA is hefty enough to remain stable with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; mounted on it, yet it remains somewhat portable so it can be easily transported. It measures around 15 cm high (though an attached &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will raise the total height by a few centimeters) and has a footprint of around 8 cm by 9 cm.<br/>
<br/>
The NOVA is topped with an elevated angled surface hiding a Qi2 charging pad, allowing an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to magnetically attach and charge at up to 15 watts depending on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model. The MagSafe-compatible Qi2 standard has only recently started making its way into a broad array of products, and while Apple has already one-upped Qi2 with its new 25-watt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> charging on the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, Qi2 should still be plenty sufficient for most users.<br/>
<br/>
The phone charging surface is plain plastic with no distinct pad or graphics indicating where to place the device. Magnetic alignment makes it easy to find the right spot even without those features, so it allows for a very clean look when there's no phone on the charger.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/journey-nova-charger-rear.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972698" /><br/>
The rear of the station includes a flip-up Apple Watch charging puck that delivers fast charging on supported Apple Watch models. The flip-up feature lets you hide the puck away while not in use and protect it if you choose to toss the charging station in a bag for travel.<br/>
<br/>
The rear-mounted Apple Watch puck design means your watch won't be visible while charging on a nightstand, end table, or desk, but if you're also charging a phone in either horizontal StandBy or vertical orientation, that's likely a better option for viewing the time and other information.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, a hollow opening oriented toward the front of the charging station serves as a spot to drop a compatible AirPods case for charging. The AirPods charging spot has a grippy pad to help keep the AirPods in position, but it doesn't include magnets to help with aligning AirPods cases with that feature. Still, the placement seems fairly forgiving to me, and I didn't have any issues getting my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> to consistently charge.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/journey-nova-charger-light.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972696" /><br/>
A touch-activated light inside the opening can help you find the AirPods charging spot in the dark or even just provide a bit of light in a dark room for any other needs.<br/>
<br/>
The NOVA charging station comes with a 1.5-meter USB-C to USB-C cable to power the unit, although you'll have to provide your own power adapter. I always prefer that a power adapter be included in the box, especially for more premium priced accessories, so that's a bit of a downside here. Allowing you to provide your own adapter does offer more flexibility if you prefer to power it from a multi-port charger, a flat charger for tucking behind furniture, or other options, so just be aware of that potential additional cost. You'll want at least a 30-watt charger to be able to charge everything at full speed.<br/>
<br/>
Journey also includes an adhesive magnetic ring and alignment guide in the box, which allows you to add magnetic capabilities to older iPhones and other smartphone models that support wireless charging but not &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;/Qi2.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://shrsl.com/4q4vd">NOVA 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> is normally priced at &#36;139.99, but there's currently a 20% off pre-order discount that brings the price down to &#36;112.00. Many other 3-in-1 chargers from reputable brands with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;/Qi2 and Made for Apple Watch certification are in the &#36;120–&#36;150 range, so this is in the same ballpark. Remember that you do have to provide your own power adapter though, but the current pre-order discount brings things down enough to keep pricing competitive even with that possible additional cost.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Journey provided MacRumors with a NOVA 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station for the purposes of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Journey. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/journey/">Journey</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/journey-nova-3-in-1-charging-station/">Review: Journey&#039;s NOVA 3-in-1 Qi2 Charging Station Powers Up Your Devices With a Unique Minimalist Design</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-journeys-nova-3-in-1-qi2-charging-station-powers-up-your-devices-with-a-unique-minimalist-design.2440963/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Highlights &#039;Scribble to Siri&#039; Feature on iPadOS 18.1 in Interview</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/scribble-to-siri/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-scribble-to-siri-feature-on-ipados-18-1-in-interview.2440962/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:48:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/scribble-to-siri/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In 2020, iPadOS 14 was released with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/06/25/ipados-14-apple-pencil-scribble/">"Scribble" feature</a> that automatically converts any handwriting written with the Apple Pencil into typed text. Scribble works in any text field, and this means the feature works with the revamped Siri on iPadOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/iPadOS-Scribble-Feature.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-858205" /><br/>
iPadOS 18.1 introduces the first Apple Intelligence features, including the ability to type to Siri in an on-screen overlay. Given that Scribble works in any text field, this means you can now write a Siri query with an Apple Pencil and it will automatically be converted to typed text. Apple highlighted this "Scribble to Siri" feature, and discussed the new iPad mini, in an <a href="https://www.techradar.com/tablets/ipad-mini/apple-tells-us-why-scribble-to-siri-and-math-notes-take-the-ipad-mini-to-new-heights">interview with <em>TechRadar</em>'s Jacob Krol</a> this week.<br/>
<br/>
Apple previously confirmed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/airpods-pro-hearing-features-launching-in-ios-18-1/">iPadOS 18.1 will be released to the public next week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Scribble works with any Apple Pencil, but the revamped version of Siri is limited to devices with Apple Intelligence, including iPad Pro, iPad Air, and iPad mini models equipped with the M1 chip, M2 chip, M4 chip, or A17 Pro chip.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Scribble-to-Siri.gif" alt="" width="486" height="522" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972887" /><em>Scribble to Siri (Credit: TechRadar)</em></div><br/>
Typing to Siri technically already existed as an accessibility setting, but you could not easily switch between typing and talking to Siri like you can now.<br/>
<br/>
Read the full interview with Apple marketing employees Tom Boger and Kurt Knight <a href="https://www.techradar.com/tablets/ipad-mini/apple-tells-us-why-scribble-to-siri-and-math-notes-take-the-ipad-mini-to-new-heights">on <em>TechRadar</em></a> for more details about Scribble to Siri and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/scribble-to-siri/">Apple Highlights &#039;Scribble to Siri&#039; Feature on iPadOS 18.1 in Interview</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-highlights-scribble-to-siri-feature-on-ipados-18-1-in-interview.2440962/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Tested Blood Sugar App for Preventing Diabetes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-diabetes-prevention-app-test/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tested-blood-sugar-app-for-preventing-diabetes.2440961/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 10:29:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-diabetes-prevention-app-test/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been testing a health-focused app that's aimed at diabetes prevention, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-10-25/apple-secretly-tests-blood-sugar-app-in-sign-of-health-ambitions">Bloomberg</a></em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>. The app isn't slated for release, but it could help inform some of Apple's future products related to blood sugar management.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-health-app.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1145" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893452" /><br/>
Select employees with prediabetes were invited to test the app, which offered assistance with food selection and lifestyle changes. Employees who participated confirmed that they had prediabetes with a blood test, and then actively monitored their meals and their blood sugar using glucose monitoring devices.<br/>
<br/>
The app was used to demonstrate to employees how healthy and unhealthy food choices could impact their blood sugar and lead to disease progression. A significant glucose spike after a carbohydrate-heavy meal, for example, could encourage testers to consume more protein and make different choices. Intervening at the prediabetes stage could help millions of people avoid developing diabetes 2.<br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman, Apple used the app to look at how blood sugar data could be used, and what future tools might be helpful for consumers. For the last several years, Apple has been working to add non-invasive blood glucose monitoring functionality to the Apple Watch. Currently, most blood sugar tests require a skin prick, but Apple is developing a method that uses optical absorption spectroscopy and lasers to determine the concentration of glucose in the body without puncturing the skin.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/22/apple-blood-glucose-monitoring-technology/">As of last year</a>, Apple's work on blood glucose monitoring had reached a "proof-of-concept" stage. Apple has a functional prototype device, but it is still much too large to incorporate into a device the size of the Apple Watch. It will likely be several more years before Apple is able to release an Apple Watch that has noninvasive blood sugar tracking features.<br/>
<br/>
In the meantime, Apple could develop more advanced food logging and glucose tracking tools for the Health app, expanding integration with third-party blood glucose monitors.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/apple-diabetes-prevention-app-test/">Apple Tested Blood Sugar App for Preventing Diabetes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tested-blood-sugar-app-for-preventing-diabetes.2440961/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iOS 18.2 Ramps Up Apple Intelligence</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-2-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-2-ramps-up-apple-intelligence.2440953/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:26:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-2-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/ios-18-2-ramps-up-apple-intelligence/id1602394741?i=1000674458981">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss the first beta version of iOS 18.2 – a significant update that continues the rollout of Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/gVlkfS9DHn0?si=-eCEM3DCujIvSLte" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
iOS 18.1 will bring the first Apple Intelligence features to Apple devices. The update includes Writing Tools, the ability for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> to answer Apple product questions, smart replies to emails and messages, audio transcripts, the Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode, and a new Clean Up tool in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, as well as email, text, and notification summaries. iOS 18.1 is expected to be officially released on Monday, October 28.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-2-beta-features/">Everything New in iOS 18.2 Beta 1</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Ahead of this, Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-releases-ios-18-2/">seeded the first beta version</a> of iOS 18.2 to developers. The update further expands Apple Intelligence's capabilities, with new Mail app categories, Image Playground to generate pictures, Image Wand in Notes, Genmoji to create custom emojis, ChatGPT integration in &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, Visual Intelligence on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, expanded Writing Tools, and support for regional versions of English outside the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/the-macrumors-show-ipad-mini-7-is-here/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a>, Apple Intelligence and Genmoji, and the chances of an October Apple event to introduce M4 Macs.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-2-apple-intelligence/">The MacRumors Show: iOS 18.2 Ramps Up Apple Intelligence</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-ios-18-2-ramps-up-apple-intelligence.2440953/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Are We Free From Price Increases to Apple Services This Year?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/no-apple-services-price-increases-in-2024-yet/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/are-we-free-from-price-increases-to-apple-services-this-year.2440951/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:05:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/no-apple-services-price-increases-in-2024-yet/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple announced price increases for some of its subscription-based services <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/24/apple-price-increase-services/">on October 24, 2022</a>, and again <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">on October 25, 2023</a>, but no such announcement has been made as the same week of October comes to an end this year. Hopefully, that means no price increases are planned for the likes of Apple Music and Apple TV+ this year, but knock on wood.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/Apple-One-Apps-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1012" height="601" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-760995" /><br/>
Here are the current monthly prices of Apple's services in the U.S.:<ul><li>Apple News+: &#36;12.99 per month</li><br/>
<li>Apple Music: &#36;10.99 per month</li><br/>
<li>Apple TV+: &#36;9.99 per month</li><br/>
<li>Apple Fitness+: &#36;9.99 per month</li><br/>
<li>Apple Arcade: &#36;6.99 per month</li></ul><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One subscription bundle</a> prices have not changed either.<br/>
<br/>
Take this as a bit of good news on a Friday, or we reminded Apple that it still needs to increase prices and we will forever regret publishing this story.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/no-apple-services-price-increases-in-2024-yet/">Are We Free From Price Increases to Apple Services This Year?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/are-we-free-from-price-increases-to-apple-services-this-year.2440951/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All the New Features Coming to macOS Sequoia Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/new-features-macos-sequoia-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-new-features-coming-to-macos-sequoia-next-week.2440949/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:45:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/new-features-macos-sequoia-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On October 28, Apple is expected to release macOS Sequoia‌ 15.1, bringing to Macs the first Apple Intelligence features such as Writing Tools, new Siri features, Smart Replies, and more. In addition, macOS 15.1 adds a handful of welcome tweaks and improvements to existing Mac capabilities. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
Here's what we can expect from the first major update to macOS Sequoia later this month. Note that Apple Intelligence features require Macs powered by Apple silicon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Mirroring Drag and Drop Support</h2><br/>
One of the most anticipated iPhone Mirroring features coming in macOS 15.1 is support for drag and drop. After updating to the new software, you will be able to drag files from an ‌iPhone‌ to a Mac and vice versa. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iphone-mirroring-drag-and-drop.jpg" alt="finder" width="2940" height="1912" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969047" /><br/>
‌iPhone‌ Mirroring makes file transfers between devices effortless, even when the ‌iPhone‌ is locked and charging. With an iPhone running iOS 18.1, you can drag files, such as photos, from your Mac directly to the open Photos app on your ‌iPhone‌, and they'll transfer instantly. For PDFs, open the Files app and drag the document from your Mac to the ‌iPhone‌. Transferring files from ‌iPhone‌ to Mac follows the same process — simply drag the file to your desired location on the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Low Power Mode Toggle</h2><br/>
Low Power Mode is a long-standing ‌iPhone‌ feature for conserving battery, and was introduced to the Mac with macOS Monterey. Since then, it has remained hidden in System Settings, but in macOS 15.1, Apple is simplifying access by adding a Low Power Mode toggle to the Battery menu for MacBook users, allowing it to be enabled or disabled in just two clicks. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/low-power-mode.jpg" alt="Mac" width="1456" height="622" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969049" /><br/>
The battery icon also now turns yellow when Low Power Mode is active, similar to iOS. It's worth noting that some advanced settings, like automatically enabling Low Power Mode when unplugged, remain within System Settings. When enabled, Low Power Mode optimizes the system to conserve energy by slightly reducing performance, suspending background tasks, lowering screen brightness, and capping ProMotion display refresh rates at 60Hz where applicable.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Writing Tools </h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
You can select any text on your Mac and use Apple Intelligence to access Writing Tools for summaries and other features. The proofreading feature scans your text for spelling and grammar errors, providing suggestions for word choice and sentence structure improvements. You can quickly accept all recommendations or review them individually with accompanying explanations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/writing-tools-macos-01.jpg" alt="" width="2022" height="756" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969201" /><br/>
If you're looking to refine your writing style, the rewrite function allows for tone adjustment without altering the core content. You can choose from options such as Friendly, Professional, or Concise to tailor your message to your intended audience.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/writing-tools-macos.jpg" alt="" width="2266" height="804" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969200" /><br/>
Additionally, the update introduces versatile summarization capabilities. You can select text and generate concise summaries in various formats, including paragraphs, key points, lists, or tables. This feature seamlessly integrates with apps like Mail and Messages, making it easier to distill and share written information.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Enhanced Siri</h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
The Siri window now offers greater flexibility, allowing you to position it anywhere on their screen. A new responsive glow animation provides visual feedback, indicating when Siri is actively listening without disrupting ongoing tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/siri-macos-15.jpg" alt="siri" width="1315" height="713" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969203" /><br/>
If you prefer typing, the Type to Siri feature can be quickly accessed by double-pressing the Command key, and it now includes suggested requests. Siri's improved contextual awareness also lets you ask follow-up questions without repeating previously established information.<br/>
<br/>
The update also brings more natural language processing capabilities. Siri can now better understand and interpret you if you stumble over your words or change direction mid-sentence, making interactions feel more conversational and less rigid.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Siri's knowledge base has been expanded to include comprehensive information about Apple products and support, so you can inquire about device features and settings. Siri can even locate specific settings even if you're unsure of their exact names.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smart Replies and Mail Summaries</h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
To facilitate faster responses, Mail and Messages now include a Smart Reply feature. This intelligent system offers contextual quick-tap responses based on the content of received messages, allowing you to reply promptly with minimal effort.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/mail-smart-reply.jpg" alt="" width="1670" height="946" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969205" /><br/>
<br/>
In Mail, a new summarize button allows you to quickly distill the content of incoming emails, providing concise overviews at a glance. This feature also extends to multiple Messages notifications and your Mail inbox, where brief summaries replace the first few lines of each message. Mail also prioritizes time-sensitive communications by automatically elevating them to the top of your inbox. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Photos Cleanup Tool</h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
With macOS Sequoia 15.1, Apple is bringing a powerful new feature to the Photos app called Clean Up. Thanks to advanced object detection algorithms, this editing tool can automatically identify potentially unwanted objects in your images, allowing you to effortlessly remove them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/macos-15-1-cleanup-tool1.jpg" alt="" width="1578" height="1176" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969212" /><br/>
At the same time, users retain full control over the editing process, with the ability to manually select objects for removal by clicking, circling, or brushing over them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/macos-15-1-cleanup-tool2.jpg" alt="photos" width="1566" height="1172" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969213" /><br/>
You can zoom in on images to meticulously remove smaller blemishes or imperfections using brush strokes. Notably, Clean Up is designed to preserve the integrity of main subjects like people, even if they are inadvertently selected during the editing process.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Transcription Summaries</h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
In macOS Sequoia, Apple added a transcription feature to Notes that lets you capture audio recordings and automatically generates a verbatim transcript of the content. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/transcription-summary-macos.jpg" alt="notes" width="2108" height="1110" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969218" /><br/>
In macOS Sequoia 15.1, the feature also provides a concise summary of the transcribed text, offering a quick overview of the recorded material. The transcript is useful for recording lectures and meetings as it ensures that no important details are missed, while the addition of a summary provides a quick reference for key topics, action items, or main discussion points.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Focus Modes</h2><br/>
<h3>Apple Intelligence</h3><br/>
A dedicated new Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode filters out all but the most important notifications, ensuring you only see those that require your attention.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/reduce-interruptions-focus.jpg" alt="" width="1498" height="828" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969210" /><br/>
When customizing or creating a new Focus mode, there's a new option to enable Intelligent Breakthrough and Silencing. This feature lets critical notifications come through while muting less important ones, similar to how the Reduce Notifications Focus works.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/new-features-macos-sequoia-next-week/">Here Are All the New Features Coming to macOS Sequoia Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-the-new-features-coming-to-macos-sequoia-next-week.2440949/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.2 Adds Daily Sudoku Puzzles for Apple News+ Subscribers in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/ios-18-2-adds-sudoku-to-apple-news-plus/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-adds-daily-sudoku-puzzles-for-apple-news-subscribers-in-u-s.2440947/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:36:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/ios-18-2-adds-sudoku-to-apple-news-plus/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple News</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting with iOS 18.2, Apple News+ subscribers in the U.S. have access to daily sudoku puzzles, with easy, moderate, and challenging difficulty levels.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Sudoku-Apple-News-iOS-18.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972812" /><br/>
A scoreboard tracks your sudoku stats, including your total number of puzzles solved, fastest completion times per difficulty level, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Sudoku is also available in Apple News+ on iPadOS 18.2, and likely macOS Sequoia 15.2. It is the fourth puzzle game to be included with an Apple News+ subscription, alongside Crossword, Crossword Mini, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-17-5-apple-news-quartiles-game/">Quartiles</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple News+ costs &#36;12.99 per month, and the service is also included in the Apple One Premier subscription bundle alongside Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, Apple Fitness+, and iCloud+ with 2TB of storage for &#36;37.95 per month.<br/>
<br/>
The first iOS 18.2 beta was released this week for devices with Apple Intelligence support, including iPhone 15 Pro models and all iPhone 16 models. The software update is expected to be widely released to the public in December.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.2 also includes additional Apple Intelligence features, such as Image Playground and Genmoji. Check out our list of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-2-beta-features/">everything new in the first iOS 18.2 beta</a> for an overview of most of the new features and changes discovered so far.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/ios-18-2-adds-sudoku-to-apple-news-plus/">iOS 18.2 Adds Daily Sudoku Puzzles for Apple News+ Subscribers in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-2-adds-daily-sudoku-puzzles-for-apple-news-subscribers-in-u-s.2440947/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Announcements Next Week: What NOT to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/what-not-to-expect-apple-october-announcements/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-announcements-next-week-what-not-to-expect.2440945/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 07:02:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/what-not-to-expect-apple-october-announcements/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has teased an "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-m4-announcements-next-week/">exciting week of announcements</a>" starting on Monday, and going on its teaser image, new Macs are sure to feature prominently. However, there are some hardware updates on Apple's roadmap that are unlikely to be a part of those announcements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/10.28.24-Event-What-Not-To-Expect-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972803" /><br/>
Below, we've recapped what <em>not</em> to expect from Apple's series of product announcements through the last week of October going into November.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m3-macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950298" /><br/>
Apple in March 2024 launched updated 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air models equipped with Apple's M3 chip, and the company will soon start production of M4 versions ahead of an early 2025 launch, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/09/when-to-expect-m4-macbook-air-mac-studio-mac-pro/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. There are no new design changes planned for the ‌MacBook Air‌ models, and the focus will be on the M4 chip. The ‌machines will arrive next year between January and March. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Mac Studio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Studio-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946114" /><br/>
Apple plans to refresh the Mac Studio after the M4 MacBook Air has been released in early 2025. It will be equipped with a variation of the M4 processor, which could be an M4 Ultra or Max chip. The current model comes in both M2 Max and M2 Ultra variants. Mark Gurman claims that the ‌Mac Studio‌ was on track to be updated alongside the ‌MacBook Air‌, but it is now going to see a refresh <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/m4-macbook-air-production-beginning-soon/">between March and June</a>. In previous reports, he said the ‌Mac Studio‌ would come out in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-studio-m4-mac-pro-2025/">mid-2025</a>, so it is unclear what has changed. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 Mac Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-Mac-Pro-Feature-Warm-2.jpg" alt="" width="2672" height="1503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948229" /><br/>
Apple last updated the Mac Pro in June 2023, adding an M2 Ultra chip and officially completing the transition away from Intel chips. Apple will refresh the Mac Pro in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/m4-macbook-air-production-beginning-soon/">summer of 2025</a>, according to Mark Gurman. Like the Mac Studio, the next Mac Pro will skip the M3 series. Instead it will be equipped with the highest-end version of the M4 chip, codenamed "Hidra." Based on the description of the chip, it could be positioned as an "Ultra" or "Extreme" chip. It could also support up to 512GB of memory, a notable increase over the current 192GB limit. <br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone SE 4</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
Apple plans to release a new iPhone SE with Apple Intelligence support early next year, with a launch in March or April most likely, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/01/new-iphone-se-and-ipad-air-early-2025-rumor/">according to Mark Gurman</a>. The fourth-generation iPhone SE is expected to have a similar design as the base iPhone 14, with rumored features including a 6.1-inch OLED display, Face ID, a newer A-series chip, a USB-C port, a single 48-megapixel rear camera, 8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support, and an Apple-designed 5G modem. Supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo claims that Apple suppliers will begin mass production in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/iphone-se-4-mass-production-timeframe/">December</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Fanned-Pink.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869882" /><br/>
Apple has already updated the iPad Air and iPad Pro this year, and the company released the new iPad mini 7 earlier this month, which leaves the entry-level iPad as the most likely candidate next in line to receive an update. Don't expect an announcement next week though.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's most affordable iPad model will receive an 11th-generation update with Apple Intelligence capabilities in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/entry-level-ipad-apple-intelligence-late-2025/">late 2025</a>, according to Mark Gurman. The timeline indicates a significant gap since the last refresh of the entry-level iPad, which occurred in October 2022. The delayed update could be attributed to the technical requirements of implementing AI capabilities in a budget-friendly &#36;349 device.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Pro 3</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/airpods-pro-2-gradient.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-967392" /><br/>
Despite being released over two years ago, Apple's AirPods Pro 2 continue to dominate the wireless earbud market, but they aren't expected to see a refresh until <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/airpods-lineup-overhaul-2024/">next year</a>, according to Gurman. The 2025 ‌AirPods Pro‌ will be updated with a new design and a faster chip, plus the earbuds will inherit Apple's upcoming new <a href="https://www.apple.com/airpods-pro/hearing-health/">hearing health features</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/what-not-to-expect-apple-october-announcements/">Apple Announces Announcements Next Week: What NOT to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-announcements-next-week-what-not-to-expect.2440945/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTuber Creates the Apple Event We Aren&#039;t Getting This Month</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/youtuber-creates-an-apple-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-creates-the-apple-event-we-arent-getting-this-month.2440942/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 06:08:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/youtuber-creates-an-apple-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Jon Prosser</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's marketing chief Greg Joswiak on Thursday <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-m4-announcements-next-week/">teased an "exciting week of announcements"</a> planned next week, and that likely rules out a prerecorded Apple Event video this month, despite Apple streaming a short, spooky "Scary Fast" event last October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Jon-Prosser-MacBook-Pro-Render.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972805" /><br/>
Nevertheless, YouTube channel Front Page Tech has stepped in with its own rendition of the Apple Event we aren't getting this month. In the video, Jon Prosser does his best impression of Apple CEO Tim Cook and announces all of the rumored new Macs with M4 chips. The video is somewhat of a parody, so don't take it too seriously, but it's also an impressive production feat that Prosser's team spent nearly a month working on.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/H8lEZKazs70?si=UDpesdM7GDRrkBpl" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
After you are done watching, check out our own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/what-to-expect-from-apple-announcements-next-week/">recap of everything that Apple is expected to announce next week</a> to learn more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jon-prosser/">Jon Prosser</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/youtuber-creates-an-apple-event/">YouTuber Creates the Apple Event We Aren&#039;t Getting This Month</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-creates-the-apple-event-we-arent-getting-this-month.2440942/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.1: How to Record and Transcribe Phone Calls</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-record-your-phone-calls/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-how-to-record-and-transcribe-phone-calls.2440927/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 03:21:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-record-your-phone-calls&#038;post_date=1729862492/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[From business meetings to family memories, there are countless reasons to record a phone call, but until now, iPhone users have had to rely on third-party apps or complex workarounds. That changes on October 28 with the release of iOS 18.1, which introduces native call recording and transcription powered by Apple Intelligence. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/call-recording-ios-18-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972752" /><br/>
Apple's new Phone app feature not only records conversations but automatically creates searchable transcripts and AI-generated summaries, all while maintaining Apple's commitment to privacy and transparency. When you start recording, all participants automatically hear an announcement, ensuring everyone knows they're being recorded. A visible indicator also remains on screen throughout the call for as long as the recording continues. <br/>
<br/>
To further protect user privacy, all recordings are stored locally in the Notes app with end-to-end encryption, and the new Apple Intelligence-powered transcription happens entirely on your device, meaning conversations never leave your iPhone. Here's how to make your first phone call recording in iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Recording a Phone Call</h2><br/>
<ol><br/>
  <li>Start or answer a phone call.</li><br/>
  <li>Tap the record button (the waveform icon) in the top-left corner of the call screen.</li><br/>
  <li>An automated voice will notify all participants that recording has begun.</li><br/>
  <li>The recording will automatically save to the Notes app when the call ends or when you stop the recording.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ios-18-1-call-recording-steps.jpg" alt="phone" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972760" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Finding and Managing Phone Call Recordings</h2><br/>
Once saved, recordings appear in the Notes app as audio files with attached transcripts. Tap any recording to access a range of options: You can play back the audio, read the full transcript, view an AI-generated summary of the conversation, or share and delete recordings as needed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1289" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960200" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Legal Considerations</h2> <br/>
While iOS 18.1 makes recording calls easier than ever, it's important to understand your legal obligations. Although Apple's automated announcement helps ensure transparency, you should familiarize yourself with local recording laws. Regardless, it's always best to get explicit verbal consent before the start of any recorded conversation. <br/>
<br/>
Phone call recording and transcription features will be available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/25/ios-18-these-iphones-wont-support-ai/">compatible iPhone models</a> when iOS 18.1 is released on Monday, October 28.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-record-your-phone-calls/">iOS 18.1: How to Record and Transcribe Phone Calls</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-how-to-record-and-transcribe-phone-calls.2440927/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Won&#039;t Get These Apple Intelligence Features Until 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-intelligence-2025-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-wont-get-these-apple-intelligence-features-until-2025.2440899/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 14:06:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-intelligence-2025-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to introduce the first Apple Intelligence features in iOS 18.1, debuting Writing Tools, notification summaries, smart replies, and more. iOS 18.1 will be followed by iOS 18.2, which Apple started testing this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
iOS 18.2 has Genmoji, Image Playground, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> ChatGPT integration, but there are still some Apple Intelligence features that won't be introduced until even later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Siri Features</h2><br/>
Apple plans to make major updates to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, and has outlined new functionality that will make &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; much more helpful. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to learn more about you through your communications and actions on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but this personal context won't be coming until a later update.<br/>
<br/>
Personal context will incorporate texts, emails, notes, and more, so you'll be able to ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; for things like a flight number buried in an email, or a recipe that a friend once texted you.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will also be able to do more in apps, both first and third-party, with in-app actions. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do things like edit a photo for you and then send it to someone in the Messages app, or pull a PDF from an email and save it to the Files app.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will also be able to get information and take action in third-party apps, doing things like getting a weather readout from Carrot Weather or scheduling an event in Fantastical.<br/>
<br/>
New &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; capabilities will either come in iOS 18.3 or iOS 18.4 in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Genmoji on macOS</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.2 includes support for Image Playground, but it does not have Genmoji integration as of yet. You can create Genmoji with iOS 18.2 and iPadOS 18.2, but there is no Mac feature for making custom emoji characters.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Memory Movies on macOS</h2><br/>
The Memory Movie feature that lets you create slideshows from your photos using text descriptions is limited to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> in iOS/iPadOS 18.1 and later. It will come to &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Priority Notifications</h2><br/>
Apple is working on a feature that will show you your most important notifications first. Priority Notifications will show up at the top of your notification stack.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Languages</h2><br/>
Apple plans to add support for more languages in 2025, including Chinese, English (India), English (Singapore), French, German, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Portuguese, Spanish, Vietnamese, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Intelligence Release Timing</h2><br/>
Writing Tools, the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; design, Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, notification summaries, smart replies, Clean Up in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, and several other features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">are available in iOS 18.1</a>, which will be released on Monday, October 28.<br/>
<br/>
Image Playground, Genmoji, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; ChatGPT integration, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-releases-ios-18-2/">and other features</a> will be released in iOS 18.2, which will likely launch in December. iOS 18.2 will be the last iOS update of 2024.<br/>
<br/>
All other Apple Intelligence features are expected in iOS 18.3 and iOS 18.4, which will be released in 2025. iOS 18.3 could come as soon as late January, while iOS 18.4 will likely be a March update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-intelligence-2025-features/">You Won&#039;t Get These Apple Intelligence Features Until 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-wont-get-these-apple-intelligence-features-until-2025.2440899/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discontinued These Four Products This Year, But One Will Return</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-discontinued-these-products-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinued-these-four-products-this-year-but-one-will-return.2440890/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:30:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-discontinued-these-products-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we get into the final months of 2024, now is a good opportunity to look back at devices and accessories that Apple discontinued throughout the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Discontinued-Products-Goodbye.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971596" /><br/>
Apple products discontinued this year include the iPad 9, SuperDrive, FineWoven cases for the iPhone, and the Powerbeats Pro earbuds.<br/>
<br/>
This list <strong>excludes most previous-generation devices</strong> that were discontinued this year as part of annual updates to Apple's product lineup, such as the iPhone 15 Pro and Apple Watch Series 9. The one exception to this rule is the iPad 9, as that device was discontinued in May, over a year and a half after the iPad 10 launched.<br/>
<br/>
Check out our previous lists of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/27/apple-discontinued-products-in-2023/">Apple products discontinued in 2023</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/apple-discontinued-products-2022/">2022</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/12/29/5-products-discontinued-by-apple-in-2021/">2021</a> as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad 9</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/iPad-9th-gen-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2040" height="1147" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-812369" /><br/>
On the same day that it unveiled new iPad Pro and iPad Air models in May, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/ipad-9-discontinued-ipad-10-now-starts-at-349/">discontinued the ninth-generation, entry-level iPad</a>. In addition, Apple lowered the price of the tenth-generation iPad, which now starts at &#36;349 in the U.S., down from &#36;449.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>SuperDrive</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/8-Old-SuperDrives.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928630" /><br/>
In August, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/06/apple-superdrive-could-be-discontinued/">SuperDrive went out of stock</a> on Apple's online store in the U.S., and it is now listed as sold out or unavailable in all countries. Given it has yet to return, it seems likely that Apple has discontinued the 16-year-old accessory.<br/>
<br/>
Introduced in 2008, the SuperDrive is an external CD/DVD drive that was released alongside the original MacBook Air, which lacked a built-in CD/DVD drive. Despite having an outdated USB-A cable attached to it, the SuperDrive remained available on Apple's online store until just recently, becoming one of the company's longest-sold products.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>FineWoven Cases</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947658" /><br/>
Apple last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">discontinued its leather accessories</a>, including iPhone cases, and it introduced a new "FineWoven" fabric material as a replacement.<br/>
<br/>
"FineWoven" cases for the iPhone 15 series <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/finewoven-iphone-cases-brown-like-rotten-banana/">were widely panned</a>, and it appears that Apple was well aware of this feedback, as the material is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/apple-discontinues-finewoven-cases/">no longer offered for iPhone 16 cases</a> just a year later. It is unclear if Apple will come up with a new solution.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Powerbeats Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Powerbeats-Pro-Original.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971547" /><br/>
Apple this month quietly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/apple-discontinues-powerbeats-pro/">discontinued the Powerbeats Pro</a>, around five and a half years after the wireless earbuds launched.<br/>
<br/>
Powerbeats Pro are a sportier, fitness-focused alternative to AirPods Pro with built-in, adjustable ear hooks for a secure fit. Key features of the original Powerbeats Pro include the H1 chip that debuted in the AirPods 2, IPX4-rated sweat and water resistance, up to nine hours of battery life, and silicone ear tips with four size options.<br/>
<br/>
In a short teaser video last month, Apple revealed that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/04/beats-teases-powerbeats-pro-2/">launching new Powerbeats Pro 2 next year</a>. The earbuds look similar to the original Powerbeats Pro, but they have a more vertical, slimmer design. <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris later discovered iOS 18 code revealing that the Powerbeats Pro 2 will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/09/powerbeats-pro-2-heart-rate/">feature heart rate monitoring</a> during workouts, and gain support for Active Noise Cancellation, Spatial Audio, and Adaptive Audio.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-discontinued-these-products-in-2024/">Apple Discontinued These Four Products This Year, But One Will Return</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinued-these-four-products-this-year-but-one-will-return.2440890/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware Ahead of Hearing Aid Feature Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-releases-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7b19/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-ahead-of-hearing-aid-feature-launch.2440886/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:43:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-releases-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7b19/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, with the software available for both the USB-C and Lightning models. The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 firmware has a build number of 7B19, up from the 7A305 firmware <a href="hhttps://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/26/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7a305/">released in September</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-825981" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/AirPods-Pro-Firmware-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2322" height="1306" /><br/>
The new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 firmware comes just ahead of when Apple plans to launch Hearing Health features in iOS 18.1. Hearing Health includes a hearing test that mimics an audiologist's test, and hearing aid functionality should that test sense mild to moderate hearing loss.<br/>
<br/>
Release notes for the update are as follows:<blockquote><ul><li>When used with an iPhone or iPad running iOS 18.1 or iPadOS 18.1 or later, AirPods Pro 2 with firmware update 7B19 enable three new features—a Hearing Test, Hearing Aid, and Hearing Protection.</li><br/>
<li>The Apple Hearing Test feature provides scientifically-validated hearing test results from the comfort of home (intended for users 18 years or older).</li><br/>
<li>The Hearing Aid feature provides personalized, clinical-grade assistance that is automatically applied to sounds in your environment as well as music, videos, and calls (intended for users 18 years or older with perceived mild to moderate hearing loss)</li><br/>
<li>The Hearing Protection feature helps users minimize exposure to loud environmental noise across listening modes (available in the United States and Canada)</li></ul><br/>
Features require AirPods Pro 2 with firmware version 7B19 or later. All features may not be available for all countries or regions.</blockquote><br/>
Apple has approval for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 to function as an over-the-counter hearing aid in the United States. The hearing aid capabilities will boost conversations and other environmental sounds for those who have hearing loss issues.<br/>
<br/>
The update also includes a Hearing Protection feature that will continuously monitor the wearer's environment to reduce the impact of loud sounds. This functionality will be limited to the U.S. and Canada at launch.<br/>
<br/>
Hearing Health will be introduced in iOS 18.1, which is set to be released next Monday.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't have a way to manually upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air when the AirPods are in a charging case and connected to an iOS device or Mac.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-releases-airpods-pro-2-firmware-7b19/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware Ahead of Hearing Aid Feature Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-ahead-of-hearing-aid-feature-launch.2440886/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TestFlight Now Lets Developers Set Testing Criteria and Include App Screenshots</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/testflight-testing-criteria-app-screenshots/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testflight-now-lets-developers-set-testing-criteria-and-include-app-screenshots.2440884/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:19:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/testflight-testing-criteria-app-screenshots/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TestFlight</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=fps422ld">updated</a> its TestFlight app, adding new features that are designed to streamline the app beta testing process. TestFlight is the app that developers can use to distribute their app to beta testers ahead of when the app is released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/New-TestFlight.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972715" /><br/>
The app has also been redesigned on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Invites to beta test an app include an app description, plus developers can opt to include screenshots and information about their app category.<br/>
<br/>
To narrow down potential testers, developers can set tester criteria that must be met in order to join a beta. Testers who decide not to join a particular beta can provide feedback to a developer explaining why. Apple's release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote>This update includes several key improvements to enhance your testing experience:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Invitations include a beta app description and developers can now also choose to include screenshots and their app category.</li><br/>
 	<li>Developers can now set tester criteria you must meet in order to join a beta.</li><br/>
 	<li>You can share with developers why you decided not to join a beta through a new feedback option.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Additionally, this update includes stability improvements and bug fixes.</blockquote><br/>
TestFlight is a free app for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, Mac, and Vision Pro, and it can be downloaded from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/testflight/id899247664">Direct Link</a>]<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/testflight/">TestFlight</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/testflight-testing-criteria-app-screenshots/">TestFlight Now Lets Developers Set Testing Criteria and Include App Screenshots</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testflight-now-lets-developers-set-testing-criteria-and-include-app-screenshots.2440884/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Private Cloud Compute Virtual Research Environment, Provides Bounties for Vulnerabilities</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-private-cloud-compute-security-info/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-private-cloud-compute-virtual-research-environment-provides-bounties-for-vulnerabilities.2440882/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:57:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-private-cloud-compute-security-info/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Private Cloud Compute is a cloud intelligence system that Apple designed for private artificial intelligence processing, and it's what Apple is using to keep Apple Intelligence requests secure when they need to be processed in the cloud.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963424" /><br/>
Apple promised to allow security and privacy researchers to verify the end-to-end security and privacy promises that Apple made with Private Cloud Compute, and today, Apple made its Private Cloud Compute Virtual Research Environment (VRE) and other materials <a href="https://security.apple.com/blog/pcc-security-research">publicly available to all security researchers</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has a Private Cloud Compute (PCC) Security Guide that details all of the components of PCC and how they work to provide privacy for cloud-based AI processing. Apple released the source code for select components of PCC that help implement its security and privacy requirements, which allows for a deeper dive into PCC.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-private-cloud-compute-security.jpg" alt="" width="1260" height="626" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972691" /><br/>
The Virtual Research Environment is a set of tools that lets researchers perform their own security analysis on PCC using a Mac. The VRE can be used for inspecting PCC software releases, verifying the consistency of the transparency log, booting a release in a virtualized environment, and modifying and debugging PCC software for deeper investigation. The VRE can be accessed in the macOS 18.1 Developer Preview and can be used with a Mac that has an Apple silicon chip and 16GB+ unified memory.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these tools, Apple is expanding its Apple Security Bounty to include rewards for vulnerabilities that demonstrate a compromise of the fundamental privacy and security guarantees of Private Cloud Compute. Security researchers who locate a vulnerability can earn up to &#36;1 million.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-private-cloud-compute-security-info/">Apple Shares Private Cloud Compute Virtual Research Environment, Provides Bounties for Vulnerabilities</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-private-cloud-compute-virtual-research-environment-provides-bounties-for-vulnerabilities.2440882/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second macOS Sequoia 15.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/macos-sequoia-15-1-rc-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sequoia-15-1-release-candidate.2440880/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:38:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/macos-sequoia-15-1-rc-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided developers and public beta testers with the second release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1 update, with the new software coming one week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-15-1-beta-7/">released the seventh beta</a>. Apple introduced the first RC on Monday, and there's likely a new version to address an underlying bug.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta. Public beta testers can sign up on Apple's website.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 introduces the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-features/">first Apple Intelligence features</a>, adding support for Writing Tools, new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features, Smart Replies in Mail and Messages, Priority messages in the Mail app, Memory Movie and Clean Up in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-unavailable-features/">does not include</a> Image Playground, Genmoji, or more advanced &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Using Apple Intelligence features requires a Mac that has an Apple silicon chip.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/macos-sequoia-15-1-rc-2/">Apple Seeds Second macOS Sequoia 15.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-macos-sequoia-15-1-release-candidate.2440880/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From Apple&#039;s &#039;Exciting Week of Announcements&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/what-to-expect-from-apple-announcements-next-week/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-exciting-week-of-announcements.2440877/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:36:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/what-to-expect-from-apple-announcements-next-week/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Magic Keyboard</category>
		<category>Magic Mouse</category>
		<category>Magic Trackpad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's marketing chief Greg Joswiak today teased that the company has an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/apple-m4-announcements-next-week/">"exciting week of announcements" planned next week</a>. Joswiak said to "Mac" your calendars, and the post includes an animated icon for the Finder app on the Mac, so it is clear that at least some of next week's announcements will be related to the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zJjmOP_gKpw?si=Xgt8akvA1TT09gXE" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to MacRumors on YouTube for more videos!</a></em></div><br/>
Below, we have recapped what to expect from Apple's announcements next week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hardware</h2><br/>
<h3>MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
Apple is expected to announce new 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models, including an entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip, and higher-end 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 Pro and M4 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
No major external design changes have been rumored for the laptops this year, with improvements such as an OLED display and thinner design not expected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/10/macbook-pro-wont-switch-to-oled-in-2025-rumor/">until 2026 at the earliest</a>. However, the entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro is expected to gain an additional Thunderbolt port compared to the current model, based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-potentially-facing-worst-leak-since-iphone-4/">alleged leaks earlier this month</a>. Those same leaks revealed that the MacBook Pro lineup might finally start with 16GB of RAM, instead of 8GB, which was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/apple-new-macs-16gb-ram-standard/">rumored even before the leaks happened</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last redesigned the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro in 2021, and the latest models with the M3 family of chips were released last October.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>iMac</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946085" /><br/>
The next iMac is expected to be equipped with the standard M4 chip, up from the M3 chip in the current model released a year ago. No major design changes have been rumored for Apple's all-in-one desktop computer this year.<br/>
<br/>
It is likely that the Magic Keyboard with Touch ID, Magic Mouse, and Magic Trackpad accessories that are included in the box with the iMac will finally feature USB-C ports, as part of Apple's transition away from Lightning. More on that below.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Mac mini</h3><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/M4-Mac-mini-Ortho-Silver-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972060" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini</em></div><br/>
The next Mac mini is expected to be available with M4 and M4 Pro chip options. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/mac-mini-redesign-rumor/">expects the next Mac mini to be smaller</a>, making it closer in size to an Apple TV, and he said that the computer will gain two front-facing USB-C ports. All in all, the Mac mini is expected to receive its biggest redesign since 2010.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if the next Mac mini will also start with 16GB of RAM, instead of the current 8GB.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>USB-C Magic Accessories</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/magic-trackpad-orange-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-852993" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris recently discovered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-new-magic-mouse-trackpad-keyboard/">code references to new versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard</a>, and these accessories will likely switch from Lightning to USB-C for charging alongside the new iMac. In the EU, a regulation requiring USB-C as a common charging port goes into effect later this year.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if the accessories will have any other changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Software</h2><br/>
<h3>iOS 18.1 With First Apple Intelligence Features and More</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Generic-iOS-18.1-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963325" /><br/>
Apple recently confirmed that new AirPods Pro 2 hearing health features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/airpods-pro-hearing-features-launching-in-ios-18-1/">will be available as part of iOS 18.1 next week</a>, so there could be an announcement when the software update is released, especially since it also includes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">first set of Apple Intelligence features</a> for the iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, and all iPhone 16 models.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said Apple has planned to release the update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/apple-to-release-ios-18-1-on-october-28/">on Monday, October 28</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The following other updates are expected to be widely released next week as well:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iPadOS 18.1</li><br/>
<li>macOS Sequoia 15.1</li><br/>
<li>watchOS 11.1</li><br/>
<li>tvOS 18.1</li><br/>
<li>HomePod Software 18.1</li><br/>
<li>visionOS 2.1</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Earnings</h2><br/>
Apple will be discussing its earnings results for the fourth quarter of its 2024 fiscal year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/apple-earnings-on-halloween/">on Thursday, October 31</a> at 2 p.m. Pacific Time. That call will provide early insight into iPhone 16, Apple Watch Series 10, and AirPods 4 sales, and Apple will likely touch on some of its Mac-related announcements on the call too.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-keyboard/">Magic Keyboard</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-mouse/">Magic Mouse</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magic-trackpad/">Magic Trackpad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/24/what-to-expect-from-apple-announcements-next-week/">What to Expect From Apple&#039;s &#039;Exciting Week of Announcements&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-apples-exciting-week-of-announcements.2440877/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
