<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 21:03:25 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Likely to Launch in These Nine Countries Next</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-likely-to-launch-in-these-nine-countries-next.2421867/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:55:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon add 12 new languages to the virtual keyboard on the Vision Pro, based on code discovered by <em>MacRumors</em>. Right now, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> keyboard only supports English (US) and Emoji, which makes sense as it is limited to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1278" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930653" /><br/>
To bring the Vision Pro to new countries, Apple needs to add support for additional languages. The code indicates the following languages will be added:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Cantonese, Traditional</li><br/>
 	<li>Chinese, Simplified</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Australia)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Canada)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Japan)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Singapore)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (UK)</li><br/>
 	<li>French (Canada)</li><br/>
 	<li>French (France)</li><br/>
 	<li>German (Germany)</li><br/>
 	<li>Japanese</li><br/>
 	<li>Korean</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
It's likely that these language additions hint at the countries where Apple will launch the Vision Pro next, including Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, Japan, Singapore, South Korea, and the UK. Hong Kong and Taiwan are also potential candidates.<br/>
<br/>
When the Vision Pro launched, Apple said that it would bring the Vision Pro to additional countries later this year, but the company did not provide timing. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> believes that Apple will expand Vision Pro availability to additional markets prior to the June Worldwide Developers Conference.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">Apple Vision Pro Likely to Launch in These Nine Countries Next</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-likely-to-launch-in-these-nine-countries-next.2421867/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Throwboy Launches Giant Pillow Modeled After Mac Finder Icon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/throwboy-launches-giant-pillow-modeled-after-mac-finder-icon.2421865/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:10:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Throwboy, known for its line of pillows designed to look like classic Macs, this week launched a new jumbo version of the Apple fan favorite Icon Pillow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Big-Boy-Throwboy-6.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1536" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941208" /><br/>
Designed to look like the Finder icon from early Macs, the jumbo Icon Pillow measures in at 37 inches by 37 inches by 15 inches, and it is the biggest pillow that Throwboy has created to date. It is made of a soft plush material with fleece eyes and smile, and it is so big that it weighs in at 16 pounds.<br/>
<br/>
According to Throwboy, the jumbo Icon Pillow is the ultimate home decor for tech lovers, and it is sized for snuggling with. It is filled with a plush, poly filling that is meant to give it a bouncy fill, and it is designed to be durable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Big-Boy-Throwboy-5.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1536" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941210" /><br/>
Throwboy makes the Icon Pillow in a range of sizes, from jumbo to the more reasonable <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/icon-pillow">13 inch by 13 inch version</a>. There's also a <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/icon-pocket-pillow-1">mini pocket Icon pillow</a> and one that <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/sad-icon-pillow">comes with a sad face</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The jumbo Icon Pillow can be <a href="https://throwboy.com/collections/throwboy-pillows/products/icon-pillow-jumbo-size">purchased from Throwboy</a> for &#36;390. It is available in the U.S., UK, and Canada.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/">Throwboy Launches Giant Pillow Modeled After Mac Finder Icon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/throwboy-launches-giant-pillow-modeled-after-mac-finder-icon.2421865/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Suppliers Donate to Restore Fund for Sustainable Forests and Other Carbon Removal Projects</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-suppliers-donate-to-restore-fund-for-sustainable-forests-and-other-carbon-removal-projects.2421855/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:49:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Environment</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apple-expands-innovative-restore-fund-with-tsmc-and-murata/">today announced</a> that suppliers Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) and Japanese company Murata Manufacturing are investing in its Restore Fund, a program aimed at scaling investments in high-quality nature-based carbon removal while also protecting critical ecosystems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-restore-fund.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941203" /><br/>
TSMC is investing up to &#36;50 million and Murata is investing up to &#36;30 million, with the money managed by Climate Asset Management. Apple established the Restore Fund in 2021 with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/15/apple-launches-restore-fund/">&#36;200 million donation</a>, and expanded it in 2023 with another &#36;200 million.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is using some of the money to support the creation of <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apples-restore-fund-cultivates-new-roots-in-the-atlantic-forest/">sustainably certified working forests</a> on degraded pasture and agricultural lands in South America. The project is meant to meet increasing global demand for timber while reducing pressure on natural forests.<br/>
<br/>
Two of the partners that Apple is working on the forests have planted eucalyptus, an ideal tree for sustainable forests because of its fast growth rate, ability to restore degraded land, and lower water consumption than other kinds of trees.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's third partner is developing sustainable forests of tropical hardwoods native to Brazil's Atlantic Forest, with some of the land also going toward restoring tree species that are nearing extinction. The Restore Fund will be used for other projects that focus on ecosystem conservation and restoration, with selection underway. Apple set a goal of removing 1 million metric tons of carbon dioxide from the air by 2025, which it is on track to exceed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants to be carbon neutral across its entire supply chain by 2030. More than 300 suppliers have signed up for the Supplier Clean Energy Program that commits them to achieving 100 percent renewable energy for all Apple production by the end of the decade, and Apple has also asked its partners to decarbonize their Apple-related operations.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-environment/">Apple Environment</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/">Apple Suppliers Donate to Restore Fund for Sustainable Forests and Other Carbon Removal Projects</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-suppliers-donate-to-restore-fund-for-sustainable-forests-and-other-carbon-removal-projects.2421855/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Accuses Apple of Charging &#039;Unjustified Fees&#039; for Required Non-App Store Purchase Link</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-accuses-apple-of-charging-unjustified-fees-for-required-non-app-store-purchase-link.2421851/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:14:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> is once again after Apple, this time accusing the Cupertino company of violating a court ruling that requires Apple to allow developers to offer in-app links to direct customers to third-party purchase options on the web.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
Apple tweaked its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">U.S. App Store policies</a> back in January, and developers are permitted to put one link in their apps that leads to a website where customers can make a purchase without using the in-app purchase system. Apple is still charging commission for these purchases, requiring developers to pay between 12 and 27 percent (three percent lower than the 15/30 standard fee).<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is unhappy with the fee that Apple continues to charge, <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/713133409/Epic-Games-v-Apple-Motion-to-Enforce-Injunction">today telling the court</a> that Apple has not complied with the order, and asking that Apple be held in contempt of court. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; claims that the fees make the links "commercially unusable," thereby subverting the injunction.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple violates the Injunction in three ways. First, with respect to External Links, Apple has imposed new fees and enacted a slew of new rules that work together to make the links commercially unusable. This new fee and accompanying web of restrictions subverts the purpose of the Injunction, allowing Apple to continue extracting its excessive commissions and making it effectively impossible for a developer to inform users about, and direct users toward, an alternative platform for making a purchase.<br/>
<br/>
Second, Apple continues to categorically prohibit any steering using "buttons" or "other calls to action". Specifically, Apple does not allow External Links that resemble a "button" in any way.<br/>
<br/>
Third, Apple's Guideline 3.1.3 still prohibits certain apps, including all multiplatform services (i.e., apps that operate across multiple platforms and allow users to access the same content across these platforms, including popular games such as Minecraft), from "within the app, encourag[ing] users to use a purchasing method other than in-app purchase". This language expressly contravenes the Injunction by prohibiting any steering to alternative purchasing methods.</blockquote><br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; collected statements from other developers that have spoken out against Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> fees, including Paddle CEO Christian Owens and Down Dog CEO Benjamin Simon.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was initially ordered to make the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes in 2021 as part of its court battle with &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;. Judge Yvonne Gonzalez-Rogers, who oversaw the case, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-vs-apple-decision/">took issue</a> with Apple's anti-steering rules. Apple was able to delay implementing the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes for a few years <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">while it appealed</a>, but none of the courts decided to change the verdict. Apple ultimately took it to the Supreme Court, but the court <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">declined to hear the case</a>, so Apple had to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">comply immediately</a> at the beginning of the year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has said that it is fully in compliance with the injunction. From Apple's January statement of compliance:<blockquote>As of January 16, 2024, Apple has fully complied with the Injunction: It is striking the relevant parts of the App Store Review Guidelines applicable to apps on the U.S. storefronts of the iOS and iPadOS App Stores and implementing new rules that permit developers to (i) include in their apps buttons or links with calls to action that direct customers to purchasing mechanisms in addition to IAP and (ii) communicate with customers through points of contact obtained voluntarily from customers through account registration within the app. As a result of these changes, developers have the option of informing consumers, both within and outside the app, about alternative purchase mechanisms in addition to IAP.</blockquote>Epic Games claims that the fee Apple charges for the link is "financially unattractive" for developers who want to choose another payment solution, and it "prevents any meaningful competition between payment solutions." The company wants the court to require Apple to bring its policies into compliance with the injunction.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/">Epic Games Accuses Apple of Charging &#039;Unjustified Fees&#039; for Required Non-App Store Purchase Link</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-accuses-apple-of-charging-unjustified-fees-for-required-non-app-store-purchase-link.2421851/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Teardown Shows Apple Fixed Base Model&#039;s Biggest Flaw</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-teardown-shows-apple-fixed-base-models-biggest-flaw.2421843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:11:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The repair website iFixit today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jXY9tCBpf48">shared a video teardown</a> of the base model 13-inch MacBook Air with the M3 chip and 256GB of storage, and it shows that this configuration is equipped with two 128GB flash storage chips. This change results in significantly faster SSD speeds compared to the equivalent MacBook Air with the M2 chip, which has a single 256GB storage chip, as the SSD can read and write from the two chips simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
YouTube channel Max Tech <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/09/base-model-m3-macbook-air-faster-ssd/">ran Blackmagic's Disk Speed Test tool</a> with a 5GB file size test on both the M2 and M3 models of the 13-inch MacBook Air with 256GB of storage and 8GB of RAM, and they found the SSD in the M3 model achieved up to 33% faster write speeds and up to 82% faster read speeds compared to the SSD in the M2 model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's decision to switch to a single 256GB chip for the base model M2 MacBook Air was controversial, even though the slower SSD speeds are unlikely to be noticed by the average user working on common day-to-day tasks. Fortunately, the base model M3 MacBook Air's SSD speeds are now roughly equivalent to the base model M1 MacBook Air again, so customers no longer need to be concerned about this potential limitation.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jXY9tCBpf48?si=gDJPempJs82JBtn0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple still sells a 13-inch M2 MacBook Air with 256GB of storage for &#36;999, so customers who want maximum SSD performance should avoid that model.<br/>
<br/>
Beyond this SSD-related change, the teardown shows that the M3 MacBook Air models have a virtually identical internal design as the M2 models. The video provides a look at the battery cells with adhesive pull tabs, logic board, trackpad, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> iFixit's CEO Kyle Wiens said the base model 15-inch MacBook Air with the M3 chip and 256GB of storage also has two 128GB storage chips.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/">M3 MacBook Air Teardown Shows Apple Fixed Base Model&#039;s Biggest Flaw</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-teardown-shows-apple-fixed-base-models-biggest-flaw.2421843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Closer to Potential U.S. Ban as House Passes Bill Requiring Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-closer-to-potential-u-s-ban-as-house-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2421834/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:46:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. House of Representatives today approved legislation that would force TikTok owner ByteDance to sell the social media network or face a ban in the United States. The Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act will now go to the Senate, where its fate is unclear.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="866" height="480" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-738083" /><br/>
U.S. lawmakers want TikTok to be sold to a company outside of China due to concerns that the Chinese government could force ByteDance to hand over data from users located in the United States. If China made the request, ByteDance would not be able to refuse. There have also been suggestions that China could use TikTok to spread political propaganda.<br/>
<br/>
ByteDance has attempted to alleviate these fears by storing data from U.S. users on servers owned by Oracle, but the White House and lawmakers do not believe that is enough.<br/>
<br/>
If passed, the bill would require ByteDance to sell TikTok within six months to a company approved by the U.S. government. Should ByteDance not sell the company, U.S. app stores would not be able to distribute the app without breaking the law, effectively leading to a ban. China would also need to approve the sale, and the Chinese government <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/23/technology/tiktok-congress-hearing.html">made it clear</a> last year that it would "firmly oppose" a forced sale.<br/>
<br/>
There are a limited number of companies with enough capital to be able to afford TikTok, and the obvious choices, such as Google or Meta, would likely be barred from acquiring it due to antitrust concerns.<br/>
<br/>
Should the bill make it through the Senate, U.S. President Joe Biden confirmed that he would sign it into law. A number of senators have expressed worries about the wording of the act, and it does not have universal support at this time.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/">TikTok Closer to Potential U.S. Ban as House Passes Bill Requiring Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-closer-to-potential-u-s-ban-as-house-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2421834/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Most Subscription-Based Apps Do Not Make Money</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-most-subscription-based-apps-do-not-make-money.2421830/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:33:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Most mobile apps with subscriptions do not make money, a new in-depth analysis finds. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Clorange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833988" /><br/>
The "<a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/state-of-subscription-apps-2024/">State of Subscription Apps</a>" report comes from RevenueCat (via <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/03/12/most-subscription-mobile-apps-dont-make-money-new-report-shows/">TechCrunch</a></em>), a prominent mobile subscription toolkit provider. With nearly 30,000 apps utilizing its platform for monetization management, RevenueCat is able to provide a reliable overview of the subscription app landscape thanks to its data collection capabilities. The analysis delves into data from over 29,000 apps and 18,000 developers, collectively responsible for more than &#36;6.7 billion in revenue and over 290 million subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
RevenueCat found that while the top-performing 5% of subscription apps amass revenue 200 times greater than those in the bottom quartile, the median monthly revenue for apps after one year is less than &#36;50. Only 17.2% of apps cross the &#36;1,000 monthly revenue mark. Reaching this milestone significantly boosts the likelihood of further financial growth, with 59% of these apps progressing to achieve &#36;2,500 in monthly revenue, and 60% of those reaching the &#36;5,000 mark. A mere 3.5% of apps achieve &#36;10,000 in monthly revenue.<br/>
<br/>
Health and fitness apps generate at least twice the revenue of all other categories combined, both in the bottom quartile and among the top 5% of earners. In contrast, travel and productivity apps face the most significant challenges, with even the top performers in these categories struggling to make over &#36;1,000 per month after a year on the market.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these statistics, the subscription app market continues to grow and the average price for monthly subscriptions has increased by 14% from &#36;7.05 to &#36;8.01. However, the report also noted a recent shift in consumer behavior, with a 14% drop in subscriber retention over 12 months.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/">Report: Most Subscription-Based Apps Do Not Make Money</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-most-subscription-based-apps-do-not-make-money.2421830/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE to Just &#36;189</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-to-just-189.2421826/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:53:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a>, which is just &#36;10 higher compared to its all-time low price. This deal is available in the Silver Aluminum Case with Winter Blue Sport Loop and Midnight Aluminum Case with Midnight Sport Loop, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866330" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's available in Midnight, Silver, and Starlight Aluminum options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This model of the Apple Watch SE launched in September 2022 and remains Apple's most affordable Apple Watch. The Apple Watch SE lacks some of the upgraded features you'll find in some Series 9 or Ultra 2 models, like temperature sensing, ECG functionality, and blood oxygen monitoring, but it will otherwise provide you with all key Apple Watch features, and at the cheapest price possible.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-189/">Amazon Discounts 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE to Just &#36;189</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-to-just-189.2421826/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here&#039;s Everything We Know About Apple&#039;s Next-Generation CarPlay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-next-generation-carplay-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-everything-we-know-about-apples-next-generation-carplay.2421823/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 07:42:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-next-generation-carplay-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been nearly two years since Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/06/apple-announces-multi-display-carplay/">first previewed next-generation CarPlay</a> at WWDC 2022, and it has still yet to become available in any vehicles. Below, we recap the latest information about the upcoming software system.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/next-generation-carplay-multi-display.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848463" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Apple's render of next-generation CarPlay from WWDC 2022</em></div><br/>
Next-generation CarPlay will have deeper integration with a vehicle's instrument cluster, climate controls, FM radio, and more. It will also support multiple displays across the dashboard, and offer a variety of personalization options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Launch Timing</h2><br/>
Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed their customized next-generation CarPlay designs</a> in December. Aston Martin said it would release its first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay support in 2024, including a new model of its high-end DB12 sports car. Porsche did not provide a timeframe or specific details about its own plans.<br/>
<br/>
A spokesperson for Porsche this week told us that it has no update to provide about next-generation CarPlay availability at this time, while a spokesperson for Aston Martin has yet to respond to our request for comment.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Porsche's next-generation CarPlay preview from December 2023</em></div><br/>
In January, Apple updated its website to confirm that the first vehicle models with support for next-generation CarPlay <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">will debut "in 2024,"</a> but it has yet to provide a more specific timeframe. This wording is shown on Apple's websites for several countries, including the U.S., Canada, Australia, New Zealand, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Committed Automakers</h2><br/>
When it first announced next-generation CarPlay, Apple said the following automakers were committed to offering it in new vehicles:<ul><li>Acura</li><br/>
<li>Audi</li><br/>
<li>Ford</li><br/>
<li>Honda</li><br/>
<li>Infiniti</li><br/>
<li>Jaguar</li><br/>
<li>Land Rover</li><br/>
<li>Lincoln</li><br/>
<li>Mercedes-Benz</li><br/>
<li>Nissan</li><br/>
<li>Polestar</li><br/>
<li>Porsche</li><br/>
<li>Renault</li><br/>
<li>Volvo</li></ul>Beyond the addition of Aston Martin, it is unclear if this list has changed since that initial announcement at WWDC 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Aston-Martin.jpeg" alt="" width="980" height="551" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927535" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Aston Martin's next-generation CarPlay preview from December 2023</em></div><br/>
Apple has not indicated if any next-generation CarPlay apps or features will be available in existing vehicles with standard CarPlay support.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
<h3>Instrument Cluster Integration</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Multi-Display-CarPlay-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="896" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848187" /><br/>
Next-generation CarPlay will integrate with a vehicle's instrument cluster, including the speedometer, tachometer, odometer, fuel gauge, engine temperature gauge, oil pressure gauge, and more. Apple says drivers will be able to choose from several gauge cluster designs and layouts, including brand‑specific options.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Climate Controls</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/CarPlay-Next-Generation-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="3562" height="1990" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853339" /><br/>
You'll be able to access your vehicle's climate controls directly within the new CarPlay interface, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heat, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and other options.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Multi-Display Support</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/CarPlay-Next-Generation-Multi-Screens.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878824" /><br/>
Next-generation CarPlay will be able to appear across all of the displays in a vehicle, providing a consistent experience across the infotainment system, instrument cluster, and any additional screens on the dashboard. Apple says the new CarPlay will be tailored to each vehicle model to accommodate unique screen shapes and layouts. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Widgets</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/CarPlay-Next-Generation-Widgets.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878821" /><br/>
Widgets will be a key part of the new CarPlay experience, offering at-a-glance information such as trip duration, fuel economy, distance traveled, calendar events, weather, phone calls, the status of a HomeKit-enabled garage door, and more. It will also be possible to view and scroll through the widgets within the instrument cluster.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>FM Radio App</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/CarPlay-Next-Generation-Radio.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="899" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878822" /><br/>
Next-generation CarPlay will include an all-new Media app that allows you to easily control the FM radio in your vehicle, such as to change the station.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Apps</h2><br/>
iOS 17.4 for the iPhone includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">hidden code-level references to eight new CarPlay apps</a>:<ul><li><strong>Auto Settings:</strong> This app will let you manage paired iPhones and adjust vehicle settings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Car Camera:</strong> This app will display the vehicle's rear-view camera feed.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Charge:</strong> For electric vehicles, this app will display battery level, charging status, time remaining until the battery is fully charged, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Climate:</strong> This app will provide access to a vehicle's climate controls within CarPlay, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heating system, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Closures:</strong> This app will display if any of the vehicle's doors are opened, and it might also display vehicle warning symbols.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Media:</strong> This app will provide access to FM and AM radio station controls within CarPlay, along with other media options like SiriusXM. It is unclear if SiriusXM will offer satellite connectivity, or remain limited to internet streaming. Users will be able to select from a list of music genres, such as Top 40 and Rock.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Tire Pressure:</strong> This app will display air pressure for each of the vehicle's tires, and provide low pressure, high pressure, and flat tire warnings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Trips:</strong> This app will provide a variety of driving-related data, including the vehicle's average speed, fuel efficiency or energy efficiency, the total time elapsed and distance traveled on a trip, and more.</li></ul>iOS 17.4 also revealed that next-generation CarPlay will likely display a "Goodbye" animation on the dashboard display after the driver shuts off the vehicle:<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Goodbye.jpg" alt="" width="1374" height="484" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932992" /><br/>
As previously announced by Apple, additional images found in iOS 17.4 confirm that users will be able to adjust the theme and color scheme of next-generation CarPlay, including the appearance of the instrument cluster:<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Cluster-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="987" height="186" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932994" /><br/>
Apple released iOS 17.4 in early March, and it is possible that it will be the minimum software version required for next-generation CarPlay when it eventually launches. However, it is also possible that Apple still has final preparations to make in iOS 17.5 and beyond, so we will ultimately have to wait and see when the software is ready.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More Images</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Aston-Martin-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1508" height="793" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927565" /><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-2.jpeg" alt="" width="1540" height="854" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927564" /><br/>
<h2>Summary</h2><br/>
Apple says next-generation CarPlay will launch in 2024, but a more specific timeframe is still unknown. Aston Martin and Porsche have previewed their next-generation CarPlay designs, and the recently-released iOS 17.4 update for the iPhone includes hidden code-level references to next-generation CarPlay apps and features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-next-generation-carplay-recap/">Here&#039;s Everything We Know About Apple&#039;s Next-Generation CarPlay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/heres-everything-we-know-about-apples-next-generation-carplay.2421823/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins Assembling iPhone 15 in Brazil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-begins-assembling-iphone-15-in-brazil/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-assembling-iphone-15-in-brazil.2421818/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 06:37:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-begins-assembling-iphone-15-in-brazil/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Brazil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has started assembling the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> model in Brazil, shifting in its global manufacturing approach to mitigate high import taxes and diversify its supply chain.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Colors-black.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911672" /><br/>
As reported by <a href="https://macmagazine.com.br/post/2024/03/12/iphone-15-ja-estaria-sendo-fabricado-tambem-no-brasil/"><em>MacMagazine</em></a> (via <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/03/12/apple-assembling-iphone-15-brazil/">9to5Mac</a></em>), the assembly process is being carried out at the Foxconn facility in São Paulo and seeks to reduce the high import fees levied on electronics in Brazil, which significantly inflate the cost of electronics for consumers in the country.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not yet reduced the retail price of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; in Brazil, where it continues to sell for R&#36;7,300 (approximately &#36;1,460) for the 128GB model. This price is nearly double the device's starting price in the United States. The initiative also is part of Apple's broader strategy to diversify its manufacturing footprint beyond China and reduce its reliance on a single region.<br/>
<br/>
Only the 6.1-inch &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; model is being assembled in Brazil. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, Pro, and Pro Max models continue to be imported from China. Brazilian customers can identify whether their &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; was assembled locally by checking the model number, with units produced in Brazil carrying the identifier "BR/A." In contrast, imported units are denoted by "BE/A" and "BZ/A." <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/brazil/">Brazil</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-begins-assembling-iphone-15-in-brazil/">Apple Begins Assembling iPhone 15 in Brazil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-assembling-iphone-15-in-brazil.2421818/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>VLC Media Player Potentially Coming to Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vlc-media-player-apple-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vlc-media-player-potentially-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2421814/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 05:41:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vlc-media-player-apple-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>VLC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.videolan.org">VideoLAN</a> is working on bringing its popular open source VLC media player to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, according to tech newsletter <em><a href="https://www.lowpass.cc/p/vlc-five-billion-downloads-vision-pro-app">Lowpass</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Vision-Pro-VLC-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-941109" /><br/>
The non-profit organization said it was currently developing a version for Apple's spatial computing headset. "We already have a version of VLC running on the Vision Pro," VideoLAN president Jean-Baptiste Kempf told <em>Lowpass</em> writer Janko Roettgers. <br/>
<br/>
However, one of the reasons the app hasn't already been released is that the potential user base is still considered too small. "I'm not sure there is any use case yet," added Kempf. <br/>
<br/>
VLC recently surpassed five billion downloads across desktop and mobile platforms, according to the organization. The cross-platform media player and framework launched 23 years ago as a student project, and continues to attract millions of new users thanks to its support for multiple codecs and its ability to play multimedia files as well as DVDs, Audio CDs, VCDs, and various streaming protocols.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, work continues on VLC 4.0. Development has taken longer than anticipated, according to Kempf, with the core of the app being completely rewritten. Recent nightly builds put the focus on content, with the default player window replaced by a view of the user's library. However, Kempf said that some changes could be reverted before the app's official release. <br/>
<br/>
Kempf said that VLC may even add access to FAST channels and other ad-supported online media in the future, potentially allowing users to start watching something right away.<br/>
<br/>
VLC 3.0.20 is a free downloaded for Mac from the <a href="https://www.videolan.org">VideoLAN website</a>. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vlc/">VLC</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vlc-media-player-apple-vision-pro/">VLC Media Player Potentially Coming to Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vlc-media-player-potentially-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2421814/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>GarageBand for Mac Updated With Important Security Fix</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/garageband-for-mac-important-security-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/garageband-for-mac-updated-with-important-security-fix.2421813/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 05:31:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/garageband-for-mac-important-security-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>GarageBand</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week updated GarageBand for Mac with an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214090">important security fix</a>. Users should update the app as soon as possible due to this security vulnerability.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/GarageBand-Mac-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941037" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214090">support document</a> for the new GarageBand version, Apple said "a use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management":<blockquote><strong>GarageBand</strong><br/>
<br/>
Available for: macOS Ventura and macOS Sonoma<br/>
<br/>
Impact: Processing a maliciously crafted file may lead to unexpected app termination or arbitrary code execution<br/>
<br/>
Description: A use-after-free issue was addressed with improved memory management.<br/>
<br/>
CVE-2024-23300: Marc Schoenefeld, Dr. rer. nat.</blockquote>GarageBand version 10.4.11 is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/garageband/id682658836">available on the Mac App Store</a>. The update also includes stability improvements and bug fixes, according to Apple.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/garageband/">GarageBand</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/garageband-for-mac-important-security-fix/">GarageBand for Mac Updated With Important Security Fix</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/garageband-for-mac-updated-with-important-security-fix.2421813/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Begins Rolling Out Music Videos in Beta Across 11 Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/spotify-begins-rolling-out-music-videos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-begins-rolling-out-music-videos-in-beta-across-11-countries.2421810/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 04:31:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/spotify-begins-rolling-out-music-videos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify today <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2024-03-13/music-videos-rolling-out-in-beta-to-premium-spotify-users-across-select-markets/">announced</a> support for music videos, a new feature the streaming service describes as a "beta" with a limited catalog that is available in 11 markets.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/spotify-music-videos.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941015" /><br/>
Music videos for supported tracks will show up in the Now Playing screen for Spotify Premium users in the UK, Germany, Italy, the Netherlands, Poland, Sweden, Brazil, Colombia, Philippines, Indonesia, and Kenya.<br/>
<br/>
A "Switch to Video" icon appears above the song title in supported music tracks. Tapping starts the song from the beginning with accompanying video within the Now Playing view, which can also be rotated to landscape orientation on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Android. <br/>
<br/>
Supported artists include Ed Sheeran, Doja Cat, Ice Spice, Aluna, and Asake, and the videos can also be accessed on desktop or smart TVs. Spofity told <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/03/13/spotify-adds-music-videos-in-some-countries/">TechCrunch</a></em> that its full music catalog will eventually include "thousands" of songs.<br/>
<br/>
Previously, video content on Spotify has been limited to video podcasts and short repeating music video clips when a song plays. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> has included its own music video catalog for six years now. The feature was introduced with the release of iOS 11.3 in March 2018.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/spotify-begins-rolling-out-music-videos/">Spotify Begins Rolling Out Music Videos in Beta Across 11 Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-begins-rolling-out-music-videos-in-beta-across-11-countries.2421810/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Brave Browser Reports Spike in EU Installs After iOS 17.4 DMA Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/brave-browser-rise-installs-ios-14-7-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/brave-browser-reports-spike-in-eu-installs-after-ios-17-4-dma-changes.2421806/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:44:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/brave-browser-rise-installs-ios-14-7-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Brave</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alternative browser company <a href="https://brave.com">Brave</a> has reported a sharp increase in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> installs since Apple made sweeping changes to iOS in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act in the European Union. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/alternative-browser-list-eu.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941009" /><br/>
With the recent iOS 17.4 update, users in the EU are presented with a splash screen upon opening Safari that allows them to choose a new default browser. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is not providing just the standard browsers that have been options on iOS in the past, but a list of the most downloaded browsers on iOS devices. Some of the options include Firefox, Opera, Chrome, Brave, and Microsoft Edge.<br/>
<br/>
Brave <a href="https://x.com/brave/status/1767643225773215918?s=20">shared an image on X (Twitter)</a> of a line graph showing the number of Brave browser installations on iOS from mid-January to early March. Daily installs hovered around 7,500 to 10,000, before jumping to just over 11,000 following the release of iOS 17.4 on March 6.<br/>
<br/>
"Monopoly defenders argue that the monopolies simply offer better products," wrote Brave in a <a href="https://x.com/brave/status/1767643227534901741?s=20">subsequent post</a>. "But as you can see, when consumers get a clear choice of iOS browsers, they're choosing alternatives to Safari."<br/>
<br/>
"Maybe that's why Google still hasn't implemented a browser choice screen on Android," added the privacy-centric browser company.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Why did Apple and Google make it hard to switch default browsers for so many years?<br><br>Because it&#39;s a powerful way to block competitors.<br><br>Just look at what happened to Brave installs on iPhone in the EU when Apple rolled out a new default browser choice screen on March 6th: <a href="https://t.co/Wefz4mCHGi">pic.twitter.com/Wefz4mCHGi</a></p>&mdash; Brave Software (@brave) <a href="https://twitter.com/brave/status/1767643225773215918?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 12, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
To be eligible for consideration in the alternative browsers list, <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/browser-choice-screen/">Apple notes</a> that they must have the Default Browser Entitlement that is now available to developers and have been downloaded by "at least 5,000 users across all the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> storefronts on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the prior calendar year."<br/>
<br/>
Apple selects up to 11 of these for the browser choice screen in addition to Safari, updating the list once per calendar year. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/brave/">Brave</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/brave-browser-rise-installs-ios-14-7-eu/">Brave Browser Reports Spike in EU Installs After iOS 17.4 DMA Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/brave-browser-reports-spike-in-eu-installs-after-ios-17-4-dma-changes.2421806/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>macOS Sonoma 14.4 Causing USB Hub Issues for Some Users</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-causing-usb-hub-issues-for-some-users.2421804/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:03:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Some Mac users who updated to Apple's latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-4/">macOS Sonoma 14.4 software release</a> are experiencing connectivity issues with USB hubs and monitors with USB ports, with several reports of mice, keyboards, and other peripherals no longer being detected.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/belkin-usb-c-hub.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893632" /><br/>
Users have taken to the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonoma-14-4-breaks-usb-c-monitor-with-hubs.2421678/"><em>MacRumors</em> forums</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/MacOS/comments/1b9volo">Reddit</a>, <a href="https://x.com/rhysmorgan/status/1766171380272300262?s=20">X (Twitter)</a>, and the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255518397">Apple Support Community forums</a> to relay their experiences, a selection of which we've reproduced below.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> forum member <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/sonoma-14-4-breaks-usb-c-monitor-with-hubs.2421678/post-33005062">mjodotcom</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>14.4 definitely breaks USB hub monitor functionality. Things worked without a hitch until my work MBP upgraded to 14.4 and now no devices are detected. On my personal MBP that is still on 14.3 everything is detected without issue. Clearly a OS related problem. </blockquote>Reddit user <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/MacOS/comments/1b9volo/usb_hub_on_monitor_no_longer_working_on_macbook/">Nobodys10</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>I have my MacBook (MacBook Pro 16 M2 Pro) connected to my monitor (Gigabyte M34WQ 34 Inch IPS Ultrawide WQHD (3440 x 1440)) via a thunderbolt 3 cable.<br/>
<br/>
I have my keyboard and mouse connected to the USB ports in my monitor. After updating, my keyboard and mouse are no longer being detected on my MacBook. Before updating, it was working fine.</blockquote>Apple Support Community user <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255518397?answerId=260266531022&sortBy=best#260266531022">LucaPascarella</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>I have the same issue with my MacBook Pro M2 Max 64GB RAM and monitor Dell U3219Q; none of the USB peripherals connected to the Monitor's USB hub work.<br/>
<br/>
On the contrary, all peripherals work fine when I attach a Windows computer to the Dell Monitor. In addition, I check every USB peripheral by attaching them directly to the Mac, and of course, they are working.<br/>
<br/>
I rebooted the Mac and detached the power plug from the Monitor, trying any configurations or sequences of rebooting as possible. Nothing is working since the update to Sonoma 14.4.</blockquote>X user <a href="http://Love that macOS 14.4 has completely killed the use of my display KVM. Just not picking up any USB devices plugged into my monitor (or even that my monitor is a USB hub too).">Rhys Morgan</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>Love that macOS 14.4 has completely killed the use of my display KVM. Just not picking up any USB devices plugged into my monitor (or even that my monitor is a USB hub too).</blockquote>While Apple works on a fix, a handful of users have had some success by changing the setting "Allow accessories to connect" to "Ask for new accessories" under the Security section of System Settings ➝ Privacy & Security.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/allow-accessories-to-connect-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="1425" height="684" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941035" /><br/>
Have you had a problem connecting peripherals over USB hubs since updating to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4? Let us know in the comments.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, Matt!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-usb-hub-issues-reported/">macOS Sonoma 14.4 Causing USB Hub Issues for Some Users</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macos-sonoma-14-4-causing-usb-hub-issues-for-some-users.2421804/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.3.1, Downgrading No Longer Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-3-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-3-1-downgrading-no-longer-available.2421778/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:45:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-3-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 17.3.1 preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS. iOS 17.3.1 is no longer being signed following the March 5 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-4-features/">release of iOS 17.4</a>, an update that introduced app ecosystem changes in the EU, new emoji, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-17.3.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935028" /><br/>
Apple routinely stops signing older versions of iOS, so it is not unusual that the iOS 17.3.1 update is no longer available. Apple prevents users from installing older versions of iOS to encourage customers to keep their operating systems up to date and to prevent downgrading to older, less secure versions of the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; operating system.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 is now the only publicly released version of iOS available. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-3-1/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.3.1, Downgrading No Longer Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-3-1-downgrading-no-longer-available.2421778/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Pulse Oximetry Can Be Reactivated Through Software in 2028 or With Successful Appeal</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-software/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-pulse-oximetry-can-be-reactivated-through-software-in-2028-or-with-successful-appeal.2421763/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:23:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-software/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been selling the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-without-blood-oxygen/">without the blood oxygen monitoring feature</a> in the U.S. since mid-January, and while we've suspected Apple would be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/masimo-ceo-apple-blood-oxygen-sensor-unreliable/">reintroduce pulse oximetry</a> in models that lack it through a future software update, new information from the U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) confirms that reactivation is indeed a possibility. As a recap, Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">found to be infringing</a> on patented pulse oximetry technology owned by Masimo, and was banned from importing the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 into the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895884" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/apple-watch-ultra-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" /><br/>
The original January 12 order from CBP that allowed Apple to bring Apple Watch models with a disabled sensor in the United States <a href="https://rulings.cbp.gov/ruling/H335304">was published</a> recently (<a href="https://ipfray.com/exclusive-if-you-recently-bought-an-apple-watch-in-the-u-s-youll-likely-get-pulse-oximetry-for-free-provided-that-apples-appeal-succeeds/">via <em>ip fray</a></em>), and it gives some insight into how Apple disabled pulse oximetry. While some of the order is redacted, Apple implemented a fix that turns off pulse oximetry when an Apple Watch is paired to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>. Blood oxygen sensing becomes inaccessible to the user, and opening the blood oxygen app gives a warning that the feature is not available. Apple said that it hardcoded each Apple Watch at the factory with new software.<br/>
<br/>
As part of the process to get approval to sell &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 models without pulse oximetry enabled, Apple had to provide the code disabling the feature and test devices to Masimo. Masimo didn't want Apple to have such an easy fix, so it paired the "redesigned" Apple Watches with a jailbroken &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running an older version of iOS, and was able to get pulse oximetry working.<br/>
<br/>
Masimo tried to argue that activating pulse oximetry through a jailbroken phone meant Apple had not effectively removed the feature and the devices should not be allowed to be imported in to the U.S. Masimo also tried to say that jailbreaking is "permissible, common, and readily known," but Masimo's arguments were unsuccessful. The Exclusion Order Enforcement Branch of the U.S. Customs and Border Patrol ultimately decided that disabling pulse oximetry in the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 was enough to avoid infringing on Masimo patents, allowing those models to be offered for sale at Apple retail stores in the U.S.<br/>
<br/>
Because Masimo was able to get blood oxygen sensing working using software on a jailbroken &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Apple too would be able to reactivate the blood oxygen sensor in the models where it has been disabled through a software update. When no longer subject to an import ban, Apple will be able to reintroduce blood oxygen sensing for &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; users who are not able to access the feature.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://ipfray.com/exclusive-if-you-recently-bought-an-apple-watch-in-the-u-s-youll-likely-get-pulse-oximetry-for-free-provided-that-apples-appeal-succeeds/">ip fray</a></em>, the patents that Apple was found to have infringed on expire in August of 2028, which means that Apple will be able to re-enable pulse oximetry in affected models at that time. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">filed an appeal</a> with the United States International Trade Commission to attempt to get the ruling overturned, so if the appeal is successful, Apple could be able to re-add blood oxygen sensing sooner.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could also opt to settle with Masimo and work out a licensing deal, but at this point, it doesn't sound like that is going to happen. Masimo CEO Joe Kiani said in January that he <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/masimo-ceo-apple-blood-oxygen-sensor-unreliable/">had not spoken with Apple</a>, and while he would be open to settling, an apology and an "honest dialogue" would need to be part of any settlement discussion.<br/>
<br/>
Kiani has maligned the Apple Watch blood oxygen sensor several times, saying that customers are "better off without" the feature because it is not a "reliable, medical pulse oximeter."<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 only have disabled blood oxygen sensing capabilities in the United States, as the ban is not applicable in other countries. The Apple Watches remain fully functional outside of the U.S.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-watch-blood-oxygen-sensor-software/">Apple Watch Pulse Oximetry Can Be Reactivated Through Software in 2028 or With Successful Appeal</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-pulse-oximetry-can-be-reactivated-through-software-in-2028-or-with-successful-appeal.2421763/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Teases New Store &#039;Coming Soon&#039; at Square One Mall Near Toronto</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-teases-new-square-one-store-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-teases-new-store-coming-soon-at-square-one-mall-near-toronto.2421756/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:39:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-teases-new-square-one-store-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that it will be opening a new retail store at the Square One shopping mall in the Canadian city of Mississauga, Ontario, a suburb of Toronto. Apple's existing store in the mall will be permanently closed.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/New-Apple-Square-One.jpg" alt="" width="3800" height="2138" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940947" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The new Apple Square One</em></div><br/>
"A brand-new Apple Store is coming soon," the <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/retail/squareone/">store's page</a> says. The teaser message was <a href="https://mastodon.social/@michaelsteeber/112084399504297364">spotted by Michael Steeber</a>, who writes a <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/">weekly newsletter about Apple retail called Tabletops</a>, and tipster <a href="https://twitter.com/ApolloZhaoD/status/1767589911169839393">Apollo Zhao</a> also alerted us to the news.<br/>
<br/>
The new store is located on the second floor of Square One, above the central food court, and it has a very wide, partially-curved facade.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's existing store at Square One opened in August 2009. The new location is significantly larger, and it will better accommodate the heavy customer traffic at Square One, the second-largest indoor shopping mall in Canada.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to share an exact opening date for the new store, and the company did not immediately respond to a request for comment.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-teases-new-square-one-store-canada/">Apple Teases New Store &#039;Coming Soon&#039; at Square One Mall Near Toronto</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-teases-new-store-coming-soon-at-square-one-mall-near-toronto.2421756/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Video Comparison: M3 MacBook Air vs. M3 MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/m3-macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-comparison-m3-macbook-air-vs-m3-macbook-pro.2421739/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:42:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/m3-macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the refresh of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models in March, Apple now has M3 versions of the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, 14-inch MacBook Pro, and 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, all with the same chip inside. For those trying to decide between the MacBook Pro and the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, we did a comparison video to highlight what you're getting with each machine.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dsTKUHdjzVE" title="M3 MacBook AIR vs M3 MacBook PRO: Real World Differences!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
While the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and the 14-inch MacBook Pro have the same M3 chip, there is a difference with the low-end &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. At the entry-level &#36;1,099 price, the 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has an 8-core CPU and 8-core GPU. The more expensive &#36;1,299 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has an 8-core CPU and upgraded 10-core GPU, with all 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and 14-inch MacBook Pro models also starting with the upgraded 10-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
So you can get a &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; for as little as &#36;1,099, but at that price point, the GPU is downgraded. That won't matter for general day-to-day use, but it's something to keep in mind. The 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;1,299, and the 14-inch MacBook Pro is priced starting at &#36;1,599, so there is a major price difference.<br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch MacBook Pro is priced higher because it starts with a 512GB SSD instead of 256GB like the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, and because it has a better display. Apple uses a mini-LED Liquid Retina XDR display that has ProMotion with refresh rates up to 120Hz and up to 1,600 nits peak brightness. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has an LCD display with up to 500 nits brightness, so the real notable difference between the machines is the display quality.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mini-led/">Mini-LED</a> offers deeper blacks, more vivid colors, and it overall just looks better, especially for work where color is important like photo editing and for watching movies or other HDR content. There are no fans inside the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, while the MacBook Pro has fans for active cooling. In theory, you could see better performance out of the M3 with the active cooling when using very system intensive tasks. Ports are another difference, with the MacBook Pro featuring an HDMI 2.1 port and an SDXC card slot in addition to two Thunderbolt 4/USB-C ports. The &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; doesn't have the extra ports, and is limited to the two Thunderbolt 4 ports.<br/>
<br/>
Both versions of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; are thinner and lighter than the 14-inch MacBook Pro, so the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; wins out when it comes to portability, but the MacBook Pro has longer battery life (18 hours for the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; vs. 22 hours for the MacBook Pro. Other specs are largely the same, though there are some differences in speaker and microphone quality.<br/>
<br/>
Basically, the 14-inch MacBook Pro is more expensive but has better display quality, while the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; wins out when it comes to portability and price. Choosing one will depend on workload, but the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is the computer that we recommend for most people. You'll want to go with the MacBook Pro if display quality is important or if there are specific ports you need.<br/>
<br/>
Make sure to watch our video up above for a full comparison of the two machines, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/">we also have a comparison guide</a> that includes the M3 Pro and M3 Max chips.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/m3-macbook-air-vs-macbook-pro/">Video Comparison: M3 MacBook Air vs. M3 MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/video-comparison-m3-macbook-air-vs-m3-macbook-pro.2421739/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MicroLED Apple Watch Ultra Project Potentially Loses Another Supplier</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/microled-apple-watch-potential-supplier-lost/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microled-apple-watch-ultra-project-potentially-loses-another-supplier.2421730/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 09:56:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/microled-apple-watch-potential-supplier-lost/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch Ultra project</a> may have lost another key supplier, according to Display Supply Chain Consultants CEO Ross Young.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://www.sec.gov/ixviewer/ix.html?doc=/Archives/edgar/data/56978/000005697824000042/klic-20240311.htm">filing</a> with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Monday, manufacturing equipment company Kulicke & Soffa said that one of its "strategic customers" has canceled a project related to the "advanced display" market:<blockquote>Previously referred to as Project W, the Company has been engaged with one of its strategic customers (the "Customer") to support the Customer with the development and future mass production of certain technologies relating to advanced display (the "Project"). In connection with the Customer's strategic review of its business, the Customer has informed the Company that it has cancelled the Project.</blockquote>In a <a href="https://twitter.com/DSCCRoss/status/1767341370845598076">social media post</a> on Monday, Young suggested that "Project W" was potentially related to the microLED Apple Watch. The company said it expects to incur charges of up to &#36;130 million as a result of ceasing operations related to the project.<br/>
<br/>
Kulicke & Soffa's website advertises a "next generation LED die transfer" system for microLED and miniLED displays with "an unprecedented transfer rate at high precision." <br/>
<br/>
Earlier this month, Apple supplier AMS-Osram <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">similarly announced</a> it would "re-assess its microLED strategy" after a "cornerstone project" was "unexpectedly cancelled." Young believes that project also related to the microLED Apple Watch, so there are now at least two major suppliers that have indicated they are no longer involved.<br/>
<br/>
Both <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/blog/apple-cancels-microled-project">Display Supply Chain Consultants</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/kuo-says-microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a> believe that Apple has outright canceled the microLED Apple Watch project for now, but other sources like <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman and <em>DigiTimes</em> have <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1763297383046365515">cast doubt</a> and believe that Apple has or is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-still-dedicated-microled-apple-watch-ultra/">actively seeking alternative suppliers</a> for the project.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, a microLED Apple Watch Ultra appears to remain several years away at a minimum.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/microled-apple-watch-potential-supplier-lost/">MicroLED Apple Watch Ultra Project Potentially Loses Another Supplier</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microled-apple-watch-ultra-project-potentially-loses-another-supplier.2421730/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
