<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 17:10:55 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ring Rumors: What We&#039;ve Heard About Apple&#039;s Work on a Smart Ring</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ring/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ring-rumors-what-weve-heard-about-apples-work-on-a-smart-ring.2421957/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 15:26:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ring&#038;post_date=1710465992/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>Apple Ring</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There have been several rumors in recent weeks about Apple's work on a finger-worn smart ring, and while it's not clear if the project is in active development at this time, we thought we'd round up the rumors that are circulating.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937059" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/samsung-galaxy-ring.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="529" /><em>Samsung's upcoming Galaxy Ring</em></div><br/>
This guide aggregates what we've heard so far on an Apple-branded smart ring.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="potential_features">Potential Features</h2><br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-ring-allegedly-in-development/">February rumor</a> from <em>Electronic Times</em> suggested that Apple is "speeding up development" on a smart ring with health-related features.<br/>
<br/>
Like the Apple Watch, an Apple Ring could track heart rate, activity, sleep, and respiratory rate, using that information to provide users with sleep insights and health recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could also potentially use a smart ring as an input device for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Vision Pro, or Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ring_vs._watch">Ring vs. Watch</h2><br/>
Apple already has an Apple Watch that is able to track multiple health metrics, but a smart ring would be more comfortable for certain activities. A ring could be preferable for sleep, for example, or in situations where the wrists need to be covered, like when wearing supportive wrist wraps.<br/>
<br/>
A ring would not likely need a constant connection to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or another Apple device because it has no display, so the battery would probably last for a longer period of time. On the downside, a smart ring would convey information via Bluetooth or a similar method, so while it would collect data, that data would not be synced to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in real-time as it is with the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
There is a possibility that a smart ring would be more affordable than the Apple Watch, with higher-end smart rings priced at around &#36;300 from Apple's competitors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apples_competition">Apple's Competition</h2><br/>
Samsung is developing a Galaxy Ring that is expected to be available in the second half of the year. It can track heart rate, activity, and sleep, plus it is able to make wireless payments and control Samsung devices.<br/>
<br/>
Companies <a href="https://ouraring.com/product/rings">like Oura</a> and <a href="https://www.ultrahuman.com">Ultrahuman</a> have been making and selling smart rings for several years. The third-generation Oura ring is able to collect activity information and measure heart rate, respiratory rate, and sleep quality.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.ultrahuman.com/ring/buy/us/">Ultrahuman Ring Air</a> measures heart rate, skin temperature, respiratory rate, recovery times, and sleep.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ring_patents">Ring Patents</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/patently-apple/2020/03/apple-wins-patent-for-a-ring-accessory-to-control-content-presented-on-future-virtual-reality-glasses-headset.html">patented smart ring technology</a>. One patent, for example, explains how a smart ring (or several smart rings) could be used as a control method for a VR headset. Sensors in the ring would gather input from the user, and haptic output could provide feedback.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/patently-apple/2019/10/apple-has-won-its-first-smart-ring-patent-with-biometrics-touch-pad-sir-to-control-devices-including-a-tv.html">Another patent</a> describes using a ring with a touch-sensitive display to control a TV or tablet, while a third outlines a <a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/2023/11/apple-wins-a-patent-covering-a-smart-ring-that-uses-nfc-and-is-able-to-act-as-a-vision-pro-controller-with-in-air-gestures.html">smart ring with NFC</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
While <em>Electronic Times</em> said that Apple is seriously considering a smart ring, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/25/apple-has-explored-smart-ring-and-glasses/">claimed in February</a> that Apple is not actively developing a finger-worn device at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's industrial design team did present the idea of a smart ring focused on health and fitness to executives a few years back, but it may not be a project that Apple is planning to bring to market right now.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ring/">Apple Ring Rumors: What We&#039;ve Heard About Apple&#039;s Work on a Smart Ring</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ring-rumors-what-weve-heard-about-apples-work-on-a-smart-ring.2421957/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Complains That Apple Hasn&#039;t Approved Update With Subscription Pricing and Links in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/spotify-no-apple-approval-subscription-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-complains-that-apple-hasnt-approved-update-with-subscription-pricing-and-links-in-eu.2421950/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:08:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/spotify-no-apple-approval-subscription-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has not approved a Spotify app update that adds information on subscription pricing and links its website, Spotify complained today in an email to the European Commission (via <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/14/24100944/spotify-ios-app-update-eu-apple-dma">The Verge</a></em>). Spotify says that Apple has not "acknowledged nor responded" to its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> submission.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-vs-Spotify-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801789" /><br/>
The European Commission on March 4 fined Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">almost &#36;2 billion</a> and said that Apple abused its dominant position in the market by preventing music streaming services from telling users about more affordable subscription prices outside of their iOS apps. The EC said that it is "illegal under EU antitrust rules" for Apple to keep developers from telling customers about cheaper music subscription options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was told that it must "remove anti-steering provisions" in the European Union, and so on March 5, Spotify submitted an app update that included subscription pricing tiers and options to pay without using in-app purchase. Spotify says that it has not had a response from Apple since submitting the update.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify told the European Commission that Apple's lack of response is "yet another example" of how Apple "will seek to circumvent and/or not comply with the Commission's decision." Spotify asked the EC to require Apple to approve the app update.<br/>
<br/>
In a statement to <em>The Verge</em>, Spotify also said that Apple's delay "directly conflicts" with Apple's statements about processing app submissions within 24 hours, and "flies in the face of the timeline for adoption" from the EC.<blockquote>It's been nine days now and we're still waiting to hear from Apple about our app submission to show EU consumers pricing and a link to our website, which we are now authorized to do by the European Commission's decision on the music streaming case. Apple's delay directly conflicts with their claim that they turn around reviews on app submissions within 24 hours, and it also flies in the face of the timeline for adoption the Commission laid out.</blockquote>The ruling from the European Commission that requires Apple to eliminate anti-steering rules is separate from the app ecosystem changes that Apple made in the European Union <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/apple-releases-ios-17-4/">with iOS 17.4</a> to comply with the Digital Markets Act (DMA).<br/>
<br/>
Under the terms of the DMA, Spotify is allowed to distribute a Spotify app to EU users outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but it would be required to pay Apple's Core Technology Fee for each user. Spotify currently does not pay Apple any commission.<br/>
<br/>
The DMA also permits Spotify to direct users to make purchases on its website while also providing information on in-app promotions, discounts, and deals, but again, Spotify would need to agree to Apple's updated business terms and fees to implement these changes. Spotify has not clarified if it adopted Apple's new terms or if its update has been submitted without doing so.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/spotify-no-apple-approval-subscription-update/">Spotify Complains That Apple Hasn&#039;t Approved Update With Subscription Pricing and Links in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-complains-that-apple-hasnt-approved-update-with-subscription-pricing-and-links-in-eu.2421950/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Buys DarwinAI Ahead of Major Generative AI Updates Coming in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-acquires-darwinai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-buys-darwinai-ahead-of-major-generative-ai-updates-coming-in-ios-18.2421935/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 10:27:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-acquires-darwinai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Acquisition</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple acquired Canada-based company DarwinAI earlier this year to build out its AI team, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-14/apple-aapl-buys-canadian-ai-startup-darwinai-as-part-of-race-to-add-features">Bloomberg</a></em>. DarwinAI created AI technology for inspecting components during the manufacturing process, and it also had a focus on making smaller and more efficient AI systems.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840591" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" /><br/>
DarwinAI's website and social media accounts have been taken offline following Apple's purchase. Dozens of former DarwinAI companies have now joined Apple's artificial intelligence division. AI researcher Alexander Wong, who helped build DarwinAI, is now a director in Apple's AI group.<br/>
<br/>
Apple confirmed the acquisition with the statement that it typically gives when questioned about purchases. "Apple buys smaller technology companies from time to time" but does not discuss its purpose or plans.<br/>
<br/>
In an effort to catch up with Microsoft, Google, and others in the AI market, Apple is working hard to build artificial intelligence features for its next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and macOS 15 operating systems.<br/>
<br/>
If Apple wants to be able to rival Microsoft's Bing, OpenAI's ChatGPT, and other generative AI offerings, it will need to integrate generative AI into a range of products. Apple is testing large language models, and AI features are said to be coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, Shortcuts, Messages, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is aiming to have AI features run on-device for privacy reasons, and DarwinAI's efforts to make smaller AI systems could be of use to further that endeavor.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">has promised</a> that Apple will "break new ground" in generative AI in 2024. "We believe it will unlock transformative opportunities for our users," said Cook.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-acquisition/">Apple Acquisition</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-acquires-darwinai/">Apple Buys DarwinAI Ahead of Major Generative AI Updates Coming in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-buys-darwinai-ahead-of-major-generative-ai-updates-coming-in-ios-18.2421935/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hello Kitty to Make Special Appearance at Apple Union Square</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/hello-kitty-apple-union-square/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hello-kitty-to-make-special-appearance-at-apple-union-square.2421929/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:55:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/hello-kitty-apple-union-square/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[To celebrate an in-game event for popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> game Hello Kitty Island Adventure, Apple is teaming up with Sanrio to have Hello Kitty herself visit <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/unionsquare/">Apple Union Square</a> in San Francisco, California.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/hello-kitty-island-adventure.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941307" /><br/>
Hello Kitty will be at the San Francisco store on Wednesday, March 20 from 4:00 p.m. to 6:00 p.m. That is the week of the Game Developers Conference, so GDC attendees that are visiting the city will be able to attend to meet Hello Kitty.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that Hello Kitty will spread a message of happiness, friendship, and inclusivity, which matches the theme of the Hello Kitty Island Adventure in-game event. The virtual event, which takes place from March 18 to 25, celebrates International Day of Happiness. Players will be tasked with spreading joy through a surprise recipe and with surprise gifts.<br/>
<br/>
Chelsea Howe, Chief Product Officer of Sunblink (the developer behind Hello Kitty Island Adventure), and Jill Koch, SVP of Marketing at Sanrio, will also be accompanying Hello Kitty at Apple Union Square. The two will speak on the inspiration behind the game.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hello-kitty-island-adventure/id1553505132">Hello Kitty Island Adventure</a> is part of the <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade gaming subscription</a>, priced at &#36;6.99 per month. All members of a family group can play &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games for the single subscription price. Hello Kitty Island Adventure is updated on a regular basis with new in-game content and events.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/hello-kitty-apple-union-square/">Hello Kitty to Make Special Appearance at Apple Union Square</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hello-kitty-to-make-special-appearance-at-apple-union-square.2421929/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Chrome Gains Real-Time URL Protection on Mac and iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/chrome-real-time-url-protection/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-gains-real-time-url-protection-on-mac-and-ios.2421924/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/chrome-real-time-url-protection/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Chrome</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google <a href="https://security.googleblog.com/2024/03/blog-post.html">today announced</a> that it is upgrading Google Safe Browsing with real-time URL protection to keep Chrome users safe from malicious websites. Safe Browsing is designed to protect against phishing attacks, malware, and unwanted software by checking URLs against a master list.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Chrome-Feature-22.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851161" /><br/>
The Standard protection for Chrome previously used a list that is stored on device and updated every 30 to 60 minutes, but now websites will be checked against Google's server-side list of known bad sites in real time. Google says it expects to block 25 percent more phishing attempts with the change.<br/>
<br/>
Google is partnering with Fastly to operate an Oblivious HTTP privacy server between Chrome and Safe Browsing in order to preserve user privacy. Safe Browsing does not see the user's IP address, and Safe Browsing checks are mixed with those sent from other Chrome users.<br/>
<br/>
Chrome users can alternatively opt in to Enhanced Protection, a Safe Browsing mode that uses AI to block attacks and offers protection against malicious Chrome extensions.<br/>
<br/>
Google also recently updated Password Checkup on iOS devices. In addition to making users aware of compromised passwords, it will flag weak and reused passwords as well.<br/>
<br/>
Chrome is a free browser that is available as an alternative to Safari on the Mac, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chrome/">Chrome</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/chrome-real-time-url-protection/">Google Chrome Gains Real-Time URL Protection on Mac and iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-chrome-gains-real-time-url-protection-on-mac-and-ios.2421924/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Up to &#36;100 Off Apple&#039;s 9th Gen iPad, Available From &#36;249.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apples-9th-gen-ipad-100-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-100-off-apples-9th-gen-ipad-available-from-249-99.2421919/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:58:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apples-9th-gen-ipad-100-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A pair of deals on Apple's 10.2-inch 9th generation iPad have appeared this week at both Best Buy and Amazon, including low prices on the 64GB and 256GB Wi-Fi models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/10.2-inch-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-834111" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, you can get this tablet for <a href="https://howl.me/clPB9oS5fTS"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a> at Best Buy, down from &#36;329.99. This is a solid second-best price on the iPad, and Best Buy has it in both Silver and Space Gray. Amazon is <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matching the price</a> as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clPB9oS5fTS"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;249.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad on sale, available at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91TLNJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;379.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;479.00. This price is a match of the all-time low price on the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad. Best Buy is <a href="https://howl.me/clPCdRxORyA">providing the same discount</a>, but it's only available to My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91TLNJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apples-9th-gen-ipad-100-off/">Get Up to &#36;100 Off Apple&#039;s 9th Gen iPad, Available From &#36;249.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-up-to-100-off-apples-9th-gen-ipad-available-from-249-99.2421919/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Said iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Would Expand to These 8 U.S. States… Two Years Ago</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-wallet-app-ids-slow-adoption/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-iphone-drivers-licenses-would-expand-to-these-8-u-s-states…-two-years-ago.2421915/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 07:33:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-wallet-app-ids-slow-adoption/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Wallet</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In just four U.S. states, residents can <a href="https://learn.wallet.apple/id">add their driver's license or ID to the Apple Wallet app</a> on the iPhone and Apple Watch, providing a convenient and contactless way to display proof of identity or age at select airports, businesses, and venues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/apple-wallet-drivers-license-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1698" height="956" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-813979" /><br/>
Adoption of the feature has been slow since Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/01/apple-shares-us-states-adopting-wallet-ids/">first announced it in September 2021</a>, with IDs in the Wallet app only available in Arizona, Maryland, Colorado, and Georgia so far. Two years ago, Apple shared a list of additional states committed to supporting the feature in the future, but none of them have revealed any plans yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Participating States</h2><ul><li>Arizona (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/23/apple-launches-ids-in-wallet-arizona/">March 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Maryland (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/25/iphone-drivers-license-wallet-app-maryland/">May 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Colorado (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/colorado-ids-wallet-app-support/">November 2022</a>)</li><br/>
<li>Georgia (since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/18/iphone-drivers-license-georgia/">May 2023</a>)</li></ul><h2>Committed States</h2><br/>
In March 2022, Apple said the additional eight states listed below would "soon" allow residents to add their driver's license or state ID to the Wallet app, but it is now two years later and none of these states support the feature yet.<ul><li>Connecticut</li><br/>
<li>Hawaii</li><br/>
<li>Iowa</li><br/>
<li>Kentucky</li><br/>
<li>Mississippi</li><br/>
<li>Ohio</li><br/>
<li>Oklahoma</li><br/>
<li>Utah</li></ul>Apple said the feature would also be supported in Puerto Rico.<br/>
<br/>
In 2021, Apple said it was "already in discussions with many more states" and hoped to offer the feature nationwide in the future.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear if Apple plans to expand the feature to other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Participating Locations</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-Wallet-ID-TSA.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-868295" /><br/>
Apple Wallet app IDs can be used at select TSA checkpoints within select U.S. airports:<ul><li>Baltimore/Washington International Thurgood Marshall Airport (BWI)</li><br/>
<li>Ronald Reagan Washington National Airport (DCA)</li><br/>
<li>Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX)</li><br/>
<li>Denver International Airport (DEN)</li><br/>
<li>Hartsfield–Jackson Atlanta International Airport (ATL)</li></ul>Apple says travelers should refer to TSA checkpoint signage to confirm availability of the feature.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's website says IDs in the Wallet app can also be used to show proof of age or identity at "select businesses and venues," but adoption is limited.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-wallet/">Apple Wallet</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-wallet-app-ids-slow-adoption/">Apple Said iPhone Driver&#039;s Licenses Would Expand to These 8 U.S. States… Two Years Ago</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-iphone-drivers-licenses-would-expand-to-these-8-u-s-states…-two-years-ago.2421915/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins Selling Refurbished iMac With M3 Chip in Canada</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-refurbished-m3-imac-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-imac-with-m3-chip-in-canada.2421912/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 06:50:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-refurbished-m3-imac-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week added the latest-generation iMac with the M3 chip <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/shop/refurbished/mac/2023-imac">to its certified refurbished store</a> in Canada for the first time since the computer was introduced in October. As a reminder, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-refurbished-m3-imac/">availability in the U.S.</a> began last month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921470" /><br/>
As usual for Apple's refurbished products, the refurbished iMacs are discounted by approximately 15% compared to the equivalent brand new models, with pricing starting at &#36;1,439 CAD. A variety of configurations and color options are available.<br/>
<br/>
All of the usual accessories are included in the box, including a Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, power adapter and cord, and USB-C to Lightning cable.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says it puts refurbished Macs through "full functionality testing" and a "thorough cleaning process and inspection," and they are covered by Apple's one-year limited warranty and eligible for extended AppleCare+ coverage.<br/>
<br/>
In our view, Apple's refurbished Macs are virtually indistinguishable from brand new ones, providing a good opportunity for savings directly from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also began selling refurbished 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/refurbished-m3-macbook-pro-canada-europe/">with M3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-mbps-more-countries/">M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips</a> in Canada last month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-refurbished-m3-imac-canada/">Apple Begins Selling Refurbished iMac With M3 Chip in Canada</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-imac-with-m3-chip-in-canada.2421912/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sports App Updated for MLB and NCAA&#039;s March Madness</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-sports-app-mlb-and-ncaa-march-madness/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-updated-for-mlb-and-ncaas-march-madness.2421908/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 06:01:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-sports-app-mlb-and-ncaa-march-madness/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/apple-sports-app-announced/">new Apple Sports app</a> for the iPhone received its first update today with optimizations for the MLB and NCAA's March Madness. If you are a fan of these leagues, make sure to update the app to ensure that complete data is available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Sports-App-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1961" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937385" /><br/>
The full release notes for Apple Sports version 1.1:<blockquote>• Ready for March Madness? Follow the Men's and Women's NCAA Basketball Tournaments for real-time updates.<br/>
<br/>
• Starting with Opening Day, go deep this MLB season with play-by-play updates, betting odds, box scores, and more for all of your favorite teams.<br/>
<br/>
• Final scores are now sorted by league.</blockquote>Released last month, Apple Sports shows scores, stats, standings, upcoming games, betting odds, and more for a variety of leagues, such as the MLB, MLS, NBA, NHL, and Premier League. The app also displays real-time play-by-play information for ongoing games.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is available for free <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">on the App Store</a>, and it is compatible with the iPhone only.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-sports-app-mlb-and-ncaa-march-madness/">Apple Sports App Updated for MLB and NCAA&#039;s March Madness</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-updated-for-mlb-and-ncaas-march-madness.2421908/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Name May Still Face Trademark Issues in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/vision-pro-trademark-issues-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pros-name-may-still-face-trademark-issues-in-china.2421906/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/vision-pro-trademark-issues-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Trademark</category>
		<category>Huawei</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple's Vision Pro headset may still face <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/13/vision-pro-trademark-owned-huawei-china/">trademark issues</a> with Huawei when the company launches it  in China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
As highlighted by the <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3255397/apples-vision-pro-headset-likely-face-trademark-issues-china-huawei-has-already-registered-name?utm_source=rss_feed"><em>South China Morning Post</em></a>, Chinese tech giant Huawei registered the "Vision Pro" name in the country in 2021. This registration encompasses a wide array of goods and services, including virtual reality headsets and wearable video displays, effectively granting Huawei exclusive rights to the "Vision Pro" name in China until November 2031.<br/>
<br/>
According to the Chinese National Intellectual Property Administration (CNIPA), Apple's application for the trademark rights to "Vision Pro" is currently in a state of "refusal to re-examine." Additionally, Apple applied to trademark the brand name "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>" in June 2023, and this application is still under examination, leaving the company's branding strategy for the product in China uncertain.<br/>
<br/>
Huawei's first foray into smart eyewear came with the introduction of "Vision Glass" in December 2022, expanding its portfolio under the Vision brand, which also includes a range of smart TV screens. Following the release of Apple's Vision Pro in the United States in February, Huawei has been rumored to be preparing to launch similar devices. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trademark/">Trademark</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/huawei/">Huawei</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/vision-pro-trademark-issues-in-china/">Apple Vision Pro&#039;s Name May Still Face Trademark Issues in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pros-name-may-still-face-trademark-issues-in-china.2421906/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Proton Encrypted Mail Desktop App Now Available for Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/proton-mail-desktop-app-available-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/proton-encrypted-mail-desktop-app-now-available-for-mac.2421901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 05:09:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/proton-mail-desktop-app-available-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Security</category>
		<category>Encryption</category>
		<category>Proton</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Swiss-based privacy startup Proton today <a href="https://proton.me/blog/proton-mail-desktop-app">announced</a> the availability of its end-to-end encrypted desktop mail app for macOS and Windows, with a Linux version in beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/proton-mail-desktop-app.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941246" /><br/>
According to the company, the Proton Mail desktop app has been optimized to integrate with Macs, which means it can sync themes with the desktop's light or dark mode, display notifications natively, and offer instant switching between mail and calendar. <br/>
<blockquote>The new Proton Mail desktop app inherits from a decade of security enhancements we built for our web application. That means Proton Mail for Windows and macOS maintains our commitment to security and privacy with several key features: zero-access encryption and end-to-end encryption, protection against trackers and phishing attempts, and our high-security account protection program, Proton Sentinel.</blockquote>Proton says the ability to use a separate app from a browser for accessing email and calendar also offers additional security benefits, such as protecting emails or events from rogue browser extensions and allowing automatic updates without relying on a browser.<br/>
<br/>
The app also includes an Easy Switch tool that enables users to import  messages from Outlook or Gmail, forward new messages from Gmail, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/proton-mail-desktop-app-blog-4-min.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="600" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941248" /><br/>
Besides these additions, the desktop app should be familiar to Proton users. "Anyone who has used our web app before will instantly feel at home," says the company.<br/>
<br/>
Paying Proton account holders can download the Proton Mail app from the <a href="https://proton.me/mail/download">Proton website</a>, and the company is offering a 14-day trial for anyone on a free Proton plan. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/security/">Security</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/encryption/">Encryption</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/proton/">Proton</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/proton-mail-desktop-app-available-mac/">Proton Encrypted Mail Desktop App Now Available for Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/proton-encrypted-mail-desktop-app-now-available-for-mac.2421901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Case With Touchscreen Knock-Off Copies Apple Patent</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/airpods-case-with-touchscreen-knock-off/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-case-with-touchscreen-knock-off-copies-apple-patent.2421899/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 04:29:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/airpods-case-with-touchscreen-knock-off/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple registers many patents most of which never see the light of day as consumer products – <em>officially</em>, that is. One burgeoning knock-off merchant in China has apparently taken cues from an idea Apple had in 2021 for AirPods featuring a case with a built-in touchscreen display.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/AirPods-Pro-Case-With-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-890995" /><br/>
<a href="https://x.com/lipilipsi/status/1767962759881437321?s=20">Pictures</a> and <a href="https://x.com/lipilipsi/status/1767938637432598827?s=20">video</a> shared on X (Twitter) by occasional leaker @lipilipsi show production units of counterfeit AirPods with an OLED touchscreen integrated into the front of the case. <br/>
<br/>
Activated when the case lid is opened, the display allows users to select noise control options, "Find My" earbuds, choose equalizer presets, and lock the screen. The display also shows users the battery level of each AirPod, the current time, and Bluetooth connectivity.<br/>
<br/>
It's clear where the concept has been ripped off from. An Apple <a href="https://image-ppubs.uspto.gov/dirsearch-public/print/downloadPdf/20230095263">2021 patent</a> reads: <br/>
<blockquote>"The utility of a headphone case can be enhanced, and user control over a user's wireless headphones can be improved, by configuring a headphone case with an interactive user interface to enable user control of operations associated with the wireless headphones."</blockquote><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airpods-case-display-knockoff.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941232" /><br/>
In one embodiment, Apple envisions controlling Apple Music via the case through the use of a capacitive touchscreen with a GUI that also provides tactile feedback, allowing the user to control audio playback, adjust volume, favorite songs, and interact with their music in other ways – similar to the knock-off device we see here.<br/>
<br/>
By integrating an interactive touchscreen display in such a way, the patent argues, "deficiencies associated with user control of wireless headphones are reduced or eliminated."<br/>
<br/>
The popularity of AirPods has seen record numbers of counterfeit wireless headphones seized at the U.S. border in recent years. According to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/07/16/airpods-drive-surge-in-counterfeit-headphones/">2021 report</a>, roughly 360,000 counterfeit wireless headphones with a retail value of &#36;62.2 million were confiscated in the first nine months of the U.S. government's fiscal year, based on data from U.S. Customs and Border Protection.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-media-max-width="560"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Airport with OLED display <a href="https://t.co/tehsjwj9iF">pic.twitter.com/tehsjwj9iF</a></p>&mdash; fix Apple &#x1f34f; (@lipilipsi) <a href="https://twitter.com/lipilipsi/status/1767938637432598827?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 13, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><div class="center-wrap"><em>That should be "AirPods with OLED display"</em></div> <br/>
U.S. Customs said that 80% of all counterfeit products coming into the U.S. were from mainland China or Hong Kong. While it's unclear how many of the seized counterfeit headphones were AirPods, U.S. Customs said seizures had increased 50% in the previous five years as products such as Apple's earbuds gained popularity.<br/>
<br/>
Counterfeit AirPods can use genuine Apple serial numbers and usually look physically indistinguishable from legitimate AirPods. Many often have functional equivalent noise control features, but the touchscreen is a new one on us.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/airpods-case-with-touchscreen-knock-off/">AirPods Case With Touchscreen Knock-Off Copies Apple Patent</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-case-with-touchscreen-knock-off-copies-apple-patent.2421899/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro is &#039;Over-Engineered Devkit,&#039; Says Former Oculus Head</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-vision-pro-over-engineered-devkit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-is-over-engineered-devkit-says-former-oculus-head.2421894/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 03:37:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-vision-pro-over-engineered-devkit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's first-generation Vision Pro headset is an "over-engineered devkit" that ships with more sensors than is necessary to deliver Apple's intended experience. That's according to Hugo Barra, former VP of Android and head of Meta's phased-out Oculus headset brand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-vision-pro-setup.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923100" /><br/>
Barra, who oversaw the Oculus team in 2017 after it was acquired by Facebook, has published a surprisingly balanced <a href="https://hugo.blog/2024/03/11/vision-pro/">in-depth analysis</a> of Apple's spatial computing device, which is well worth a read. But a couple of reflections are worth highlighting. <br/>
<br/>
Barra notes that Apple has packed Vision Pro with an impressive six tracking cameras, two passthrough cameras, two depth sensors, and four eye-tracking cameras. This "over-spec'ing," says Barra, is "characteristic of a v1 product where its creator wants to ensure it survives the hardest tests early users will no doubt want to put the product through."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's decision to over-spec the Vision Pro, however, inevitably makes the headset weigh over 600 grams, and "makes it difficult for most people to wear it for more than 30-45 minutes at a time without suffering a lot of discomfort."<br/>
<blockquote>Because of its heavy weight, Vision Pro has inevitably landed in the world as a high-quality "devkit" designed to capture everyone's curiosity, hearts & minds with its magic (especially through the voice of enthusiastic tech influencers) while being realistically focused on developers as its primary audience. In other words, the Vision Pro is a devkit that helps prepare the world to receive a more mainstream Apple VR headset that could have product-market fit in 1 or 2 generations. </blockquote><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman believes Apple is working on multiple new Apple Vision models, exploring both a low-cost version and a second-generation version. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/low-cost-vision-pro-to-drop-eyesight/">With the low-cost version</a>, Gurman believes Apple will eliminate the EyeSight feature and the M-series chip, using more affordable components.<br/>
<br/>
In another notable claim, Barra reckons Apple has made the Vision Pro experience intentionally blurry in order to hide pixelation artifacts and make graphics appear smoother, which he sees as a "clever move" by Apple. <br/>
<blockquote>One of our biggest product positioning struggles within the Oculus VR team from the very beginning — especially when trying to convince reviewers — was always related to having underwhelming displays. Every single Oculus headset that ever shipped (including the latest Quest 3) has suffered from resolution/pixelation issues varying from "terrible" to "pretty bad". It's like we're living in the VR-equivalent world of VGA computer monitors.</blockquote>By making the Vision Pro optics slightly out of focus, Apple has achieved "way smoother graphics across the board by hiding the screen door effect (which in practice means that you won't see pixelation artifacts)." However, Barra laments the Vision Pro's "significant motion blur and image quality issues that render passthrough mode unusable for longer periods."<br/>
<br/>
Barra claims that it was this motion blur in passthrough mode that was one of the many reasons why he decided to return his Vision Pro. "It's just uncomfortable, leads to unnecessary eye strain, and really gets in the way of anyone using the headset for longer periods of time," he adds.<br/>
<br/>
You can find Barra's lengthy write-up of his experience with Vision Pro over <a href="https://hugo.blog/2024/03/11/vision-pro/">on his blog</a>. Apple Vision Pro starts at &#36;3,499 in the United States, with the device expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">launch in more countries later this year</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/14/apple-vision-pro-over-engineered-devkit/">Apple Vision Pro is &#039;Over-Engineered Devkit,&#039; Says Former Oculus Head</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-is-over-engineered-devkit-says-former-oculus-head.2421894/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Likely to Launch in These Nine Countries Next</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-likely-to-launch-in-these-nine-countries-next.2421867/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:55:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon add 12 new languages to the virtual keyboard on the Vision Pro, based on code discovered by <em>MacRumors</em>. Right now, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> keyboard only supports English (US) and Emoji, which makes sense as it is limited to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-vision-pro-virtual-keyboard.jpg" alt="" width="1278" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930653" /><br/>
To bring the Vision Pro to new countries, Apple needs to add support for additional languages. The code indicates the following languages will be added:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Cantonese, Traditional</li><br/>
 	<li>Chinese, Simplified</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Australia)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Canada)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Japan)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (Singapore)</li><br/>
 	<li>English (UK)</li><br/>
 	<li>French (Canada)</li><br/>
 	<li>French (France)</li><br/>
 	<li>German (Germany)</li><br/>
 	<li>Japanese</li><br/>
 	<li>Korean</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
It's likely that these language additions hint at the countries where Apple will launch the Vision Pro next, including Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, Japan, Singapore, South Korea, and the UK. Hong Kong and Taiwan are also potential candidates.<br/>
<br/>
When the Vision Pro launched, Apple said that it would bring the Vision Pro to additional countries later this year, but the company did not provide timing. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> believes that Apple will expand Vision Pro availability to additional markets prior to the June Worldwide Developers Conference.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">Apple Vision Pro Likely to Launch in These Nine Countries Next</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-likely-to-launch-in-these-nine-countries-next.2421867/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Throwboy Launches Giant Pillow Modeled After Mac Finder Icon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/throwboy-launches-giant-pillow-modeled-after-mac-finder-icon.2421865/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:10:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Throwboy, known for its line of pillows designed to look like classic Macs, this week launched a new jumbo version of the Apple fan favorite Icon Pillow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Big-Boy-Throwboy-6.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1536" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941208" /><br/>
Designed to look like the Finder icon from early Macs, the jumbo Icon Pillow measures in at 37 inches by 37 inches by 15 inches, and it is the biggest pillow that Throwboy has created to date. It is made of a soft plush material with fleece eyes and smile, and it is so big that it weighs in at 16 pounds.<br/>
<br/>
According to Throwboy, the jumbo Icon Pillow is the ultimate home decor for tech lovers, and it is sized for snuggling with. It is filled with a plush, poly filling that is meant to give it a bouncy fill, and it is designed to be durable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Big-Boy-Throwboy-5.jpg" alt="" width="2048" height="1536" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941210" /><br/>
Throwboy makes the Icon Pillow in a range of sizes, from jumbo to the more reasonable <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/icon-pillow">13 inch by 13 inch version</a>. There's also a <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/icon-pocket-pillow-1">mini pocket Icon pillow</a> and one that <a href="https://throwboy.com/products/sad-icon-pillow">comes with a sad face</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The jumbo Icon Pillow can be <a href="https://throwboy.com/collections/throwboy-pillows/products/icon-pillow-jumbo-size">purchased from Throwboy</a> for &#36;390. It is available in the U.S., UK, and Canada.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/throwboy-finder-jumbo-pillow/">Throwboy Launches Giant Pillow Modeled After Mac Finder Icon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/throwboy-launches-giant-pillow-modeled-after-mac-finder-icon.2421865/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Suppliers Donate to Restore Fund for Sustainable Forests and Other Carbon Removal Projects</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-suppliers-donate-to-restore-fund-for-sustainable-forests-and-other-carbon-removal-projects.2421855/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:49:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Environment</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apple-expands-innovative-restore-fund-with-tsmc-and-murata/">today announced</a> that suppliers Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company (TSMC) and Japanese company Murata Manufacturing are investing in its Restore Fund, a program aimed at scaling investments in high-quality nature-based carbon removal while also protecting critical ecosystems.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-restore-fund.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941203" /><br/>
TSMC is investing up to &#36;50 million and Murata is investing up to &#36;30 million, with the money managed by Climate Asset Management. Apple established the Restore Fund in 2021 with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/15/apple-launches-restore-fund/">&#36;200 million donation</a>, and expanded it in 2023 with another &#36;200 million.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is using some of the money to support the creation of <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apples-restore-fund-cultivates-new-roots-in-the-atlantic-forest/">sustainably certified working forests</a> on degraded pasture and agricultural lands in South America. The project is meant to meet increasing global demand for timber while reducing pressure on natural forests.<br/>
<br/>
Two of the partners that Apple is working on the forests have planted eucalyptus, an ideal tree for sustainable forests because of its fast growth rate, ability to restore degraded land, and lower water consumption than other kinds of trees.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's third partner is developing sustainable forests of tropical hardwoods native to Brazil's Atlantic Forest, with some of the land also going toward restoring tree species that are nearing extinction. The Restore Fund will be used for other projects that focus on ecosystem conservation and restoration, with selection underway. Apple set a goal of removing 1 million metric tons of carbon dioxide from the air by 2025, which it is on track to exceed.<br/>
<br/>
Apple wants to be carbon neutral across its entire supply chain by 2030. More than 300 suppliers have signed up for the Supplier Clean Energy Program that commits them to achieving 100 percent renewable energy for all Apple production by the end of the decade, and Apple has also asked its partners to decarbonize their Apple-related operations.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-environment/">Apple Environment</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/apple-restore-fund-suppliers/">Apple Suppliers Donate to Restore Fund for Sustainable Forests and Other Carbon Removal Projects</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-suppliers-donate-to-restore-fund-for-sustainable-forests-and-other-carbon-removal-projects.2421855/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games Accuses Apple of Charging &#039;Unjustified Fees&#039; for Required Non-App Store Purchase Link</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-accuses-apple-of-charging-unjustified-fees-for-required-non-app-store-purchase-link.2421851/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:14:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> is once again after Apple, this time accusing the Cupertino company of violating a court ruling that requires Apple to allow developers to offer in-app links to direct customers to third-party purchase options on the web.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
Apple tweaked its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">U.S. App Store policies</a> back in January, and developers are permitted to put one link in their apps that leads to a website where customers can make a purchase without using the in-app purchase system. Apple is still charging commission for these purchases, requiring developers to pay between 12 and 27 percent (three percent lower than the 15/30 standard fee).<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is unhappy with the fee that Apple continues to charge, <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/713133409/Epic-Games-v-Apple-Motion-to-Enforce-Injunction">today telling the court</a> that Apple has not complied with the order, and asking that Apple be held in contempt of court. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; claims that the fees make the links "commercially unusable," thereby subverting the injunction.<br/>
<blockquote>Apple violates the Injunction in three ways. First, with respect to External Links, Apple has imposed new fees and enacted a slew of new rules that work together to make the links commercially unusable. This new fee and accompanying web of restrictions subverts the purpose of the Injunction, allowing Apple to continue extracting its excessive commissions and making it effectively impossible for a developer to inform users about, and direct users toward, an alternative platform for making a purchase.<br/>
<br/>
Second, Apple continues to categorically prohibit any steering using "buttons" or "other calls to action". Specifically, Apple does not allow External Links that resemble a "button" in any way.<br/>
<br/>
Third, Apple's Guideline 3.1.3 still prohibits certain apps, including all multiplatform services (i.e., apps that operate across multiple platforms and allow users to access the same content across these platforms, including popular games such as Minecraft), from "within the app, encourag[ing] users to use a purchasing method other than in-app purchase". This language expressly contravenes the Injunction by prohibiting any steering to alternative purchasing methods.</blockquote><br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; collected statements from other developers that have spoken out against Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> fees, including Paddle CEO Christian Owens and Down Dog CEO Benjamin Simon.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was initially ordered to make the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes in 2021 as part of its court battle with &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;. Judge Yvonne Gonzalez-Rogers, who oversaw the case, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-vs-apple-decision/">took issue</a> with Apple's anti-steering rules. Apple was able to delay implementing the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; changes for a few years <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">while it appealed</a>, but none of the courts decided to change the verdict. Apple ultimately took it to the Supreme Court, but the court <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">declined to hear the case</a>, so Apple had to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">comply immediately</a> at the beginning of the year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has said that it is fully in compliance with the injunction. From Apple's January statement of compliance:<blockquote>As of January 16, 2024, Apple has fully complied with the Injunction: It is striking the relevant parts of the App Store Review Guidelines applicable to apps on the U.S. storefronts of the iOS and iPadOS App Stores and implementing new rules that permit developers to (i) include in their apps buttons or links with calls to action that direct customers to purchasing mechanisms in addition to IAP and (ii) communicate with customers through points of contact obtained voluntarily from customers through account registration within the app. As a result of these changes, developers have the option of informing consumers, both within and outside the app, about alternative purchase mechanisms in addition to IAP.</blockquote>Epic Games claims that the fee Apple charges for the link is "financially unattractive" for developers who want to choose another payment solution, and it "prevents any meaningful competition between payment solutions." The company wants the court to require Apple to bring its policies into compliance with the injunction.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/">Epic Games Accuses Apple of Charging &#039;Unjustified Fees&#039; for Required Non-App Store Purchase Link</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-accuses-apple-of-charging-unjustified-fees-for-required-non-app-store-purchase-link.2421851/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Teardown Shows Apple Fixed Base Model&#039;s Biggest Flaw</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-teardown-shows-apple-fixed-base-models-biggest-flaw.2421843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 11:11:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The repair website iFixit today <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jXY9tCBpf48">shared a video teardown</a> of the base model 13-inch MacBook Air with the M3 chip and 256GB of storage, and it shows that this configuration is equipped with two 128GB flash storage chips. This change results in significantly faster SSD speeds compared to the equivalent MacBook Air with the M2 chip, which has a single 256GB storage chip, as the SSD can read and write from the two chips simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
YouTube channel Max Tech <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/09/base-model-m3-macbook-air-faster-ssd/">ran Blackmagic's Disk Speed Test tool</a> with a 5GB file size test on both the M2 and M3 models of the 13-inch MacBook Air with 256GB of storage and 8GB of RAM, and they found the SSD in the M3 model achieved up to 33% faster write speeds and up to 82% faster read speeds compared to the SSD in the M2 model.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's decision to switch to a single 256GB chip for the base model M2 MacBook Air was controversial, even though the slower SSD speeds are unlikely to be noticed by the average user working on common day-to-day tasks. Fortunately, the base model M3 MacBook Air's SSD speeds are now roughly equivalent to the base model M1 MacBook Air again, so customers no longer need to be concerned about this potential limitation.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/jXY9tCBpf48?si=gDJPempJs82JBtn0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Apple still sells a 13-inch M2 MacBook Air with 256GB of storage for &#36;999, so customers who want maximum SSD performance should avoid that model.<br/>
<br/>
Beyond this SSD-related change, the teardown shows that the M3 MacBook Air models have a virtually identical internal design as the M2 models. The video provides a look at the battery cells with adhesive pull tabs, logic board, trackpad, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> iFixit's CEO Kyle Wiens said the base model 15-inch MacBook Air with the M3 chip and 256GB of storage also has two 128GB storage chips.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/m3-macbook-air-ifixit-teardown/">M3 MacBook Air Teardown Shows Apple Fixed Base Model&#039;s Biggest Flaw</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-teardown-shows-apple-fixed-base-models-biggest-flaw.2421843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Closer to Potential U.S. Ban as House Passes Bill Requiring Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-closer-to-potential-u-s-ban-as-house-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2421834/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 09:46:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. House of Representatives today approved legislation that would force TikTok owner ByteDance to sell the social media network or face a ban in the United States. The Protecting Americans From Foreign Adversary Controlled Applications Act will now go to the Senate, where its fate is unclear.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/tiktok-logo.jpg" alt="" width="866" height="480" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-738083" /><br/>
U.S. lawmakers want TikTok to be sold to a company outside of China due to concerns that the Chinese government could force ByteDance to hand over data from users located in the United States. If China made the request, ByteDance would not be able to refuse. There have also been suggestions that China could use TikTok to spread political propaganda.<br/>
<br/>
ByteDance has attempted to alleviate these fears by storing data from U.S. users on servers owned by Oracle, but the White House and lawmakers do not believe that is enough.<br/>
<br/>
If passed, the bill would require ByteDance to sell TikTok within six months to a company approved by the U.S. government. Should ByteDance not sell the company, U.S. app stores would not be able to distribute the app without breaking the law, effectively leading to a ban. China would also need to approve the sale, and the Chinese government <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2023/03/23/technology/tiktok-congress-hearing.html">made it clear</a> last year that it would "firmly oppose" a forced sale.<br/>
<br/>
There are a limited number of companies with enough capital to be able to afford TikTok, and the obvious choices, such as Google or Meta, would likely be barred from acquiring it due to antitrust concerns.<br/>
<br/>
Should the bill make it through the Senate, U.S. President Joe Biden confirmed that he would sign it into law. A number of senators have expressed worries about the wording of the act, and it does not have universal support at this time.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/house-passes-tiktok-sale-bill/">TikTok Closer to Potential U.S. Ban as House Passes Bill Requiring Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-closer-to-potential-u-s-ban-as-house-passes-bill-requiring-sale.2421834/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: Most Subscription-Based Apps Do Not Make Money</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-most-subscription-based-apps-do-not-make-money.2421830/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 08:33:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Most mobile apps with subscriptions do not make money, a new in-depth analysis finds. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Clorange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833988" /><br/>
The "<a href="https://www.revenuecat.com/state-of-subscription-apps-2024/">State of Subscription Apps</a>" report comes from RevenueCat (via <em><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2024/03/12/most-subscription-mobile-apps-dont-make-money-new-report-shows/">TechCrunch</a></em>), a prominent mobile subscription toolkit provider. With nearly 30,000 apps utilizing its platform for monetization management, RevenueCat is able to provide a reliable overview of the subscription app landscape thanks to its data collection capabilities. The analysis delves into data from over 29,000 apps and 18,000 developers, collectively responsible for more than &#36;6.7 billion in revenue and over 290 million subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
RevenueCat found that while the top-performing 5% of subscription apps amass revenue 200 times greater than those in the bottom quartile, the median monthly revenue for apps after one year is less than &#36;50. Only 17.2% of apps cross the &#36;1,000 monthly revenue mark. Reaching this milestone significantly boosts the likelihood of further financial growth, with 59% of these apps progressing to achieve &#36;2,500 in monthly revenue, and 60% of those reaching the &#36;5,000 mark. A mere 3.5% of apps achieve &#36;10,000 in monthly revenue.<br/>
<br/>
Health and fitness apps generate at least twice the revenue of all other categories combined, both in the bottom quartile and among the top 5% of earners. In contrast, travel and productivity apps face the most significant challenges, with even the top performers in these categories struggling to make over &#36;1,000 per month after a year on the market.<br/>
<br/>
Despite these statistics, the subscription app market continues to grow and the average price for monthly subscriptions has increased by 14% from &#36;7.05 to &#36;8.01. However, the report also noted a recent shift in consumer behavior, with a 14% drop in subscriber retention over 12 months.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/most-subscription-apps-do-not-make-money/">Report: Most Subscription-Based Apps Do Not Make Money</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-most-subscription-based-apps-do-not-make-money.2421830/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
