<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 03:03:19 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Craig Federighi Explains Phased Release of Apple Intelligence Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/craig-federighi-explains-phased-release-of-apple-intelligence-features.2440759/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 02:59:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		<category>Craig Federighi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a new interview with <em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fr8ALcEiYAk">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>, Apple's head of software Craig Federighi has highlighted the company's measured, multi-phase approach to introducing Apple Intelligence features, with the initial iOS 18.1 release next week marking just the beginning of a staggered rollout over several months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/apple-intelligence-black.jpeg" alt="" width="1400" height="788" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963902" /><br/>
"This is a big lift," Federighi told <em>WSJ</em>'s Joanna Stern, explaining Apple's cautious strategy to integrating AI into its devices. "You could put something out there and have it be sort of a mess. Apple's point of view is more like, 'Let's try to get each piece right and release it when it's ready.'"<br/>
<br/>
The initial release will focus on basic features including Writing Tools for text summarization, notification summaries, and a Clean Up tool in Photos for removing unwanted objects. While most processing occurs on-device, Apple's Private Cloud Compute system handles more intensive tasks through encrypted servers. In other words, user data isn't stored or accessed for AI training. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's approach differs significantly from other large language models, which typically process all user input on cloud servers. According to Federighi, the company's personally oriented, privacy-first approach is also why Siri won't offer the sort of answers that one might get from something like ChatGPT.<br/>
<br/>
"There's a trade-off across capabilities," he explained. "Those other chatbots are great if you want to ask a question about quantum mechanics, and then have them write a poem about it, but they won't open your garage or send a text message. Will these worlds converge? Of course."<br/>
<br/>
Several anticipated features showcased by Apple at WWDC in June won't appear until later updates: iOS 18.2 is expected before the end of the year, and will introduce Image Playground for generating cartoon-style images and Genmoji for creating custom emoji. The update will also add ChatGPT integration for handling complex Siri queries.<br/>
<br/>
The most significant Siri enhancements are scheduled for iOS 18.4 around March 2025. These include onscreen awareness for contextual commands, personal context for better understanding of user data, and expanded app control capabilities. Initially, Apple Intelligence will only support U.S. English, with additional languages planned for next year.<br/>
<br/>
In contrast to its rivals, Apple is taking a particularly measured approach to image manipulation. The new Clean Up tool in Photos allows users to remove unwanted objects or people from images, but avoids more complex AI-generated alterations like changing the background. "People view photographic content as something they can rely on as indicative of reality," explained Federighi. "It's important to us that we help purvey accurate information, not fantasy."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fr8ALcEiYAk?si=YlwIgNHfXvfUiGWb" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Speaking more broadly about the rollout of Apple Intelligence features, Federighi said: "This is a many-year, honestly, even decades-long arc of this technology playing out, and so we're going to do it responsibly." The new Apple Intelligence features will be available on iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 16 models, as well as Apple silicon-powered iPads and Macs, when iOS 18.1 launches on October 28.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/craig-federighi/">Craig Federighi</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/23/craig-federighi-phased-release-apple-intelligence/">Craig Federighi Explains Phased Release of Apple Intelligence Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/craig-federighi-explains-phased-release-of-apple-intelligence-features.2440759/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Game Studio Shutdown Suggests Gaming May Not Be Working Out for Netflix</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-studio-shutdown-suggests-gaming-may-not-be-working-out-for-netflix.2440744/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:57:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix recently shut down its "Team Blue" gaming studio in Southern California, according to <em><a href="https://www.gamefile.news/p/netflix-team-blue-socal-studio">Game File</a></em>. The studio included industry veterans that worked on titles like Halo, Overwatch, and God of War.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-824171" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/netflix-games-launch.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
There have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/11/09/netflix-games-ios-launch/">mobile gaming titles</a> available through Netflix since 2021, but Team Blue was supposedly working on a big budget AAA gaming title that would have represented an expansion of Netflix's gaming efforts.<br/>
<br/>
The decision to shutter the studio developing an original multi-platform AAA title suggests that gaming might not be going so well for Netflix. Back in 2022, a report suggested that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/08/netflix-games-note-engaging-subscribers/">less than one percent</a> of Netflix subscribers were engaging in games, but Netflix has made an effort to introduce more premium titles since then.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix's mobile gaming catalog includes several Grand Theft Auto titles, popular roguelike Hades, Cozy Grove, Farming Simulator, Spiritfarer, Rollercoaster Tycoon, and more. The games are included with a Netflix subscription, and no additional fees are required to play them.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix games can be downloaded as standalone games on Apple devices, and are available to play after logging in with an active Netflix account.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/netflix-game-studio-shutdown/">Game Studio Shutdown Suggests Gaming May Not Be Working Out for Netflix</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/game-studio-shutdown-suggests-gaming-may-not-be-working-out-for-netflix.2440744/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Mini 7 Models Begin Arriving to Customers in Australia and New Zealand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-7-models-begin-arriving-to-customers-in-australia-and-new-zealand.2440736/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 15:12:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's Wednesday, October 23 in Australia and New Zealand, which means that customers who pre-ordered one of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> devices are starting to receive their orders.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-red-and-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972028" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/apple-unveils-new-ipad-mini-apple-intelligence/">introduced the iPad mini 7</a> on October 15, which is also when the company began accepting pre-orders. While the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; has the same design as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> 6, it is equipped with an A17 Pro chip and 8GB RAM in order to support the Apple Intelligence features that are coming in iPadOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; also offers Wi-Fi 6E, faster USB-C data transfer speeds, Bluetooth 5.3, and support for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro. It now offers a minimum of 128GB of storage with an option to upgrade to 256GB or 512GB, and Apple also unveiled new colors.<br/>
<br/>
There are no Apple retail stores in New Zealand, but Apple Stores in Australia will have the new &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; available for walk-in purchases. We are not expecting any shortages of the new tablet.<br/>
<br/>
Following New Zealand and Australia, sales of the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; will begin in Asia, the Middle East, Europe, and finally, North America.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; is priced starting at &#36;499, and it continues to be Apple's smallest tablet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-australia-new-zealand/">New iPad Mini 7 Models Begin Arriving to Customers in Australia and New Zealand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-7-models-begin-arriving-to-customers-in-australia-and-new-zealand.2440736/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Dropped iPhone Causes Woman to Be Trapped Upside Down in Rock Crevice for Hours</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dropped-iphone-causes-woman-to-be-trapped-upside-down-in-rock-crevice-for-hours.2440733/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 14:23:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Australian woman Matilda Campbell ended up trapped in a tight rock crevice upside down after she fell trying to retrieve an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that she dropped, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2024-10-22/images-of-hunter-valley-rescue-after-woman-falls-rock-crevice/104500728">ABC Newcastle</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iphone-trapped-crevice.jpg" alt="" width="1536" height="862" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972106" /><br/>
The 23-year-old was taking images in the New South Wales Hunter Valley when she lost hold of her phone. She tried to get it, but slipped and fell three meters and became stuck between two large boulders, hanging upside down by her feet. While the news report does not make specific mention of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Campbell's social media accounts indicate she was an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user.<br/>
<br/>
It took an hour for rescuers to get to Campbell, and several more hours to free her. NSW Ambulance rescue paramedic Peter Watts told <em>ABC Newcastle</em> that Campbell was calm and collected, despite the situation. He said it was a difficult, "out-of-the-box rescue" that was unlike anything he'd previously experienced. NSW Ambulance shared images of the rescue <a href="https://www.facebook.com/NSWAmbulance">on Facebook</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Rescue crews had to remove seven boulders weighing between 80 and 500 kilograms to free Campbell, plus a wooden frame had to be constructed in case any boulders cracked and fell. Campbell was trapped for approximately seven hours, and she ended up with scrapes, bruises, and a cracked vertebra. She was not able to retrieve her &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/dropped-iphone-rock-crevice-accident/">Dropped iPhone Causes Woman to Be Trapped Upside Down in Rock Crevice for Hours</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/dropped-iphone-causes-woman-to-be-trapped-upside-down-in-rock-crevice-for-hours.2440733/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Said to Be Working on New Gaming App for iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-to-be-working-on-new-gaming-app-for-ios.2440726/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:17:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		<category>Game Center</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on an App Store-style app designed for gaming, according to a report from <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/10/22/apple-new-app-store-like-app-games/">9to5Mac</a></em>. It would merge <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> gaming content, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, and Game Center into a central location.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/06/apple-arcade-orange-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-748620" /><br/>
The app is said to feature a Play Now tab with gaming content and suggestions, plus a Game Center tab for tracking game progress and games that friends are playing. Game Center features like achievements and leaderboards will be highlighted.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to offer both &zwnj;Apple Arcade&zwnj; games and &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; games in the app, and the company will promote gaming events and details about important updates. It is possible that there will be integration with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> and Messages for remote play with friends, as well as App Clip mini game demos.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word on when Apple might release this dedicated gaming app.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/game-center/">Game Center</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-gaming-app-ios/">Apple Said to Be Working on New Gaming App for iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-said-to-be-working-on-new-gaming-app-for-ios.2440726/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second visionOS 2.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate.2440725/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:11:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a second release candidate version of an upcoming visionOS 2.1 update to developers for testing purposes. The new software comes a day after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate/">first release candidate version</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955607" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/visionOS-2-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.1 can be installed by going to the Software Update section of the Settings app on the Vision Pro and opting into Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
So far, no major new features have been discovered in the update, and it likely focuses on bug fixes and other small feature improvements. Apple's release notes say that the second visionOS 2.1 RC fixes an issue that could cause <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> songs and music videos to fail to play.<br/>
<br/>
visionOS 2.1 is expected to see a release next Monday alongside iOS 18.1.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds Second visionOS 2.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-visionos-2-1-release-candidate.2440725/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro, AirPods, and AirPods Max Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-airpods-and-airpods-max-firmware.2440718/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 11:39:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the original <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, the AirPods 2, the AirPods 3, and the Lightning version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones. The new firmware is version 6F21, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/25/apple-all-airpods-new-firmware/">prior 6A326 firmware</a> that these devices were previously running.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
There is no word on what's included in the firmware, but given that these are all older models, it is likely that the new firmware includes bug fixes and other minor improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple doesn't have a way to manually upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air when the AirPods are in a charging case and connected to an iOS device or Mac.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro, AirPods, and AirPods Max Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-airpods-and-airpods-max-firmware.2440718/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>You Can Now Try AT&amp;T&#039;s Network for Free</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-try-at-ts-network-for-free.2440716/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 11:19:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AT&amp;amp;T</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AT&T today <a href="https://about.att.com/blogs/2024/try-att.html">announced a new promotion</a> that allows potential new customers to try out the AT&T network for 30 days for free.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ATT-Banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937556" /><br/>
Customers with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that has an eSIM can download the myAT&T app or visit the AT&T <a href="http://www.att.com/wireless/free-trial/">free trial website</a> to sign up for temporary access to the AT&T network. No credit card is required for the AT&T trial, which includes 5G access.<br/>
<br/>
Compatible iPhones with eSIM capabilities include the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> 2020 and all later models, but note that devices must be unlocked. Testing AT&T's network through the Try AT&T feature does not require transferring a phone number or canceling current service. It instead operates as a second line on a compatible &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, with options to switch between the AT&T test and another carrier plan.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T is providing unlimited talk and text, 100GB of data, 25GB of personal hotspot data, AT&T 5G access, and unlimited texting from the United States to more than 230 countries. After the 30-day trial ends, service will be canceled automatically, but customers will have the option to sign up for AT&T service.<br/>
<br/>
Both Verizon and T-Mobile have previously rolled out programs that allow customers to test their networks for free, but AT&T is offering 25GB of hotspot data, which neither Verizon or T-Mobile support.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/att/">AT&amp;T</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/att-free-network-trial/">You Can Now Try AT&amp;T&#039;s Network for Free</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/you-can-now-try-at-ts-network-for-free.2440716/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iPadOS 18.0.1 for iPad Mini 7 Ahead of Tomorrow&#039;s Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-for-ipad-mini-7-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch.2440711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:55:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new version of iPadOS 18.0.1 that's designed specifically for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> that will be available as of tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature-blue-and-orange.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972026" /><br/>
The iPadOS 18.0.1 update features the same content as the iPadOS 18.0.1 update that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/apple-releases-ios-18-0-1/">released in early October</a>, but it has a 22A8380 build number. The &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; isn't out just yet, but customers in Australia and New Zealand who pre-ordered will be getting their shipments in just a few hours, and they'll be able to update during the setup process.<br/>
<br/>
iPadOS 18.0.1 includes a fix for an issue that could cause the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> to unexpectedly quit when replying to a message with a shared Apple Watch face, plus it has a security fix to address a vulnerability with the Passwords app.<br/>
<br/>
Launch versions of the &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; have a version of iOS 18.0 installed rather than iPadOS 18.0.1, which is why there's an out-of-the-box update. Next week, &zwnj;iPad mini 7&zwnj; owners can also upgrade to iPadOS 18.1, an update that includes the first Apple Intelligence features.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-ipad-mini-7/">Apple Releases iPadOS 18.0.1 for iPad Mini 7 Ahead of Tomorrow&#039;s Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ipados-18-0-1-for-ipad-mini-7-ahead-of-tomorrows-launch.2440711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: &#039;M4 Mac Launch&#039; is &#039;Next Week&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-m4-mac-launch-is-next-week.2440707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:29:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a few hours after claiming that the first Macs with M4 chips are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/gurman-says-m4-macs-launch-very-soon/">launching "very soon,"</a> <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman has followed up with a slightly more specific timeframe. In his latest <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848762199675965773">social media post</a> today, he said an "M4 Mac launch" is on Apple's schedule for next week, but he did not mention a specific day.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/M4-Mac-mini-Ortho-Black-Cooler.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-972058" /><em>A concept of a smaller Mac mini with front-facing USB-C ports</em></div><br/>
"Busy week for Apple next week: Apple Intelligence on Monday, then M4 Mac launch, then earnings results on Thursday," he posted.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848748246799429753">another social media post</a> today, Gurman said that Apple is inviting journalists and content creators to a hands-on experience in Los Angeles next Wednesday, and he believes this means the new Macs would need to be announced before then.<br/>
<br/>
In another twist, leaker Sonny Dickson today claimed that he heard the new Mac mini with five USB-C ports <a href="https://x.com/SonnyDickson/status/1848596156302971278">might launch this week</a> instead. Dickson has revealed some accurate details about upcoming Apple products through leaked cases and dummy models, but some of his hardware-related claims have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/06/09/imac-redesign-wwdc/">proven to be inaccurate</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, it looks like Apple will announce the first Macs with M4 chips in around a week from now at the latest, based on these latest claims. It's still not entirely clear if the announcements will be part of an online event, like the "Scary Fast" event on October 30 last year, or if the products will be announced in press releases on the Apple Newsroom website only. There is still time left in October for Apple to invite the media to watch an online event, but the window for that is gradually coming to a close. We'll see!<br/>
<br/>
Here is everything that Apple is likely to announce in the coming days:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>An entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip, and an additional Thunderbolt port compared to the current model</li><br/>
<li>14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M4 Pro and M4 Max chip options</li><br/>
<li>An updated iMac with the M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>A new Mac mini with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/mac-mini-redesign-rumor/">smaller Apple TV-like design, two front-facing USB-C ports, and M4 and M4 Pro chip options</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-new-magic-mouse-trackpad-keyboard/">USB-C versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard accessories</a></li></ul>The entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-potentially-facing-worst-leak-since-iphone-4/">allegedly leaked in a few unboxing videos</a> earlier this month, and it was shown to be a November 2024 model in those videos. If the videos are legitimate, that means the first Macs with M4 chips might not arrive to customers until next month, even if they are announced within the next week or so.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/m4-mac-launch-timing-rumors/">Gurman: &#039;M4 Mac Launch&#039; is &#039;Next Week&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-m4-mac-launch-is-next-week.2440707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds watchOS 11.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-11-1-release-candidate.2440706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 10:15:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming watchOS 11.1 update to developers and public beta testers for testing purposes. The new software comes approximately week after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/14/apple-seeds-fifth-beta-watchos-11-1/">fifth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchOS-11-Feature-2-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955937" /><br/>
watchOS 11.1 can be installed by going to the Apple Watch app and selecting the Software Update section under "General" in Settings. <br/>
<br/>
So far, no major new features have been discovered in the watchOS 11.1 update, though Apple's release notes indicate that there is a fix for an issue that could cause problems writing breathing disturbance data to the Health app. <br/>
<br/>
watchOS 11.1 is expected to see a release alongside iOS 18.1 next Monday.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-watchos-11-1-release-candidate-now-available/">Apple Seeds watchOS 11.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-11-1-release-candidate.2440706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Launches Tomorrow: Here Are 12 Changes to Know About</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-launches-tomorrow-here-are-12-changes-to-know-about.2440699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this month, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/15/apple-unveils-new-ipad-mini-apple-intelligence/">announced a new iPad mini</a> for the first time in three years. Ahead of the device launching this Wednesday, we have outlined 12 new features and changes with the seventh-generation iPad mini compared to the previous model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-apple-intelligence-a17-pro-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970909" /><br/>
Here's everything new with the iPad mini 7:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>A17 Pro chip:</strong> Introduced in the iPhone 15 Pro models last year, the A17 Pro chip is now available in the iPad mini 7, although it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">has a 5-core GPU</a> instead of a 6-core GPU. Apple says the iPad mini 7 offers up to 30% faster CPU performance compared to the previous iPad mini with the A15 Bionic chip.</li><br/>
<li><strong>8GB of RAM for Apple Intelligence support:</strong> The new iPad mini is compatible with Apple Intelligence, which will be available <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/airpods-pro-hearing-features-launching-in-ios-18-1/">starting with iPadOS 18.1 next week</a>. Geekbench results confirmed that the device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-benchmarks-confirm-8gb-ram/">equipped with 8GB of RAM</a>, the minimum requirement for Apple Intelligence. That's up from 4GB of RAM in the iPad mini 6.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Pencil Pro support:</strong> The new iPad mini is compatible with the Apple Pencil Pro.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Pencil hover:</strong> This feature lets you preview the Apple Pencil's stroke on the canvas before the accessory touches the screen.</li><br/>
<li><strong>"Jelly scrolling" fixed?</strong> Most reviews said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/does-ipad-mini-7-fix-jelly-scrolling/">"jelly scrolling" is much less noticeable or fully absent on the new iPad mini</a>, but one prominent technology website disagreed, so we await teardowns for further confirmation.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Faster USB-C port:</strong> The USB-C port on the iPad mini 7 supports data transfer speeds of up to 10 Gbps, compared to 5 Gbps for the iPad mini 6.</li><br/>
<li><strong>eSIM only:</strong> All cellular models of the iPad mini 7 lack a nano-SIM card slot worldwide and instead rely solely on digital eSIM technology.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Wi-Fi 6E support:</strong> The new iPad mini supports the faster Wi-Fi 6E standard, which extends the capabilities of regular Wi-Fi 6 to the 6 GHz band. You will also need a router with Wi-Fi 6E support.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Double the base storage:</strong> iPad mini now starts with 128GB of storage, compared to 64GB for the previous model.</li> <br/>
<li><strong>Final Cut Pro support:</strong> Final Cut Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-compatible-with-final-cut-pro/">compatible with the new iPad mini</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Improved HDR photos:</strong> The new iPad mini supports "Smart HDR 4," whereas the previous model supports "Smart HDR 3." Apple says Smart HDR 4 makes photos look "even more detailed and vivid."</li><br/>
<li><strong>"iPad mini" inscription:</strong> The new iPad mini has an "iPad mini" inscription on the back of device. Previous models of the device are inscribed with "iPad."</li></ul><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-all-new-features-and-changes/">iPad Mini 7 Launches Tomorrow: Here Are 12 Changes to Know About</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-launches-tomorrow-here-are-12-changes-to-know-about.2440699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: 15 Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-15-differences-compared.2337402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:16:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1729620960/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently introduced the seventh-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, offering the A17 Pro chip, Apple Intelligence support, 8GB of memory, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover support, and more. Earlier this year, Apple debuted the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, featuring the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro support, and a larger display size option. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/ipad-mini-vs-air-early-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2498" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839261" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; effectively shares the design of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, with both devices possessing many of the same features such as an all-screen design with no Home button, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> in the top button, and stereo speakers. Despite theoretically being different product lines, the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; are almost identical in terms of specifications and are even available in the same color options. There are still some minor differences between the devices, such as their display sizes and chips, that set the devices apart.<br/>
<br/>
Should you buy the more expensive, larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, or opt for the smaller and more affordable &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;? Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two iPads is best for you. All of the differences between the two devices are listed below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; (seventh generation, 2024)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; (sixth generation, 2024)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>8.3-inch display with 326 ppi</td><br/>
 <td>11-inch or 13-inch display with 264 ppi</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>500 nits max SDR brightness</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: 500 nits max SDR brightness<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: 600 nits max SDR brightness</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smaller, compact design for maximum portability</td><br/>
 <td>Larger design, better for productivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 0.66 pounds (297 grams)</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: Weighs 1.02 pounds (462 grams)<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: Weighs 1.36 pounds (617 grams)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A17 Pro chip (introduced with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro in 2023, made with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> N3 process)</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip (introduced with redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> in 2022, made with TSMC's enhanced 5nm N5P process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>8-core CPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>9-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated media Engine<br/>
Hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC<br/>
Video decode engine<br/>
Video encode engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a> support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Volume buttons on top</td><br/>
 <td>Volume buttons on right side</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12MP Ultra Wide front camera</td><br/>
 <td>Landscape 12MP Ultra Wide front camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>True Tone flash</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Compatible with Bluetooth keyboards only</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-connector/">Smart Connector</a> to support Apple's Magic Keyboard and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-keyboard/">Smart Keyboard</a> Folio</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, or 512GB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, or 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;499</td><br/>
 <td><strong>11-inch</strong>: Starts at &#36;599<br/>
<strong>13-inch</strong>: Start at &#36;799</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is the best all-around option for the majority of users, providing a large screen for productivity and consuming entertainment in a slim, portable design. The additional &#36;100 needed to buy the 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; over the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is more than justified for the benefits that come with its larger display and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, not least the ability to practically use it as a laptop replacement with the Magic Keyboard and &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Yet, most customers who choose the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will do so because of its screen size rather than in spite of it. The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is ideal for comfortably reading ebooks, playing handheld games, and easy transport and storage. Those who buy the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will likely have a specific use case in mind for how they will use the device, such as for note-taking on the go with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, throwing into a small bag to use on public transport, or giving it to a kid as their first tablet.<br/>
<br/>
If you do not see the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller display, easy one-handed grip, lightweight design, and portable form factor as an advantage for your use case and are focused on a more versatile display size, you will likely prefer the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, especially as it is now available with a 13-inch size option. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is more of an all-around device that works as a potential laptop replacement with support for &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj;, with the added bonuses that come with a bigger screen for productivity and entertainment.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/">iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: 15 Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide-15-differences-compared.2337402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook and COO Jeff Williams Visiting China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-coo-jeff-williams-visiting-china.2440693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:59:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Jeff Williams</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> and COO Jeff Williams are in China this week to promote Apple's products and initiatives in the region. Throughout their trip, Cook has been <a href="https://m.weibo.cn/u/5524254784?luicode=20000061&lfid=4883088750673991">active on Weibo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/tim-cook-jeff-williams-china.jpg" alt="" width="6300" height="4235" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-972030" /><br/>
Cook and Williams met students from China Agricultural University and Zhejiang University, exploring how they use iPhones and iPads to improve sustainable agricultural practices. Cook thanked the China Rural Development Fund (CFRD) and everyone involved in the Science and Technology Backyards initiative for their work in promoting efficiency and sustainability in farming.<br/>
<br/>
They also met renowned Chinese fashion photographer Chen Man, who captured images of Cook using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max. Cook spent time with musician Lexie Liu, who shared insights into her creative process and how she uses Apple products, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Mac. Cook and Williams also visited developers at Gala Sports, where they witnessed a demonstration of the game NBA Rivals on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>.<br/>
<br/>
A significant aspect of Cook's trip was the announcement of Apple's support for a national parks initiative in China through a partnership with the China Green Carbon Foundation (CGCF). The visit marks Cook's second trip to China in 2024, following a visit in March, which included the opening of Apple's 57th store in the Greater China region and meetings with key suppliers. <br/>
<br/>
Simultaneously, Apple's Senior Vice President Worldwide Marketing Greg Jozwiak is <a href="https://x.com/gregjoz/status/1848372693923504398">visiting Europe</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jeff-williams/">Jeff Williams</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/cook-and-williams-visiting-china/">Apple CEO Tim Cook and COO Jeff Williams Visiting China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-and-coo-jeff-williams-visiting-china.2440693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Mini Compatible With Final Cut Pro, But Lacks Stage Manager</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-compatible-with-final-cut-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-compatible-with-final-cut-pro-but-lacks-stage-manager.2440692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:41:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-compatible-with-final-cut-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Final Cut Pro</category>
		<category>Stage Manager</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/23/apple-releases-final-cut-pro-logic-pro-for-ipad/">released Final Cut Pro for iPad Pro and iPad Air models</a> with the M1 chip and newer, and now we have confirmed that the professional video editing app is also compatible with the new seventh-generation iPad mini.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-iPad-Final-Cut-Pro-Logic-Pro-hero-feature-actual-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2499" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896926" /><br/>
Apple recently updated the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/final-cut-pro-for-ipad/id1631624924">App Store listing</a> for Final Cut Pro to indicate the app is now compatible with both M-series chips and the A17 Pro chip in the new iPad mini. Apple's audio editing app Logic Pro is also compatible with the new iPad mini, as that app merely requires any iPad model with an A12 Bionic chip or newer.<br/>
<br/>
However, some Final Cut Pro features are not compatible with the new iPad mini due to hardware or software limitations, as outlined in the app's description.<br/>
<br/>
We have also confirmed that the new iPad mini is not compatible with the Stage Manager feature, which is not very surprising given the device's smaller 8.3-inch display size compared to the larger 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro and iPad Air models.<br/>
<br/>
On supported iPads, Stage Manager allows users to resize apps into overlapping windows for an improved multitasking experience. Stage Manager also fully supports an external display with up to 6K resolution, allowing users to work with up to four apps on the iPad and up to four apps on the external display simultaneously.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad mini launches this Wednesday.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/final-cut-pro/">Final Cut Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ipad-mini-7-compatible-with-final-cut-pro/">New iPad Mini Compatible With Final Cut Pro, But Lacks Stage Manager</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-mini-compatible-with-final-cut-pro-but-lacks-stage-manager.2440692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Kicks Off Week-Long Sale With Big Discounts on Monitors and TVs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/samsung-week-long-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-kicks-off-week-long-sale-with-big-discounts-on-monitors-and-tvs.2440691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:31:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/samsung-week-long-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung has begun a <a href="https://howl.me/cnlVGcT3IGL">new week-long savings event</a>, and it includes discounts on TVs, smartphones, monitors and memory, wearables, appliances, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/samsung-new-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-889540" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
One of the most notable offers during this sale is a bundle deal with Samsung's TVs and monitors. When you purchase <a href="https://howl.me/cnlV16oWQ0u">select gaming monitors</a> at the same time as one of Samsung's OLED S95D TVs, you can save up to &#36;1,075 on your entire order.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVGcT3IGL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Samsung Week Discount Event</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung is also offering the 27-inch Odyssey G3 Gaming Monitor for free (&#36;229.99 value) when you purchase <a href="https://howl.me/cnlV62G9wMC">select gaming monitors</a>. You can find a collection of the monitors on sale during Samsung Week below, as well as a few TVs and Galaxy devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors and Storage</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVMG7DfcK">990 EVO 5.0 NVMe SSD 2TB</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;239.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVLMVgenn">2TB Portable SSD</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;284.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmh387N2uIj">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;699.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVXiv4IUK">27-inch Odyssey G6 Pro Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;899.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKayx1Nx">34-inch Odyssey OLED G8 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVKXc8UKH">32-inch Odyssey Quantum Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,079.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmSCTMeMf1L">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,999.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX0OsAHAg">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,199.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVRaSFAOn">85-inch QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,579.99, down from &#36;2,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cnlVQujFbtE">85-inch Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;2,299.99, down from &#36;3,699.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Galaxy Products</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbV7Ybcky">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,600 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbXJFsJWi">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;945 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbYxetDfM">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;350</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbZknUAIi">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;100</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<b><em>Interested in hearing more about top deals as we head into the holidays? <a href="http://eepurl.com/itTnTk">Sign up</a> for our newsletter and we'll keep you updated so you don't miss the biggest deals of the season!</em></b><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/samsung-week-long-sale/">Samsung Kicks Off Week-Long Sale With Big Discounts on Monitors and TVs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-kicks-off-week-long-sale-with-big-discounts-on-monitors-and-tvs.2440691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: New MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac Mini Models With M4 Chips Launching &#039;Very Soon&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/gurman-says-m4-macs-launch-very-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-macbook-pro-imac-and-mac-mini-models-with-m4-chips-launching-very-soon.2440689/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:11:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/gurman-says-m4-macs-launch-very-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to launch its first Macs with the M4 series of chips "very soon," according to <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848723937880117481"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
In a social media post today, Gurman said these Macs will include new MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac mini models specifically. He continues to expect the next Mac mini to feature a "revamped" design, in line with his previous reporting that said the new model will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/mac-mini-redesign-rumor/">nearly as small as an Apple TV and gain two front-facing USB-C ports</a>.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes are rumored for the next MacBook Pro and iMac models, but the entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro is expected to gain an additional Thunderbolt port compared to the current model, based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-potentially-facing-worst-leak-since-iphone-4/">alleged leaks earlier this month</a>.<br/>
<br/>
It's not entirely clear if Apple plans to hold an online event this month, like its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">"Scary Fast" event on October 30 last year</a>, or if the new Macs will be announced with Apple Newsroom press releases only like the iPad mini 7. If there is an event this month, Apple would likely invite the media to watch it online very soon. Apple sent out invites for the October 30 event last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-october-mac-event-2023/">on October 24</a>, six days in advance.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the new Macs will be accompanied by unspecified "USB-C accessories." <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris recently discovered code references to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/apple-new-magic-mouse-trackpad-keyboard/">new versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard</a>, and these accessories will likely switch from Lightning to USB-C for charging alongside the new iMac. In the EU, a regulation requiring USB-C as a common charging port goes into effect later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Here is everything that Apple is likely to announce:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>14-inch MacBook Pro with the standard M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro with M4 Pro and M4 Max chip options</li><br/>
<li>iMac with the standard M4 chip</li><br/>
<li>A redesigned, smaller Mac mini with M4 and M4 Pro chip options</li><br/>
<li>Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard accessories with USB-C ports</li></ul><strong>Update:</strong> In a <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1848748246799429753">follow-up post</a>, Gurman said that Apple is inviting the media and content creators to a hands-on experience in Los Angeles next Wednesday, and he believes this means the new Macs would need to be announced before then.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/gurman-says-m4-macs-launch-very-soon/">Gurman: New MacBook Pro, iMac, and Mac Mini Models With M4 Chips Launching &#039;Very Soon&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-macbook-pro-imac-and-mac-mini-models-with-m4-chips-launching-very-soon.2440689/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Reviews Say &#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; is Fixed, With a Major Exception</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/does-ipad-mini-7-fix-jelly-scrolling/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-reviews-say-jelly-scrolling-is-fixed-with-a-major-exception.2440687/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 06:44:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/does-ipad-mini-7-fix-jelly-scrolling/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first iPad mini 7 reviews were published today, and many of them said that "jelly scrolling" display behavior is either less noticeable or fully unnoticeable on the device. However, one prominent technology website disagrees.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-mini-7-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970887" /><br/>
The major exception is <em>The Verge</em>.<br/>
<br/>
"The 'jelly scrolling' effect from the last model is still very much present," opined <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/10/22/24275956/apple-ipad-mini-2024-review"><em>The Verge</em>'s David Pierce</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a follow-up comment <a href="https://www.threads.net/@imdavidpierce/post/DBbbQEiJYyi">shared on Threads</a>, Pierce said "I'm sitting here scrolling on both the 2021 and 2024 Mini, and if you forced me to pick which one is better I'd say the 2024 wiggles LESS. But it still wiggles."<br/>
<br/>
Many other reviews said that "jelly scrolling" seems to be fixed, as a result of Apple making <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/ipad-mini-7-jelly-scrolling/">display-related hardware changes</a> to minimize the effect.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://sixcolors.com/post/2024/10/ipad-mini-2024-review-a-familiar-friend-gets-an-a-i-refresh/">Jason Snell, writing for <em>Six Colors</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>It's my understanding that the new model's display circuitry is different from the old model, and I couldn't detect any "jelly scrolling" in my use. It doesn't mean it's for sure gone, and I'm looking forward to eagle-eyed "jelly scrolling" experts reporting back with their results, but I sure couldn't see it, even when I recorded myself scrolling at a high frame rate and played it back frame by frame.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.stuff.tv/review/apple-ipad-mini-a17-pro-review/">Craig Grannell, writing for <em>Stuff</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Apple reckons it's optimised the display, but won't provide any details on how. To my eyes, the jelly scrolling doesn't look as bad as I recall it being last time, but bear in mind two things. First, I don't have the old iPad mini to compare. Secondly, I wasn't too fussed about this last time anyway.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.engadget.com/mobile/tablets/ipad-mini-7-review-safe-boring-and-everything-i-want-in-a-small-tablet-130039378.html">Nathan Ingraham, writing for <em>Engadget</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>One bit of good news about the screen is that it seems Apple has fixed the "jelly-scrolling" problem that plagued the prior iPad mini. Jelly-scrolling occurs when one side of a screen doesn't refresh at exactly the same rate as the other, and this effect was noticeable in portrait mode with the old iPad mini. It's not something that I ever noticed while using the new iPad mini. I am curious to see if the issue has been totally resolved or if my eyes just didn't catch it, but I'll continue using the iPad mini in the coming weeks to see if I spot any display issues.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.wired.com/review/apple-ipad-mini-a17-pro-2024/">Brenda Stolyar, writing for <em>WIRED</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>But I can't talk about the iPad Mini display without going over the infamous jelly scrolling fiasco on the 2021 model. iPad Mini owners bemoaned that one side of the screen refreshed slower than the other when scrolling up and down on the display. I didn't experience this with my Mini, but Apple did make it a point to optimize the LCD in the latest model to alleviate this issue. Apple was tight-lipped on exactly what it changed, but for what it's worth, I once again have yet to see any problems on my test unit.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tomsguide.com/tablets/ipads/ipad-mini-7-review">Tony Polanco, writing for <em>Tom's Guide</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Lastly, I didn't notice the infamous "jelly scrolling" screen-tearing effect that plagued the iPad mini 6 during my testing. I can't say whether or not Apple fixed this issue or I simply didn't see it. But if that should change, I'll update this review.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macstories.net/stories/ipad-mini-review-the-third-place/">Federico Viticci, writing at <em>MacStories</em></a>:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>And while the display technology is unchanged  it's an IPS display that refreshes at 60 Hz  the so-called jelly scrolling issue has been fixed thanks to an optimized display controller.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
"Jelly scrolling" refers to screen tearing, which can cause text or images on one side of the screen to appear to be tilted downwards because of a mismatch in refresh rates. It can cause one side of the display to look as if it is responding faster than the other side, resulting in a visual disturbance that is hard to ignore once noticed.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/ipad-mini-jelly-scrolling-ifixit.jpg" alt="" width="3558" height="2002" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836653" /><em>"Jelly scrolling" on iPad mini 6</em></div><br/>
The effect is noticeable on the iPad mini 6 when the device was used in portrait orientation, leading to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/27/ipad-mini-6-jelly-scroll-issue-vertical/">complaints from customers</a> over the past three years.<br/>
<br/>
Shortly after the iPad mini 6 launched, an Apple spokesperson told <em>Ars Technica</em> on background that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/28/apple-jelly-scrolling-normal-behavior/">"jelly scrolling" was "normal" behavior</a> for iPads with LCD displays. Given that LCDs refresh line by line, there is a tiny delay between when the lines at the top and lines at the bottom are refreshed. The effect is particularly noticeable on the iPad mini 6 because it can be seen in portrait orientation rather than landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad mini launches this Wednesday, October 23.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/does-ipad-mini-7-fix-jelly-scrolling/">iPad Mini 7 Reviews Say &#039;Jelly Scrolling&#039; is Fixed, With a Major Exception</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-reviews-say-jelly-scrolling-is-fixed-with-a-major-exception.2440687/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18.1: AirPods Pro 2 Hearing Protection Availability Limited to US and Canada at Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ios-airpods-pro-2-hearing-features-us-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-airpods-pro-2-hearing-protection-availability-limited-to-us-and-canada-at-launch.2440675/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 05:02:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ios-airpods-pro-2-hearing-features-us-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/airpods-pro-hearing-features-launching-in-ios-18-1/">Hearing Protection feature for AirPods Pro 2</a> launching with iOS 18.1 next week will initially be available only in the United States and Canada, according to <a href="https://www.apple.com/airpods-pro/hearing-health/">Apple's website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/airpods-pro-voice-isolation.jpg" alt="" width="1380" height="776" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957064" /><br/>
The Hearing Protection feature continuously monitors the user's environment and reduces the impact of loud sounds, such as traffic or concerts, in real time. This function will be integrated across various listening modes, including noise cancellation and transparency mode  but only in the US and Canada at launch.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the Hearing Test and Hearing Aid features are expected to be available fall 2024, according to Apple. Apple has obtained FDA authorization in the United States to market AirPods Pro 2 as "clinical grade" hearing aids. However, the company said in September that the Hearing Aid feature is pending marketing authorization from global health authorities, so there is a question mark over worldwide availability.<br/>
<br/>
The new hearing health functions allow AirPods Pro 2 owners to take hearing tests directly through their iPhone, with results stored in the Health app. For users who show signs of hearing loss, the AirPods can function as genuine hearing aids, boosting specific frequencies in real-time. The update also introduces advanced hearing protection features that automatically reduce exposure to loud environmental sounds.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/21/18-new-things-your-iphone-can-do-ios-18-1/">18 New Things Your iPhone Can Do in iOS 18.1</a></li></ul><br/>
The company is expected to release iOS 18.1 to the public on Monday, October 28, bringing the new AirPods Pro 2 capabilities to eligible users.<br/>
<br/>
<small><em>Article corrected to Hearing Protection regional limitations, not hearing features per se. Apologies for the error.</em></small><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/ios-airpods-pro-2-hearing-features-us-canada/">iOS 18.1: AirPods Pro 2 Hearing Protection Availability Limited to US and Canada at Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-1-airpods-pro-2-hearing-protection-availability-limited-to-us-and-canada-at-launch.2440675/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Create Dark Mode Icons for Apps That Won&#039;t Go Dark</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-create-a-dark-mode-icon-for-almost-any-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-create-dark-mode-icons-for-apps-that-wont-go-dark.2440668/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 02:15:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-create-a-dark-mode-icon-for-almost-any-app&#038;post_date=1729599320/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Dark Mode</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you tried making your iPhone's Home Screen app icons dark using the new customization options in iOS 18? If so, you may have run up against the issue that, despite all efforts, some app icons simply refuse to turn dark. Well, we may have a solution for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/dark-mode-icons-custom.jpg" alt="dark mode icons" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971744" /><br/>
It's been over two months since Apple released iOS 18, but not all app developers have updated their apps to include equivalent dark mode icons (we're looking at you, Amazon). And while iOS 18 tries to automatically generate dark icons when developers haven't provided them, it doesn't always work.<br/>
<br/>
If that leaves one or two light icons spoiling your otherwise carefully crafted dark-themed Home Screen, don't despair. The following steps describe a relatively simple method you can use that will give most stubborn app icons a passable dark appearance. Big thanks to Redditor <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/comments/1fjxymi/i_created_dark_mode_icons_for_apps_that_dont_have/">Straight_Random_2211</a> for sharing their custom dark icon assets and process, which we've distilled below:<br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>On your iPhone, download the "Get App Icon" shortcut: [<a href="https://www.icloud.com/shortcuts/1ce47e64a1f74e6ba76ef5fd36951de6">Shortcut Link</a>].</li><br/>
<li>Run the shortcut and type in the name of the app whose icon you want to make dark, then select it from the search results. The icon will be saved in your photo library.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/get-app-icon-shortcut.jpg" alt="shortcuts" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971754" /><br/>
<li>Next, save the following dark-background image to your photo library (long press  <strong>Save to Photos</strong>): [<a href="https://ibb.co/6r5kkmn">Image Link</a>]</li><br/>
<li>Visit Remove.bg's <a href="https://www.remove.bg/t/change-background">"change background" web tool</a>, then tap the blue <strong>Upload Image</strong> button and choose the app icon that's saved in your photos.</li><br/>
<li>Under "Background Image," tap <strong>Select File</strong>, then choose the dark background image that's also saved in your photos.</li><br/>
<li>Press and hold the resulting image on the remove.bg webpage, then tap <strong>Save to Photos</strong> in the contextual menu.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/custom-dark-mode-app-icon.jpg" alt="twitch" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971764" /><br/>
<li>Now, open Shortcuts and tap the <strong>+</strong> button at the top to create a new Shortcut, then select the <strong>Open App</strong> action.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the blue "App" text in the "Open App" action, then choose the app whose icon you want to make dark.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the chevron at the top of the screen, select <strong>Add to Home Screen</strong> from the dropdown menu.</li><br/>
<li>Label the shortcut as the app's name and choose your custom dark icon for the photo, then tap <strong>Add</strong> to finish.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/home-screen-shortcut-dark-app-icon.jpg" alt="custom dark icon" width="4377" height="2796" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-971769" /><br/>
</ol>With a bit of luck, your custom dark mode icon will look the part on your personalized Home Screen. Note: If you have several app icons that you want to create dark mode equivalents for, make sure to create a new "Open App" shortcut for each one as you go. If you don't, you may end up accidentally creating several icon shortcuts that refer back to the same app.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-18-create-a-dark-mode-icon-for-almost-any-app/">iOS 18: Create Dark Mode Icons for Apps That Won&#039;t Go Dark</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-create-dark-mode-icons-for-apps-that-wont-go-dark.2440668/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
