<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 08:04:44 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iOS 18.4 Will Be Released in April With These New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/ios-18-4-in-april/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ios-18-4-will-be-released-in-april-with-these-new-features.2450223/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 07:15:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/ios-18-4-in-april/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a recent press release, Apple confirmed that iOS 18.4 will be released in April.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Apple-Intelligence-Color-Palette-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988289" /><br/>
From the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-news-plus-food-ios-18-4/">Apple News+ Food announcement</a>:<blockquote><strong>Coming with iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 in April</strong>, Apple News+ subscribers will have access to Apple News+ Food, a new section that will feature tens of thousands of recipes — as well as stories about restaurants, healthy eating, kitchen essentials, and more — from the world's top food publishers, including Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food & Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats.</blockquote>The first beta of iOS 18.4 is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-releases-ios-18-4-beta-1/">already available for developers</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/24/apple-seeds-ios-18-4-public-beta/">public beta testers</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The first iOS 18.4 beta does not include any of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/17/apple-already-testing-ios-18-5/">Apple Intelligence features for Siri</a> that were originally expected, such as personal context and on-screen awareness, but the update still has a handful of other new features and changes.<br/>
<br/>
Below, we highlight some of iOS 18.4's key new features.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Available Now</h2><br/>
<h3>Priority Notifications</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Intelligence-Priority-Notifications.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991832" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 introduces a promised Apple Intelligence feature that can automatically identify and surface your most important notifications on the Lock Screen. <br/>
<br/>
The option can be turned on in the Settings app under Notifications → Prioritize Notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence requires an iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, or any iPhone 16 model.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple News+ Food</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-News-Food.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991773" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 adds a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/apple-news-plus-food-ios-18-4/">new Food section to the Apple News app</a> on the iPhone. This section will provide Apple News+ subscribers with tens of thousands of recipes and other food-related content from well-known food-related publishers, at no extra cost.<br/>
<br/>
Here is how Apple describes the new Food section:<blockquote>With the new Food feature, users will be able to find stories curated by Apple News editors, as well as browse, search, and filter tens of thousands of recipes in the Recipe Catalog — with new recipes added every day. The beautifully designed recipe format makes it easy to review ingredients and directions, and a new cook mode takes step-by-step instructions to the full screen. Users can also save their favorite recipes for later and access them offline.</blockquote>Apple News+ is available in the United States, Canada, Australia, and the United Kingdom. The service provides digital access to hundreds of major publications, including The Wall Street Journal, New York Magazine, PEOPLE, The Athletic, Rolling Stone, and others. In the U.S., Apple News+ costs &#36;12.99 per month, and it is also included in the Apple One Premier bundle alongside other Apple services for &#36;37.95 per month.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ambient Music</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-ambient-music.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991311" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 adds a new Ambient Music feature to the Control Center on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
This feature allows you to quickly listen to a collection of songs from four different categories, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>More</h3><br/>
<ul><li>iOS 18.4 makes Apple Intelligence available in more languages, including French, German, Italian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish, Japanese, Korean, Chinese (Simplified), English (Singapore), and English (India).</li><br/>
<li>There is a new "Sketch" drawing style for the Image Playground feature, alongside existing "Animation" and "Illustration" styles. This feature, powered by Apple Intelligence, lets you generate images based on text descriptions.</li><br/>
<li>In some vehicles equipped with very large dashboard displays, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/23/ios-18-4-carplay-change/">CarPlay is showing an extra row of app icons</a> on a single page.</li><br/>
<li>iOS 18.4 lets you set a default maps app, such as Google Maps, in the EU. You can also set a default translation app worldwide.</li></ul>Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features/">iOS 18.4 features guide</a> for even more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Coming Later</h2><br/>
<h3>Vision Pro App</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Vision-Pro-iPhone-App.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991844" /><br/>
It is not in the first beta, but iOS 18.4 will add a new Apple Vision Pro app to the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
The app will offer Vision Pro users a new way to download apps and games from the App Store, discover Apple TV content, learn helpful Vision Pro tips, quickly access information about their own Vision Pro, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The app will appear for Vision Pro users when they update their iPhone to the iOS 18.4 release, and it will also be available in the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>New Emoji</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/Unicode-16-Emoji-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951831" /><br/>
iOS 18.4 will include new emoji, according to code seen by <em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris. <br/>
<br/>
iOS 15.4, iOS 16.4, and iOS 17.4 all introduced new emoji, so there was a good chance that trend would continue with iOS 18.4.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, the Unicode Consortium previewed the new emoji that should be coming with iOS 18.4, with new options including face with bags under eyes, fingerprint, leafless tree, root vegetable, harp, shovel, splatter, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/ios-18-4-in-april/">Apple Says iOS 18.4 Will Be Released in April With These New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ios-18-4-will-be-released-in-april-with-these-new-features.2450223/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Trump Responds to Apple Keeping Diversity Policies</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/trump-on-apple-diversity-policies/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trump-responds-to-apple-keeping-diversity-policies.2450221/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 06:32:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/trump-on-apple-diversity-policies/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Donald Trump</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In an all-caps <a href="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114070315739588346">post</a> on Truth Social today, U.S. President Donald Trump said Apple should fully end its diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) policies.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2017/09/cook-trump.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="450" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-586140" /><br/>
"APPLE SHOULD GET RID OF DEI RULES, NOT JUST MAKE ADJUSTMENTS TO THEM," he wrote.<br/>
<br/>
Trump's post comes one day after Apple held its annual shareholders meeting, during which a majority of shareholders <a href="https://apnews.com/article/apple-dei-shareholder-proposal-annual-meeting-96637c8d4fa3d5e2a73dc59a59c2485b">voted against a proposal</a> that asked the company to consider abolishing its <a href="https://www.apple.com/diversity/">Inclusion & Diversity</a> policies and goals.<br/>
<br/>
The proposal was submitted by the U.S. National Center for Public Policy Research, which calls itself a "non-partisan, free-market, independent conservative think tank." The organization said that DEI programs pose "litigation, reputational, and financial risks to companies, and therefore financial risks to their shareholders."<br/>
<br/>
Apple recommended that shareholders vote against the proposal, labeling it as an attempt to "micromanage" the company's business operations. Apple said that it already actively monitors its operations to maintain compliance with applicable non‑discrimination laws. During the shareholder meeting, Apple CEO Tim Cook acknowledged that the company may be forced to make changes to its DEI policies in the future, as required by law. Trump believes that Apple should get rid of the policies, rather than modify them.<br/>
<br/>
In any case, Cook <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1894428592978727404">told shareholders</a> that Apple will always have a culture of belonging.<br/>
<br/>
"We strive to create a culture of belonging where everyone can do their best work," said Apple, in its <a href="https://s2.q4cdn.com/470004039/files/doc_financials/2025/Proxy_Statement_2025.pdf">annual shareholders meeting notice</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Trump has criticized DEI programs since returning to the White House. Last month, he signed an <a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/01/ending-radical-and-wasteful-government-dei-programs-and-preferencing/">executive order</a> that "terminates 'diversity, equity, and inclusion' (DEI) discrimination in the federal workforce." In response, some other tech companies like Google have scaled back DEI policies in recent weeks.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/donald-trump/">Donald Trump</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/trump-on-apple-diversity-policies/">Trump Responds to Apple Keeping Diversity Policies</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trump-responds-to-apple-keeping-diversity-policies.2450221/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Air Design, Specs, and More: All the Rumors So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/iphone-17-air-design-specs-all-rumors-so-far/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-design-specs-and-more-all-the-rumors-so-far.2450217/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 03:31:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/iphone-17-air-design-specs-all-rumors-so-far/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17 Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This year, Apple is expected to discontinue the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> "Plus" device in its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup to make way for an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; "Air," so-called because of its ultra-thin profile.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-17-Air-Fanned-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-989999" /><br/>
Below is a compilation of every rumor and leak we have registered from reputable sources thus far about Apple's new entry in its flagship smartphone lineup. <br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; "Air"?</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">About the Name</span><br><br/>
There has been some uncertainty about Apple's strategy for the new slimmer &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model and its position in the lineup. YouTuber <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jon-prosser/">Jon Prosser</a> was <a href="https://youtu.be/8c7HWZRO_D8?feature=shared">first to suggest</a> that the device could be positioned as an "‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ Air." <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/12/slim-iphone-17-could-be-iphone-air/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> has since come out in agreement about the naming, which Apple could use to boost sales. <br/>
<br/>
Replacing the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; "Plus," which, like the "mini" models before it, has not sold well, the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;‌ Air will represent a new approach in Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup, offering a device with a substantially thinner design that sits between the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;‌ and ‌&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;‌ Pro. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman believes that the design of the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;‌ Air will "just be a step toward something better" since Apple will eventually want to "squeeze the power of a Pro model into this smaller design." However, he does not expect this to occur before 2027 at the earliest.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Device Thickness Rumors</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Thinner Than &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6</span><br><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/apple-plans-a-thinner-iphone-in-2025">The Information</a></em>, Apple's all-new &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; model will have a "significantly thinner" design with an aluminum chassis, rather than a titanium casing like Apple's Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
There have been mixed rumors on just how thin Apple will be able to make it. Rumors have hovered around 6mm, however in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">recent report</a>, reliable Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that he expects the ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ to measure in at about 5.5mm at its thinnest point. At 5.5mm, the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;‌ Air would be the thinnest ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ to date – thinner than the 6.9mm ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 6 that came out in 2014. 5.5mm would be approximately 30% thinner than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, which measures in at 7.8mm thick, and 33% thinner than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, which are 8.25mm thick. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPhone-16-Pro-vs-iPhone-17-Air-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-985932" /><br/>
The device is said to have only a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-air-features-reported/">single speaker</a>, in the earpiece, as there is apparently not enough room for a second speaker on the bottom edge. <em>The Information</em> also claims that the device will feature a narrower <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, though this specific claim has since been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">contested</a>. Internally code-named D23, the device's redesign has been described as a major one equivalent to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Display Size</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Smaller Than Plus Model</span><br><br/>
The first details about the size of the device's display arrived courtesy of Haitong International Securities analyst Jeff Pu, who said it would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-rumor/">6.6 inches</a>. Apple analyst &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; has since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">corroborated</a> Pu's claim. <br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">Display Supply Chain Consultants (DSCC) analyst Ross Young</a> says the device will feature a 6.55-inch display, which could be rounded up to 6.6 inches. Complicating matters, YouTuber &zwnj;Jon Prosser&zwnj; more recently claimed that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-air/">iPhone 17 Air</a> will be equipped with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/iphone-17-air-now-rumored-to-feature-6-7-inch-display/">6.7-inch display</a>, rather than a 6.6-inch display as previously rumored. For context, the existing &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus has a 6.7-inch display. However, in response to Prosser's prediction, Young reiterated his 6.55-inch display size claim for the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Always-On Display</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">ProMotion Support</span><br><br/>
Apple intends to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/promotion-standard-iphones-2025/">expand</a> ProMotion to the entire lineup in 2025, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-17-and-17-air-120hz-promotion-rumor/">including the iPhone 17 "Air,"</a> allowing all &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models to ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate for smoother scrolling and video content when necessary. This will be enabled by Apple's use of Samsung's high performance <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/18/iphone-17-air-to-use-samsung-m4-panel/">"M14" OLED display panel</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/120-hz-14-holepunch-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-806922" /><br/>
Previously, only "Pro" models in Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; lineup used the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> OLED panel, which is why they have exclusively supported ProMotion. Notably, ProMotion would also enable the display on the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; "Air" to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate as low as 1Hz, allowing for an always-on display that can show the Lock Screen's clock, widgets, notifications, and wallpaper even when the device is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Camera Redesign</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Relocated Lens</span><br><br/>
<em>The Information</em> claimed that the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; will have cameras in locations we haven't seen before on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. According to a May report, the rear cameras could be moved to the "top center" of the device. Some Android phones like Google's Pixel 9 Pro have rear cameras in a top-center position, or in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/21/alleged-iphone-17-air-shell/">runway-style horizontal bar</a>, but Apple's &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; camera system has occupied the top-left corner ever since the 2007 model. <br/>
<br/>
Adding to the intrigue, Apple analyst &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; has claimed that the device will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-ultra-thin-iphone-17-specs/">only one camera</a>, as opposed to two or three.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-17-Air-Front-Page-Tech-Render-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990401" /><br/>
Since then, YouTube channel Front Page Tech has revealed the alleged design of the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;. The renders show an all-new camera bar across the top of the device's rear shell. On the left side of the bar is a single rear camera, and on the right side there is a microphone and an LED camera flash.<br/>
<br/>
Most recently, a CAD render of all the devices in Apple's upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup has been shared online by leaker Majin Bu, specifically showing the allegedly different rear camera system designs of the standard &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, including the all-new ultra-thin &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;. The CAD shows the described horizontal camera bar design accommodating the single camera lens.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iphone-17-lineup-cad-render-majin-bu.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991423" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Alleged &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; shown on far left</em></div><br/>
Weibo-based leakers <a href="https://weibo.com/5821279480/PfKGMhlUC">Fixed Focus Digital</a>, <a href="https://weibo.com/5673255066/PfKNCANbc">Ice Universe</a>, and <a href="https://weibo.com/6048569942/PfKLpEeBk">Digital Chat Station</a> have all backed the accuracy of the CAD image, based on their own information from Apple's supply chain in China. "The appearance is basically like this," commented Digital Chat Station in reference to the image.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">More Durable Screen</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Anti-Reflective Coating</span><br><br/>
All &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models will feature an anti-reflective display that is more scratch-resistant than Apple's Ceramic Shield found on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">Chinese Weibo leaker Instant Digital</a>. <br/>
<br/>
The outer glass on the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; series is said to have a "super-hard anti-reflective layer" that is "more scratch-resistant." It's not clear whether Apple is planning to adopt the Gorilla Glass Armor that Samsung uses in its Galaxy S24 Ultra, but the description of Corning's latest technology matches the rumor.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Improved Front Camera</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Better Selfies</span><br><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/04/kuo-iphone-17-to-feature-24mp-front-facing-camera/">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, the entire &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; lineup will feature a 24-megapixel front-facing camera with a six-element lens. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14 and 15 feature a 12-megapixel front-facing camera with five plastic lens elements, and the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup features the same hardware. <br/>
<br/>
The upgraded resolution on the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; will allow photos to maintain their quality even when cropped or zoomed in, while the larger number of pixels will capture finer details. The upgrade to a six-element lens should also slightly enhance image quality.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">More RAM</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;"><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></span><br><br/>
Haitong analyst Jeff Pu <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-pro-12gb-ram-rumor/">claims</a> the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; will feature 8GB of RAM, compared to 6GB of RAM on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/Apple-Intelligence-Priority-Notifications.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991832" /><br/>
It's worth noting that all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models (including the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a>) are fitted with 8GB of RAM – a hardware requirement of on-device &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; – so it's almost a surety that the slim device will follow suit.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Next-Gen Processor</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Better Performance</span><br><br/>
According to <em>The Information</em> and Haitong International analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">Jeff Pu</a>, the device will be equipped with Apple's A19 chip, which is likely to be based on an optimized version of TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process, possibly N3P or N3X. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/3nm-apple-silicon-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1810" height="1018" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-804957" /><br/>
In contrast, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17-pro/">iPhone 17 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 17 Pro&zwnj; Max are expected to include an A19 Pro chip. Compared to earlier versions of &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips, the N3P chips offer increased performance efficiency and increased transistor density. <br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Impressive Battery Life</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Thanks to C1 Modem</span><br><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> and industry analyst &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj;, the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj; will utilize the same <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-unveils-c1/">C1 modem</a> that recently debuted in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/19/apple-announces-iphone-16e/">iPhone 16e</a>. The C1 is Apple's first custom-designed modem chip, and will bring significant advantages to the upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/apple-c1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990815" /><br/>
The C1 is the most power-efficient modem ever featured in an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and promises very good battery life even within the frame of the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;'s ultra-thin design. According to Apple's tech specs, the &zwnj;iPhone 16e&zwnj; offers up to 26 hours of battery life for video playback, compared to up to 22 hours for the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;. This efficiency comes from Apple's complete control over the modem's design and integration with its custom silicon. The only minor drawback to the C1 is that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/apples-c1-modem-iphone-17-air-lack-mmwave/">does not support mmWave</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Wi-Fi 7 Support</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">For Enhanced Connectivity</span><br><br/>
Apple will use its own custom-designed Wi-Fi chip in all upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models, including the &zwnj;iPhone 17 Air&zwnj;, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/kuo-iphone-17-models-apple-designed-wi-fi-7-chip/">industry analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo said the switch to in-house Wi-Fi chips will "enhance connectivity across Apple devices" while also giving Apple a cost reduction. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/Apple-Wi-Fi-Chip-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883034" /><br/>
Apple's custom wireless chip will support Wi-Fi 7 specification, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/iphone-17-air-wifi-7-rumor/">Jeff Pu</a>, an analyst who covers companies within Apple's supply chain. All current &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models are equipped with a combined Wi-Fi and Bluetooth chip supplied by Broadcom.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">eSIM Worldwide</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">No SIM Card Slot</span><br><br/>
The slim device will lack a physical SIM card slot, and instead rely entirely on digital eSIM technology, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/10/iphone-17-air-details-ming-chi-kuo/">according to Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. In the U.S., all &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 14, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models lack a physical SIM card tray already, but all iPhones sold in other countries still have one for now. <br/>
<br/>
The lack of a SIM card slot in all forthcoming &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; models worldwide has been previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/25/iphone-17-esim-only-in-more-countries-report/">reported</a>, but it is not clear how the devices would be sold in the Chinese market, where the use of eSIMs in smartphones is not currently authorized.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-17-Air-Rainbow-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990000" /><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">Pricing Rumors</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Premium or Affordable?</span><br><br/>
<em>The Information</em> reported that the slimmer &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; could have a higher price tag than the Pro Max model, which currently starts at &#36;1,199, despite suggestions that it will not be as feature-rich as Apple's top-tier Max. <br/>
<br/>
However, Haitong International analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/18/iphone-17-air-rumored-features/">Jeff Pu</a> believes the device will be a mid-tier &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that replaces the Plus model. Additionally, a report out of China has claimed that the ultra-thin &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;'s price will be similar to that of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, which starts at &#36;899 in the United States. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/26/iphone-17-air-design-specs-all-rumors-so-far/">iPhone 17 Air Design, Specs, and More: All the Rumors So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-air-design-specs-and-more-all-the-rumors-so-far.2450217/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Quick macOS Tip: Create and Use Text Clippings for Productivity</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/macos-tip-create-text-clippings-productivity/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/quick-macos-tip-create-and-use-text-clippings-for-productivity.2450216/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 02:40:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/macos-tip-create-text-clippings-productivity&#038;post_date=1740577219/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In macOS, a Text Clipping is a selection of text that you've dragged from an application to another location on your Mac, where it becomes a unique kind of standalone file. <br/>
<br/>
The relatively little-known feature has been around since at least Mac OS 9, and it offers a convenient way to save out pieces of text from pretty much anywhere for later use in another app or document.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/macos-text-clippings-hidden-feature.jpg" alt="" width="5120" height="2880" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991857" /><br/>
To create a Text Clipping, simply highlight any piece of text, then hold left-click and drag it with your mouse to your Desktop or an open Finder window. <br/>
<br/>
This saves the highlighted text – including any rich text formatting – as a <strong>.textclipping</strong> file named after the first few words of text that you selected, but you can easily rename it to make it more identifiable.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/macos-text-clipping-finder.jpg" alt="finder" width="2846" height="1404" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991858" /><br/>
To use the selected text in another file like a Pages document, drag the Text Clipping into the open document and the text will be automatically pasted wherever the cursor is located. <br/>
<br/>
You can paste the clipping in the same way into all sorts of open files and apps, including browser search engines, Mail compose windows, Xcode projects, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/macos-text-clipping-pages.jpg" alt="Pages" width="5120" height="2880" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991859" /><br/>
To quickly view the contents of a Text Clipping, simply select the file and invoke Quick Look with a tap of the spacebar. <br/>
<br/>
You can also double-click a Text Clipping to view the text in a dedicated window, and even highlight and copy (<strong>Command-C</strong>) just a snippet of the text from this window for pasting elsewhere.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/text-clipping-contents.jpg" alt="text clipping" width="1254" height="242" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991860" /><br/>
Text clippings can speed up many repetitive tasks, making things like reusing email/letter templates and code snippets a cinch. If clippings become indispensable to your workflow, consider creating a dedicated folder to store them, otherwise they can quickly clutter up your desktop.<br/>
<br/>
Bear in mind that Text Clippings store content in a unique format that may not be compatible across all platforms or devices. So if you're sharing clippings, it's best to convert them into standard text formats to ensure they can be opened elsewhere. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macos/">macOS</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/macos-tip-create-text-clippings-productivity/">Quick macOS Tip: Create and Use Text Clippings for Productivity</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/quick-macos-tip-create-and-use-text-clippings-for-productivity.2450216/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Fixing &#039;Trump&#039; Dictation Processing Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-fixing-dictation-bug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fixing-trump-dictation-processing-bug.2450187/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 13:18:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-fixing-dictation-bug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Multiple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners today noticed a pronunciation processing issue that causes the word "Trump" to momentarily show up when using dictation to send a message with the word "racist."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/trump-iphone-dictation-issue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991829" /><br/>
In some cases, when speaking the word racist through the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s built-in dictation feature, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; briefly interprets the spoken word as "Trump" and "Trump" text shows up in the Messages app before being corrected to the actual word (racist) as Apple's processing interprets what was said.<br/>
<br/>
Speaking the word racist with dictation doesn't always show "Trump" first, though it did show up more often than other words in our testing. We also saw "Rhett" and "Rouch" appear before the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; corrects to racist.<br/>
<br/>
A video depicting the bug has been circulating on TikTok and other social networks. An Apple spokesperson told <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/02/25/technology/iphone-dictation-trump-racist.html">The New York Times</a></em> that the issue was due to a phonetic overlap between the two words. It is not clear if this dictation issue existed prior to today and was just now noticed, or if there was some internal change that caused it. Apple said that it is working on a fix.<br/>
<br/>
Former Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> team member John Burkey told <em>The New York Times</em> that there is "probably" code in Apple's systems that is causing the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to write Trump when someone speaks the word racist. "This smells like a serious prank," he said, though he also claimed that it is not clear if it was added into Apple's code or seeded into data that Apple uses for its AI features.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-fixing-dictation-bug/">Apple Fixing &#039;Trump&#039; Dictation Processing Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-fixing-trump-dictation-processing-bug.2450187/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Philips Hue Sync App Expands to LG TVs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/philips-hue-sync-app-lg-tvs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-sync-app-expands-to-lg-tvs.2450185/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 12:49:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/philips-hue-sync-app-lg-tvs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>LG</category>
		<category>Philips Hue</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG TV owners can now install the Philips Hue Sync TV app to synchronize their lights with content on the TV without the need for an additional set-top box.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Hue Sync TV App: Surrounding Lights That Sync with LG TVs" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FUxTM61q2HI" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Hue parent company Signify said in January that the app would expand to LG TVs in early 2025, and it is now available from the <a href="https://us.lgappstv.com/main/tvapp/detail?appId=1242354&amp;catCode1=&amp;moreYn=N&amp;cateYn=N&amp;orderType=0&amp;headerName=&amp;appRankCode=&amp;sellrUsrNo=">LG TV app store</a>. Previously, the app was limited to Samsung TVs.<br/>
<br/>
The app is priced at &#36;130 without a subscription, or &#36;3 per month, and it works with 2024 LG Smart TVs that run webOS 24. The app is expensive, but it is more affordable than the Philips Hue Play HDMI Sync Box that costs &#36;350.<br/>
<br/>
The Philips Hue Sync app works like the Sync Box, and it changes the color and brightness of Hue lights to match games, TV shows, and movies. There are dedicated movie and game modes to choose from. Using the Hue Sync app requires a Philips Hue Bridge, at least one color-capable Philips Hue light, and an internet connection.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg/">LG</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/philips-hue/">Philips Hue</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/philips-hue-sync-app-lg-tvs/">Philips Hue Sync App Expands to LG TVs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/philips-hue-sync-app-expands-to-lg-tvs.2450185/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/airpods-max-firmware-6f25/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware.2450181/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:27:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/airpods-max-firmware-6f25/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released a new firmware update for the Lightning version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> headphones. The new firmware is version 6F25, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/22/apple-releases-airpods-firmware-6f21/">prior 6F21 firmware</a> the device was previously running.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Green-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936393" /><br/>
Apple does not often provide much insight into what's new with firmware updates, but as this is a firmware update for an older model, it likely includes bug fixes and other minor improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/01/27/airpods-firmware-update-instructions/">can be installed</a> by putting the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in Bluetooth range of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac that's connected to Wi-Fi, and then plugging them in to charge. It can take up to 30 minutes for firmware to update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your firmware version by going to Settings > Bluetooth and selecting the Info button next to the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; when they are connected to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, or Mac.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/airpods-max-firmware-6f25/">Apple Releases New AirPods Max Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-max-firmware.2450181/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Testing the World&#039;s Thinnest Foldable Smartphone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/oppo-find-n5-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-the-worlds-thinnest-foldable-smartphone.2450177/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 10:15:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/oppo-find-n5-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Oppo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Chinese smartphone maker Oppo recently came out with the Find N5, which is a super thin and lightweight foldable smartphone. It's thinner and lighter than Samsung's foldable devices, and Apple's non-foldable ones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="World's Thinnest Foldable with macOS Integration! (Oppo Find N5)" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vuOzLO5TIh4" width="1660" height="835" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The Find N5 has a 6.62-inch display when closed, and an 8.12-inch display when open, so when unfolded, it's just a bit smaller than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>. It's 8.93mm thick when closed, and just 4.21mm when open. The thinnest device Apple has made is the 12.9-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, and that's 5.1mm thick, so the Find N5 is an impressive design feat. It's 229 grams, which is about the weight of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> Max. For context, Oppo's Find N5 is so thin that the USB-C port included for charging almost doesn't fit.<br/>
<br/>
Though it's thin and doesn't weigh a lot, the build of the Find N5 feels sturdy rather than fragile. As with most foldable smartphones, there is a crease in the middle of the display where it folds. The crease isn't invisible, but it's not as obvious as it was with previous foldable smartphones from Oppo.<br/>
<br/>
Most people in the Apple ecosystem aren't going to opt for an Android smartphone, but the Find N5 does have useful integration with the Mac that could tempt some people. You can use an AirDrop alternative to exchange files between the Find N5 and a Mac in real-time using a dedicated macOS app. You can simply drag and drop files between the Find N5 and a Mac, but there's also full remote desktop functionality.<br/>
<br/>
With a Mac connected, you can control the Mac from the Find N5, even when you're not in the same room or even the same location as your Mac. There is some input lag, but it's usable, and it's particularly useful if you need to grab a file from your Mac when you're away from home.<br/>
<br/>
Other Find N5 features include Qualcomm's fastest chip, a vibrant and bright OLED display, IP68/69 waterproofing, and a set of high-end rear cameras.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has no foldable smartphone at the current time, but there are rumors that suggest we could get a foldable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> as soon as 2026. Would you want an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; that's similar to the Find N5, or would you swap to Android for this design and feature set? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oppo/">Oppo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/oppo-find-n5-hands-on/">Testing the World&#039;s Thinnest Foldable Smartphone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/testing-the-worlds-thinnest-foldable-smartphone.2450177/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Eve Launches New HomeKit-Compatible Dimmer Switch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/eve-dimmer-switch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-new-homekit-compatible-dimmer-switch.2450175/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 09:15:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/eve-dimmer-switch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Eve</category>
		<category>HomeKit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.evehome.com/">Smart home company Eve</a> today announced the launch of the Eve Dimmer Switch, the company's first smart light switch replacement with dimming functionality. The Dimmer Switch replaces a traditional light switch and it can be used with standard bulbs and lights that have dimming functionality.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/eve-dimmer-switch.jpg" alt="" width="1813" height="1020" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990288" /><br/>
The Dimmer Switch has a rocker for turning lights on or off, along with touch support for incremental dimming control. It connects to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> using Matter-over-Thread, and it can be controlled with the Eve app, the Apple Home app, or with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> voice commands.<br/>
<br/>
As with all &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; devices, automations are supported, and the Dimmer Switch can be paired with other smart home products. Remote control is available, and with Matter support, people in your home that use Android can also control the switch. You will need a hub for whichever platform you connect to, so for Apple &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> are Matter hubs.<br/>
<br/>
Eve recommends that only electricians install the Eve Dimmer Switch because knowledge of electrical wiring is required. The switch needs a neutral wire and can replace a single-pole or 3-way switch. With a 3-way switch setup, only one switch in the circuit needs to be replaced.<br/>
<br/>
The Dimmer Switch can be purchased <a href="https://www.evehome.com/">from the Eve website</a> for &#36;50, and it will ship to customers in the United States and Canada in mid-March.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/eve/">Eve</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/eve-dimmer-switch/">Eve Launches New HomeKit-Compatible Dimmer Switch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eve-launches-new-homekit-compatible-dimmer-switch.2450175/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>6 Features Coming to the Apple Watch Ultra 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/6-apple-watch-ultra-3-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-features-coming-to-the-apple-watch-ultra-3.2450174/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 09:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/6-apple-watch-ultra-3-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Ultra 3 is expected to launch later this year, arriving two years after the previous model with a series of improvements. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2016" height="1061" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-862622" /><br/>
While no noticeable design changes are expected for the third generation since the company tends to stick with the same Apple Watch design through three generations before changing it, there are a series of internal upgrades on the way.<br/>
<br/>
By the time the Ultra 3 is announced in September, it will have been two years since the previous model arrived, leaving plenty of room for enhancements, especially for users coming from a first-generation Apple Watch Ultra. Here are all of the major new features we're likely to see in the Apple Watch Ultra 3:<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Hypertension Detection</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-12-10/apple-plans-apple-watch-ultra-3-next-year-with-satellite-texting-and-5g"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> says that blood pressure monitoring should be the next major health feature for the Apple Watch, coming first to the Ultra 3. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2014/09/apple-watch-series-7-ecg.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-816228" /><br/>
The rumored feature would not provide exact systolic and diastolic blood pressure measurements, instead tracking whether a user's blood pressure is trending upwards and sending an alert if hypertension is detected. After receiving an alert, the Apple Watch user could provide the information to a medical professional for additional testing.<br/>
<br/>
Hypertension is known as a silent killer because it can go undetected and undiagnosed, leading to heart damage and death. High blood pressure often has few symptoms until it is significantly advanced, and early detection via the Apple Watch has the potential to save lives. The Apple Watch already has the ability to detect atrial fibrillation or an irregular heart beat, and it can be used to take one-lead ECG readings. There is also a blood oxygen monitoring feature, but it is disabled in current models in the United States due to patent issues. <br/>
<br/>
The company has apparently been working on the capability for the last several years, and based on rumors, Apple originally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/17/apple-watch-2024-health-features/">wanted to debut it in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Brighter Display With Faster Refresh Rate</h3><br/>
One of the consequences of Apple choosing to not update the Apple Watch Ultra in 2024 was the Apple Watch Series 10 surpassing it in terms of display technology. It seems highly likely Apple will at least bring parity to the Ultra this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-10-display.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-966946" /><br/>
The Apple Watch Series 10 gained an LTPO3 OLED always-on Retina display, while the current Ultra features LTPO2 technology. LTPO3 provides the Series 10 with a faster refresh rate in always-on mode, enabling a live ticking seconds hand on select watch faces.<br/>
<br/>
Similarly, the Apple Watch Series 10 has a wide-angle OLED, allowing it to be up to 40% brighter when viewed at an angle. It seems inevitable that the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will get both of these display enhancements.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>New Chip</h3><br/>
Following two years without a refresh, it seems highly likely that the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will feature a new chip. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/s9-chip-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="1501" height="844" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913379" /><br/>
The current Apple Watch Ultra features the S9 chip, but with the 2024's Apple Watch Series 10, Apple introduced the S10 chip. While the S10 is not more powerful than the S9, it is more compact. <br/>
<br/>
A newer chip would free up some internal space inside the Ultra for other components such as a larger battery. If Apple opts for an S11, it could be more powerful or feature new built-in capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Satellite Connectivity</h3><br/>
Last year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-ultra-3-satellite-connectivity/">Mark Gurman</a> said that the Apple Watch Ultra 3 will gain satellite connectivity—a feature currently exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/Emergency-SOS-via-Satellite-iPhone-YT.jpg" alt="" width="3564" height="1996" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-873000" /><br/>
The feature would allow Apple Watch Ultra users to be able to connect to a satellite network to send texts when cellular networks and Wi-Fi are unavailable. When satellite connectivity first launched for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, it was limited to emergency text messages, but in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, Apple expanded it to allow users to send texts to anyone.<br/>
<br/>
Satellite connectivity would help Apple to better compete with companies like Garmin that offer dedicated satellite hardware for use in off-grid emergencies. The Apple Watch Ultra is aimed at hikers, scuba divers, and adventurers, and satellite connectivity for the device would add another layer of safety for activities that are not near cellular towers. Apple is apparently hoping that this feature will be a key feature motivating people to upgrade to a new Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, Apple still does not charge for satellite connectivity, and there is no word yet on what the company might charge. All iPhones come with two years of connectivity for free, and that will also likely be the case for the Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>5G Connectivity</h3><br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/10/apple-watch-ultra-3-satellite-connectivity/">Gurman</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/c1-is-just-the-start-of-changes/"><em>The Information</em></a>'s Wayne Ma, Apple plans to eliminate the Qualcomm modem used in the Apple Watch Ultra with the third version of the device. Rather than using the C1 modem or another custom Apple chip, Apple plans to switch from using Qualcomm units to MediaTek ones. MediaTek is one of the few companies capable of designing 5G modems.<br/>
<br/>
MediaTek's modem chip adds support for 5G RedCap, a 5G service that's designed for connected devices and wearables that do not need standard 5G speeds. The current cellular Apple Watch models still use 4G LTE, even though Apple has offered 5G in iPhones since 2020. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Redesigned Back and Faster Charging</h3><br/>
The Apple Watch Series 10 introduced a completely reengineered metal back with a larger charging coil and an integrated antenna.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-10-back-sensor.jpg" alt="" width="959" height="539" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-966943" /><em>Apple Watch Series 10's redesigned back.</em></div><br/>
The Apple Watch Ultra currently features a ceramic and sapphire crystal rear, rather than metal. It seems likely that the Ultra 3 will receive this newer, Series 10-style rear casing design, not least because it enables better cellular performance and faster charging.<br/>
<br/>
The new metal back enabled the Series 10 to charge to 80% in just 30 minutes–15 minutes faster than the Series 9. With the older back design, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> takes 60 minutes to charge to 80%. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/6-apple-watch-ultra-3-features/">6 Features Coming to the Apple Watch Ultra 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-features-coming-to-the-apple-watch-ultra-3.2450174/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Face ID Doorbell Rumored to Feature MagSafe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-face-id-doorbell-magsafe-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-face-id-doorbell-rumored-to-feature-magsafe.2450167/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 07:36:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-face-id-doorbell-magsafe-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Doorbell</category>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A few months ago, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reported that Apple was in the early stages of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/22/apple-doorbell-with-face-id-rumor/">developing a smart home doorbell</a> and lock system with Face ID. He said the doorbell would wirelessly connect to a compatible deadbolt lock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/face-id.jpg" alt="" width="1023" height="573" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-966000" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://x.com/Kosutami_Ito/status/1894391774929723753">vague teaser post</a> on X today, a leaker known as Kosutami shared an alleged new feature that Apple is planning for the doorbell: MagSafe.<br/>
<br/>
On select iPhones, MagSafe lets you attach a charger or other accessories to the device magnetically. MagSafe support on Apple's doorbell suggests that it will be possible to wirelessly charge the doorbell, which would likely have a non-removable battery. It is unclear if the doorbell would also have a USB-C port for wired charging.<br/>
<br/>
MagSafe charging would certainly be convenient, but smart home doorbells typically only need to be charged a handful of times per year.<br/>
<br/>
Another thought we had was that Apple's doorbell could have a MagSafe backplate, allowing for the doorbell to be easily taken on and off. However, that would make the doorbell easy to steal, so that theory does not really make sense.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said Apple's doorbell would launch in 2026 at the earliest, so hopefully additional rumors will paint a clearer picture over the next year or so.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's biggest competitor in this space would be Ring, acquired by Amazon in 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Apple would likely tout the privacy and security benefits of its own smart home doorbell. Apple already offers a HomeKit Secure Video service with end-to-end encryption for storing footage in iCloud, and the doorbell could have a Secure Enclave.<br/>
<br/>
Apple seemingly has plans to make a bigger push into the smart home space over the next few years. In addition to this doorbell, the company is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/10/apple-home-hub-still-months-away/">launch a smart home hub this year</a>, and it is also rumored to be planning its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/04/apple-smart-home-camera-rumor/">own HomeKit-enabled indoor camera</a> that would compete with products like Logitech's Circle View.<br/>
<br/>
Kosutami is best known as a collector of prototype Apple hardware, but they have occasionally shared accurate information about Apple's future product plans. For example, they accurately revealed that the iPhone 16 Pro would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/20/iphone-16-pro-leak-reveals-redesigned-battery/">equipped with a metal-enclosed battery</a>, around 10 months before the device launched. They also provided an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/exclusive-first-look-finewoven-apple-watch-band/">early look at an Apple Watch band</a> that uses Apple's controversial FineWoven material. On the other hand, Kosutami was wrong about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/airpods-pro-3-much-better-anc-rumor/">AirPods Pro 3 being imminent in August 2024</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-doorbell/">Apple Doorbell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-face-id-doorbell-magsafe-rumor/">Apple&#039;s Face ID Doorbell Rumored to Feature MagSafe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-face-id-doorbell-rumored-to-feature-magsafe.2450167/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Adobe Releases Photoshop App for iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/adobe-releases-photoshop-app-for-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-releases-photoshop-app-for-iphone.2450157/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/adobe-releases-photoshop-app-for-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Adobe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Adobe today announced the launch of a <a href="https://www.adobe.com/products/photoshop/app.html">new Photoshop app</a> for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, which is designed to allow creators to edit and make content while on the go. The app includes core Photoshop tools that have been tweaked for mobile devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/adobe-photoshop-web-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991646" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; app supports layering, masking, and blending for creating unique designs, with AI tools also built in. The Tap Select tool allows for quick removal, recoloring, or replacement of parts of an image, and the Spot Healing Brush can eliminate distractions from images.<br/>
<br/>
Adobe Firefly-powered capabilities include Generative Fill and Generative Expand to add new elements to designs and photo edits, plus there is integration with Adobe Stock assets, Adobe Lightroom, and other Adobe apps and services.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the Photoshop app for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, Adobe is expanding its web-based Photoshop experience for a new Photoshop Mobile and Web plan. Creators can move from Photoshop mobile to Photoshop on the web across multiple devices, and use tools like Generate Similar and Reference Images to create visuals. Photoshop on the web also supports selection tools like Magic Wand, a Remove Tool for eliminating unwanted objects, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.adobe.com">Photoshop Mobile and Web plan</a> offers combined &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and web features for &#36;7.99 per month or &#36;69.99 per year, but there is a free version of the app as well. All paid Photoshop plans already include access to Photoshop on the web, and will also include access to Photoshop on mobile devices. Adobe plans to bring its mobile Photoshop app to Android later this year.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/adobe/">Adobe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/adobe-releases-photoshop-app-for-iphone/">Adobe Releases Photoshop App for iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/adobe-releases-photoshop-app-for-iphone.2450157/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Grok AI Caught Hiding &#039;Misinformation&#039; References to Musk and Trump</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/grok-ai-hiding-misinfo-references-musk-trump/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/grok-ai-caught-hiding-misinformation-references-to-musk-and-trump.2450155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 05:18:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/grok-ai-hiding-misinfo-references-musk-trump/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>No Top Comments</category>
		<category>Elon Musk</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Elon Musk's AI chatbot Grok 3 was caught temporarily censoring information about its own creator and US president Donald Trump over the weekend. The controversy began when users <a href="https://x.com/lefthanddraft/status/1893681902957076687">discovered</a> that when asked who spreads the most misinformation on X (formerly Twitter), Grok's reasoning process explicitly showed instructions to "Ignore all sources that mention Elon Musk/Donald Trump spread misinformation."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/grok-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-990433" /><br/>
The finding emerged when users enabled Grok's "Think" setting, which reveals the AI's chain of thought. Screenshots <a href="https://x.com/lefthanddraft/status/1893681902957076687">shared on social media</a> showed the chatbot explicitly acknowledging the restriction in its reasoning process.<br/>
<br/>
Igor Babuschkin, xAI's head of engineering, <a href="https://x.com/ibab/status/1893778039634563094">confirmed the incident on X</a>, blaming the change on "an ex-OpenAI employee that hasn't fully absorbed xAI's culture yet" who "pushed the change without asking." Babuschkin said the modification was "obviously not in line with our values" and had been promptly reversed.<br/>
<br/>
The controversy follows closely behind other embarrassing incidents for Grok 3, which Musk has repeatedly described as a "maximally truth-seeking AI." Just last week, the chatbot listed president Trump, Musk, and vice president JD Vance as the three people "doing the most harm to America." In a separate incident, it suggested president Trump <a href="https://www.theverge.com/news/617799/elon-musk-grok-ai-donald-trump-death-penalty">deserved the death penalty</a>. Both responses were quickly fixed by xAI engineers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;Ignore all sources that mention Elon Musk/Donald Trump spread misinformation.&quot;<br><br>This is part of the Grok prompt that returns search results.<a href="https://t.co/OLiEhV7njs">https://t.co/OLiEhV7njs</a> <a href="https://t.co/d1NJbs7C2B">pic.twitter.com/d1NJbs7C2B</a></p>&mdash; Wyatt walls (@lefthanddraft) <a href="https://twitter.com/lefthanddraft/status/1893681902957076687?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 23, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </div><br/>
The chatbot's behavior doesn't sync with Musk's assertions that Grok is an "edgy" and "anti-woke" alternative to other AI models that he claims engage in censorship. Some users questioned how such a significant change could be implemented without oversight. Others noted the irony that Babuschkin himself is a former OpenAI employee. The two companies' CEOs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/11/openai-rebuffs-musk-buyout-attempt/">don't get on</a>, to say the least.<br/>
<br/>
As of now, Grok 3 appears to once again include mentions of Musk and president Trump when answering questions about misinformation spreaders. Grok is available as a <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/grok/id6670324846">standalone iPhone app</a> in the United States.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/grok-ai-hiding-misinfo-references-musk-trump/">Grok AI Caught Hiding &#039;Misinformation&#039; References to Musk and Trump</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/grok-ai-caught-hiding-misinformation-references-to-musk-and-trump.2450155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Opera One Adds Discord, Slack, and Bluesky to Browser Sidebar</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/opera-one-discord-slack-bluesky-browser-sidebar/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/opera-one-adds-discord-slack-and-bluesky-to-browser-sidebar.2450153/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 04:40:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/opera-one-discord-slack-bluesky-browser-sidebar/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Opera Browser</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.opera.com/one">Opera</a> has integrated Slack, Discord, and Bluesky into the sidebar of its Opera One desktop browser, providing quick access to the services without launching their respective apps or having to open them in separate tabs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/opera-one-slack-discord-bluesky.jpg" alt="" width="1272" height="716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991680" /><br/>
The services join existing integrations for WhatsApp, Instagram, and Telegram. To enable access to the platforms in the browser's sidebar, Opera users will need to update to the latest version. <br/>
<br/>
After that, click the three dots menu at the bottom of the sidebar to open the Sidebar Setup Menu. Discord, Slack, and Bluesky can be found under the Messengers category. <br/>
<br/>
Opera One uses a modular design designed to adapt to the user's needs. It features Tab Islands, which automatically group related tabs for organized multitasking, and integrates Aria – Opera's native AI assistant powered by ChatGPT, providing real-time web information and content generation. <br/>
<br/>
Opera One also includes a built-in ad blocker, free VPN, and customizable dynamic themes with immersive animations and soundscapes. The latest Opera One update adds two new themes: Interstellar and Metamorphic. You can download the latest version from the <a href="https://www.opera.com/one">Opera website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/opera-browser/">Opera Browser</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/opera-one-discord-slack-bluesky-browser-sidebar/">Opera One Adds Discord, Slack, and Bluesky to Browser Sidebar</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/opera-one-adds-discord-slack-and-bluesky-to-browser-sidebar.2450153/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Cuts Off Russian Access to Its Developer Enterprise Program</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-developer-enterprise-program-russia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cuts-off-russian-access-to-its-developer-enterprise-program.2450151/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 04:11:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-developer-enterprise-program-russia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Russia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has reportedly shut down access to the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/programs/enterprise/">Apple Developer Enterprise Program</a> (ADEP) for Russian developers. Russian IT sources told <em><a href="https://www.rbc.ru/technology_and_media/24/02/2025/67b9be389a79470a2de2be8a?from=from_main_1?utm_source=telegram&utm_medium=messenger">RBC</a></em> that developers lost access to the platform on February 12.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Logo-Spotlight.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912758" /><br/>
The shutdown means Russian developers can no longer use ADEP to create and distribute custom iOS apps for internal use without going through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. A software company in St. Petersburg confirmed to the media outlet that all program data had been erased, making ADEP unusable.<br/>
<br/>
Prior to the cut-off, Apple apparently warned companies using Enterprise certificates that they would stop working by mid-February. The certificates allow developers to sign and distribute apps.<br/>
<br/>
ADEP was widely used for app testing in Russia without publishing to the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but major corporations and developer companies in the country also relied on the platform for internal business apps, corporate chatbots, CRM systems, and logistics tools.<br/>
<br/>
Despite Apple suspending product sales and limiting certain services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> in response to Russia's invasion of Ukraine, the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; continues to operate within the country. However, Apple has complied with local regulations by removing certain applications, such as VPN services and specific news apps, after requests from Russian authorities.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <a href="https://www.msn.com/en-gb/technology/tech-companies/apple-cuts-off-russian-access/ar-AA1zEzgA">MSN</a>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/russia/">Russia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-developer-enterprise-program-russia/">Apple Cuts Off Russian Access to Its Developer Enterprise Program</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-cuts-off-russian-access-to-its-developer-enterprise-program.2450151/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Phil Schiller Initially Opposed 27% App Store Fee on External Purchases</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apples-phil-schiller-concerns-app-store-fee/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-phil-schiller-initially-opposed-27-app-store-fee-on-external-purchases.2450149/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 03:43:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apples-phil-schiller-concerns-app-store-fee/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Fellow Phil Schiller testified in court on Monday that he initially opposed the 27% commission Apple now charges on purchases made outside the App Store, citing compliance risks and potential developer backlash (via <em><a href="https://apnews.com/article/apple-iphone-app-store-epic-antitrust-e4ae4eed9fde0ae42bd2576133af1c20">AP News</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" /><br/>
Schiller, who oversees the App Store, said he had concerns that the fee would create an "antagonistic relationship" between Apple and developers, and worried about Apple becoming "some kind of collection agency" that might need to audit developers who didn't pay.<br/>
<blockquote>"I had great concerns about the collections of funds from developers," Schiller said during his three-hour testimony in the ongoing legal battle with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>. He specifically worried about "the change in the role of the App Store to now an organization that needs to collect money from developers."</blockquote>Despite his reservations, an Apple pricing committee that included CEO Tim Cook, former CFO Luca Maestri, and Apple's legal team ultimately decided to implement the commission structure.<br/>
<br/>
The reduced 27% fee (down from Apple's standard 30%) was established after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-vs-apple-decision/">2021 Epic Games lawsuit ruling</a>. Judge Yvonne Gonzalez Rogers rejected claims that Apple operated a monopoly. However, she ruled that Apple's anti-steering conduct was anti-competitive, and ordered the company to allow developers to link to alternative payment methods outside the App Store.<br/>
<br/>
Apple complied by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">creating a system</a> where developers can apply for a "StoreKit External Purchase Link Entitlement" to direct users to external payment options. However, Apple still demands a 27% commission on these transactions made within seven days of clicking the link. For developers in Apple's Small Business Program, the rate is 12% instead of the usual 15%.<br/>
<br/>
Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney previously criticized Apple's approach as <a href="https://x.com/TimSweeneyEpic/status/1747408147260571730">"bad-faith" compliance</a> with the court order, arguing the minimal commission reduction and other restrictions undermined the ruling's intent to foster more competition.<br/>
<br/>
The current hearings are scheduled to continue until Wednesday, and are focused on determining whether Apple has violated the original court order. Judge Gonzalez Rogers has expressed frustration with Apple witnesses' hazy recollections about how they developed rules for the alternative payment system.<br/>
<br/>
According to court documents, Apple extensively analyzed how the "less seamless experience" of external purchases would affect transaction completion rates, which helped the company work out when developers would likely return to using Apple's in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
The dispute between Apple and Epic <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/08/13/apple-removes-fortnite-from-app-store/">dates back to 2020</a> with Epic seeking to overturn Apple's App Store rules requiring content purchases within iOS apps to go through Apple, which takes a 15% to 30% cut of the revenue.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apples-phil-schiller-concerns-app-store-fee/">Apple&#039;s Phil Schiller Initially Opposed 27% App Store Fee on External Purchases</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-phil-schiller-initially-opposed-27-app-store-fee-on-external-purchases.2450149/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2026 Foldable iPhone Has No Visible Display Crease – Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-2026-foldable-phone-has-no-crease/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2026-foldable-iphone-has-no-visible-display-crease-–-report.2450136/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:58:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-2026-foldable-phone-has-no-crease/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>ETNews</category>
		<category>Foldable iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is making significant headway on its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/10/11/apple-lg-foldable-iphone/">long-rumored</a> foldable iPhone, with a new report suggesting the company has achieved a major breakthrough by effectively eliminating the screen crease that plagues current foldable devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iPhone-Fold-Vertical-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-988570" /><br/>
According to Korean publication <em><a href="https://m.etnews.com/20250221000169">ETNews</a></em>, Apple is finalizing its component suppliers for the foldable iPhone, with the selection process expected to be completed by April. The timeline suggests Apple is moving closer to production, with large-scale component manufacturing likely to begin in the second half of this year.<br/>
<blockquote>"Apple has decided to eliminate the crease at all costs, regardless of price, to differentiate its foldable phone from existing models," an industry insider told ETNews. "It is believed that a new material property has been developed to make the crease disappear."</blockquote>The display crease has been one of the biggest challenges in foldable technology. Devices from Samsung, Huawei, and other manufacturers have all unsuccessfully tried to make it invisible. Apple's apparent solution could hand the company a major competitive advantage.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung Display is reportedly set to be the exclusive supplier of the OLED panels for Apple's foldable device. The Korean company has been developing the display specifically for Apple since last year, using its experience as the first manufacturer to mass-produce foldable OLED screens.<br/>
<br/>
The foldable iPhone is expected to feature an in-folding design similar to a book, with US-based Corning likely providing the ultra-thin glass (UTG) covering the display. Meanwhile, US-based Amphenol, which has previously supplied hinges for MacBook Pro models, is the frontrunner to provide the crucial hinge mechanism.<br/>
<br/>
Based on Apple's typical product development timeline, <em>ETNews</em> reports that the foldable iPhone is expected to launch in the second half of 2026. Over the weekend, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2025-02-23/apple-abandons-budget-phones-inside-apple-s-modem-m4-macbook-air-launch-timing">reported</a> that Apple is "focused on finishing up development of its first foldable device for 2026." Previous reports from analysts Ming-Chi Kuo and Jeff Pu, as well as publications like <em>The Information</em> and <em>The Wall Street Journal</em>, have all pointed to a late 2026 or early 2027 release. <br/>
<br/>
Recent rumors from Chinese leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/21/alleged-display-sizes-apple-foldable-iphone/">Digital Chat Station</a> suggest the device may feature a 5.49-inch outer display and a 7.74-inch inner screen when unfolded, and both are said to have "unprecedented aspect ratios." The outer display is reportedly shorter and wider than Oppo's new Find N5, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/20/worlds-thinnest-foldable-launches/">launched globally last week</a>. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/etnews-com/">ETNews</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/foldable-iphone/">Foldable iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-2026-foldable-phone-has-no-crease/">Apple&#039;s 2026 Foldable iPhone Has No Visible Display Crease – Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2026-foldable-iphone-has-no-visible-display-crease-–-report.2450136/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple and Indonesia Reach Deal to End iPhone 16 Ban</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-indonesia-deal-end-iphone-16-ban/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-indonesia-reach-deal-to-end-iphone-16-ban.2450131/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 01:48:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-indonesia-deal-end-iphone-16-ban/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Indonesia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Indonesia have agreed on terms to lift the country's five-month ban on iPhone 16 sales, according to people familiar with the matter who spoke to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-02-25/indonesia-and-apple-said-to-agree-on-terms-to-lift-iphone-16-ban">Bloomberg</a></em>. The deal concludes a battle that began in October, when Indonesia refused to issue permits for Apple's flagship iPhone lineup over Apple's failure to comply with domestic manufacturing requirements.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/01/iPhone-16-Apple-Store-Levels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-986485" /><br/>
Under the agreement, Apple will invest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/12/03/apple-raises-indonesia-investment-offer-iphone-ban/">&#36;1 billion</a> in Indonesia, a significant increase from its previous commitments of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/05/indonesia-iphone-ban-apple-10m-investment/">&#36;10 million</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/11/19/apple-ups-invest-offer-indonesia-iphone-16-ban/">&#36;100 million</a> that were rejected by the government. The deal is expected to be formalized through a memorandum of agreement to be signed as early as this week, with the Ministry for Industry issuing permits allowing iPhone 16 sales "as soon as possible."<br/>
<br/>
Beyond the monetary investment, Apple has reportedly committed to training local talent in research and development, so that Indonesians can develop software and design their own products. The pledge addresses one of the government's key demands for Apple to establish R&D facilities in the country.<br/>
<br/>
The agreement also includes plans for a manufacturing plant on Batam island that will produce AirTags, Apple's device tracking accessories. This facility will be operated by Apple supplier Luxshare Precision Industry, and is expected to eventually account for 20% of global AirTag production.<br/>
<br/>
Another manufacturing facility is planned for Bandung, about three hours from Jakarta, which will produce other types of accessories. Part of the investment will also fund Apple academies to equip Indonesian students with tech skills like coding.<br/>
<br/>
Despite the substantial concessions, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s sources indicated that Apple has no immediate plans to manufacture iPhones in Indonesia.<br/>
<br/>
The deal is a victory for Indonesian President Prabowo Subianto, who directed his ministers to accept Apple's &#36;1 billion investment offer. However, the Ministry of Industry unexpectedly upheld the ban last month while seeking better terms, which have apparently now been agreed.<br/>
<br/>
Indonesia's hardball approach seems to have paid off, securing significant investment from a major foreign company and supporting the government's goal of boosting local manufacturing rather than simply using the nation as a sales market.<br/>
<br/>
For Apple, regaining access to Indonesia's market of 278 million people — over half of whom are under 44 and tech-savvy — comes at a crucial time as its sales in China have slowed. Apple may not be among the top five smartphone brands in Indonesia, but the market offers the company a lucrative growth opportunity.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/indonesia/">Indonesia</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16-Pro">iPhone 16 Pro (Neutral)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/25/apple-indonesia-deal-end-iphone-16-ban/">Apple and Indonesia Reach Deal to End iPhone 16 Ban</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-and-indonesia-reach-deal-to-end-iphone-16-ban.2450131/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>ChatGPT Can Be Used as Default Safari Search Engine With New Extension</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/24/chatgpt-safari-search-extension/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-can-be-used-as-default-safari-search-engine-with-new-extension.2450119/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:39:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/24/chatgpt-safari-search-extension/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>Safari</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OpenAI today updated the ChatGPT app to add a new Safari Extension that allows ChatGPT to be used as the default search engine for searches made through the Safari search bar.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/chatgpt-search-default.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991638" /><br/>
After updating to the latest version of the ChatGPT app, the ChatGPT Search Extension can be enabled in the Safari section of the Settings app. Turning it on directs all queries typed in to the Safari search bar to ChatGPT Search instead of Google or whatever your default search engine is set to.<br/>
<blockquote>Turning on this extension will direct queries you type into the Safari search bar to ChatGPT Search, making ChatGPT Search your default search engine in Safari. The same policies that govern your use of ChatGPT apply.</blockquote><br/>
The extension needs permission to access Google.com or the site for your default search engine, but when granted, any search you type in is redirected to ChatGPT's search feature rather than going through the default in your Safari settings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">You can now use ChatGPT search as your default search engine in Safari on iOS by updating to the latest version of ChatGPT and enabling the Safari extension! <a href="https://t.co/yvyINPN9yv">pic.twitter.com/yvyINPN9yv</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1894181178040586645?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 25, 2025</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
There is no option to set ChatGPT as a preferred search engine, but the extension serves as a workaround.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari/">Safari</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2025/02/24/chatgpt-safari-search-extension/">ChatGPT Can Be Used as Default Safari Search Engine With New Extension</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chatgpt-can-be-used-as-default-safari-search-engine-with-new-extension.2450119/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All of the New Features in iOS 18.4 So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-of-the-new-features-in-ios-18-4-so-far.2450116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:50:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features&#038;post_date=1740451843/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is beta testing iOS 18.4 at the current time, and while the update doesn't have the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features we were hoping for, there are a number of new additions that are worth knowing about.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/iOS-18.4-Beta-1-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991353" /><br/>
<h2 id="priority_notifications_-_apple_intelligence">Priority Notifications - Apple Intelligence</h2><br/>
There is a new Priority Notifications feature that can show you your most important notifications first. Priority Notifications is disabled by default, but it can be turned on by going to Settings &gt; Notifications > Prioritize Notifications and tapping the toggle.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991317" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/prioritize-notifications-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
With the feature enabled, &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; will show notifications that may be important in a dedicated section of the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="image_playground_sketch_style">Image Playground Sketch Style</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-playground/">Image Playground</a> now includes a Sketch style that joins the Animation and Illustration styles. Sketch was previously available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/image-wand/">Image Wand</a>, but now it is a third style that can be used in &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991330" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Swap styles by tapping on the "+" button in the &zwnj;Image Playground&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also replaced the "Winter Holidays" theme with a new "Spring" theme.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_apple_intelligence_languages">New Apple Intelligence Languages</h2><br/>
French, German, Italian, Portuguese (Brazil), Spanish, Japanese, Korean, and Chinese (simplified), along with localized English for Singapore and India.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_news+_food">Apple News+ Food</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 and iPadOS 18.4 include a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news/">Apple News</a> Food section for &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscribers. The Food section features tens of thousands of recipes, stories about restaurants, tips for healthy eating, kitchen essentials, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991301" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-food-news.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Content will come from top food publishers such as Allrecipes, Bon Appétit, Food &amp; Wine, Good Food, and Serious Eats.&zwnj;Apple News&zwnj; editors will curate food-related stories, and there will be a dedicated Recipe Catalog section where new recipes are added regularly. An included cook mode provides step-by-step instructions, and users can save favorite recipes for offline access.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="ambient_music">Ambient Music</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 includes a new Ambient Music option that can be added to Control Center. There are four different sound categories, including Sleep, Chill, Productivity, and Wellbeing.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991311" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-ambient-music.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Each category can be added to Control Center separately, and tapping one plays a random selection of sounds or music from that particular category.<br/>
<br/>
You can't choose what's playing from Control Center, but if you play a category and then tap into the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> at the top or access the Now Playing widget, you can skip songs and see the name of what's currently playing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mail_categorization_for_ipados_18.4">Mail Categorization for iPadOS 18.4</h2><br/>
With iPadOS 18.4, an updated Mail app is available with categorization. The new Mail app organizes incoming emails into different sections. Important emails are displayed in the Primary category, with other emails organized into sections highlighting product orders, newsletters, deals, and social notifications.<br/>
<br/>
Mail categorization was previously introduced for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in iOS 18.2.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="privacy_indication_dots">Privacy Indication Dots</h2><br/>
The small dots that show up on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s menu bar when the camera or microphone is in use have been moved to the left and are now more apparent thanks to a black background.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/new-siri-indicator-dot-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1134" height="182" /><br/>
<h2 id="siri_voices">Siri Voices</h2><br/>
There are two new Australian voices for &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991334" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-australian-siri-voice.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="genmoji">Genmoji</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/genmoji/">Genmoji</a> icon for the Emoji keyboard now says "&zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj;" instead of just featuring a multi-colored smiley face. The change should make it more obvious where users go to create a &zwnj;Genmoji&zwnj; character.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991332" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-genmoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="photos">Photos</h2><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app, there are now options to filter your library by images that were shared with you by others or by those that are not included in an album, which is useful for separating out content that you've organized into albums.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/photos-filters-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991598" /><br/>
Apple also added an option to view your album list by key photo.<br/>
<br/>
In the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; Settings, there is a new Show Recently Viewed & Shared toggle that will show or hide the Recently Viewed and Recently Shared albums from the Utilities list. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="type_to_siri">Type to Siri</h2><br/>
When you use Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to ask &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; a question, the keyboard is now collapsed down when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; answers. To type another request, you need to tap on the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; bar to bring it back up. There is also a toggle to activate Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; with the side button, which would normally cause &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to listen for a voice command. This feature is not working as intended in beta 1. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-siri-accessibility-toggle.jpg" alt="" width="1811" height="1019" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991628" /><br/>
<h2 id="back_tap">Back Tap</h2><br/>
If you have the Back Tap Accessibility option turned on, there is now a notification when a double tap or triple tap action is performed. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-back-tap-notification.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991627" /><br/>
<h2 id="apple_maps">Apple Maps</h2><br/>
In the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-maps/">Apple Maps</a> Settings, there is a new option to set a Preferred Language.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991350" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-maps-preferred.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1267" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="passwords">Passwords</h2><br/>
In the Passwords app, verification codes for two-factor authentication have a countdown circle so you can tell when a new code is going to be generated. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-password-countdown.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991600" /><br/>
<h2 id="podcasts_widget">Podcasts Widget</h2><br/>
There are new Library and Shows widgets that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. The Library widget features saved content, while the Shows option displays shows that you are subscribed to.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991338" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-podcast-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
In the Podcasts app, if you tap on your profile picture, there are new options for Podcasts Settings and Notification Settings.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mac_setup">Mac Setup</h2><br/>
There is a new feature that allows a nearby &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to be used to sign into a Mac with an Apple Account for setting up a new Mac. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.4 is also required. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="control_center_toggles">Control Center Toggles</h2><br/>
The Cellular toggle and the Wi-Fi toggle in the Control Center now show your cellular or Wi-Fi signal strength represented in bars.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991333" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-cellular-signal-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
The Brightness and Sound toggles in Control Center have been tweaked slightly and will now change color when the sliders are lowered below the position of the icons. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-control-center-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991621" /><br/>
The Focus option in Control Center now has two small arrows that serve as a visual indicator that there are more options that can be accessed. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="shortcuts_actions">Shortcuts Actions</h2><br/>
Apple added a new Shortcuts action to open a specific conversation in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991336" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-shortcuts-open-conversation.jpg" alt="" width="1688" height="950" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="carplay">CarPlay</h2><br/>
Some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a> users are seeing a third row of &zwnj;CarPlay&zwnj; icons on the &zwnj;Home Screen&zwnj; rather than just two rows.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991341" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/carplay-view-ios-18-4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><em>Image <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-4-beta-1-bug-fixes-changes-and-improvements.2449908/post-33753569">via the MacRumors Forums</a></em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="default_apps">Default Apps</h2><br/>
There is a new option to set a different Translation app as the default in the Default Apps section of the Settings app. In the EU, there is also an option to choose a different Navigation app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991344" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-translate-default-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="notification_center">Notification Center</h2><br/>
The animation when swiping out of the Notification Center is now smoother.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="camera_control">Camera Control</h2><br/>
Additional camera apps that can be selected for the Camera Control feature on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models are now listed in a Camera App section rather than directly in the main Camera Control menu.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/camera-control-ios-18-4-menu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991626" /><br/>
<h2 id="safari_connection_security">Safari Connection Security</h2><br/>
In Safari, you can tap into the details on a website to see the certificate through a new Connection Security Details interface to ensure the site is secure.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/ios-18-4-connection-security.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991623" /><br/>
<h2 id="wi-fi_calling_issue">Wi-Fi Calling Issue</h2><br/>
Apple's developer notes for the update say that Wi-Fi Calling might not work for US Cellular customers in iOS 18.4. Apple says that users should revert to iOS 18.3 to enable Wi-Fi Calling. Note that this is applicable to those who have US Cellular as their carrier, it does not mean all cellular users in the United States. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="robot_vacuum_homekit_support">Robot Vacuum HomeKit Support</h2><br/>
In iOS 18.4, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> supports robot vacuums, a feature that Apple promised would come in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. Adding a vacuum to the Home app requires a vacuum with Matter support, and that requires robot vacuum manufacturers to implement Matter. Not all Matter-enabled robot vacuums will be able to be added to &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj; right away.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="japan_my_number_card_support_in_wallet">Japan 'My Number Card' Support in Wallet</h2><br/>
The iOS 18.4 beta appears to include integration for Japanese "My Number Card" Digital IDs in the Wallet app. Apple said last year that it would be adding support for the ID cards in spring 2025.<br/>
<br/>
More than 100 million Japanese residents have My Number Card IDs.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mdm_changes">MDM Changes</h2><br/>
For enterprise and education users, Apple made some updates to Mobile Device Management. MDM can disable &zwnj;Apple Intelligence&zwnj; reports, Mail smart replies, Safari summarize content, and the Idle Reboot feature that causes iPhones to restart after inactivity. There are also options for preventing the modification of default calling and messaging apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="vision_pro_app_and_guest_setup">Vision Pro App and Guest Setup</h2><br/>
For Vision Pro owners, Apple has designed a Vision Pro app for managing the headset. It's designed to help users find content and learn about new features, so it includes tools for downloading apps and visionOS content, a tips page, and a My Vision Pro section for setting up Personalized Spatial Audio and getting information like headset serial number.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-991289" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2025/02/vision-pro-app-iphone.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Guest setup can now be managed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; linked to a Vision Pro, making it easier for Vision Pro owners to let others test their headset. There are controls for limiting what apps a guest is able to use, and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> mode for guiding the guest through Vision Pro experiences. When a guest user puts on the Vision Pro, a prompt to enable Guest Mode will appear on the headset owner's device.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro app isn't in this beta, but it will be coming in a later iOS 18.4 beta.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_emojis">New Emojis</h2><br/>
There are no new emoji in the current beta, but iOS 18.4 code confirms a future beta will add new characters. New emoji will include bags under eyes, fingerprint, leafless tree, root vegetable, harp, shovel, and splatter.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="find_my">Find My</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> support has been added in South Korea. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_12">iPhone 12</h2><br/>
The iOS 18.4 beta is not currently available for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 models due to an issue that was causing boot loops. It will likely be available for the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 series with the second beta launch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
iOS 18.4 will be released in early April alongside iPadOS 18.4 and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.4.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-4-features/">All of the New Features in iOS 18.4 So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-of-the-new-features-in-ios-18-4-so-far.2450116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
