<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:03:06 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 M3 MacBook Air Refresh: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m3-macbook-air-refresh-what-to-expect.2420765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 14:17:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709255855/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mega Guides</category>
		<category>2024 MacBook Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">the MacBook Pro line</a> with M3 chips late last year, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> has yet to be refreshed with the new hardware. That could change as soon as late March, with rumors suggesting an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac-centric event is in the works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/macbook-air-purple-february.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936772" /><br/>
We're expecting new versions of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, and this guide highlights everything we know about the upcoming machines.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="size_and_design">Size and Design</h2><br/>
As of last year, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is available in two sizes instead of one. Apple makes a 13.6-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and a 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, so consumers can choose between favoring portability or screen size.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is going to refresh both versions of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;. The look of the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; was last updated in June of 2022, and there are no rumors of design changes this time around. Apple will continue to use the same flat MacBook Pro-style body that was introduced in 2022, with full-size black Magic Keyboard, large Force Touch trackpad, dual USB-C ports, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, Thunderbolt charging, slim bezeled display, and aluminum chassis.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/MacBook-Air-15-Inch-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898576" /><br/>
The only difference between the two models in terms of design will be the display size.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is available in silver, space gray, starlight, and midnight, which is a new dark blue color. We could see the three standard colors and another special color, or a whole new color lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="updated_m3_chip">Updated M3 Chip</h2><br/>
With no design changes planned, chip updates will be the main focus of the refresh. The current &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models use the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, with Apple planning to upgrade the machines with the M3 chip that was first introduced in the MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-Chip-Apple-Event-Slide.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920110" /><br/>
The M3 chip is built on Apple's next-generation 3-nanometer process, which basically means that it offers better performance and power efficiency than the 5-nanometer &zwnj;M2&zwnj;. For context, there are 25 billion transistors in the M3 chip, up from 20 billion in the &zwnj;M2&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
CPU benchmarks indicate that the M3 is approximately 17 percent faster than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; when it comes to single-core tasks, and 21 percent faster at multi-core tasks. GPU performance is up approximately 15 percent, but there are other GPU improvements that give the M3 chip a notable boost.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip has a new GPU architecture that uses Dynamic Caching, which basically means that tasks use the exact amount of memory that they need and adapt in real-time for maximum utilization. The result is improved performance for GPU-intensive apps and games.<br/>
<br/>
For games and 3D software, the M3 chip supports hardware-accelerated ray tracing and mesh shading. Hardware-based ray tracing is faster than software-based ray tracing, so any game or app that uses ray tracing will perform better. Complex lighting effects won't take up as many system resources, speeding up rendering times.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that almost all Mac games do not support ray tracing, so for gaming, this is a feature that will be useful in the future rather than immediately. For 3D tasks in apps like Blender, there will be speed improvements.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new media engine in the M3 chip that supports AV1 decode. AV1 is a video codec that streaming platforms are using for higher-quality video content at a low bitrate. AV1 is becoming increasingly popular for 4K and 8K videos, and AV1 decoding is another good future proofing feature to have even for those that don't need it immediately.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_upgrades">Other Upgrades</h2><br/>
The next &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models are likely to get Wi-Fi 6E support, allowing them to connect to the 6GHz Wi-Fi band offered by compatible 6GHz routers. There's a good chance battery life will be improved thanks to the upgrade to M3 chip technology.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="worth_updating">Worth Updating?</h2><br/>
If you have an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, it's not going to be worth updating to the M3 version because the improvements aren't notable enough. You won't see design changes, and while the M3 is better, it's not <em>that</em> much better.<br/>
<br/>
Most people who have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip may not want to update either, but there's more to gain with the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; to M3 upgrade both in terms of performance and in design. The &zwnj;M1&zwnj; machines used the prior &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; design, so updating to M3 gets you the sleek new look.<br/>
<br/>
For those coming from an older Intel-based &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; or another Intel-based machine, the M3 will be a radical improvement.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="launch_date">Launch Date</h2><br/>
We're expecting to see new M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models introduced sometime in March or April, and signs right now point toward a launch at the end of March. We don't yet have details on a potential Apple event, but we should be hearing more in the next few weeks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air/">Apple&#039;s 2024 M3 MacBook Air Refresh: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-m3-macbook-air-refresh-what-to-expect.2420765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Beta Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-beta-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2420754/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 11:41:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today introduced a new beta firmware update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2, both the USB-C and Lightning versions. The new firmware is version 6E188, up from the prior 6B34 firmware <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/">released in December</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not often provide details or notes on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware, so it is unclear what's new. Note that this software is <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/install-beta/#airpods-beta">limited to developers</a> at the current time. <br/>
<br/>
There are no clear cut instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware update, we'll update this article.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/airpods-pro-2-beta-firmware-6e188/">Apple Releases New Beta Firmware for AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-beta-firmware-for-airpods-pro-2.2420754/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Seemingly &#039;Canceled&#039; For Now</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-seemingly-canceled-for-now.2420753/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 11:26:11 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple supplier ams OSRAM on Wednesday <a href="https://ams-osram.com/news/press-releases/revised-microled-strategy">announced</a> it would "re-assess its microLED strategy" after a "cornerstone project" was "unexpectedly cancelled" that day. The company's stock plunged nearly 40% following the news, earlier <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/02/29/rumored-apple-watch-ultra-with-micro-led-might-be-dead">shared by <em>AppleInsider</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Counterpoint Research's <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/">Display Supply Chain Consultants</a> told <em>MacRumors</em> that it believes this project related to the rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display</a>. The research firm said low production yields, along with high costs and risk, are likely the primary reasons for the project being canceled with ams OSRAM. The firm said it remains to be seen if Apple looks for another supplier, or sticks with OLED displays for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
ams OSRAM said "discussions with the related customer are ongoing," so an Apple Watch Ultra with a microLED display is not completely ruled out, and it may just be further delayed. The device was expected to launch in 2025 or 2026, depending on the source, but it may take even longer to be released, if ever, given this latest development.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is believed to have been actively developing microLED technology since it acquired California-based company LuxVue in 2014. Benefits of microLED displays compared to OLED displays typically include increased brightness, improved power efficiency, higher contrast ratio, and more, but the technology is still expensive.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/microled-apple-watch-ultra-canceled-for-now/">Apple Watch Ultra With MicroLED Display Seemingly &#039;Canceled&#039; For Now</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-with-microled-display-seemingly-canceled-for-now.2420753/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Setapp Will Be One of iPhone&#039;s First Alternative App Marketplaces in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/setapp-will-be-one-of-iphones-first-alternative-app-marketplaces-in-eu.2420747/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 09:33:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Setapp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacPaw today <a href="https://macpaw.com/news/setapp-ios-beta-announcement">announced</a> that <a href="https://setapp.com">Setapp</a> will be available as an alternative app marketplace on the iPhone in the EU starting in April. Those wanting access to the beta version can <a href="https://setapp.com/join-waitlist">join a waitlist</a>, and developers interested in the platform can apply <a href="https://setapp.com/for-ios-developers">on this page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Setapp-iOS.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938882" /><br/>
Alternative app marketplaces are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">among the several changes</a> that Apple is implementing in the EU with iOS 17.4, in order to comply with the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
On the Mac, Setapp is a popular subscription-based service that provides users with access to a curated collection of dozens of popular apps for &#36;9.99 per month. This includes apps like Ulysses, iStat Menus, Spark Mail, Unite, Yoink, and more. Starting with iOS 17.4 and later, Setapp will be available directly on the iPhone in the EU.<br/>
<br/>
MacPaw said the Setapp Mobile beta will offer a "carefully selected assortment of apps":<blockquote>• <strong>Productivity and Business Tools:</strong> Boost your efficiency with tools for managing your schedule, staying on track, personalizing your internet experience, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Creative and Design Software:</strong> Unlock your creative potential with intuitive tools designed for photo animation, document creation, and more.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Lifestyle and Productivity:</strong> Improve your daily routines with apps that help you build better habits, stay updated with the latest news, and efficiently manage your notes and ideas.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Utility Apps:</strong> Make everyday tasks easier with applications that enable you to share files effortlessly, monitor your spending, and streamline your idea organization process.<br/>
<br/>
• <strong>Specialized Professional Tools:</strong> Engage with advanced applications tailored for detailed document searches, comprehensive database management, and more.</blockquote>MacPaw is one of the first companies to announce plans to offer an alternative app marketplace on the iPhone in the EU, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">along with Epic Games</a>. Setapp subscribers on the Mac can already access a collection of iOS apps with a QR code system, and the alternative app marketplace will offer a more streamlined experience. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release iOS 17.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/ios-17-4-release-date/">on or before March 6</a>, the deadline for complying with the Digital Markets Act. For additional details about the changes coming to the App Store and more in the EU, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">read our previous coverage</a>. The changes do not apply outside of the EU, nor do they apply to iPadOS in any country.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/setapp/">Setapp</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/setapp-alternative/">Setapp Will Be One of iPhone&#039;s First Alternative App Marketplaces in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/setapp-will-be-one-of-iphones-first-alternative-app-marketplaces-in-eu.2420747/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MagSafe Duo Charger Hits All-Time Low Price of &#36;79.99, MagSafe Charger on Sale for &#36;27.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-hits-all-time-low-price-of-79-99-magsafe-charger-on-sale-for-27-99.2420730/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:21:47 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot today has a couple of <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">deals on Apple accessories</a>, including low prices on the MagSafe Charger and MagSafe Duo Charger. Additionally, Amazon has steep discounts on FineWoven and Silicone Cases for iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/magsafe-duo-perspective-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1332" height="750" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-770700" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Woot. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Both of the MagSafe Chargers in this sale are in brand new condition and come with a one year Apple manufacturer limited warranty. You'll find an estimated delivery between March 7 and March 11, although those dates may change depending on your location.<br/>
<br/>
The highlight of the sale is the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. This is a match for the best-ever price on the accessory. The MagSafe Duo Charger can simultaneously charge an iPhone via MagSafe and an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Woot also has the MagSafe Charger for <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-24%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_25"><strong>&#36;27.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;39.00. This beats Woot's previous price on the accessory by &#36;2 and is one of the lowest prices that we've tracked so far in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/magsafe-charger-new-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-846479" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-24%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_25"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;27.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there are <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_gw_dly_snb">plenty of other deals</a> in the Woot sale, including the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-appaccmu9f2ama-apple-watch-magnetic-charging%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_20">Apple Watch Magnetic Charging Dock</a> for &#36;34.99 (&#36;44 off) and the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-watch-band-milanese-loop-3%3Fref%3Dw_gw_zl_bs_3">Apple Watch Milanese Loop</a> for &#36;36.99 (&#36;62 off). You'll also find USB-C cables, previous generation Apple Watches, iPhone cases, Apple Watch bands, and more at a discount. <br/>
<br/>
Finally, over at Amazon there is also a large collection of FineWoven and Silicone Cases on sale for the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max. You can find these for as low as &#36;23.81 right now on Amazon, and no coupon codes are required to get these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;27.61, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWZ9JC9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Silicone Case</a> - &#36;27.34, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;36.64, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHXDVMXJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;23.81, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2XFLN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Silicone Case</a> - &#36;33.96, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1HZST%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;51.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHWVCV1Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Max Silicone Case</a> - &#36;34.84, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/magsafe-duo-charger-low-price/">MagSafe Duo Charger Hits All-Time Low Price of &#36;79.99, MagSafe Charger on Sale for &#36;27.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/magsafe-duo-charger-hits-all-time-low-price-of-79-99-magsafe-charger-on-sale-for-27-99.2420730/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: AI Server Industry Aiming to Win Business From Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business-from-apple.2420728/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 07:00:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[AI server makers are hoping to obtain orders from Apple ahead of its highly anticipated unveiling of new AI features later this year, according to Taiwanese research firm <a href="https://www.trendforce.com/presscenter/news/20240229-12048.html">TrendForce</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-840591" /><br/>
Server manufacturer Supermicro is reportedly "aggressively expanding" its efforts to secure AI-related orders from Apple. The company has the potential to double its shipments of AI servers this year, supported by orders from existing clients including CoreWeave and Tesla.<br/>
<br/>
Late last year, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/23/apple-ai-server-spending-2024/">reported</a> that Apple is expected to spend around &#36;4.75 billion on servers to support its AI technology in 2024, up from &#36;620 million in 2023. The company could purchase up to 20,000 servers this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is widely expected to announce a range of new AI features at WWDC later this year as part of the preview of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and its other software updates. At its annual shareholder meeting yesterday, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said that the company will "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">break new ground</a>" in generative AI in 2024. "We believe it will unlock transformative opportunities for our users," he added.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business/">iOS 18: AI Server Industry Aiming to Win Business From Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-ai-server-industry-aiming-to-win-business-from-apple.2420728/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Do-It-Yourself Repair Program to M3 Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-do-it-yourself-repair-program-to-m3-macs.2420691/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 05:26:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Aaron Perris</dc:creator>
		<category>Self Service Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon expand its self-service repair program to the M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, M3 14-inch MacBook Pro, and M3 16-inch MacBook Pro, according to a trio of support documents published today. <strong>(Update: Parts and manuals for M3 Macs are now available — see below).</strong><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-MacBook.jpeg" alt="" width="3920" height="2205" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938858" /><br/>
First introduced in the U.S. in 2022, Apple's repair program lets customers purchase genuine Apple parts and tools. Apple also provides manuals so that customers can repair their devices without having to visit an Apple retail location or an Apple Authorized Service Provider. Repairs have been available for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/22/apple-expands-self-service-repair-program-to-macbook-air-and-macbook-pro/">Apple's notebooks</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/20/apple-self-service-repair-mac-desktops/">desktops</a> since 2022, but repair components and instructions for the M3 models were just made available.<br/>
<br/>
The support document covering the M3 MacBook Pro models details replacing the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/103908">bottom casing of a MacBook</a>, the parts needed to make a repair, and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/103897">what tools</a> are necessary to complete the repair. For the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, Apple provides a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/105134">detailed list of part numbers</a> required for various repairs on the display, logic board, fans, housing, and more.<br/>
<br/>
At the time of writing, some of the part numbers listed in the support documents are not available on Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a> Store, but we will likely see them added soon. It is not clear when Apple plans to announce the expansion of the repair program to M3 Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás Álvarez</a>!)</em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Update: Now Live</h2><br/>
Following our report, Apple has added parts for the 14-inch MacBook Pro, 16-inch MacBook Pro, and &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with M3, M3 Pro, and/or M3 Max chips to its <a href="https://selfservicerepair.com/en-US/order">self-service repair store</a> in the U.S. and select European countries. Apple has also published <a href="https://support.apple.com/en_US/manuals/maclaptops">repair manuals for these MacBook Pro</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en_US/manuals/macdesktops">iMac</a> models on its website.<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://nr.apple.com/dv7I5H2Ih6">press release</a>, Apple announced a few related changes.<br/>
<br/>
First, it is making Apple Diagnostics available for M3 Macs in the U.S. early next month:<blockquote>Launched late last year for iPhone and Mac, Apple Diagnostics troubleshooting sessions give customers the same ability as Apple Authorized Service Providers and Independent Repair Providers to test devices for optimal part functionality and performance, as well as identify which parts may need repair.</blockquote>Second, Apple is making the System Configuration process easier for all Mac models in all countries where the self-service repair program is available:<blockquote>Mac users will no longer need to contact the Self Service Repair support team to run the final step of a repair, but the team will still be available to assist as needed. The updated process will become available early next month in all countries where Self Service Repair is supported.</blockquote><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/self-service-repair/">Self Service Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-self-service-repair-m3-macs/">Apple Expands Do-It-Yourself Repair Program to M3 Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-do-it-yourself-repair-program-to-m3-macs.2420691/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Sales in China Increasingly Dependent on Promotions</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-sales-in-china-increasingly-dependent-on-promotions.2420725/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 05:20:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple resellers in China are offering discounts on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models by as much as &#36;180, indicating an unusually lengthy drop in demand, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-29/apple-s-iphone-steeply-discounted-in-china-on-weak-demand">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iphone-15-pro-box.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918442" /><br/>
According to the media outlet, Alibaba's Tmall is trying to drive sales of the premium handsets by offering them at less than the roughly &#36;120 discount Apple offered around the same time last year. <br/>
<br/>
The discounts follow Apple's own <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/15/apple-offers-rare-iphone-discounts-china/">rare price reductions</a> on its website ahead of the Lunar New Year holiday in February. Apple has since returned to selling its &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup at original prices.<br/>
<br/>
The promotions indicate Apple's latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> generation is struggling to achieve the same popularity of previous models in China. Apple sales in China dropped 13% to &#36;20.8 billion in the quarter ended December, falling short of the &#36;23.5 billion predicted by analysts.  <br/>
<br/>
Strong interest in Android phones with generative AI features are believed to be fueling the trend, which is expected to deepen throughout 2024. "The pressure was mainly coming from other Android vendors as we saw Apple decline by around 10% year-on-year in the month while Huawei grew triple-digits over the same period, IDC analyst Will Wong told <em>Bloomberg</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's next major software update,‌ ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, is expected to include a slew of new AI features, while some AI capabilities are rumored to be exclusive to upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models. But it's unclear how game-changing the features will prove to be, and whether they will arrive in time to revive the slump in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/">iPhone 15 Sales in China Increasingly Dependent on Promotions</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-sales-in-china-increasingly-dependent-on-promotions.2420725/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iPod Hi-Fi Launched 18 Years Ago – and Lasted Just 554 Days</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago-–-and-lasted-just-554-days.2420717/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 02:54:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Reflecting on the iPod Hi-Fi, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2006/02/28/ipod-hi-fi-introduced-plus-leather-ipod-cases/">launched</a> 18 years ago, many long-time readers may remember it as Apple's ambitious foray into the home audio market, long before smart speakers were a thing. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ipod-hi-fi.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938838" /><br/>
Priced at &#36;349, it promised audiophile-quality sound within a compact design, offering home audio without the clutter of traditional stereo components. It featured a built-in Universal Dock for iPods, providing a seamless integration that allowed users to charge their device while playing music. <br/>
<br/>
With its capability to produce a wide frequency range and room-filling sound without distortion, the iPod Hi-Fi combined Jony Ive's minimalist design aesthetic and high-quality audio performance. Its versatility was further highlighted by the inclusion of an Apple Remote, and the option for AC or battery power, making it portable. <br/>
<br/>
Many products in the iPod series achieved remarkable success, but the iPod Hi-Fi wasn't one of them. The device was praised for its big rich sound, bass response, and ease of use, but its high price was a turn-off for many Apple device users. Also, the connector prominently positioned atop the speaker unit exposed docked iPods to potential knocks and damage. <br/>
<br/>
Despite its innovative features, the iPod Hi-Fi remained a niche product in Apple's lineup​​, and the combination iPod dock/speaker system never took off. Apple discontinued it on September 5, 2007, just 554 days after its launch.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/apple-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago/">Apple&#039;s iPod Hi-Fi Launched 18 Years Ago – and Lasted Just 554 Days</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-ipod-hi-fi-launched-18-years-ago-–-and-lasted-just-554-days.2420717/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Adapt William Gibson&#039;s Cyberpunk Novel &#039;Neuromancer&#039; for TV+</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adapt-william-gibsons-cyberpunk-novel-neuromancer-for-tv.2420714/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 02:04:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a TV adaptation of William Gibson's acclaimed 1984 cyberpunk sci-fi novel <em>Neuromancer</em>, the company <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-announces-neuromancer-new-drama-based-on-the-multi-award-winning-science-fiction-novel-by-william-gibson/">announced</a> on Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/neuromancer.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938829" /><br/>
The new 10-episode drama will be created by Graham Roland and JD Dillard as a co-production between Skydance Television and Anonymous Content. "Neuromancer" will also be produced by Drake's DreamCrew Entertainment, with Roland serving as show runner and Dillard set to direct the pilot episode.<br/>
<br/>
From the TV+ <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-announces-neuromancer-new-drama-based-on-the-multi-award-winning-science-fiction-novel-by-william-gibson/">press release</a>:<br/>
<blockquote>The series will follow a damaged, top-rung super-hacker named Case who is thrust into a web of digital espionage and high stakes crime with his partner Molly, a razor-girl assassin with mirrored eyes aiming to pull a heist on a corporate dynasty with untold secrets.<br/>
<br/>
"We're incredibly excited to be bringing this iconic property to Apple TV+," said creators and executive producers Roland and Dillard. "Since we became friends nearly 10 years ago, we've looked for something to team up on, so this collaboration marks a dream come true. 'Neuromancer' has inspired so much of the science fiction that's come after it and we're looking forward to bringing television audiences into Gibson's definitive 'cyberpunk' world."<br/>
<br/>
</blockquote>The debut novel by Gibson, <em>Neuromancer</em> has been praised as one of the first and most-respected works within the cyberpunk genre and has received numerous accolades, including the Nebula Award, the Philip K. Dick Award and the Hugo Award. The novel served as the first book in the "Sprawl" trilogy and was followed by <em>Count Zero</em> and <em>Mona Lisa Overdrive</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Gibson's work introduced a gritty, technologically saturated view of the future that was revolutionary at the time. The author's vision introduced the now-familiar concepts of cyberspace (a term Gibson is credited with popularizing), virtual reality, and AI, presenting them in a way that was both innovative and prophetic.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ has become something of a sanctuary for unique science fiction, featuring everything from renowned novels such as "Foundation" and "Silo" to original series like "For All Mankind" and "Severance." Apple TV+‌ received a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-tv-price-increasing-significantly/">price increase</a> in October, and the service now costs &#36;9.99 per month in the U.S. for new and existing subscribers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/william-gibson-neuromancer-apple-tv/">Apple to Adapt William Gibson&#039;s Cyberpunk Novel &#039;Neuromancer&#039; for TV+</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-adapt-william-gibsons-cyberpunk-novel-neuromancer-for-tv.2420714/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spaces Hosts on X Can Now Broadcast Video During a Chat Session</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spaces-hosts-on-x-can-now-broadcast-video-during-a-chat-session.2420711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 01:25:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spaces, or live audio chat sessions on Twitter (now X), now support video, owner Elon Musk announced on Wednesday by reposting a <a href="https://x.com/cb_doge/status/1762865068671176773?s=20">video tutorial</a> by the user DogeDesigner.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
When hosts create a new Spaces session, they will see a new option to "enable video," and can use their phone's front or back-facing cameras, in either landscape or portrait mode, for their video feed. <br/>
<br/>
Currently, only hosts can turn on video, making them front and center of attention, while co-hosts and listeners are represented by icons surrounding the broadcast. Users have to join the Spaces session to view the video, just as they do to listen in.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">BREAKING: Video Spaces are now live on <br><br>Here&#39;s how to host a video space: <a href="https://t.co/PgYHiq0jhU">pic.twitter.com/PgYHiq0jhU</a></p>&mdash; DogeDesigner (@cb_doge) <a href="https://twitter.com/cb_doge/status/1762865068671176773">February 28, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Video Spaces are distinct from X's live broadcasting feature, which lets users stream video to their profile and followers' timelines. The latter is more akin to the old Periscope functionality that Twitter supported back in its heyday.   <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/x-spaces-enables-video-feeds/">Spaces Hosts on X Can Now Broadcast Video During a Chat Session</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spaces-hosts-on-x-can-now-broadcast-video-during-a-chat-session.2420711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Spent More Than &#36;10 Billion on Apple Car Before Canceling Project</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-spent-more-than-10-billion-on-apple-car-before-canceling-project.2420692/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 17:13:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple spent more than &#36;10 billion working on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> over the last decade, according to a report from <em><a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/28/technology/behind-the-apple-car-dead.html">The New York Times</a></em> that details the issues the project faced during development. Apple first launched the project in 2014 and let it flounder for more than a decade before <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">calling it off</a> earlier this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774148" /><br/>
Money was spent on research and development, along with the thousands of Apple engineers and car experts that worked on the project. Some employees within Apple are said to have suspected that the endeavor was likely to fail from the beginning, and they referred to the car as "the Titanic disaster" instead of its "Project Titan" codename.<br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> signed off on the project, but members of the car team knew that it was going to be close to impossible. An electric vehicle with self-driving capabilities would need to cost at least &#36;100,000, and it would have razor thin margins and stiff competition.<br/>
<br/>
While Apple reportedly held discussions with Elon Musk about a possible purchase of Tesla, the company decided that building its own car made more sense than attempting to integrate Tesla into Apple. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/02/19/tesla-ceo-acquisition-unlikely/">Way back in 2014</a>, Musk said that he had "conversations" with Apple, but he said at the time that an acquisition seemed "very unlikely." <br/>
<br/>
Apple was never able to find the right leader for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project. As we detailed in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">look back at the Apple Car's history earlier today</a>, the project had four different leads and was scaled up and scaled back several times over the course of the last 10 years. According to <em>The New York Times</em>, the ultimate reason that it failed was because Apple was simply unable to develop the software and algorithms for a car with autonomous driving.<br/>
<br/>
The more than 2,000 employees that worked on the car project are being redistributed, some will join other teams at Apple to work on AI and other technologies, and some will be laid off. Apple will take what it learned from the car project and apply it to other devices like AI-powered AirPods with cameras, robot assistants, and augmented reality.<br/>
<br/>
More on the downfall of the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; and some of the technologies that Apple came up with can be found in the <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/02/28/technology/behind-the-apple-car-dead.html">full <em>The New York Times</em> report</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-car-10-billion-spent/">Apple Spent More Than &#36;10 Billion on Apple Car Before Canceling Project</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-spent-more-than-10-billion-on-apple-car-before-canceling-project.2420692/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Car History - Where Did Development Go Wrong?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-history-where-did-development-go-wrong.2420682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 14:19:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history&#038;post_date=1709169559/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After spending a decade <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">developing an autonomous car</a>, Apple this week decided it was time to pull an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpower/">AirPower</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">shut down the project</a>. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a> is no more, and Apple is no longer planning to release an Apple-branded electric vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-774145" /><br/>
The hundreds of engineers and car experts who were working on the vehicle will be laid off or distributed to other teams within Apple, including the AI team. The &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; is one of the longest running rumors that we've been reporting on without a product materializing, so we thought we'd take a look back at some of the key moments in the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;'s history to provide some insight into what went wrong.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2015_-_early_development">2015 - Early Development</h2><br/>
In early 2015, a van leased to Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/04/mysterious-apple-car/">surfaced on the streets</a> of Concord, California with LiDAR equipment on its roof. Apple had been using vans like this for mapping purposes, but the hardware looked similar to hardware being used by companies testing self-driving software. This one vehicle sighting ended up sparking a slew of rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/04/winningappleconceptcar1.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="450" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-445134" /><em><div class="center-wrap">An imagined <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/04/07/designers-fanciful-apple-car-concepts/">Apple Car concept</a></div></em><br/>
That same month, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/09/apple-project-tesla-competitor/">unnamed Apple employee</a> told <em>Business Insider</em> that Apple would "give Tesla a run for its money," and <em>Financial Times</em> claimed that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/13/apple-automotive-research-lab/">was recruiting</a> automotive technology and vehicle design experts to work in a "top-secret research lab." <em>The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wsj-com/">Wall Street Journal</a></em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/13/apple-working-on-electric-car/">then broke a story</a> with in-depth details on the hundreds of employees working on an Apple-branded minivan-like electric vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
There were a number of other key headlines and details shared in 2015.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> reportedly approved the self-driving car project in 2014.</li><br/>
 <li>At the time, the project was led by Steve Zadesky, Apple VP of Product Design and a former Ford engineer. It was overseen by Dan Riccio, Apple's SVP of hardware engineering.</li><br/>
 <li>In 2015, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/02/19/apple-car-production-2020/">hoping to produce the car</a> by 2020. Later, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/21/apple-car-development-speeds-up/">the WSJ said</a> it could be ready as soon as 2019.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple was said to be meeting with Magna Steyr, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/03/05/bmw-denies-i3-apple-car-report/">BMW</a>, and automotive companies as it sought a partner.</li><br/>
 <li><em>The Guardian</em> published a report that Apple wasn't just working on an electric vehicle, it was working on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/08/14/apple-car-test-track-discussions/">autonomous vehicle</a>. The report also said that Apple had prototypes ready for testing, which wasn't accurate.</li><br/>
 <li>Former General Motors CEO Dan Akerson said that Apple was underestimating the difficulty of operating in the car business. "They have no idea what they're getting into," he said.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple hired a ton of vehicle experts from automotive companies and from companies with expertise in autonomous vehicles.</li><br/>
 <li>Apple's "secret" car headquarters <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/03/13/apple-car-hq-sunnyvale/">were located</a> in Sunnyvale, California, close to the Infinite Loop campus.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2016_and_2017_-_first_signs_of_strife_lead_to_major_upheaval">2016 and 2017 - First Signs of Strife Lead to Major Upheaval</h2><br/>
The first hints of trouble with the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; project surfaced in January 2016, with &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; lead Steve Zadesky <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/01/22/apple-car-steve-zadesky-to-leave-apple/">departing the company</a>. Around this time, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/01/08/apple-car-cars-auto-domains/">registered several domain names</a>, including apple.car and apple.auto.<br/>
<br/>
Former Apple SVP of technologies Bob Mansfield came out of retirement <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/07/28/apple-car-autonomous-driving-system/">to head up the project</a>, and under his direction, rumors suggested that Apple was focusing on an autonomous driving system with the aim of partnering with a car manufacturer in the future. Apple kept aggressively hiring, and at this time, split development into the hardware for the car and the software that would run on it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/04/Apple-Car-front-side.jpg" alt="" width="800" height="265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-498042" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Another &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; concept from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/04/14/motor-trend-apple-car-renders/">Motor Trend</a></div></em><br/>
With the transition to Mansfield's leadership, hundreds of employees were fired or reassigned, and in late 2016, there was a major upheaval. Apple "abandoned" plans to build its own vehicle and gave Mansfield's team <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2016/10/17/apple-late-2017-deadline-self-driving-system/">a 2017 deadline</a> to prove the feasibility of a self-driving system.<br/>
<br/>
In early 2017, white Lexus RX450h SUVs outfitted with LiDAR equipment and piloted by Apple employees <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/04/27/apple-self-driving-lexus-suv-spotted/">were spotted in the Bay Area</a>, and Apple has used these vehicles to test its autonomous driving systems up until now. Apple was also rumored to be testing its self-driving technology <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/28/apple-autonomous-vehicles-arizona-test-site/">at a facility in Arizona</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple's Self-Driving Car Spotted on 101 in Palo Alto" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DtQcNHw-w8M" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple at this time was also working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/08/22/apple-self-driving-campus-shuttle/">building an autonomous shuttle</a> in partnership with Volkswagen to ferry employees to the Infinite Loop campus, but that was nixed.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; made the unusual decision to confirm that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/06/13/tim-cook-confirms-apple-autonomous-driving/">working on autonomous driving</a>. "We're focusing on autonomous systems," Cook said. "It's a core technology that we view as very important." He went on to say that it was the "mother of all AI projects," describing it as "one of the most difficult AI projects actually to work on."<br/>
<h2 id="2018_and_2019_-_full_car_shelved_quiet_work_on_autonomous_driving_systems">2018 and 2019 - Full Car Shelved, Quiet Work on Autonomous Driving Systems</h2><br/>
In 2018, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/05/14/apple-expands-self-driving-car-fleet/">continued to expand</a> the number of SUVs it was using to test autonomous driving software. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; would be Apple's next "star product" and that it would launch in 2023 to 2025. Kuo claimed it would revolutionize the auto market, likening it to the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
2018 was a quiet year for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; as Apple worked on self-driving systems behind the scenes, but toward the end of the year there was speculation that the car project was back on due to the hiring of former <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2018/08/10/former-tesla-lead-engineer-returns-to-apple/">Ford lead engineer Doug Field</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In 2019, there were little hints that the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; was still in the works. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/17/apple-car-next-generation-lidar-sensors-report/">had talks</a> with LiDAR sensor suppliers, looking for advanced designs. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/25/apple-acquires-self-driving-car-startup-drive-ai/">also purchased</a> self-driving vehicle startup Drive.ai.<br/>
<br/>
Mid-year, there was a fun rumor that Jony Ive had wanted to design the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/28/jony-ive-apple-car-without-steering-wheel/">without a steering wheel</a>, a concept that would resurface later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2020_and_2021_-_another_leadership_shakeup_renews_interest_in_apple_car">2020 and 2021 - Another Leadership Shakeup Renews Interest in Apple Car</h2><br/>
2020 was the year of the pandemic, and for 11 months, we heard nothing about the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;. Behind the scenes though, the project was undergoing another leadership change. Bob Mansfield was out, and &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; development <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/apple-car-join-giannandrea/">shifted to John Giannandrea</a>, Apple's AI chief, with Doug Field overseeing day-to-day operations.<br/>
<br/>
In December, rumors suggested an Apple-branded vehicle <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/21/apple-car-production-rumored-2024/">was back on</a>, and that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/09/apple-car-tsmc-chips/">allegedly in talks</a> with well-known automotive electronics suppliers.<br/>
<br/>
2021 brought numerous rumors of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/10/apple-hyundai-apple-car-deal/">Apple partnership with Hyundai</a> for the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;, and Hyundai even confirmed the relationship before walking it back. The deal <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/05/apple-pauses-car-talks-hyundai-kia/">ultimately dissolved</a>, perhaps because of Hyundai's lack of discretion. Apple held talks with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/05/apple-car-kia-talks-georgia-assembly/">multiple Japanese automakers</a>, but no partnership materialized. For a time, there were rumors that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/02/kuo-apple-car-use-hyundai-e-gmp-platform/">Apple would use</a> Hyundai's E-GMP electric battery platform, but that didn't happen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/csm_hyundai-ev-platform-apple-car.jpg" alt="" width="1345" height="618" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-781438" /><br/>
Toward the end of the year, Doug Field left Apple, and there was yet another leadership change, with Apple Watch chief Kevin Lynch taking over under John Giannandrea.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2022_and_2023_-_steering_wheel-free_design_rumored_as_project_loses_focus">2022 and 2023 - Steering Wheel-Free Design Rumored as Project Loses Focus</h2><br/>
In 2022, &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; rumors heated up after <em>The Information</em> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/11/apple-car-design-rumors/">published a report</a> suggesting that Apple was working on a design with four seats that faced inward, a curved ceiling, and large seat-back screens that raised and lowered. There was talk of a car without a steering wheel or pedals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2015/02/canoo-interior-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1333" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826229" /><em><div class="center-wrap">&zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; was rumored to have a design similar to the Canoo, pictured in the image above. Canoo's self-driving car has no steering wheel and a limousine-like interior.</div></em><br/>
The same report said that Apple's self-driving technology was lacking, with Apple's SUVs hitting curbs, having trouble staying in their lanes, and struggling to navigate streets. One vehicle reportedly almost ran into a person.<br/>
<br/>
Late in 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/apple-car-project-scaled-back-delayed/">again abandoned plans</a> for a fully autonomous vehicle, instead aiming for a self-driving mode that worked on highways. Apple was said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/06/apple-car-pricing-2026-launch/">planning an Apple Car launch for 2026</a>, offering a scaled back version of the vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
Rather than the fantastical design without a steering wheel, the car was said to have a more traditional design and a price point around &#36;100,000.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors about the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; dried up in 2023 and we heard little about it all year. In September 2023, Apple analyst &zwnj;Ming-Chi Kuo&zwnj; said the project had "lost all visibility," and he warned that without an acquisition, Apple would not have a chance of producing a car within the next several years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="2024_-_apple_car_in_trouble">2024 - Apple Car in Trouble</h2><br/>
In January 2024, <em>Bloomberg</em> said that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/23/apple-car-scaled-down-2028-launch/">had scaled back the Apple Car design</a> a <strong>second</strong> time, forgetting plans of more advanced autonomous functionality. Apple wanted the car to be able to drive on its own on highways, but that was too ambitious. Instead, Apple settled for driver-assistance features similar to how Tesla vehicles operate, with the car offering steering and brake/acceleration support.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/vanamara-apple-car-concept3.jpg" alt="" width="1500" height="808" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-828956" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/12/10/apple-car-3d-render-based-on-patents/">Apple Car concept</a> based on Apple's patented designs</em></div><br/>
While Apple had been aiming for a 2026 launch, with the new project changes, that was pushed to 2028. <em>Bloomberg</em> warned that if Apple decided it was unable to provide an electric vehicle with this more limited feature set, executives might cancel the project.<br/>
<br/>
Just a month after that report, Apple executives decided to go ahead and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">give up on the Apple Car</a>, focusing instead on AI. Some &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; employees will move to Apple's generative AI team, while others will be laid off or will need to apply for new positions within Apple.<br/>
<br/>
As of now, the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; joins two other canceled Apple projects - <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/03/29/apple-officially-cancels-airpower/">the AirPower</a> charging mat nixed in 2019 and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> set that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/05/18/apple-nixed-plans-for-television-set/">rumored for several years</a> right around 2014.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="wrap-up">Wrap-Up</h2><br/>
Looking back at the &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj;'s history, it's clear that the multiple leadership changes and almost yearly redirects of the project ultimately led to Apple's decision to end work on developing a vehicle.<br/>
<br/>
Apple executives were never quite convinced of the viability of an &zwnj;Apple Car&zwnj; because of the enormous cost and safety risk involved with autonomous driving capabilities, and there was no one at Apple that was able to bring it to fruition.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-car-history/">Apple Car History - Where Did Development Go Wrong?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-car-history-where-did-development-go-wrong.2420682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Refurbished M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro Models in More Countries</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-mbps-more-countries/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-m3-pro-and-m3-max-macbook-pro-models-in-more-countries.2420681/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 14:18:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-mbps-more-countries/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with the M3 Pro and/or M3 Max chips to its certified refurbished store <a href="https://www.apple.com/ca/shop/refurbished/mac/macbook-pro">in Canada</a> and select European countries, such as <a href="https://www.apple.com/uk/shop/refurbished/mac/macbook-pro">the UK</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/de/shop/refurbished/mac/macbook-pro">Germany</a>, and <a href="https://www.apple.com/it/shop/refurbished/mac/macbook-pro">Italy</a>, for the first time since the laptops debuted in October. Availability in the U.S. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-macbook-pro/">began earlier this month</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
As usual for Apple's refurbished products, these refurbished MacBook Pro models are discounted by approximately 15% compared to the equivalent brand new models. A variety of configurations and color options are available in Canada, but inventory is currently more limited in Europe. The stock changes frequently, so check back often.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says it puts refurbished Macs through "full functionality testing" and a "thorough cleaning process and inspection," and they are covered by Apple's one-year limited warranty and eligible for extended AppleCare+ coverage.<br/>
<br/>
In our view, Apple's refurbished Macs are virtually indistinguishable from brand new ones, providing a good opportunity for savings directly from Apple. However, larger discounts are often <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">available from resellers like Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In related news, Apple began selling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-refurbished-m3-imac/">refurbished iMac models with the M3 chip</a> in the U.S. today.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-mbps-more-countries/">Apple Now Selling Refurbished M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro Models in More Countries</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-m3-pro-and-m3-max-macbook-pro-models-in-more-countries.2420681/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad Pro&#039;s Thin Design Highlighted in CAD Drawings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/2024-ipad-pro-cad-drawings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pros-thin-design-highlighted-in-cad-drawings.2420679/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 13:22:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/2024-ipad-pro-cad-drawings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is working on a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> that is set to launch as soon as March, and the refresh will mark the biggest design update to the Pro lineup since 2018.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
Apple is transitioning to OLED displays, and the swap will allow for a major change to the overall thickness of the device. CAD drawings of the upcoming ~11-inch and ~13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models give us some insight into just how thin the tablets will be.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/11-inch-ipad-pro-2024.jpg" alt="" width="3729" height="1269" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938780" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/11-inch-ipad-pro-2024-thickness.jpg" alt="" width="1120" height="188" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938785" /><em><div class="center-wrap">11-inch 2024 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;</div></em><br/>
CAD drawings of unreleased Apple devices often leak out of Apple's factories in China and other countries because the information is so valuable to case makers. Case makers use these measurements to design cases for new products in order to be the first to market with a protective case for a new device size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/13-inch-ipad-pro-2024.jpg" alt="" width="3832" height="1316" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938781" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/13-inch-ipad-pro-2024-thickness.jpg" alt="" width="1178" height="124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938786" /><em><div class="center-wrap">13-inch 2024 &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;</div></em><br/>
Previously leaked dimensions confirmed that the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> models will be significantly thinner than the current versions. The larger &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, for example, will be over 1mm thinner.<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>Current 11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 247.6mm x 178.5mm x 5.9 mm</li><br/>
<li>Upcoming ~11-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 249.7mm x 177.5mm x 5.1mm</li><br/>
<li>Current 12.9-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 280.6mm x 214.9mm x 6.4mm</li><br/>
<li>Upcoming ~13-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; - 281.5mm x 215.5mm x 5.0mm</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
OLED displays will bring improved HDR, better colors, deeper blacks, and other quality improvements. Apple has so far limited OLED technology to the Apple Watch and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, so this will be the first time that OLED displays have been available in an Apple device of this size.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models are also expected to be upgraded with faster 3-nanometer M3 chips, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> charging is a possibility. Apple is also expected to sell the devices with a new Magic Keyboard and an upgraded <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, with full details <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">available in our OLED iPad Pro guide</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/2024-ipad-pro-cad-drawings/">OLED iPad Pro&#039;s Thin Design Highlighted in CAD Drawings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pros-thin-design-highlighted-in-cad-drawings.2420679/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple ID Could Be Rebranded to &#039;Apple Account&#039; Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-id-to-apple-account-rebrand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-could-be-rebranded-to-apple-account-later-this-year.2420673/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 12:07:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-id-to-apple-account-rebrand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Marko Zivkovic</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to be gearing up for a major rebrand of the well-known <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>, with plans to rename it to "Apple Account." Sources familiar with Apple's work have told <em>MacRumors</em> that Apple is experimenting with the new Apple Account name, and it could be introduced as soon as this year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-ID-to-be-Renamed-to-Account-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-938763" /><br/>
An &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; is an account that allows Apple users to access services such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. The option to create and log in to an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; is available across all of Apple's platforms and has been accessible to users for over a decade. With an &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;, users can purchase apps and music, sync data wirelessly between devices using &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; and make purchases on Apple's online store, among other things.<br/>
<br/>
The rebrand from &zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj; to Apple Account is expected to occur later in 2024, likely alongside the release of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> (Codename Crystal) and macOS 15 (Codename Glow). System applications will receive modifications to reflect the change, as will Apple's website -- assuming the company chooses to implement the new branding.<br/>
<br/>
Although instances of the term "Apple Account" can be found <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/111001">on Apple's website</a>, and as part of larger phrases such as "<a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202359">Apple Account Balance</a>," our sources have said that Apple intends to replace existing mentions of "&zwnj;Apple ID&zwnj;" with "Apple Account" as a means of rebranding the feature.<br/>
<br/>
It is currently unclear why Apple is considering this change, and  it's important to consider that Apple often has multiple marketing names ready before new services or products launch. With the operating system for the recently released Vision Pro headset, for instance, Apple used three different names in its internal testing –- realityOS, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/xros/">xrOS</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>. Consequently, there is a possibility that we may not see the Apple Account branding come to fruition, for one reason or another.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-id-to-apple-account-rebrand/">Apple ID Could Be Rebranded to &#039;Apple Account&#039; Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-could-be-rebranded-to-apple-account-later-this-year.2420673/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook Says Apple Will &#039;Break New Ground&#039; in Generative AI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-says-apple-will-break-new-ground-in-generative-ai.2420670/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 10:58:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AAPL</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today held its annual shareholders meeting, and during the event, Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> once again commented on Apple's AI plans. Cook said that the company will "break new ground" in generative AI in 2024. "We believe it will unlock transformative opportunities for our users," said Cook.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-840591" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/hey-siri-banner-apple.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" /><br/>
Cook has made several statements on Apple's artificial intelligence ambitions in recent months. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/tim-cook-generative-ai-comments/">Back in November</a>, he said that Apple was "investing quite a bit" in AI, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">in February</a>, he said that the company was spending a "tremendous amount of time and effort" on AI, with more details to come later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Multiple rumors have said that Apple will add new generative AI features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, with plans to use AI to boost the capabilities of many of the built-in iOS apps.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from Cook's comments on AI, the shareholder meeting was business as usual. As <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-28/apple-shareholders-vote-down-request-for-ai-transparency-report">noted by <em>Bloomberg</em></a>, shareholders rejected a proposal asking Apple for an AI transparency report with details on whether AI is being used ethically.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's board and executive compensation plans were approved, but no shareholder proposals were accepted. Al Gore and James Bell are set to retire from Apple's board, while former Aerospace Corp. CEO Wanda Austin will join.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/aapl/">AAPL</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">Tim Cook Says Apple Will &#039;Break New Ground&#039; in Generative AI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-says-apple-will-break-new-ground-in-generative-ai.2420670/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Begins Selling Refurbished iMac With M3 Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-refurbished-m3-imac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-imac-with-m3-chip.2420664/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 08:51:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-refurbished-m3-imac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Apple Refurbished Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added the iMac with the M3 chip <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/refurbished/mac/2023-imac">to its certified refurbished store</a> in the U.S. for the first time since the computer was introduced in October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921470" /><br/>
As usual for Apple's refurbished products, the refurbished iMacs are discounted by approximately 15% compared to the equivalent brand new models, with pricing starting at &#36;1,099. A variety of configurations and color options are available.<br/>
<br/>
All of the usual accessories are included in the box, including a Magic Keyboard, Magic Mouse, power adapter and cord, and USB-C to Lightning cable.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says it puts refurbished Macs through "full functionality testing" and a "thorough cleaning process and inspection," and they are covered by Apple's one-year limited warranty and eligible for extended AppleCare+ coverage.<br/>
<br/>
In our view, Apple's refurbished Macs are virtually indistinguishable from brand new ones, providing a good opportunity for savings directly from Apple. However, larger discounts are sometimes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">available from resellers like Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently began selling <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/apple-refurbished-14-inch-m3-macbook-pro/">refurbished MacBook Pro models with the M3 chip</a>, and later models with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/refurbished-m3-pro-m3-max-macbook-pro/">M3 Pro and M3 Max chips</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-refurbished/">Apple Refurbished Products</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/apple-refurbished-m3-imac/">Apple Begins Selling Refurbished iMac With M3 Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-begins-selling-refurbished-imac-with-m3-chip.2420664/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Chinese Automakers Shocked at Apple&#039;s Decision to Cancel Car Project</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/chinese-shocked-at-apple-car-cancelation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chinese-automakers-shocked-at-apples-decision-to-cancel-car-project.2420658/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 08:14:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/chinese-shocked-at-apple-car-cancelation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Car</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>South China Morning Post</category>
		<category>Xiaomi</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's decision to cancel its electric vehicle project has surprised ambitious new Chinese automakers like Xiaomi, the <a href="https://www.scmp.com/tech/big-tech/article/3253542/chinese-ev-players-surprised-apples-decision-cancel-car-project-xiaomi-ceo-lei-saying-he-remains?"><em>South China Morning Post</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/12/Apple-car-wheel-icon-feature-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-774149" /><br/>
Yesterday, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> revealed that after a decade of work and millions of dollars in development costs Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-cancels-electric-car-project/">canceled its plans</a> to bring an EV to market, moving many of the 2,000 staff working on the project to generative AI instead. The decision has come as a surprise to new tech-focused Chinese EV brands like Xiaomi, Li Auto, and Xpeng, who saw a future Apple car as one of their main rivals.<br/>
<br/>
Xiaomi is one of China's biggest electronics companies and is best known for its line of smartphones. The company unveiled its first EV, the SU7, late last year and it is set to go on sale after further testing. The project required over &#36;1.4 billion in development and over 3,400 engineers.<br/>
<br/>
Founder and chairman Lei Jun today posted on Weibo that he was "very shocked" by the news of Apple's decision to cancel its EV. He added that he "knows deeply how difficult it is to make cars," but Xiaomi has made an "unshakeable strategic choice" to move into EVs. He Xiaopeng, chairman of Chinese EV maker Xpeng, expressed similar disbelief that Apple is abandoning its car plans.<br/>
<br/>
Li Xiang, CEO of Beijing-based EV maker Li Auto, remarked on Weibo that Apple's decision to shift emphasis from EVs to AI was "absolutely right." "AI will become the top-level entrance for all devices, services, applications and transactions, in which Apple should stay on top," he added.<br/>
<br/>
Chinese brands possess a rapidly growing proportion of global EV sales. Last year, China's BYD overtook Tesla as the world's top EV manufacturer.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-car/">Apple Car</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/scmp-com/">South China Morning Post</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/xiaomi/">Xiaomi</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/chinese-shocked-at-apple-car-cancelation/">Chinese Automakers Shocked at Apple&#039;s Decision to Cancel Car Project</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/chinese-automakers-shocked-at-apples-decision-to-cancel-car-project.2420658/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple Vision Pro Unlikely to Receive Major Upgrades Until 2027</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-vision-pro-major-upgrades-unlikely-until-2027/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-vision-pro-unlikely-to-receive-major-upgrades-until-2027.2420656/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 07:56:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-vision-pro-major-upgrades-unlikely-until-2027/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It may take several years for the Vision Pro headset to receive major hardware upgrades, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-at-Steve-Jobs-Theater.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898794" /><br/>
"It is currently estimated that new models with significant changes to the Vision Pro specification may not be in mass production until 2027," Kuo <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/vision-pro%E6%9B%B4%E6%96%B0-%E7%BE%8E%E5%9C%8B%E5%B8%82%E5%A0%B4%E9%9C%80%E6%B1%82%E5%B7%B2%E5%A4%A7%E5%B9%85%E6%94%BE%E7%B7%A9-%E5%85%A8%E7%90%83%E7%99%BC%E4%BD%88%E6%99%82%E7%A8%8B%E9%A0%90%E6%B8%AC-%E4%BE%9B%E6%87%89%E9%8F%88%E6%93%B4%E7%94%A2%E8%88%87%E9%80%80%E8%B2%A8%E7%8E%87%E8%A7%A3%E8%AE%80-%E6%96%B0%E6%A9%9F%E7%A8%AE%E9%A0%90%E6%B8%AC-%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E7%AD%96%E7%95%A5-vision-pro-update-us-market-demand-f12ab8423404">said today</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Based on his latest supply chain checks, Kuo believes Apple has not started working on a second-generation Vision Pro, or a lower-priced version of the headset with reduced specs. However, research and development could be underway.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo does expect a modified Vision Pro to enter mass production in late 2025 to early 2026, but he said Apple is focused on improving costs and production, leading him to believe that the "user experience will not differ from the current model." It is possible these changes might not even be announced to the public, beyond a potential price cut.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo expects Apple to release the Vision Pro in additional countries <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">before WWDC in June</a>. The headset launched in the U.S. earlier this month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-vision-pro-major-upgrades-unlikely-until-2027/">Kuo: Apple Vision Pro Unlikely to Receive Major Upgrades Until 2027</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apple-vision-pro-unlikely-to-receive-major-upgrades-until-2027.2420656/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
