<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 03:03:30 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Leaked M4 MacBook Pro Appears for Sale on Russian Classifieds Site</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/09/leaked-m4-macbook-pro-russian-classified-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/leaked-m4-macbook-pro-appears-for-sale-on-russian-classifieds-site.2439604/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 02:05:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/09/leaked-m4-macbook-pro-russian-classified-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>M4</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a continuation of the latest unprecedented leak, Apple's yet-to-be-announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-macbook-pro/">M4 MacBook Pro</a> has reportedly surfaced on <a href="https://www.avito.ru">Avito</a>, a popular Russian classified ads website. The development follows recent videos from Russian YouTube channels showcasing what appears to be the unreleased laptop model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/m4-macbook-pro-leak-russian-ad.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="850" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970162" /><br/>
According to <a href="https://x.com/aaplpro/status/1843589085237051515">reports on social media</a>, the listing on Avito advertised a 14-inch MacBook Pro featuring the next-generation M4 chip. The device was supposedly configured with 16GB of RAM and 512GB of storage, and offered in a new Space Black finish – a color currently exclusive to the M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro models. The asking price was said to be around 720,000 rubles (approximately &#36;7,500), which is significantly higher than current MacBook Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
Notably, it appears that multiple units of the unreleased MacBook Pro were offered for sale, suggesting a batch was stolen from a Chinese warehouse and somehow made it into Russia. The listing reportedly included a note stating that the price changes daily and buyers should confirm before purchase. However, as of now, these listings have been removed from the platform, which prohibits the sale of "nonexistent" products.<br/>
<br/>
The latest leak comes on the heels of <a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/eqPZ42NNTGI">unboxing videos</a> shared by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/alleged-m4-macbook-pro-unboxing-video/">Russian YouTube channels</a> over the weekend. These videos purportedly show the upcoming MacBook Pro, revealing potential upgrades such as a three Thunderbolt port 4 for the base model (up from two previous-generation TB3 ports) and 16GB of RAM as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-new-macs-16gb-ram-standard/">new minimum memory configuration</a>.<br/>
<br/>
While the authenticity of these leaks remains unconfirmed, they do line up with recent rumors about Apple's plans for its Mac lineup. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has suggested that Apple may introduce M4-powered Macs as soon as the end of October, with a potential release date of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/apple-to-launch-new-m4-macs-nov-1/">November 1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
If genuine, this leak represents a significant breach in Apple's typically stringent security measures. The last time Apple faced a leak of this magnitude was in 2010 when an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 4 prototype was accidentally left at a bar in California.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not commented on these leaks, and it remains unclear how the company will respond to this apparent breach. As always, potential buyers should approach unofficial listings with caution, especially for unannounced products.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4/">M4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/09/leaked-m4-macbook-pro-russian-classified-ad/">Leaked M4 MacBook Pro Appears for Sale on Russian Classifieds Site</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/leaked-m4-macbook-pro-appears-for-sale-on-russian-classifieds-site.2439604/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Here Are All of the Apple Intelligence Features in iOS 18.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-in-ios-18-1.2439580/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:26:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence&#038;post_date=1728437167/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon release iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> 15.1, and these updates will bring the first Apple Intelligence features for compatible iPhones, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963424" /><br/>
Not all of the Apple Intelligence features that Apple has in the works are coming in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 updates, and there will be Apple Intelligence capabilities added in future iOS 18.2, iOS 18.3, and iOS 18.4 updates.<br/>
<br/>
We've rounded up everything Apple Intelligence-related that will be included in the iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 updates when the software comes out later this month.<br/>
<br/>
Note that Apple Intelligence is still being refined and perfected, and when it launches, it will launch in a beta capacity.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="writing_tools">Writing Tools</h2><br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960221" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-writing-tools.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Proofread text checks for spelling and grammar errors, including word choice and sentence structure. You can accept all suggestions with a tap or go through them one by one with explanations.</li><br/>
 <li>Rewrite cleans up what you've written and shifts the tone without impacting your content. Options include Friendly, Professional, and Concise.</li><br/>
 <li>You can select text and get a summary of it with Apple Intelligence. You can choose to create a paragraph, pull out key points, make a list, or create a table. Summaries are available in Mail, Messages, and more.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
You can select any text on your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac and use Apple Intelligence to access Writing Tools for summaries and other features.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="siri">Siri</h2><br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960222" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-siri.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>There's a new glow around the edges of the display when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is activated, applicable to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a>. On Mac, the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; window can be placed anywhere. The glow animates responsively to the sound of your voice so you can tell when &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is listening without interrupting other things you're doing.</li><br/>
 <li>A double tap at the bottom of the display brings up the Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; interface so you can type requests instead of speaking them. On Mac, you need to press the Command key twice to bring up Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;. Type to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; includes suggested requests so you can get your questions answered faster.</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can maintain context between requests so you can ask a question and then reference it in a second reply. If you ask about the temperature in Raleigh, for example, and then follow up with "what's the humidity?" &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; should know you mean in Raleigh.</li><br/>
 <li>If you stumble over your words when speaking to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, or change what you're saying mid-sentence, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will follow along.</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has Apple's product knowledge and support base for answering questions about your device's features and settings, and can even find settings when you don't know the exact name by using natural language search.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mail">Mail</h2><br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960207" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-smart-replies.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>There is a summarize button for summarizing any of your incoming emails, plus you will see a brief summary of an email in your inbox list rather than the first few lines of the email.</li><br/>
 <li>Mail surfaces time sensitive messages first when applicable, putting them at the top of your inbox so you see what's important right away.</li><br/>
 <li>Smart Reply provides quick-tap responses to emails that you've been sent, with contextual options based on what's in the email.</li><br/>
 <li>Multiple notifications from Mail will be summarized on your Lock Screen so you can see what's in an email without opening the app.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages">Messages</h2><br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960223" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-messages-smart-reply.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Messages has Smart Reply options for incoming texts, which analyze the content of messages to offer suggestions of what you might want to say.</li><br/>
 <li>Multiple Messages notifications are summarized on your Lock Screen.</li><br/>
 <li>You can use all of the Writing Tools features in the Messages app for proofreading and refining what you're planning to send.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="photos">Photos</h2><br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960208" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-memory-maker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>You can create a Memory Movie with just a description, such as "My cat in 2024," or "Orlando in the summer." The feature automatically picks relevant photos and chooses songs, but you can tweak through the Memory Mixes feature or choose a mood to guide the direction of the audio. You can also add in specific scenes and images you want to see throughout the memory when you're creating the prompt.</li><br/>
 <li>Natural language search is available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a>, so you can just describe what you're looking for, such as "Eric rollerskating while wearing green."</li><br/>
 <li>Search can also find specific moments in video clips.</li><br/>
 <li>Search offers up smart complete suggestions for narrowing down what you might want to find.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h3 id="clean_up">Clean Up</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app also includes "Clean Up," a feature that lets you remove unwanted objects from your photos. The Clean Up tool in the ‌&zwnj;Photos&zwnj;‌ app is able to automatically detect objects in an image that might not be wanted, but you can also tap, circle, or brush over an unwanted object to remove it.<br/>
<br/>
Zooming in on an image can help with using a finger as a brush to remove smaller blemishes and issues with an image, and it is intelligent enough not to remove part of a person even if a person or main subject is selected.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962933" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Photos-Clean-Up-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Clean Up works on all images in the ‌&zwnj;Photos&zwnj;‌ library, including older images and images captured by other devices like a point and shoot camera or a DSLR.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="transcription_summaries">Transcription Summaries</h2><br/>
In Notes and other apps, you can record audio and get a transcript along with a summary of your transcript, which is useful for recording lectures and other audio. Transcription isn't an Apple Intelligence feature, but summaries are. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="focus_modes">Focus Modes</h2><br/>
There is a dedicated Reduce Interruptions Focus Mode that only shows you important notifications that need attention while filtering out everything else.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960224" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-mode-changes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
When customizing an existing Focus mode or creating a new one, there is a new toggle to turn on Intelligent Breakthrough and Silencing. This option allows important notifications to interrupt you, while muting notifications that are not important, which is the same thing that the Reduce Notifications Focus does. You can override the notification settings for specific apps and people, which is how it worked prior to iOS 18.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960225" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-focus-reduce-interruptions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="notification_summaries">Notification Summaries</h2><br/>
Your incoming notifications are summarized so you can see what's new for each app at a glance. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ios-18-apple-intelligence-notification-summary.jpg" alt="notifications" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-968372" /><br/>
<h2 id="phone">Phone</h2><br/>
Summaries of transcriptions generated from your phone calls are supported in iOS 18.1. The iOS 18.1 update adds the option to record a phone call and get a transcription, which is not an Apple Intelligence feature. What does require Apple Intelligence, though, is getting a summary from that transcription without reading through the entire thing.<br/>
<br/>
Note that you can start a recording by tapping on the record button in the upper left corner of the display when on a phone call. All participants are notified that the call is being recorded before the recording starts.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960199" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-call-recording-1.jpg" alt="" width="5416" height="3047" /><br/>
Recorded phone calls are stored in the Notes app, where you can tap in to view a transcript and get a summary generated from that transcript.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="safari">Safari</h2><br/>
When reading an article in Reader Mode, there is an option to have Apple Intelligence summarize the article for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960226" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-safari-summarize.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<h2 id="app_store">App Store</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> supports natural language and descriptive app tags to make it easier to find exactly what you're looking for.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_report">Apple Intelligence Report</h2><br/>
In the Privacy and Security section of the Settings app you can access an Apple Intelligence Report that lets you export your Apple Intelligence data as part of Apple's promise for transparency around Apple Intelligence. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> is required to access and export Apple Intelligence data.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960227" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence-report.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_waitlist">Apple Intelligence Waitlist</h2><br/>
When iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are released, you will need to go to the Settings app and join the Apple Intelligence waitlist. Apple is using a waitlist mechanic to ensure that behind the scenes downloads go smoothly and that the system isn't overloaded.<br/>
<br/>
While on the waitlist, Apple devices download necessary files for on-device processing, and the waitlist should only take a few hours at most. The waitlist is on a per-account basis, so you only need to sign up for it on one device to have access on multiple devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_compatibility">Apple Intelligence Compatibility</h2><br/>
The iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 betas are only available to registered developers with an eligible device. Devices that cannot run Apple Intelligence will not see the update.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>All <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models</li><br/>
 <li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Pro Max</li><br/>
 <li>All Apple silicon iPads</li><br/>
 <li>All Apple silicon Macs</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_availability">Apple Intelligence Availability</h2><br/>
Apple Intelligence is only available in U.S. English at this time, and it is not available to developers in the European Union or China. Device region and language need to be set to the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_launch_date">Apple Intelligence Launch Date</h2><br/>
iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; 15.1 are expected to be released on Monday, October 28.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_intelligence_features_coming_later">Apple Intelligence Features Coming Later</h2><br/>
iOS 18.2, which we should get before the end of the year, is expected to bring support for ChatGPT integration with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;, Image Playground, and Genmoji.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.3, coming sometime around January, could bring some new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; features, but that's not yet guaranteed.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18.4 is expected to have the bulk of the &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; Apple Intelligence features including support for on-screen awareness for responding to what's on your display, better per-app controls and app integration, and personal context for more personalized responses to queries. We'll likely get iOS 18.4 around March.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will also be adding support for additional languages in 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">Here Are All of the Apple Intelligence Features in iOS 18.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/here-are-all-of-the-apple-intelligence-features-in-ios-18-1.2439580/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Shift Toward More Staggered Releases Could Bring More Innovation and Less Predictability</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-release-schedule-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-shift-toward-more-staggered-releases-could-bring-more-innovation-and-less-predictability.2439574/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:23:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-release-schedule-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to be slowly moving away from regular, timed hardware and software releases that come on an annual basis, instead favoring more of a staggered product release cycle, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> highlighted in his most recent <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-10-06/when-will-apple-intelligence-be-released-when-is-apple-releasing-m4-macs-ipad-m1xksx7q">Power On newsletter</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m3-macbook-air-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950298" /><br/>
Gurman suggests that Apple Intelligence is evidence that Apple is "ever-so-slightly" moving away from a big fall launch for its hardware and software products. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> debuted without any Apple Intelligence features, despite the fact that Apple Intelligence was a key focal point of &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; at the Worldwide Developers Conference, and heavily advertised for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
Instead, the first Apple Intelligence features will come out in October in an iOS 18.1 update, and Apple plans to add new Apple Intelligence capabilities in iOS 18.2, iOS 18.3, and iOS 18.4. Everything that Apple highlighted in June 2024 won't be available until well into 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has delayed some software features in the past, introducing them in later updates, but with Apple Intelligence, Apple announced everything well in advance and made it clear that the software updates would roll out over time.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman suggests that Apple could continue on this path, adopting a strategy that will see it release products when they're ready rather than pushing to get devices out on a scheduled timeline. As Apple's product lineup has grown more complex, software has also become more complicated. This year, Apple had to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/17/apple-pulls-ipados-18-m4-ipad-pro/">pull iPadOS 18</a> for the new M4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models after it was released, plus it had to remove beta versions of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/03/apple-pulls-third-software-update-in-past-month/">watchOS 11.1</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/24/apple-pulls-homepod-18-1-beta-2/">HomePod Software 18.1</a> because the software was causing significant issues.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is not expected to stop offering yearly releases of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but there are signs that it is holding updates on some other products. There was no new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> this year (and it seems to be on a 3-year update cycle as of now), nor did Apple introduce a new Apple Watch Ultra, instead adding a new color for the Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
Macs and iPads that are planned for 2025 will come at various points throughout the year and may not be tied to specific events like WWDC and the September &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; event. Gurman has previously said Apple will introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2025-macbook-air/">new MacBook Air models</a>, new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-se-4/">new iPhone SE</a> early in 2025, with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/m4-mac-studio-m4-mac-pro-2025/">to follow in mid-2025</a> and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a> to come later.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman suggests that continuing on with a staggered approach could result in more innovation thanks to fewer timing constraints, and that such a strategy would also make Apple less predictable, which is something that the company aims for.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-release-schedule-changes/">Apple&#039;s Shift Toward More Staggered Releases Could Bring More Innovation and Less Predictability</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-shift-toward-more-staggered-releases-could-bring-more-innovation-and-less-predictability.2439574/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The 10 Best Apple Deals Under &#36;100 for Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/under-100-for-prime-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-10-best-apple-deals-under-100-for-prime-day.2439555/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:20:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/under-100-for-prime-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">Prime Day continues</a> today, we're highlighting all of the best Apple deals you can get for under &#36;100 on Amazon. This includes Apple Pencil, AirTags, iPhone cases, USB-C chargers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Prime-Big-Deal-Days-Hero-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969559" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/"><strong>every Apple deal available during Prime Day</strong></a> in our dedicated post. Remember that you'll need an <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon Prime membership</a> to get Prime Day deals, and you can sign up for Prime on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>&#36;30 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/prime-day-airtag.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970043" /><br/>
<br/>
In the cheapest category, you can get Apple's 20W USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;14.99, down from &#36;19.00 and the AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99, down from &#36;29.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-20W-USB-C-Power-Adapter%2Fdp%2FB08L5M9BTJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>20W USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;14.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-USB-C-Woven-Charge-Cable%2Fdp%2FB0BJMDHRPS%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>60W USB-C Woven Cable (1m) for &#36;15.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CWXNS552%3Fref%3Dods_ucc_kindle_B0CWXNS552_rc_nd_ucc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;4 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;24.99</div></a></div><h2>&#36;50 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/prime-day-magsafe.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970042" /><br/>
<br/>
For accessories priced between &#36;30 and &#36;50, there are a few sales on Amazon for Prime Day. You can get the 35W Dual USB-C Port Power Adapter for &#36;39.99, down from &#36;59.00, as well as discounts on iPhone 16 cases.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ4QQ5W%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>1-meter MagSafe Charger for &#36;32.78</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-USB-C-Compact-Power-Adapter%2Fdp%2FB0D1XRRQZJ%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>35W Dual USB-C Power Adapter for &#36;39.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-Silicone-MagSafe-Control%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQKKQN%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>iPhone 16 Pro Silicone Case for &#36;37.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-Silicone-MagSafe-Control%2Fdp%2FB0DGHJL1R1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>iPhone 16 Pro Max Silicone Case for &#36;37.99</div></a></div><h2>&#36;100 Or Under</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/prime-day-apple-pencil-pro.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970041" /><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, we're tracking a few deals on Apple products that are just under &#36;100 for Prime Day. You can get an AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.99 (&#36;19 off), an Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;98.00 (&#36;31 off), and USB-C Apple Pencil for &#36;67.00 (&#36;11 off).<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-MX542LL-A-AirTag-pack%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;79.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>Apple Pencil USB-C for &#36;67.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;31 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;98.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more Prime Day discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">big Prime Day post</a> where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the event. Remember that you'll need an Amazon Prime membership to get Prime Day deals. <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">You can sign up for Prime</a> on Amazon if you don't have the service yet.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/under-100-for-prime-day/">The 10 Best Apple Deals Under &#36;100 for Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-10-best-apple-deals-under-100-for-prime-day.2439555/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Four New Games Coming to Apple Arcade, Including Wheel of Fortune</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-arcade-november-2024-games/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/four-new-games-coming-to-apple-arcade-including-wheel-of-fortune.2439557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:16:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-arcade-november-2024-games/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today in an emailed press release announced four new games coming to Apple Arcade on November 7, including <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/wheel-of-fortune-daily/id6469643458">Wheel of Fortune Daily</a>, which is based on the iconic TV show. The other three games coming next month include <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/drive-ahead-carcade/id6468031571">Drive Ahead! Carcade</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/arkanoid-vs-space-invaders/id6503027740">Arkanoid vs Space Invaders+</a>, and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/texas-holdem-poker-pokerist/id6477283493">Texas Hold'em Poker: Pokerist+</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Arcade-Wheel-of-Fortune-Daily.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970084" /><br/>
Developed by Frosty Pop, Wheel of Fortune Daily will be available in Apple Arcade across the iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple TV, and Apple Vision Pro. The game features classic Wheel of Fortune bonus puzzles, where the player starts with the letters R, S, T, L, N, and E, chooses three more consonants and a vowel, and attempts to solve the puzzle.<br/>
<br/>
"Wheel of Fortune Daily turns America's Game® into a simple, short, daily experience you can enjoy anytime and anywhere," the game's description says.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Apple-Arcade-Wheel-of-Fortune-Daily-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970089" /><br/>
Accessible through the App Store, Apple Arcade is a subscription-based service that provides access to hundreds of games, all free of ads and in-app purchases. In the U.S., Apple Arcade costs &#36;6.99 per month and is bundled in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-one/">Apple One plans</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-arcade-november-2024-games/">Four New Games Coming to Apple Arcade, Including Wheel of Fortune</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/four-new-games-coming-to-apple-arcade-including-wheel-of-fortune.2439557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Waiting for a New Apple TV? Here&#039;s What the Latest Rumors Say</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-tv-rumor-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/waiting-for-a-new-apple-tv-heres-what-the-latest-rumors-say.2439546/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:57:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-tv-rumor-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The current Apple TV was released two years ago this month, so you may be wondering when the next model will be released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about a next-generation Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
In January 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reported that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">new Apple TV was planned for release in the first half of 2024</a>:<blockquote>Beyond the future smart displays and new speaker, Apple is working on revamping its TV box. A new version with the current design is in the works for the first half of next year with a faster processor, the people said.</blockquote>The first half of 2024 passed by without a new Apple TV, so that rumor has expired.<br/>
<br/>
Last month, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">Gurman said</a> "stable inventory" of the Apple TV suggested that a new model was not on the "immediate horizon" after all:<blockquote>While the company has been working on an update to the Apple TV set-top box for as early as this year, no new model has come to fruition and stable inventory of the device suggests a new version isn’t on the immediate horizon.</blockquote>All in all, there is no longer a clear timeframe for the next Apple TV. If you are considering purchasing an Apple TV, we recommend at least waiting until October is finished, just in case a new model is announced this month like in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Here is when the previous five Apple TV models were announced:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>Second-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> April 2021</li><br/>
<li><strong>First-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> September 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple TV HD:</strong> September 2015</li><br/>
<li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV:</strong> March 2012</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Whenever it comes out, the next Apple TV is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">faster processor</a> than the current A15 Bionic chip, and even lower pricing. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo suggested that the next Apple TV <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">could have a sub-&#36;100 starting price</a>. In the U.S., the current Apple TV is available with 64GB or 128GB of storage for &#36;129 and &#36;149, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes have been rumored for the next Apple TV specifically, but Gurman said Apple has considered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">adding a built-in camera</a> to a future model. tvOS 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-iphone-facetime-camera-apple-tv/">added a FaceTime app to the Apple TV</a>, allowing for users to have video calls by using the rear camera on a connected iPhone or iPad. If the Apple TV gained a built-in camera, users would no longer need to rely on an external device for video calls on the TV.<br/>
<br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV roundup</a> for more details.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-tv-rumor-recap/">Waiting for a New Apple TV? Here&#039;s What the Latest Rumors Say</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/waiting-for-a-new-apple-tv-heres-what-the-latest-rumors-say.2439546/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Releases New USB-Powered Tool to Remove iPhone 16&#039;s Battery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ifixit-usb-tool-to-remove-iphone-16-battery/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-releases-new-usb-powered-tool-to-remove-iphone-16s-battery.2439544/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:43:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ifixit-usb-tool-to-remove-iphone-16-battery/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The batteries inside the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus use an innovative type of adhesive that can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/18/iphone-16-and-16-plus-9v-battery-removal/">loosened with low-voltage electrical current</a>. Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/20/iphone-16-repair-manual/">official repair guide</a> recommends using a 9V battery with alligator clips for this process, but DIY repair website iFixit has released a new USB-powered tool as an alternative solution.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/iFixit-VoltClip.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970054" /><br/>
As reported <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/10/8/24262373/ifixit-iphone-16-battery-repair-adhesive">by <em>The Verge</em></a>, iFixit is now selling a <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/products/voltclip">VoltClip tool</a> that is essentially a pair of alligator clips with an integrated USB-C adapter. With a USB-C to USB-C cable, which is not provided, you can connect the tool to any USB-C charger or device that supports 9V or 12V output. iFixit has a <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/Guide/How+to+Use+the+VoltClip+to+Debond+an+iPhone+Battery+Adhesive/177712">step-by-step guide</a> with complete instructions.<br/>
<br/>
The adhesive debonding process takes roughly 60 to 90 seconds.<br/>
<br/>
The tool is <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/products/voltclip">available for &#36;10.95</a> on iFixit's online store in the U.S., with same-day shipping available on orders placed before 1 p.m. Pacific Time each day.<br/>
<br/>
This electrical removal process does not extend to iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max batteries, which still have stretch-release adhesive pull tabs.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-16">iPhone 16 (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ifixit-usb-tool-to-remove-iphone-16-battery/">iFixit Releases New USB-Powered Tool to Remove iPhone 16&#039;s Battery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-releases-new-usb-powered-tool-to-remove-iphone-16s-battery.2439544/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch SE Drops to Just &#36;169.99 for Prime Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-watch-se-drops-prime-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-drops-to-just-169-99-for-prime-day.2439539/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 08:16:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-watch-se-drops-prime-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Prime Day deals are rolling in today, and now we're tracking the return of all-time low prices on the second generation Apple Watch SE. If you want a full list of all the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">best Prime Day discounts on Apple products</a>, our dedicated article has sales on AirPods, MacBooks, iPads, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/prime-day-apple-watch-se.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970027" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ1L1T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is an all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ1L1T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ1MLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ1MLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another best-ever price on the Apple Watch SE for Prime Day.<br/>
<br/>
There are also multiple cellular models on sale for Prime Day, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ75HCG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.99</strong></a> for the 40mm cellular Apple Watch SE, down from &#36;299.00. The 44mm cellular Apple Watch SE has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHSQC9R%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00, and both of these are record low prices.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-watch-se-drops-prime-day/">Apple Watch SE Drops to Just &#36;169.99 for Prime Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-se-drops-to-just-169-99-for-prime-day.2439539/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+&#039;s &#039;Severance&#039; to Get Rare Blu-Ray Release Ahead of Season 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/severance-to-get-blu-ray/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-s-severance-to-get-rare-blu-ray-release-ahead-of-season-2.2439537/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:55:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/severance-to-get-blu-ray/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>+'s acclaimed sci-fi series "Severance" is set to receive a rare Blu-ray release this December, just ahead of the much-anticipated second season (via <a href="https://www.blu-ray.com/news/?id=35303"><em>Blu-ray.com</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/04/severance-apple-tv-plus.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-842248" /><br/>
Severance premiered on &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ in February 2022. It was an immediate hit upon its debut, quickly gaining attention for its unique premise and dark tone. The show follows Mark Scout (played by Adam Scott) and his colleagues at Lumon Industries, where employees undergo a procedure called "severance." This process separates their work and personal lives by splitting their memories in two, creating a stark division between their identities inside and outside of work. <br/>
<br/>
The release of the first season on Blu-ray on December 17, 2024 will allow fans and collectors to own a physical copy of the series for the first time. The launch marks one of the rare occasions where an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ show will be available outside the streaming platform and on physical media.<br/>
<br/>
While &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ offers a growing catalog of original content, physical media releases have been infrequent. Unlike some streaming platforms that have embraced physical distribution of their most successful series, Apple typically retains a tight hold on its streaming exclusives. In the case of Severance, the release is being handled by Fifth Season, one of the co-production companies involved in the making of the show. Apple itself is not directly responsible for the Blu-ray's distribution.<br/>
<br/>
Severance on Blu-ray is <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FSeverance-Season-One-Blu-ray%2Fdp%2FB0DJC3GWYG%3Ftag%3Dbluray-011-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1%26m%3DATVPDKIKX0DER">available to pre-order</a> on Amazon now for &#36;42.98. It is worth noting that the release is only in Full HD (1080p), without the option of UHD (4K). Season two of Severance is set to be released exclusively on &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;+ on January 17, 2025.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/severance-to-get-blu-ray/">Apple TV+&#039;s &#039;Severance&#039; to Get Rare Blu-Ray Release Ahead of Season 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-s-severance-to-get-rare-blu-ray-release-ahead-of-season-2.2439537/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Final iPod Nano and iPod Shuffle Models Are Now Obsolete</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/obsolete-ipods/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-final-ipod-nano-and-ipod-shuffle-models-are-now-obsolete.2439535/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:41:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/obsolete-ipods/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added the final iPod nano and iPod shuffle models to its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/102772">obsolete products list</a> worldwide, marking the end of an era.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/ipod_nano_2015_feature.jpg" alt="" width="1552" height="873" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757305" /><br/>
Apple introduced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/07/15/apple-launches-new-ipod-touch-nano-shuffle/">new color options</a> for the seventh-generation iPod nano and fourth-generation iPod shuffle in 2015, and those models are now obsolete in particular. Apple went on to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/07/27/apple-removes-ipod-nano-ipod-shuffle/">discontinue the iPod nano and iPod shuffle</a> entirely in 2017.<br/>
<br/>
Apple considers a device to be "obsolete" once seven years have passed since the company stopped distributing it for sale. Once a device is obsolete, it is no longer eligible for repair at an Apple Store or Apple Authorized Service Provider, with the only exception being MacBook battery replacements for up to a 10-year period.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also added the iPhone 6 to its obsolete products list today. Apple had already classified the larger iPhone 6 Plus as obsolete <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/01/apple-says-iphone-6-plus-is-now-obsolete/">in April</a>, but the smaller iPhone 6 had remained available through resellers in select countries for longer, so it only became obsolete now.<br/>
<br/>
Last, Apple added the 2017 model of the 12-inch MacBook and the sixth-generation iPad to its vintage products list today. Apple considers a device to be "vintage" once five years have passed since the company stopped distributing it for sale. Apple might offer to repair a vintage product, but only if parts remain available.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vintage-and-obsolete/">Vintage and Obsolete Apple Products</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/obsolete-ipods/">Apple Says Final iPod Nano and iPod Shuffle Models Are Now Obsolete</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-final-ipod-nano-and-ipod-shuffle-models-are-now-obsolete.2439535/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts M4 iPad Pro Models to All-Time Low Prices for Prime Day, Starting at &#36;849</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-pro-prime-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-m4-ipad-pro-models-to-all-time-low-prices-for-prime-day-starting-at-849.2439534/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:33:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-pro-prime-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">Prime Day</a> has Apple's 256GB Wi-Fi 11-inch M4 iPad Pro for just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;849.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. This is a match of the all-time low price on the tablet, and it's accompanied by numerous discounts across the entire M4 iPad Pro lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-pro-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969573" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Deals are primarily focused on Wi-Fi models, but you can find a few cellular tablets on sale at this time as well. Most of these deals also require you to clip an on-page coupon to see the final deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>11-inch M4 iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;849.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,049.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,449.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9Q9KB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,549.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J72NMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,840.00 (&#36;159 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JBX6ML%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">2TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,949.00 (&#36;150 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,149.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,349.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,748.00 (&#36;151 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7T414%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,844.00 (&#36;156 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;200 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-pro-prime-day/">Amazon Discounts M4 iPad Pro Models to All-Time Low Prices for Prime Day, Starting at &#36;849</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-m4-ipad-pro-models-to-all-time-low-prices-for-prime-day-starting-at-849.2439534/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Prime Day Deals Arrive for Entire M3 MacBook Air Lineup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/prime-day-deals-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prime-day-deals-arrive-for-entire-m3-macbook-air-lineup.2439532/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:14:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/prime-day-deals-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">Amazon Prime Day is live</a> and it includes a huge sale across the MacBook Air lineup, including both the M2 and M3 MacBook Air models. We already covered the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apples-m2-macbook-air-drops/">M2 MacBook Air deals available for Prime Day</a>, so this article will focus entirely on M3 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/m3-macbook-air-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-970003" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>13-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Amazon is taking &#36;250 off the 13-inch M3 MacBook Air with multiple all-time low prices for Prime Day. You can get the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air for &#36;849.00 in every color, down from &#36;1,099.00. Both 512GB models are on sale as well with best-ever prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;849.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BNQC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>15-Inch M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
Amazon also has the 15-inch M3 MacBook Air for up to &#36;275 off during Prime Day. These start at &#36;1,044.00 for the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air, down from &#36;1,299.00, and again include both 512GB models. Overall, every 15-inch M3 MacBook Air deal from Amazon this week represents all-time low prices on each model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;255 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,044.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;265 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,234.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;275 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,424.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/prime-day-deals-m3-macbook-air/">Prime Day Deals Arrive for Entire M3 MacBook Air Lineup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prime-day-deals-arrive-for-entire-m3-macbook-air-lineup.2439532/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini 7 Coming Next Month: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-mini-7-coming-next-month-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-coming-next-month-what-to-expect.2439526/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:16:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-mini-7-coming-next-month-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Rumors strongly suggest Apple will release the seventh-generation iPad mini in November, nearly three years after the last refresh. Here's a roundup of what we're expecting from the next version of Apple's small form factor tablet, based on the latest rumors and reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iPad-mini-review-thumb.jpg" alt="" width="4114" height="2314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-818321" /><br/>
<h2>Design and Display</h2><br/>
The new iPad mini is likely to retain its compact 8.3-inch display and overall design introduced with the sixth generation. However, one rumor suggests Apple may address the "jelly scrolling" issue by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/jelly-scrolling-reduced-on-ipad-mini-7/">rotating the screen assembly</a>. This change would be made to minimize the noticeable lag when scrolling vertically in portrait orientation, which is a point of frustration for some users of the current model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Performance Boost</h2><br/>
While the iPad Pro and iPad Air now boast M-series chips, the iPad mini 7 is expected to stick with the A-series. It's likely to feature either the A17 Pro chip from the iPhone 15 Pro or the A18 chip found in the iPhone 16. This upgrade should provide a significant performance boost over the A15 Bionic in the current model, as well as provide support for Apple Intelligence features.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Connectivity Improvements</h2><br/>
The new iPad mini is almost certain to include Wi-Fi 6E support, allowing connection to the 6GHz band on compatible routers. Bluetooth 5.3 is also expected, bringing the latest wireless connectivity standards to the compact tablet. Cellular models may transition entirely to eSIM, potentially eliminating the physical nano-SIM slot.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Camera Enhancements</h2><br/>
Apple might relocate the front-facing camera to the landscape edge, as seen in the latest iPad Air. This change could improve the video calling experience, especially when using the device in landscape orientation. The camera may also receive upgrades like HDR 4 support and a wider aperture.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil Compatibility</h2><br/>
The iPad mini 7 will likely support the Apple Pencil Pro, which introduced features like squeeze gestures, haptic feedback, and Find My integration. Apple Pencil Pro hover functionality may also be included.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Color Options</h2><br/>
While the current iPad mini is available in space gray, starlight, pink, and purple, the new model may adopt a color palette similar to the iPad Air. This could mean the introduction of blue and the removal of pink from the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Release and Availability</h2><br/>
With supplies of the current iPad mini dwindling in stores, a November release seems increasingly likely. Indeed, well-connected <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman recently said that Apple could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/apple-to-launch-new-m4-macs-nov-1/">release a new iPad mini alongside new M4 Macs in early November</a>, potentially on the first day of the month. The new model is likely to maintain similar pricing to its predecessor, starting at &#36;499 for the Wi-Fi model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Future iPad Models</h2><br/>
Rumors suggest that Apple is developing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-foldable-2026-could-replace-ipad-mini/">foldable iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-planning-to-bring-oled-to-ipad-mini-and-air/">incorporating OLED display technology</a> into the device, though neither of these updates are anticipated for 2024. An OLED display or a foldable iPad mini is not expected to arrive until 2026, 2027, or possibly even later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Summing Up</h2><br/>
By all accounts, Apple's iPad mini 7 will be a modest yet meaningful upgrade, bringing Apple Intelligence support as well as performance and usability enhancements, rather than a dramatic redesign. As always, we'll have to wait for Apple's official announcement to confirm these details.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/ipad-mini-7-coming-next-month-what-to-expect/">iPad Mini 7 Coming Next Month: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-7-coming-next-month-what-to-expect.2439526/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Swift Student Challenge Returns in February Ahead of WWDC 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-announces-2025-swift-student-challenge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-swift-student-challenge-returns-in-february-ahead-of-wwdc-2025.2439524/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 06:11:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-announces-2025-swift-student-challenge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/10/apples-swift-student-challenge-to-open-in-february-2025/">announced</a> it will begin accepting submissions for the 2025 Swift Student Challenge for a three-week period starting in February.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/2025-Swift-Student-Challenge.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1152" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969979" /><br/>
The annual Swift Student Challenge gives <a href="https://developer.apple.com/swift-student-challenge/eligibility/">eligible student developers</a> around the world the opportunity to showcase their coding skills and creativity by building experimental "app playgrounds" with the Swift Playgrounds or Xcode apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said it will select 350 winners based on "innovation, creativity, social impact, or inclusivity," and it will invite 50 of those winners to spend three days at Apple Park in Cupertino, California next summer, with travel and lodging included. The trip will likely coincide with Apple's annual developers conference WWDC, which is typically held in June.<br/>
<br/>
This earlier-than-usual announcement gives students an adequate amount of time to prepare for the next Swift Student Challenge. Students can learn more and sign up to be notified when applications open on the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/swift-student-challenge/">Apple Developer website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to announce dates for WWDC 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/apple-announces-2025-swift-student-challenge/">Apple Announces Swift Student Challenge Returns in February Ahead of WWDC 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-swift-student-challenge-returns-in-february-ahead-of-wwdc-2025.2439524/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Prime Day Introduces Best Prices We&#039;ve Ever Seen on AirPods Pro 2, USB-C AirPods Max, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/airpods-prime-day-best-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prime-day-introduces-best-prices-weve-ever-seen-on-airpods-pro-2-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more.2439523/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 05:51:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/airpods-prime-day-best-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">Prime Day kicked off</a> earlier today, and it includes some of the best prices we've ever seen on multiple AirPods models. There's also a new record low price on the USB-C AirPods Max among the deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/airpods-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969576" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the return of the all-time low price on the AirPods Pro 2, you can get this model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;168.99</strong></a> today, down from &#36;249.00. It's been a few months since we last tracked this deal for the AirPods Pro 2, and it's a great deal for the Pro-model AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For the AirPods Max models, we're tracking two record low prices on Amazon. You can get the 2020 Lightning models for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;394.99</strong></a> and the brand new 2024 USB-C models for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJKT2X9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a>, both down from &#36;549.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;155 OFF</div>AirPods Max (Lightning) for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJKT2X9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, there's the AirPods 3 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;129.99</strong></a> (&#36;39 off) and AirPods 4 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a> (&#36;10 off). In regards to the AirPods 3, this is a second-best price on the model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">Prime Day article</a> has more information about the discounts on MacBooks, iPads, and more. If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/airpods-prime-day-best-prices/">Prime Day Introduces Best Prices We&#039;ve Ever Seen on AirPods Pro 2, USB-C AirPods Max, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prime-day-introduces-best-prices-weve-ever-seen-on-airpods-pro-2-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more.2439523/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Prime Day Deals on AirPods, Apple Watch, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-prime-day-deals-on-airpods-apple-watch-and-more.2439522/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 05:19:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon's <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fprimebigdealdays%2F">Prime Big Deal Days</a> event is in full swing today, offering customers the first chance to get some holiday shopping done early. Similar to the first Prime Day, it will last for two days (October 8-9) and you can find a large selection of deals across Amazon's storefront, covering savings on tech, clothing, video games, groceries, and much, much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/Prime-Big-Deal-Days-Hero-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969557" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For our coverage, we're focusing entirely on Apple and Apple-related discounts that can be purchased during this 48-hour event on Amazon. As of today, this includes deals on AirPods, Apple Watch, iPad, and MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
As is typical for Prime Day deals, these markdowns are very time sensitive, so sales listed below may disappear fast, and new ones may appear even faster. With this in mind, we'll keep this article updated throughout the event, and keep an eye on the MacRumors front page as we'll be posting particularly great deals in separate articles this week.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, and perhaps most importantly, Amazon Prime Big Deal Days requires you to have an <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime%3Fref_%3Dnav_cs_primelink_nonmember">Amazon Prime membership</a> to take advantage of the discounts. Amazon Prime offers a one month free trial, and otherwise costs &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;139.00 per year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/airpods-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969576" /><br/>
<br/>
Starting with AirPods, you'll find a wide selection of solid deals across the AirPods lineup on Amazon during Prime Day. This includes a &#36;10 discount on the new AirPods 4 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a>, as well as an all-time price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;168.99</strong></a> price on the AirPods Pro 2.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHMNQ5Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>AirPods 4 for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1WXVQTN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D1XD1ZV3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 for &#36;168.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;155 OFF</div>AirPods Max (Lightning) for &#36;394.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJKT2X9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>AirPods Max (USB-C) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-watch-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969575" /><br/>
<h3>SE</h3><br/>
Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ1L1T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.99</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is an all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHQ1L1T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;169.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ1MLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;79 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHZ1MLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another best-ever price on the Apple Watch SE for Prime Day.<br/>
<h3>Ultra 2</h3><br/>
Amazon has further discounted the Apple Watch Ultra 2 in Black this week. You can get a few models of the Black Titanium watch for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3PBKT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;734.89</strong></a>, down from &#36;799.00. This beats the sale price we tracked last week by about &#36;15, and marks a new all-time low price for the Black Apple Watch Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3PBKT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;64 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 (Black) for &#36;734.89</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The models on sale include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ3PBKT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Black Titanium Case with Dark Green Alpine Loop (S)</a> and the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ7N8VH%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Black Titanium Case with Dark Green Alpine Loop (M)</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<h2>9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969767" /><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a> in both colors, down from &#36;329.00. This is a match of the record low price on this version of the 2021 tablet, and it's a deal we haven't seen in a few weeks. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;129 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-2-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969766" /><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the newer models, Amazon has the 64GB Wi-Fi 10th generation iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.00</strong></a> in every color, down from &#36;349.00. You can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;447.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;499.00. In regards to the 256GB model, this is a best-ever price on the tablet.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Cellular models are also seeing all-time low prices during Prime Day. The 64GB Cellular 10th generation iPad has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDWX34%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.00</strong></a> (&#36;50 off), while the 256GB Cellular model is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBH659%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;598.00</strong></a> (&#36;51 off).<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/ipad-pro-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969573" /><br/>
For the newest M4 iPad Pros, Amazon is offering up to &#36;200 off select models of both the 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro. Deals are primarily focused on Wi-Fi models, but you can find a few cellular tablets on sale at this time as well. Many of these deals also require you to clip an on-page coupon to see the final deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;849.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,049.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7SJP9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,449.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6RX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,589.00 (&#36;110 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J72NMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,840.00 (&#36;156 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JBX6ML%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">2TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,949.00 (&#36;150 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,149.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,349.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71MS9%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">1TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;1,749.00 (&#36;150 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7T414%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi with Nano-Texture Glass</a> - &#36;1,844.00 (&#36;156 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;200 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/m2-macbook-air-new-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969782" /><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air, you can get this model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C7MJX3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;749.00</strong></a> in three colors, down from &#36;999.00. For more storage, Amazon has the 512GB model of the same computer for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;949.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,199.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C7MJX3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;749.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;949.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Although Apple updated the MacBook Air back in March, it kept these 13-inch M2 models around as a low-cost option for customers. This means that the M2 MacBook Air should be perfect for anyone who doesn't care about owning newest generation notebook, but would rather save money while still getting a reliable computer.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/macbook-pro-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969574" /><br/>
<br/>
The cheapest M3 MacBook Pro model you'll find right now is on the 14-inch M3 Pro 512GB model, priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>. That's a &#36;300 discount and the best price we've ever tracked, but you can also find a few other solid markdowns on more 14-inch MacBook Pros and 16-inch MacBook Pros at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,299.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LZWJ1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 1TB</a> - &#36;1,499.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5MKMD4%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,999.00 (&#36;500 off)</li></ul><h2>Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/apple-pencil-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969572" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple Pencil deals include low prices on the Apple Pencil 2 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;99.00</strong></a> and Apple Pencil Pro at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;116.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;11 OFF</div>Apple Pencil USB-C for &#36;67.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;31 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;98.00</div></a></div><h2>Magic Keyboard</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/magic-keyboard-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969571" /><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 11-inch Magic Keyboard in Black for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;273.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. This is an all-time low price on the accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J65R9N%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;25 OFF</div>11-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;273.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon also has the 13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard on sale, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;319.00</strong></a> in Black and White, down from &#36;349.00. These are also record low prices on the Magic Keyboard, and you'll find similar delivery estimates of mid October for these models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J63BWD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>13-inch M4 iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for &#36;319.00</div></a></div><h2>MagSafe Charger</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/magsafe-charger-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969570" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon recently introduced a few deals on Apple's new lineup of MagSafe Chargers, including the 1-meter model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ4QQ5W%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;32.78</strong></a> and 2-meter model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHHJXTC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;44.00</strong></a>. Although these discounts represent just a few dollars in savings, they are the first notable sales on the 2024 MagSafe Chargers and the best deals you'll find online right now.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGJ4QQ5W%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>1-meter MagSafe Charger for &#36;32.78</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0DGHHJXTC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;5 OFF</div>2-meter MagSafe Charger for &#36;44.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The new MagSafe Chargers provide overall faster charging speeds with compatible iPhone models. When paired with a 30W power adapter, iPhone 16 models can charge at up to 25W wirelessly over MagSafe, which is 10W faster than a regular non-MagSafe Qi2 wireless charger.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/studio-display-prime-day.jpeg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969568" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has &#36;249 off the Apple Studio Display for Prime Day, starting at &#36;1,347.00 for the standard glass option. For this model, this is a solid second-best price on the monitor.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>Apple Studio Display (standard glass) for &#36;1,347.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/the-best-prime-day-deals-october-2024/">The Best Prime Day Deals on AirPods, Apple Watch, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-prime-day-deals-on-airpods-apple-watch-and-more.2439522/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: Send Messages Without a Wi-Fi or Cellular Connection</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-messages-without-wi-fi-cellular-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-send-messages-without-a-wi-fi-or-cellular-connection.2439520/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 04:49:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-messages-without-wi-fi-cellular-iphone&#038;post_date=1728398982/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Emergency SOS via Satellite</category>
		<category>Messages</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In iOS 18, Apple further enhanced its satellite connectivity features for iPhone users with the introduction of Messages via satellite. Keep reading to learn how it works.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-Messages-via-Satellite.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955787" /><br/>
Available in the United States and Canada to owners of iPhone 14 models and newer, Messages via satellite enables users to exchange iMessages and SMS texts, including emoji and Tapbacks, through satellite connections when traditional networks are unavailable. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is using the infrastructure that it set up for Emergency SOS via satellite for this feature, but you don't need to be in an emergency situation to use it, and the service is currently offered at no additional charge.<br/>
<br/>
When an iPhone detects it's out of cellular or Wi-Fi range, it prompts users with an alert offering quick access to satellite-enabled services. These include Emergency SOS, Roadside Assistance, Find My, and Messages. Users can also access the feature directly from the Messages app when off the grid, with iOS providing on-screen guidance to help point the iPhone toward an available satellite.<br/>
<br/>
iMessages sent via satellite are end-to-end encrypted. However, it's worth noting that while iMessage functionality is fully supported, SMS capabilities are more limited to prevent abuse from automated systems. Emergency contacts and designated family members can initiate SMS contact at any time, but for other contacts, the iPhone user must send the first satellite SMS to enable responses.<br/>
<br/>
To familiarize yourself with this potentially life-saving feature, Apple has included a demo mode in iOS 18. You can access this demonstration by following these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app on your iPhone.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap <strong>Apps</strong>, then tap <strong>Messages</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap <strong>Satellite Connection Demo</strong>.</li><br/>
</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ios-18-messages-via-satellite.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960711" /><br/>
<br/>
This demo guides you through the process of establishing a satellite connection and sending messages, providing valuable practice for real-world scenarios and emergencies where the feature might be crucial.<br/>
<br/>
While the current version doesn't support Rich Communication Services (RCS), Apple could well bridge the remaining gap between traditional and satellite-based communications by expanding the feature's capabilities in a future iOS update.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emergency-sos-via-satellite/">Emergency SOS via Satellite</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/messages/">Messages</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/send-messages-without-wi-fi-cellular-iphone/">iOS 18: Send Messages Without a Wi-Fi or Cellular Connection</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-send-messages-without-a-wi-fi-or-cellular-connection.2439520/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Pro With M4 Chip May Support Up to Two External Displays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/macbook-pro-m4-two-external-displays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-with-m4-chip-may-support-up-to-two-external-displays.2439515/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 02:33:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/macbook-pro-m4-two-external-displays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>Thunderbolt 4</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming entry-level M4 14-inch MacBook Pro may be capable of supporting up to two external displays with the lid open, up from one display supported in the current M3 model, if recent leaks are anything to go by.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/New-MacBook-Pros-Launching-Tomorrow-With-These-4-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921192" /><br/>
Apple's existing M3 14-inch MacBook Pro comes with two Thunderbolt 3 USB-C ports, not three Thunderbolt 4 ports like the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models powered by M3 Pro and M3 Max chips.<br/>
<br/>
Apart from fewer USB-C ports, the lack of Thunderbolt 4 support on the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the base M3 chip means it only supports one display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz (or one display with up to 4K resolution at 120Hz over HDMI) when the lid is open. Currently the only way to support to two external displays simultaneously is with the lid closed, based on the resolution (up to 6K) and refresh rate (up to 60Hz) of each external display.<br/>
<br/>
However, assuming the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-potentially-facing-worst-leak-since-iphone-4/">alleged Russian leaks</a> of Apple's unannounced 14-inch MacBook Pro with an M4 chip are reliable, the new M4 variant of Apple's entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro will come with three Thunderbolt 4 ports, as opposed to the two Thunderbolt 3 / USB4 ports found on the current model. This would mean it can support two external displays with the lid open instead of just one.<br/>
<br/>
While the upgrade from two TB3 ports to three TB4 ports has yet to be confirmed, such a change would better align the entry-level machine's capabilities with Apple's more powerful MacBook Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
As a reminder, M3 Pro supports up to two external displays with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz over Thunderbolt. The M3 Pro-powered MacBook Pro models also support one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz over Thunderbolt and one external display with up to 4K resolution at 144Hz over HDMI.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the M3 Max supports up to four external displays in the following configuration: Up to three external displays with 6K resolution at 60Hz over Thunderbolt and one external display with up to 4K resolution at 144Hz over HDMI.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-m3pro-max-ports.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919715" /><br/>
Alternatively, M3 Max MacBook Pro models can support up to three external displays by connecting two displays with 6K resolution at 60Hz over Thunderbolt and one display with up to 8K resolution at 60Hz, or one display with 4K resolution at 240Hz over HDMI.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, both the M3 Pro and M3 Max also support native DisplayPort over USB-C, and one display with up to 8K resolution at 60Hz or 4K resolution at 240Hz over HDMI.<br/>
<br/>
We should know for certain what the specs are for the base M4 14-inch MacBook Pro before the month is out. Apple is expected to announce new iMac, Mac mini, and MacBook Pro models with M4 chips towards the end of October, with at least some of the new Macs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/06/apple-to-launch-new-m4-macs-nov-1/">rumored to be released on November 1</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thunderbolt-4/">Thunderbolt 4</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/08/macbook-pro-m4-two-external-displays/">MacBook Pro With M4 Chip May Support Up to Two External Displays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-with-m4-chip-may-support-up-to-two-external-displays.2439515/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Need a Halloween Costume Idea? Ask Siri!</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/siri-halloween-costume-ideas-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/need-a-halloween-costume-idea-ask-siri.2439489/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 17:06:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/siri-halloween-costume-ideas-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Siri</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you're looking for a silly Halloween costume idea, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> has some suggestions for you. Apple's personal assistant is equipped with a long list of costume suggestions that are updated on a yearly basis.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/siri-halloween-costume-suggestions.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969926" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s suggestions often involve puns, some of which are clever and some of which are downright silly. Some of &zwnj;Siri&zwnj;'s costume ideas:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Dress up like a cat, put on an eyepatch, and be Nick Furry.</li><br/>
 	<li>If you wear a white sheet and draw tattoos all over your face, you'd be Ghost Malone.</li><br/>
 	<li>You could be a disembodied voice. Oh no wait. That's kind of my thing.</li><br/>
 	<li>Dress in yellow and white, then put on some little red horns, and be a deviled egg.</li><br/>
 	<li>Jump up and down, over and over, and shake your fist. You can tell people you're antigravity.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; for a Halloween costume idea is a feature that's been around for almost a decade now, but it's easy to forget the option exists, and there are also typically new costume suggestions to see each year.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to suggesting Halloween costumes, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can also read a selection of Halloween poems to you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/10/siri-halloween-poem.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-969927" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can give costume suggestions on iOS 17, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and earlier versions of iOS, as well as macOS and Apple Watch.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/siri-halloween-costume-ideas-2024/">Need a Halloween Costume Idea? Ask Siri!</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/need-a-halloween-costume-idea-ask-siri.2439489/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 205 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-205/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-205-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2439493/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:51:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-205/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser that was <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to allow users to test features that are planned for future release versions of the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960117" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Safari-Technology-Preview-Updated-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 205 includes fixes and updates for CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Lockdown Mode, SVG, Tables, Text, Web API, Web Driver, Web Extensions, and WebAssembly.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Sonoma and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, the newest version of macOS. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a> from Apple's website. Complete release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while it is designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download and use.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/10/07/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-205/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 205 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-205-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2439493/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
