<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 09:02:34 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Responds to Being Sued by U.S. Department of Justice</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-responds-to-being-sued-by-u-s-department-of-justice.2422451/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 07:50:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Apple Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice today <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-sues-apple-monopolizing-smartphone-markets">announced</a> it has <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/media/1344546/dl?inline">filed an antitrust lawsuit</a> against Apple. The lawsuit alleges that Apple has an illegal monopoly in the smartphone market with the iPhone and the device's locked-down ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-Logo-16x9-US-Flag-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926535" /><br/>
In a statement shared with <em>MacRumors</em>, Apple said the lawsuit is "wrong on the facts and the law," and the company vowed to "vigorously defend" itself:<blockquote>At Apple, we innovate every day to make technology people love—designing products that work seamlessly together, protect people's privacy and security, and create a magical experience for our users. This lawsuit threatens who we are and the principles that set Apple products apart in fiercely competitive markets. If successful, it would hinder our ability to create the kind of technology people expect from Apple—where hardware, software, and services intersect. It would also set a dangerous precedent, empowering government to take a heavy hand in designing people's technology. We believe this lawsuit is wrong on the facts and the law, and we will vigorously defend against it.</blockquote>The complaint was filed today in a U.S. District Court in New Jersey by the Justice Department and 16 other U.S. state and district attorneys general. Apple is accused of violating various U.S. federal and state antitrust laws, including the Sherman Act.<br/>
<br/>
In its press release, the Justice Department highlighted some of the allegations:<blockquote>- <strong>Blocking Innovative Super Apps</strong>. Apple has disrupted the growth of apps with broad functionality that would make it easier for consumers to switch between competing smartphone platforms.<br/>
- <strong>Suppressing Mobile Cloud Streaming Services.</strong> Apple has blocked the development of cloud-streaming apps and services that would allow consumers to enjoy high-quality video games and other cloud-based applications without having to pay for expensive smartphone hardware.<br/>
- <strong>Excluding Cross-Platform Messaging Apps.</strong> Apple has made the quality of cross-platform messaging worse, less innovative, and less secure for users so that its customers have to keep buying iPhones.<br/>
- <strong>Diminishing the Functionality of Non-Apple Smartwatches.</strong> Apple has limited the functionality of third-party smartwatches so that users who purchase the Apple Watch face substantial out-of-pocket costs if they do not keep buying iPhones.<br/>
- <strong>Limiting Third Party Digital Wallets.</strong> Apple has prevented third-party apps from offering tap-to-pay functionality, inhibiting the creation of cross-platform third-party digital wallets.</blockquote>Apple's anticompetitive conduct also affects "web browsers, video communication, news subscriptions, entertainment, automotive services, advertising, location services, and more," according to the Justice Department.<br/>
<br/>
Jonathan Kanter, Assistant Attorney General of the Justice Department's Antitrust Division:<blockquote>For years, Apple responded to competitive threats by imposing a series of "Whac-A-Mole" contractual rules and restrictions that have allowed Apple to extract higher prices from consumers, impose higher fees on developers and creators, and to throttle competitive alternatives from rival technologies. Today's lawsuit seeks to hold Apple accountable and ensure it cannot deploy the same, unlawful playbook in other vital markets.</blockquote>The entire complaint spans <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/media/1344546/dl?inline">88 pages</a>, so there is a lot of information to unpack. Stay tuned for more coverage throughout the day.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lawsuit/">Apple Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-sued-by-us-department-of-justice/">Apple Responds to Being Sued by U.S. Department of Justice</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-responds-to-being-sued-by-u-s-department-of-justice.2422451/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Hit New Record Low Price of &#36;179.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/airpods-pro-2-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-hit-new-record-low-price-of-179-99-on-amazon.2422443/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 06:04:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/airpods-pro-2-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C/MagSafe Charging Case have hit a new all-time low price of <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This deal has arrived <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/amazons-big-spring-sale/">during Amazon's Big Spring Sale</a>, which also includes great discounts on iPads, Anker accessories, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Blue-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895402" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
There are a few minor changes to the AirPods Pro 2 besides the addition of USB-C, including additional dust resistance and support for lossless audio with the Vision Pro headset. Amazon estimates a delivery window between March 23 and March 26 if ordered today.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories. Additionally, we track sales for every model of the AirPods in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-deals/">Best AirPods Deals</a> guide, so be sure to bookmark that page while you shop around for the wireless headphones.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/airpods-pro-2-new-low-price/">AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C Hit New Record Low Price of &#36;179.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c-hit-new-record-low-price-of-179-99-on-amazon.2422443/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube TV Gains Multiview Support on iPhone and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/youtube-tv-multiview-iphone-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-tv-gains-multiview-support-on-iphone-and-ipad.2422440/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 04:10:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/youtube-tv-multiview-iphone-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>YouTube TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://tv.youtube.com/welcome/">YouTube TV</a> subscribers can now watch several programs at once on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, thanks to support for Multiview rolling out, Google has confirmed (via <em><a href="https://9to5google.com/2024/03/20/youtube-tv-multiview-iphone-ipad-android/">9to5Google</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/youtube-tv.jpg" alt="" width="1100" height="619" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841452" /><br/>
Multiview lets users watch four different cable channels on-screen at the same time. The feature works from the "Home" tab, which includes stream options like "Top Picks for You" and "Watch in Multiview," but it only works for sports events. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribers on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will need to update to version 8.11 or later to access Multivew. According to YouTube TV, "device and content restrictions apply" for Multiview, and it is limited to "pre-selected games only."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/youtube-tv-multiview-iphone.gif" alt="" width="500" height="375" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942479" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Video Credit: <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/youtubetv/comments/1bftqyc/comment/kv2wo9r/">Redditor _oh_jay</a></em></div><br/>
A Basic YouTube TV plan costs &#36;72.99 a month, and there are various add-on packages available such as NBA League Pass, which is currently &#36;49.99 for the entire season. YouTube TV said it plans to launch Multiview on Android in the coming months. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube-tv/">YouTube TV</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/youtube-tv-multiview-iphone-ipad/">YouTube TV Gains Multiview Support on iPhone and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-tv-gains-multiview-support-on-iphone-and-ipad.2422440/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iPhone AI Talks With Google and OpenAI Still Ongoing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-iphone-ai-talks-with-google-and-openai-still-ongoing.2422438/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 03:25:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in ongoing discussions with Google and OpenAI to use their generative large-language models as the backbone of new iPhone AI features, but no formal announcement is expected until the summer, according to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-21/nvidia-meta-stock-gains-turn-magnificent-seven-into-two">Bloomberg</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iphone-open-ai.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942472" /><br/>
Today's report follows the news <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/apple-google-gemini-ios-18-iphone/">earlier this week</a> that Apple has been in talks with Google to integrate its Gemini AI engine into the iPhone as part of iOS 18. <br/>
<br/>
Apple CEO Tim Cook has promised that the company will "break new ground" in AI this year, and iOS 18 is expected to play a big role. However, Apple's internal work is said to be focused on smaller-scale AI features that operate on-device and do not require an internet connection.<br/>
<br/>
To drive more powerful cloud-based generative AI features, such as the ability to create images and write essays based on single prompts, Apple is seeking a partner that has the necessary large-scale hardware infrastructure and compute capabilities already in place.<br/>
<br/>
Siri is expected to take advantage of the artificial intelligence improvements that Apple plans to bring in iOS 18. One leaker has <a href="https://twitter.com/Tech_Reve/status/1722418466647625999?s=20">suggested</a> that Apple is planning to use large-language models to entirely revamp Siri and turn it into the "ultimate virtual assistant."<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman says that one of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">specific features</a> Apple is developing is an improved interaction between Siri and the Messages app, which would let Siri auto-complete sentences more effectively and answer complex questions.<br/>
<br/>
But with the likes of Nvidia and other AI companies continuing to reshape the technology landscape, some investors are reportedly concerned that Apple will fail to keep up with the pace of change, and may not see the "hypergrowth" expected of it unless the iPhone maker can boost its credibility by deploying generative AI features this year. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/">Apple&#039;s iPhone AI Talks With Google and OpenAI Still Ongoing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-iphone-ai-talks-with-google-and-openai-still-ongoing.2422438/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile&#039; Finally Launches on iPhone and iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-launches-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-finally-launches-on-iphone-and-ipad.2422430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 01:38:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-launches-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Activision</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em><a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile/id1638368439">Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile</a></em> finally launched globally today on iOS and Android, after spending the last couple of years in various beta versions and soft launches. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/cod_warzone_mobile.jpg" alt="" width="950" height="534" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942221" /><br/>
The game features two main Battle Royale maps, Verdansk and Rebirth Island, as well as cross-progression for players of <em>Call of Duty: Modern Warfare III</em> and the PC/console version of <em>Call of Duty: Warzone</em>.<br/>
<blockquote>Level up your weapons and XP no matter where you are. Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile supports shared progression with the console and PC versions of Call of Duty: Warzone and Modern Warfare III. Simply log in using your Activision ID, and most content acquired in Modern Warfare III and Call of Duty: Warzone is seamlessly transferred and becomes continuously available between your games.</blockquote>For gamers playing on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip or later, the game includes a "Peak Graphics" mode that runs in 2K with improved textures, lighting, draw distance, ambient occlusion, and resolution caching.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rWNlFdpJ_-8?si=VM_8swUzcrYD5PK0" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<em>Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile</em> requires iOS 16/iPadOS 16 or later, and has been <a href="https://apps.apple.com/app/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile/id1638368439">available to pre-order on the App Store</a> since November 2022, back when Activision was originally targeting a May 2023 release. More than 50 million players have pre-registered for the game already, according to <em>MacRumors</em> sister site <em><a href="https://toucharcade.com/2024/02/28/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-launching-globally-on-march-21st/">TouchArcade</a></em>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activision/">Activision</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-launches-iphone/">&#039;Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile&#039; Finally Launches on iPhone and iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/call-of-duty-warzone-mobile-finally-launches-on-iphone-and-ipad.2422430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: No iPad Announcement Planned for March 26</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/gurman-no-ipad-announcement-march-26/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-no-ipad-announcement-planned-for-march-26.2422423/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 21:32:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/gurman-no-ipad-announcement-march-26/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Earlier this week, leaker "Instant Digital" on Chinese blogging site Weibo claimed that Apple will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/">making an iPad-related announcement next Tuesday, March 26,</a> suggesting a potential press release introduction ahead of pre-orders and a launch date. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1770662077449093624">now weighed in</a>, however, to say that this claim is "not true."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/When-To-Expect-New-iPads-Feature-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-925408" /><br/>
While disputing a March 26 announcement, Gurman has not shared any specific claims of his own regarding an announcement or launch date for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models that are in the works, recently pointing to a general time frame of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/new-ipads-end-of-march-or-april-gurman/">"around the end of March or in April."</a><br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Not true <a href="https://t.co/4vec7H4mk4">https://t.co/4vec7H4mk4</a></p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1770662077449093624?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 21, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">offered a bit more color on the timing</a> in the most recent edition of his <em>Power On</em> newsletter, saying that the "variant of iPadOS 17.4" that will ship on the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models won't be ready until at least late this month, with it potentially taking "a couple weeks" to get the software installed on the initial shipments. That timing, Gurman says, will likely take things "deeper into next month" for a launch of the new iPads although an announcement could happen a bit sooner.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside revamped &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models with OLED displays, Apple's M3 chip, and additional enhancements, we're also expecting updated &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models including a new 12.9-inch size option. Apple is reportedly planning to introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">new Magic Keyboard for the iPad Pro</a> and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">new Apple Pencil</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/gurman-no-ipad-announcement-march-26/">Gurman: No iPad Announcement Planned for March 26</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-no-ipad-announcement-planned-for-march-26.2422423/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Promotes Face ID in New iPhone 15 Ad Called &#039;Nice Try!&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/iphone-15-face-id-ad-nice-try/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-face-id-in-new-iphone-15-ad-called-nice-try.2422421/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:54:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/iphone-15-face-id-ad-nice-try/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		<category>Face ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tlRPZIFWj-E">new iPhone 15 ad</a> called "Nice Try!" on its YouTube channel in Singapore, promoting how Face ID protects your privacy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tlRPZIFWj-E?si=XjP_TIlsomQljRQZ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the 30-second video ad, an iMessage notification appears on a girl's iPhone 15 placed on a dining table, while she is in another room. Nosy family members attempt to unlock the device to read the message, but Face ID prevents them from doing so.<br/>
<br/>
To prevent messages from being previewed on the Lock Screen without Face ID, open the Settings app, tap Notifications → Show Previews, and select When Unlocked.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/face-id/">Face ID</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/iphone-15-face-id-ad-nice-try/">Apple Promotes Face ID in New iPhone 15 Ad Called &#039;Nice Try!&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-promotes-face-id-in-new-iphone-15-ad-called-nice-try.2422421/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Posts Vision Pro Job Listings in Australia, China, and Japan Following UK Last Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-vision-pro-job-listings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-posts-vision-pro-job-listings-in-australia-china-and-japan-following-uk-last-year.2422419/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:17:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-vision-pro-job-listings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this week posted identical job listings related to the Vision Pro in <a href="https://jobs.apple.com/en-us/details/200543179/sales-briefing-experience-specialist-apple-vision-pro?team=SLDEV">Australia</a>, <a href="https://jobs.apple.com/en-us/details/200539692/briefing-experience-specialist-apple-vision-pro">China</a>, and <a href="https://jobs.apple.com/en-us/details/200543180/briefing-experience-specialist-apple-vision-pro?team=SLDEV">Japan</a>, as international availability of the headset looms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Apple is looking to hire a so-called "Briefing Experience Specialist" in all three countries. This is a sales position that will involve demonstrating the Vision Pro's capabilities to business/enterprise customers, according to the job listing.<br/>
<br/>
"You will design and deliver demonstrations that present the capabilities of the product and its revolutionary new technology," the job listing says. "You will also showcase solutions, representative use cases, and transformative user workflows that inspire customer investment in the technology, the visionOS platform, and the product itself."<br/>
<br/>
Apple posted the <a href="https://www.glassdoor.co.uk/job-listing/briefing-experience-specialist-apple-vision-pro-apple-JV_IC2671300_KO0,47_KE48,53.htm?jl=1008933059382">same job listing</a> for the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.imore.com/apple/uk-may-be-next-vision-pro-launch-location-as-briefing-experience-specialist-role-at-apple-opens-up">in the U.K. last year</a>, but the headset remains available in the U.S. only following its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-launch-day/">February 2 launch</a>.<br/>
<br/>
On its website, Apple says the Vision Pro will launch in more countries later this year, but the company has not provided a more specific timeframe, or indicated exactly where the headset will become available next. Last month, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said he believed the Vision Pro would launch internationally <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">before Apple's annual developers conference WWDC</a>, which typically takes place in the first week of June.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> contributor Aaron Perris recently obtained information that suggests Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">preparing to expand the Vision Pro</a> to Australia, Canada, China, France, Germany, Japan, Singapore, South Korea, and the U.K. at a minimum, and the "Briefing Experience Specialist" job listings have now been posted in at least four of those countries.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Thanks, Alicia!</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-vision-pro-job-listings/">Apple Posts Vision Pro Job Listings in Australia, China, and Japan Following UK Last Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-posts-vision-pro-job-listings-in-australia-china-and-japan-following-uk-last-year.2422419/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>UPS Worker Accused of Stealing and Reselling Apple Products Worth Over &#36;1 Million</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/ups-worker-apple-product-theft/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ups-worker-accused-of-stealing-and-reselling-apple-products-worth-over-1-million.2422410/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:17:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/ups-worker-apple-product-theft/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A former UPS worker located in Winnipeg, Canada has been accused of stealing Apple products valued at more than &#36;1.3 million, and reselling them for profit.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912516" /><br/>
According to Canada's <em><a href="https://globalnews.ca/news/10370850/former-ups-worker-charged-stolen-apple-products/">Global News</a></em> and the <em><a href="https://www.winnipegfreepress.com/breakingnews/2024/03/19/former-ups-worker-accused-of-stealing-reselling-apple-electronics-worth-more-than-1-3-m">Winnipeg Free Press</a></em>, UPS worker Orville Beltrano stole approximately 866 Apple devices from the warehouse where he had worked since 2013. Beltrano served as a supervisor at the location, and he was selling the products that he swiped on Kijiji.<br/>
<br/>
Between September 2023 and January 2024, Beltrano deposited more than &#36;232,000 in his bank accounts. He was fired by UPS on January 22, and arrested the same day. In his home and vehicle, investigators found &#36;9,000 in cash, a Mac laptop, and jewelry valued at over &#36;9,000.<br/>
<br/>
Beltrano admitted to stealing Apple products and jewelry from UPS, and said that he used the money to purchase a home worth &#36;680,000 and to pay off a &#36;60,000 Audi hatchback purchased in 2021. He has been charged with theft over &#36;5,000, theft under &#36;5,000, possession of property obtained by crime over &#36;5,000, and possession of the proceeds of crime.<br/>
<br/>
The theft was discovered after UPS launched an investigation in December to determine why so many Apple devices were disappearing from the warehouse in Winnipeg. Surveillance cameras were installed, and Beltrano was found to be stealing products from pallets that were supposed to be shipped to Ontario. He allegedly stole more 120 iPhones in a single shift in January 2024.<br/>
<br/>
Prosecutors have asked the court to approve the seizure of Beltrano's house, cash, bank accounts, and vehicle.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/ups-worker-apple-product-theft/">UPS Worker Accused of Stealing and Reselling Apple Products Worth Over &#36;1 Million</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ups-worker-accused-of-stealing-and-reselling-apple-products-worth-over-1-million.2422410/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Check Out This Functional 3D Printed Macintosh</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/functional-3d-printed-macintosh/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-functional-3d-printed-macintosh.2422404/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:50:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/functional-3d-printed-macintosh/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Designer Kevin Noki recently spent months creating his own homemade, functional Macintosh built from the ground up, which he dubbed the "Brewintosh." Designed to look like the Macintosh Plus, the machine Noki crafted features a 3D printed exterior and components, and it works like the real deal.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="3D Printed Full-Size Macintosh - The Brewintosh" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7N9oz4Ylzm4" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
In a 47-minute video, Noki walks through the process that he used to create the device. As <em><a href="https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2024/03/3d-printed-mac-replica-is-a-maker-masterwork-inside-an-entirely-accurate-shell/">Ars Technica</a></em> points out, Noki went completed more than 29 complex steps, each of which was a major task on its own. He started out by measuring every single surface and angle of a Macintosh Plus, modeling it in AutoDesk Fusion 360, and then printing the parts, putting them together, filling gaps, sanding, and texturing.<br/>
<br/>
He modified a 10-inch thrift store screen to have LED backlighting and a dimmer knob, he crafted a power assembly, built in connectors, speakers, and other hardware, and designed a Mini vMac emulator using Linux. The whole process is fascinating to watch.<br/>
<br/>
The Mac Plus is the exact right size and texture, it supports 3.5-inch disks, it supports appropriate Apple keyboards and mice, and has every other detail you would expect from a real Mac. Printing the components took over 48 hours, and the whole project spanned 40 weeks.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/functional-3d-printed-macintosh/">Check Out This Functional 3D Printed Macintosh</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-functional-3d-printed-macintosh.2422404/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Facing Imminent U.S. Antitrust Lawsuit</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-facing-imminent-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-facing-imminent-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit.2422399/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:10:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-facing-imminent-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Justice Department is preparing to sue Apple for violating antitrust law as soon as Thursday, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-03-20/doj-to-sue-apple-for-antitrust-violations-as-soon-as-thursday">Bloomberg</a></em>. The lawsuit will be the culmination of an investigation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/23/doj-tech-company-antitrust-review/">that initially started</a> in 2019 as an antitrust review of major technology companies. U.S. regulators have already sued Google, Meta, and Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912524" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-sizes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" /><br/>
Over the last several years, Apple officials have met with the DoJ multiple times, and the investigation has covered everything from iMessage to ad practices. Some of what the DoJ has looked into:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>How the Apple Watch works better with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> than other smart watches do.</li><br/>
 	<li>How Apple locks competitors out of iMessage.</li><br/>
 	<li>How Apple blocks financial firms from offering tap-to-pay services similar to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>Whether Apple favors its own apps and services over those provided by third-party developers.</li><br/>
 	<li>How Apple has blocked cloud gaming apps from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>How Apple restricts the ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌'s location services from devices that compete with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a>.</li><br/>
 	<li>How App Tracking Transparency impacted the collection of advertising data.</li><br/>
 	<li>In-app purchase fees collected by Apple.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Apple competitors like Tile, Beeper, Basecamp, Meta, and Spotify have had discussions with antitrust investigators to voice their complaints about Apple's practices, as have big banks. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, the DoJ plans to argue that Apple has used illegal practices to maintain a dominant market position, blocking competitors from hardware and software features on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Back in 2020, a United States House Judiciary Subcommittee investigation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/06/us-antitrust-report-apple-recommendations/">concluded that</a> Apple, Meta, Google, and Amazon have the "kinds of monopolies" last seen in "the era of oil barons and railroad tycoons." The subcommittee recommended new antitrust law, but the DoJ opted to target Google before going after Apple because Apple was embroiled in an antitrust lawsuit with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in iOS 17.4 had to make sweeping changes to the way the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; operates in the European Union to comply with the Digital Markets Act, and it was also recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">fined &#36;2 billion</a> in Europe for anti-competitive behavior against rival music services.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-facing-imminent-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit/">Apple Facing Imminent U.S. Antitrust Lawsuit</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-facing-imminent-u-s-antitrust-lawsuit.2422399/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games to Charge 12% Fee for App Sales From Alternative iPhone Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/epic-games-store-fee/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-to-charge-12-fee-for-app-sales-from-alternative-iphone-store.2422393/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:32:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/epic-games-store-fee/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> in February said that it would <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/epic-games-store-ios-eu/">launch an Epic Games Store</a> on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> in the European Union, and today the company held an event at the Game Developers Conference (GDC) to provide additional information on the upcoming store debut and the fees that it will charge for apps distributed through its marketplace (via <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/03/20/epic-will-take-12-cut-of-epic-games-store-sales-when-it-launches-on-iphone-this-year/">9to5Mac</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/epic-games-store-ios.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942385" /><br/>
For games distributed through the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store, Epic will collect a 12 percent share of revenue, which is the same fee that it charges on Windows and Mac machines. Apps will get 100 percent of the revenue they earn for the first six months, with Epic taking no cut, and there are no fees for apps that offer in-game purchases and use their own payment processing method.<br/>
<br/>
A game sold through the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store will need to pay both Epic's 12 percent fee, and Apple's 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee (CTF) for each "first annual" install after one million installs. Apps distributed through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> under Apple's updated EU business terms will pay the CTF and a commission of 10 to 17 percent, down from the standard 15 to 30 percent cut that Apple takes.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;App Store&zwnj; apps making under &#36;1 million annually will pay 10 percent under the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; Small Business Program, and that's also the fee that Apple charges for subscriptions that customers keep for over a year. More successful apps earning over &#36;1 million and new subscriptions are subject to a 17 percent fee. Note that Apple also charges an additional three percent fee for using the in-app purchase payment system, so developers who distribute through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; and use in-app purchases will pay 13 to 20 percent.<br/>
<br/>
As an example, an app with fewer than one million downloads that is distributed through the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; under the new business terms would pay the CTF and 10 percent fee, a total ultimately lower than the CTF + 12 percent fee that the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store would collect. From &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;: <br/>
<blockquote>"The Epic Games Store has a 88/12 revenue split for developers who distribute paid-for apps on PC and Mac and that will continue on mobile platforms. Developers do not pay Epic anything to distribute free apps. If developers offer in-app purchases, they can choose to either use our payment processing system with the 88/12 revenue share or use a third party payment processor and keep 100% of that revenue, just like they do today."</blockquote>Epic Games CEO Tim Sweeney has called Apple's EU changes and fees a "devious new instance of Malicious Compliance" and has promised that &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; will continue to "argue to the courts and regulators that Apple is breaking the law" even as it prepares to launch the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store. <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store is set to come to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; in the European Union before the end of 2024. It will not be available in the United States and other countries.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/epic-games-store-fee/">Epic Games to Charge 12% Fee for App Sales From Alternative iPhone Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-to-charge-12-fee-for-app-sales-from-alternative-iphone-store.2422393/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta, Microsoft, X and Match Join Epic Games in Protesting Fees for Non-App Store Purchase Links</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/microsoft-meta-app-store-fee-amicus-brief/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-microsoft-x-and-match-join-epic-games-in-protesting-fees-for-non-app-store-purchase-links.2422385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 12:04:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/microsoft-meta-app-store-fee-amicus-brief/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Epic Games vs. Apple</category>
		<category>Meta</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta, Microsoft, X, and Match today joined <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> to protest the way Apple complied with a court ruling requiring it to walk back its anti-steering rules. In an amicus brief in support of &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; (via <em><a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/apple-faces-legal-protest-from-meta-microsoft-x-and-match-7fe41d0f">The Wall Street Journal</a></em>), the four companies said that the fees Apple is charging are too high, and that there are too many restrictions on how developers link to their websites. "The Apple Plan comports with neither the letter nor the spirit of this Court's mandate," reads the brief.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800065" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/app-store-blue-banner-epic-1.jpg" alt="" width="1794" height="1009" /><br/>
For context, Apple was ordered to change its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules in 2021 as part of the decision in the &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; case. The judge took issue with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/09/10/epic-games-vs-apple-decision/">the anti-steering guidelines</a> that kept apps from directing consumers to lower prices available outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Apple delayed implementing the changes while it attempted to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/apple-epic-appeal-supreme-court/">appeal the ruling</a>, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/supreme-court-declines-to-hear-apple-vs-epic-case/">the appeal was not successful</a> and Apple had to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/us-app-store-alternative-purchase-option/">update its rules</a> in January.<br/>
<br/>
Developers are now allowed to include a single link in their app, with that link going to a website where customers can make a purchase without using the in-app purchase system. Apple is still collecting commission for purchases made this way, requiring developers to pay between 12 and 27 percent (three percent lower than the standard 15/30 fee).<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/epic-games-apple-unjustified-fees/">last week told the court</a> that Apple has not complied with the order, and that the Cupertino company should be held in contempt of court. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; said that Apple's implementation makes links "commercially unusable" due to the fee and the "accompanying web of restrictions."<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft, Meta, X, and Match further complained that Apple is not allowing apps to include "even the most basic information" about alternative purchase options. Apple does not allow apps to let customers know about how to receive a discount by purchasing directly from a website, for example.<br/>
<br/>
Meta said that it should be able to direct users to the web to pay for boosted posts to avoid Apple's fee, and Microsoft complained that Apple's rules limit options for providing subscriptions and discounts. X, formerly Twitter, said that Apple's 27 percent fee eliminates incentives to include an external link, while Match claimed that the rules prevent price competition for digital transactions.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in January claimed that it was in full compliance with the injunction, and that it has given developers a way to inform customers about alternative purchase mechanisms both in their apps and outside of their apps.<br/>
<br/>
The amicus brief filed today supports &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj;' recent filing. &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; has asked the court to force Apple to bring its policies into compliance with the injunction, so it will be up to the court to decide whether Apple's rule change does enough to satisfy the requirements of the initial judgment.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games-vs-apple/">Epic Games vs. Apple</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/meta/">Meta</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/microsoft-meta-app-store-fee-amicus-brief/">Meta, Microsoft, X and Match Join Epic Games in Protesting Fees for Non-App Store Purchase Links</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-microsoft-x-and-match-join-epic-games-in-protesting-fees-for-non-app-store-purchase-links.2422385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Pro Rumored to Feature Thinner Bezels Than Previous Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-models-thinner-bezels-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-rumored-to-feature-thinner-bezels-than-previous-models.2422383/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 11:47:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-models-thinner-bezels-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The next-generation iPad Pro models will feature thinner bezels around the screen compared to previous models, according to a rumor shared today by a previously-accurate <a href="https://weibo.com/5143897135/O5VxfdQGB">leaker known as "Instant Digital"</a> on Chinese social media platform Weibo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/M3-iPad-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917548" /><br/>
The leaker claimed that the next 11-inch and 12.9-inch iPad Pro models will have 7.12mm and 7.08mm bezels, respectively, when excluding the metal edges of the devices. If these measurements are accurate, the bezels would be around 10% to 15% thinner than on previous iPad Pro models released between 2018 and 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Other key new features rumored for the next iPad Pro models include Apple's latest M3 chip, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/upcoming-oled-ipad-pro-thinner/">thinner enclosure</a>, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/08/ipad-air-ipad-pro-landscape-facetime-camera/">landscape front camera</a>, rear camera design tweaks, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">potentially MagSafe wireless charging</a>. New accessories are also expected, including an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">updated Magic Keyboard</a> with a partly-aluminum enclosure and an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/05/new-apple-pencil-to-launch-this-month/">updated Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"Instant Digital" has a mostly-accurate track record with Apple rumors over the past year. The account was correct about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted rear glass on the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">yellow color option</a> for the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus, and more, but it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/">incorrectly said</a> the iPad Air would receive a hardware update last year.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad Pro models should be announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-likely-to-begin-shipping-in-april/">in late March or early April</a>, according to Ross Young, CEO of Display Supply Chain Consultants. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/">Tuesday, March 26</a> has been specifically rumored as a potential iPad Pro announcement date.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to update the 10.9-inch iPad Air, and release an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/10/12-9-inch-ipad-air-display-shipments/">all-new 12.9-inch iPad Air</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-models-thinner-bezels-rumor/">New iPad Pro Rumored to Feature Thinner Bezels Than Previous Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-rumored-to-feature-thinner-bezels-than-previous-models.2422383/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Leadership Talks iPhone While Riding Golf Cart Around Apple Park</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-park-golf-cart-interview/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leadership-talks-iphone-while-riding-golf-cart-around-apple-park.2422366/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:47:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-park-golf-cart-interview/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Park</category>
		<category>Greg Joswiak</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's marketing chief Greg Joswiak, vice president of iPhone marketing Kaiann Drance, and a few other senior employees at the company recently participated in a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3LyW9gVstuE">ride-along interview</a> with YouTube video creator Brian Tong.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Park-Brian-Tong.jpg" alt="" width="1916" height="1076" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942319" /><em>Greg Joswiak talks with Brian Tong in a golf cart ride at Apple Park</em></div><br/>
The interview took place in a golf cart driving around Apple Park, with various employees hopping in and out to talk with Tong along the way.<br/>
<br/>
The video provides an update on the "state of the iPhone," with Joswiak and others discussing the device's past, present, and future. Apple also once again <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/01/apple-ai-details-coming-later-this-year/">hinted at AI-related announcements later this year</a>, with the company widely expected to announce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">iOS 18 with new generative AI features</a> at Apple's developers conference WWDC in June.<br/>
<br/>
The video is worth a watch if you are an iPhone enthusiast, or if you simply want to see Joswiak pretend to get hit by a golf cart.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3LyW9gVstuE?si=JodXymwmE82aU3ih" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/greg-joswiak/">Greg Joswiak</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-park-golf-cart-interview/">Apple Leadership Talks iPhone While Riding Golf Cart Around Apple Park</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leadership-talks-iphone-while-riding-golf-cart-around-apple-park.2422366/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches All-in-One &#039;Manuals, Specs, and Downloads&#039; Website</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-manuals-specs-downloads-website/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-all-in-one-manuals-specs-and-downloads-website.2422363/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 08:12:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-manuals-specs-downloads-website/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Support</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently added a <a href="https://support.apple.com/docs">new "Documentation" page</a> to its website that provides links to user guides, repair manuals, tech specs, software downloads, and more for a variety of products. Some of this information was previously found across separate pages on Apple's website, and it has now been combined in one place for convenient access.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/Apple-Support-App-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908138" /><br/>
The page includes categories for the Mac, iPhone, iPad, iPod, Vision Pro, Apple Watch, Apple TV, AirPods, HomePod, displays like the Studio Display and Pro Display XDR, accessories like the Apple Pencil and Magic Keyboard, and software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Documentation-Website.jpg" alt="" width="1948" height="1010" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942288" /><br/>
There is also a search tool on the page that provides links to support documents and other relevant information based on the keywords entered.<br/>
<br/>
The new page was earlier spotted by <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/etc/support/entry-46403.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a>, and it may be worth bookmarking for reference purposes.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-support/">Apple Support</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/apple-manuals-specs-downloads-website/">Apple Launches All-in-One &#039;Manuals, Specs, and Downloads&#039; Website</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-all-in-one-manuals-specs-and-downloads-website.2422363/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon&#039;s Prime Day &#039;Big Spring Sale&#039; Debuts Big Discounts on Apple Devices, Anker Accessories, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/amazons-big-spring-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-prime-day-big-spring-sale-debuts-big-discounts-on-apple-devices-anker-accessories-and-more.2422359/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 07:50:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/amazons-big-spring-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon this week is hosting a "<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fevents%2Fbigspringsale%2F%3F_encoding%3DUTF8%26pd_rd_w%3DurmHl%26content-id%3Damzn1.sym.6776e672-6a82-4766-9fe9-bd329e7e4096%26pf_rd_p%3D6776e672-6a82-4766-9fe9-bd329e7e4096%26pf_rd_r%3D8TV83XNJ1Y2849SC9MMD%26pd_rd_wg%3Dyuc7v%26pd_rd_r%3Dbb4d17d2-52a8-4e26-bfab-5af463fe1948">Big Spring Sale</a>," which includes deals and offers on everything from Apple devices to clothes, kitchen electronics, furniture, and much more. The new event is set to run through March 25, so you'll have a few days of discounts to shop, with new markdowns appearing every day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Amazons-Big-Spring-Sale10-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-942382" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
We're focusing on the tech-related discounts during the Big Spring Sale, and in the first list below you can find all of the highlights of the electronics category for the event. You'll also find specific deals on iPads and AirPods further down, as well as the best Anker and Jackery deals. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fevents%2Fbigspringsale%2F%3F_encoding%3DUTF8%26pd_rd_w%3DurmHl%26content-id%3Damzn1.sym.6776e672-6a82-4766-9fe9-bd329e7e4096%26pf_rd_p%3D6776e672-6a82-4766-9fe9-bd329e7e4096%26pf_rd_r%3D8TV83XNJ1Y2849SC9MMD%26pd_rd_wg%3Dyuc7v%26pd_rd_r%3Dbb4d17d2-52a8-4e26-bfab-5af463fe1948"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SITEWIDE DEALS</div>Amazon's Big Spring Sale</div></a></div><ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2F95934351%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_28_95934351_dt_sl5_28">Sonos Devices</a> - Up to 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2F77eeeae9%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3D4YGZQFB4HTRJX9MQN4ZM%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_13_77eeeae9_dt_sl5_28">Anker</a> - Up to 43% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2Ffbf69055%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_2_fbf69055_dt_sl5_28">Fire TV Devices</a> - Up to 40% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2F2da8637c%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_5_2da8637c_dt_sl5_28">Samsung Monitors</a> - Up to 43% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2F31acfc76%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_6_31acfc76_dt_sl5_28">Bose Headphones and Speakers</a> - Up to 17% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2Ffb177427%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_8_fb177427_dt_sl5_28">Soundcore Headphones</a> - Up to 50% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2Feea3cc70%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_20_eea3cc70_dt_sl5_28">Google Security Cameras and Doorbells</a> - Up to 22% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdeal%2F219f5362%3FshowVariations%3Dtrue%26pf_rd_r%3DRJSDT2J2WJ7XRT56WMEB%26pf_rd_t%3DEvents%26pf_rd_i%3Dbigspringsale%26pf_rd_p%3Dff0979e8-0a0e-48a0-af51-1d83660a6328%26pf_rd_s%3Dslot-5%26ref%3Ddlx_bigsp_gd_dcl_img_35_219f5362_dt_sl5_28">JBL Speakers</a> - Up to 15% off</li></ul><h2>Apple</h2><br/>
<h3>AirPods</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/airpods-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942253" /><br/>
Amazon has the AirPods 2 for &#36;99.00, down from &#36;129.00, and the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00. In regards to the latter deal, this is a match of the all-time low price and right now only Amazon has the deal.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;99.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;69 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><h3>Apple Pencil 2</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-pencil-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942252" /><br/>
The all-time low price on the Apple Pencil 2 has returned for the Big Spring Sale, available for &#36;79.00 on Amazon, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00</div></a></div><h3>iPad</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942251" /><br/>
Both the 9th and 10th generation iPads are seeing all-time low prices on Amazon this week, starting at &#36;249.00 for the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th gen tablet and reaching up to &#36;100 off select models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91TLNJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMW%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><h3>iPad Air</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/ipad-air-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942250" /><br/>
For the iPad Air, you can get every Wi-Fi model on sale for a record low price on Amazon. These tablets are reaching up to &#36;150 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3JJT5D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3H386P%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;149 OFF</div>iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/anker-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942249" /><br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;63.99, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1710770307988">Soundcore Motion X600 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;149.98, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV66XQ66">Nano Portable Charger with Built-In Lightning Connector</a> - &#36;18.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;157.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1710942469892">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;109.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1770-Powerhouse%2Fdp%2FB099Z2RDS5%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F1200 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,098.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,399.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Foldable-MacBook%2Fdp%2FB09C5RG6KV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;33.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;55.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;45.99, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;75.00, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul><h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/jackery-spring-sale.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942248" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2D47DQD1FRWW3_1710770158851">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;449.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IF0PS8UT4GJ7_1710770002372">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;698.99, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3S52LG1288F1D_1710770092703">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/amazons-big-spring-sale/">Amazon&#039;s Prime Day &#039;Big Spring Sale&#039; Debuts Big Discounts on Apple Devices, Anker Accessories, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazons-prime-day-big-spring-sale-debuts-big-discounts-on-apple-devices-anker-accessories-and-more.2422359/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Tim Cook Visits China Ahead of New Apple Store Opening in Shanghai</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/tim-cook-visits-shanghai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-visits-china-ahead-of-new-apple-store-opening-in-shanghai.2422356/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:54:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/tim-cook-visits-shanghai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO Tim Cook is touring Shanghai, China this week, meeting with retail employees, suppliers, developers, the film industry, and others. He has been <a href="https://weibo.com/timcook">sharing photos</a> from his trip on Chinese social media platform Weibo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Tim-Cook-Shanghai.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="702" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942239" /><br/>
Cook's visit is timed with the upcoming grand opening of Apple's new Jing'an store in Shanghai on Thursday, March 21 at 7 p.m. local time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple provided more details about the store <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/03/apple-jingan-to-welcome-its-first-customers-thursday-march-21-in-shanghai/">in a recent press release</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Jingan.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942235" /><br/>
"Located next to the landmark Jing'an Temple, Apple Jing'an is a must-see destination in Shanghai," said Apple. "Approaching the store through a grove of maple trees that line the upper plaza, visitors are treated to a stunning view of the temple. As customers descend down the stairs, they pass by terracing, double-curved walls that extend forward in a circle to form amphitheater seating that will host Today at Apple sessions specially created for Apple Jing'an to celebrate the community and its creators."<br/>
<br/>
A custom wallpaper with a flower-like Apple logo is available for download for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/retail/jingan/">on the store's page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-Jingan-Wallpaper.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-942237" /><br/>
Those who attend the grand opening of Apple Jing'an will receive a custom tote bag, pin, and Apple logo sticker, according to <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/p/exploring-apple-jingan">Michael Steeber's weekly newsletter</a> about Apple's retail stores. His newsletter provides a closer look at the store's design.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/tim-cook-visits-shanghai/">Tim Cook Visits China Ahead of New Apple Store Opening in Shanghai</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tim-cook-visits-china-ahead-of-new-apple-store-opening-in-shanghai.2422356/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPad Pro Rumored to Have Matte Screen Option Like Studio Display&#039;s Nano-Texture Glass</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-rumored-to-have-matte-screen-option-like-studio-displays-nano-texture-glass.2422354/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 06:21:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		<category>2024 iPad Air</category>
		<category>Instant Digital</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models will be offered with a matte display option for the first time, according to the Weibo leaker known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Pro-Matte-Display-Feature-1.6.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-942196" /><br/>
The Weibo user explained that the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;'s new matte display option will be offered in addition to the standard, glossy glass finish. It apparently features -4° to +29° of haze and may tout some kind of blue-light blocking technology to help protect the eyes. Matte screen protectors for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> have become popular, so it is possible that Apple is trying to offer such an option at the point of purchase for those who want it.<br/>
<br/>
It is not known if the matte display option will be "nano-texture" glass like on the Pro Display XDR and Studio Display, but it seems plausible. Nano-texture glass is effectively a matte finish that scatters light to minimize glare, which is ideal in environments with bright light sources. While matte screen coatings effectively reduce reflections, they also make the image slightly more dull and hazy. Nano-texture glass features an etched surface to help preserve image quality.<br/>
<br/>
Nano-texture glass has only been offered on desktop displays so far. It is harder to clean owing to its textured surface that grips oil and debris more tightly, and Apple cautions that it should only be cleaned with a polishing cloth made with soft, non-abrasive material. It is not clear how a matte display on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; would hold up to fingerprints as a result. <br/>
<br/>
The matte display option may also be available on the next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, but the leaker could not confirm if this will be the case. They added that new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/18/new-ipads-march-26-launch-date-rumor/">announced next week</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Instant Digital said that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/19/iphone-17-anti-reflective-display/">will feature an anti-reflective display</a> that is more scratch-resistant than Apple's Ceramic Shield found on recent models. It is not apparent if this technology is related to the new matte display option for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, but it is a possibility.<br/>
<br/>
Instant Digital has a mixed track record in terms of revealing accurate information about Apple's plans, but their claims are worth paying attention to. The source was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/03/iphone-14-new-color-rumor/">first to report</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>'s Yellow spring refresh in 2023, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/04/future-iphone-could-capture-spatial-photos-videos/">Spatial Video</a> capture on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/04/apple-watch-series-9-basically-unchanged/">minor hardware update</a>, as well as being the only source of the only rumor claiming that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus would feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/iphone-15-and-15-plus-frosted-glass-rumor/">frosted back glass</a>. However, they also made claims about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/25/ios-17-lock-screen-apple-music-rumors/">several iOS 17 features</a> and the release of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/10/ipad-air-6-rumored-to-launch-in-october/">new iPad Air in October 2023</a> that did not pan out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-ipad-air/">2024 iPad Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instant-digital/">Instant Digital</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/new-ipad-pro-to-gain-matte-option/">New iPad Pro Rumored to Have Matte Screen Option Like Studio Display&#039;s Nano-Texture Glass</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ipad-pro-rumored-to-have-matte-screen-option-like-studio-displays-nano-texture-glass.2422354/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>EU Antitrust Chief Warns Apple About App Store Fees and Safety Warnings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/eu-antitrust-chief-warns-apple-app-store-fees/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-antitrust-chief-warns-apple-about-app-store-fees-and-safety-warnings.2422345/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 04:15:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/eu-antitrust-chief-warns-apple-app-store-fees/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Key parts of Apple's compliance with the Digital Markets Act (DMA) are set to be investigated by European regulators based on developer feedback, the EU's antitrust chief warned on Tuesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/App-Store-vs-EU-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932826" /><br/>
In an interview with <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/eus-vestager-warns-about-apple-meta-fees-disparaging-rival-products-2024-03-19/">Reuters</a></em>, the European Commission's Executive Vice-President Margrethe Vestager said that Apple's introduction of new fees was already being looked at as a potential attempt to dissuade developers from using alternative app stores.<br/>
<blockquote>"There are things that we take a keen interest in, for instance, if the new Apple fee structure will de facto not make it in any way attractive to use the benefits of the DMA. That kind of thing is what we will be investigating," she told Reuters.</blockquote>Apple enabled alternative app stores in the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">earlier this month</a>, allowing third-party app stores to offer a catalog of other developers' apps as well as the marketplace developer's own apps. Apple also has a new fee structure as part of the change that has already come under fire from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/spotify-epic-games-apple-dma-complaint/">several developers and EU associations</a>. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, Vestager warned Apple and other companies against discouraging users from switching to other app marketplaces by disparaging them, saying this kind of behaviour could trigger an investigation. Apple has already claimed some of the DMA-enforced changes could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/apple-whitepaper-alternative-app-marketplaces/">expose users to security risks</a> that they are otherwise protected against when using the App Store.<br/>
<blockquote>"I would think of it as unwise to say that the services are not safe to use, because that has nothing to do with the DMA," said Vestager. "The DMA is there to open the market for other service providers to get to you and how your service provider of your operating system, how they will make sure that it is safe is for them to decide."<br/>
<br/>
"And of course, if we see or get the suspicion that this is in order to say that someone else are not doing their job of course, we might take initiatives to look into that," she added.</blockquote>Vestager said feedback from developers was key to whether she would launch investigations into companies that must comply with the DMA. Asked whether she had received any comments from third parties, she replied: "Quite a lot."<br/>
<br/>
Apple's app ecosystem changes in the European Union went into effect with the launch of iOS 17.4 on March 6. Apple has since been tweaking the app ecosystem rules that it introduced based on developer feedback and discussions with EU regulators. <br/>
<br/>
For example, third-party app stores are now able to offer apps <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-announces-app-downloads-from-websites/">directly from their own catalog</a>, and developers will soon be able to distribute apps directly from their websites as long as they meet Apple's requirements. <br/>
<br/>
Apple says it is also working out a solution that would prevent its 0.50 euro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/apple-eu-fees-could-bankrupt-app-developers/">Core Technology Fee (CTF)</a> from bankrupting developers if their free app goes viral.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/eu-antitrust-chief-warns-apple-app-store-fees/">EU Antitrust Chief Warns Apple About App Store Fees and Safety Warnings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/eu-antitrust-chief-warns-apple-about-app-store-fees-and-safety-warnings.2422345/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
