<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 04:03:27 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google, European Telecoms Giants Call on EU to Force Open iMessage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/google-asks-eu-to-force-open-imessage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-european-telecoms-giants-call-on-eu-to-force-open-imessage.2410274/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:58:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/google-asks-eu-to-force-open-imessage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google and European telecom groups have urged EU regulators to designate iMessage a "core" service that would force Apple to make the communications platform interoperable with competing chat services, reports the <em><a href="https://www.ft.com/content/ec2ec699-a91c-4389-b1a9-ae06dca836d5">Financial Times</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
In a letter sent to the European Commission, the EU's executive body, the signatories including Google and some of Europe's largest telecoms operators claimed that Apple's service meets the qualitative thresholds of the act, and should therefore be captured by the rules to "benefit European consumers and businesses."<br/>
<br/>
The "fundamental nature" of iMessage as "an important gateway between business users and their customers is without doubt justification for Apple’s designation as gatekeeper for its iMessage service," argued Google, Vodafone, Deutsche Telekom, Telefónica and Orange in the letter. They said consumers would be better off as a result of the designation because "enriched messaging" is only available between Apple users, according to the report.<br/>
<br/>
Apple declined to comment on the report, but pointed to an earlier statement that said: <blockquote>"iMessage is a great service that Apple users love because it provides an easy way to communicate with friends and family while offering industry-leading privacy and security protections.<br/>
<br/>
"Consumers today have access to a wide variety of messaging apps, and often use many at once, which reflects how easy it is to switch between them. iMessage is designed and marketed for personal consumer communications, and we look forward to explaining to the commission why iMessage is outside the scope of the DMA."</blockquote>Apple in September <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/05/imessage-isnt-popular-enough-for-regulation/">contested</a> the EU regulator labeling them as "gatekeepers" ahead of the publication of the first list of services to be regulated by the Digital Markets Act (DMA). The legislation introduces new rules that apply to services considered to be core platform services and forces them to open up their various services and platforms to other companies and developers. For example, Apple could be forced to allow third-party companies and rival apps like Meta's WhatsApp to integrate directly with iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
However, Apple argued that iMessage does not meet the number of users required for the DMA's rules to apply, and should not be obliged to comply with it. "iMessage does not constitute an important gateway in the union for business users to reach end users due to its small scale relative to other messaging services," Apple reportedly told the commission.<br/>
<br/>
Analysts estimate that iMessage has as many as one billion users around the world, but Apple has not disclosed any official numbers about the service for several years. Whether iMessage will be included on the EU's initial list of gatekeeper services will depend on how it defines the market in which it operates.<br/>
<br/>
The EU's investigation into iMessage is ongoing, and the European Commission has until February to come to a decision. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/google-asks-eu-to-force-open-imessage/">Google, European Telecoms Giants Call on EU to Force Open iMessage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-european-telecoms-giants-call-on-eu-to-force-open-imessage.2410274/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>8GB RAM on M3 MacBook Pro &#039;Analogous to 16GB&#039; on PCs, Claims Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/8gb-ram-m3-macbook-pro-like-16-gb-pc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-on-m3-macbook-pro-analogous-to-16gb-on-pcs-claims-apple.2410269/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2023 03:12:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/8gb-ram-m3-macbook-pro-like-16-gb-pc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the unveiling of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-m3-macbook-pros/">new MacBook Pro models last week</a>, Apple surprised some with the introduction of a base 14-inch MacBook Pro with M3 chip, which replaced the discontinued M2 13-inch MacBook Pro in Apple's Mac lineup. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/8gb-ram-mbp-bob-borchers.jpg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921580" /><br/>
Starting at &#36;1,599, the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro comes with 8GB of unified memory. That makes it &#36;300 more expensive than the &#36;1,299 starting price of the now-discontinued ‌M2‌ 13-inch MacBook Pro. Users can opt for 16GB or 24GB at checkout, but these configuration options cost an extra &#36;200 and &#36;400 at purchase, respectively, and cannot be upgraded at a later date because of Apple's unified memory architecture.<br/>
<br/>
This has left Apple open to criticism from users who argue that 8GB is not a sufficient amount of RAM for most creative professional workflows, and that 16GB should be the bare minimum for a machine that is marketed as "Pro," rather than an additional several hundred dollar outlay. <br/>
<br/>
In a recent interview with <a href="https://www.bilibili.com/video/BV16M411Q7BG/">Chinese ML engineer and content creator Lin YilYi</a>, Apple's VP of worldwide product marketing Bob Borchers has directly responded to this criticism. After YilYi characterized the base M3 MacBook Pro coming with 8GB of RAM as the "one major concern" of prospective buyers, Borchers replied:<br/>
<blockquote>Comparing our memory to other system's memory actually isn't equivalent, because of the fact that we have such an efficient use of memory, and we use memory compression, and we have a unified memory architecture. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Actually, 8GB on an M3 MacBook Pro is probably analogous to 16GB on other systems. We just happen to be able to use it much more efficiently.</strong> And so what I would say is I would have people come in and try what they want to do on their systems, and they will I think see incredible performance. If you look at the raw data and capabilities of these systems, it really is phenomenal. And this is the place where I think people need to see beyond the specs, and actually go and look beyond the capabilities, and listen to trusted people like you who have actually used the systems.<br/>
<br/>
People need to look beyond the specifications and actually go and understand how that technology is being used. That's the true test. </blockquote>While the 14-inch MacBook Pro with 8GB of unified memory is &#36;300 more expensive than the M2 13-inch MacBook Pro it replaces, there are a number of other benefits worth considering aside from the faster processor, such as the larger, brighter mini-LED Liquid Retina XDR display, support for 120Hz ProMotion refresh rates, and better battery life. Other improvements include additional ports, a better 1080p FaceTime HD camera, a six-speaker sound system, Wi-Fi 6E support, and Bluetooth 5.3.<br/>
<br/>
What do you think about the 8GB of unified memory supplied in the base configuration of M3 MacBook Pro. Does it suit your requirements, or make the "Pro" machine grossly underpowered for your use cases? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/8gb-ram-m3-macbook-pro-like-16-gb-pc/">8GB RAM on M3 MacBook Pro &#039;Analogous to 16GB&#039; on PCs, Claims Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/8gb-ram-on-m3-macbook-pro-analogous-to-16gb-on-pcs-claims-apple.2410269/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Offering Up to 50% Off AirPods With iPhone 14 or 14 Plus in India</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-up-to-half-off-airpods-with-iphone-14-india/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-up-to-50-off-airpods-with-iphone-14-or-14-plus-in-india.2410245/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 19:11:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-up-to-half-off-airpods-with-iphone-14-india/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>iPhone 14</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[From November 8 through November 14, Apple is offering customers in India up to 50% off select AirPods with the purchase of an <a href="https://www.apple.com/in/shop/buy-iphone/iphone-14">iPhone 14 or iPhone 14 Plus</a> in celebration of Diwali, as first reported by <a href="https://appleosophy.com/2023/11/07/apple-offering-up-to-50-off-on-airpods-with-an-iphone-14-purchase-in-india/"><em>Appleosophy</em>'s Pururaj Dutta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-14-AirPods.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921571" /><br/>
Apple is offering ₹9950 off the third-generation AirPods with a Lightning case, third-generation AirPods with a MagSafe case, or second-generation AirPods Pro with a MagSafe case when the headphones are purchased alongside an iPhone 14 or iPhone 14 Plus. The offer is available through Apple's online store and two retail stores in India.<br/>
<br/>
Full terms and conditions for the offer can be found <a href="https://www.apple.com/in/shop/browse/financing/terms#diwali">on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-up-to-half-off-airpods-with-iphone-14-india/">Apple Offering Up to 50% Off AirPods With iPhone 14 or 14 Plus in India</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-offering-up-to-50-off-airpods-with-iphone-14-or-14-plus-in-india.2410245/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Regulators Want More Control Oversight Into Apple Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-pay-oversight-cfpb/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-regulators-want-more-control-oversight-into-apple-pay.2410236/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 16:41:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-pay-oversight-cfpb/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) <a href="https://www.consumerfinance.gov/about-us/newsroom/cfpb-proposes-new-federal-oversight-of-big-tech-companies-and-other-providers-of-digital-wallets-and-payment-apps/">today proposed</a> new oversight requirements for technology companies like Apple that offer digital wallets and payment apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
According to the CFPB, payment services like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a> are growing in popularity, but the companies behind them are not subject to the same "supervisory examinations" that banks undergo.<br/>
<br/>
The newly proposed rule would require companies that handle more than five million transactions per year to adhere to the same rules as large banks, credit unions, and other financial institutions that are supervised by the CFPB.<br/>
<br/>
The CFPB claims that there have been an increasing number of complaints about tech companies in the consumer finance market, and it argues that examiners should be able to carefully scrutinize the activities of tech companies to ensure they are following the law.<br/>
<blockquote>Big Tech and other companies operating in consumer finance markets blur the traditional lines that have separated banking and payments from commercial activities. The CFPB has found that this blurring can put consumers at risk, especially when the same traditional banking safeguards, like deposit insurance, may not apply.<br/>
<br/>
Despite their impact on consumer finance, Big Tech and other nonbank companies operating in the payments sphere do not receive the same regulatory scrutiny and oversight as banks and credit unions. While the CFPB has enforcement authority over these companies, the CFPB has not previously had, inside many of these firms, examiners carefully scrutinizing their activities to ensure they are following the law and monitoring their executives.</blockquote><br/>
The CFPB wants to be able to conduct examinations of tech companies to make sure that they are following funds transfer, privacy, and consumer protection laws, and adhering to the same rules that banks must follow. If finalized, the proposed rule would give the Consumer Finance Protection Bureau more oversight into the financial services provided by companies like Apple and Google.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-pay-oversight-cfpb/">U.S. Regulators Want More Control Oversight Into Apple Pay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/u-s-regulators-want-more-control-oversight-into-apple-pay.2410236/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Invites Developers to Labs, Workshops and Vision Pro Sessions Held in November</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-developer-labs-workshops-november/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-invites-developers-to-labs-workshops-and-vision-pro-sessions-held-in-november.2410230/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 15:34:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-developer-labs-workshops-november/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=46ox5uok">today informed developers</a> about a number of new developer activities that are taking place in November, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> activities, additional Vision Pro labs, technology consultations, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757303" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-developer-banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1024" height="572" /><br/>
Apple in September began offering a range of "Meet with the Apple Experts" resources for developers, and the labs that are available this month are a continuation of that effort.<br/>
<br/>
There are a range of &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; activities where developers can learn about app discovery, engagement, custom product pages, subscription best practices, and more, plus opportunities for developers to try the Vision Pro at test labs in Cupertino, London, Munich, New York City, Shanghai, Singapore, Sydney, or Tokyo.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also offering activities focused on the Vision Pro, with the aim of helping developers learn to design and build apps and games for the headset. Developers can opt in to one-on-one consultations as well, getting advice on app design, new technologies, and other topics.<br/>
<br/>
The sessions are held in multiple time zones around the world, with some of them online and some in person. Apple's <a href="https://developer.apple.com/events/view/upcoming-events/?shouldHideClosedEvents=true">full list of Expert sessions</a> is available on its developer website.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-developer-labs-workshops-november/">Apple Invites Developers to Labs, Workshops and Vision Pro Sessions Held in November</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-invites-developers-to-labs-workshops-and-vision-pro-sessions-held-in-november.2410230/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>16-Inch M3 MacBook Pro Can Fast Charge Over USB-C With 240W Cable</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/16-inch-m3-macbook-pro-usb-c-fast-charge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/16-inch-m3-macbook-pro-can-fast-charge-over-usb-c-with-240w-cable.2410224/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:10:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/16-inch-m3-macbook-pro-usb-c-fast-charge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro models are able to fast charge at 140W over USB-C with a 240W USB-C cable, according to a support document <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212755">that was updated today</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/USB-C-60w-240w-charge-cable.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911066" /><br/>
2021 and 2022 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M-series chips are limited to faster 140W charging with the USB-C to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> 3 cable that Apple provides due to USB-C limitations, with the USB-C ports offering only up to 100W.<br/>
<br/>
The 2023 16-inch MacBook Pro can charge at the full 140W through &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; or through a USB-C port when a 140W+ power adapter is paired with a 240W cable, such as the 240W USB-C cable that Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MU2G3AM/A/240w-usb-c-charge-cable-2-m">began selling in September</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This update is only applicable to 16-inch models as 14-inch models can fast charge with a 96W charger, which USB-C ports were already able to provide for older machines.<br/>
<br/>
The option to fast charge a 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro at 140W over USB-C gives MacBook Pro owners more options when it comes to charging, though it is worth noting that the 240W cables are limited to USB 2.0 data transfer speeds. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/16-inch-m3-macbook-pro-usb-c-fast-charge/">16-Inch M3 MacBook Pro Can Fast Charge Over USB-C With 240W Cable</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/16-inch-m3-macbook-pro-can-fast-charge-over-usb-c-with-240w-cable.2410224/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the New M3 Pro MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-m3-pro-macbook-pro.2410222/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 14:02:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[MacBook Pro models with the M3 and M3 Pro chips are available starting today, and <em>MacRumors</em> videographer Dan Barbera was in New York so he popped over to the Grand Central station <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a> to pick up a new machine to demo to <em>MacRumors</em> readers.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wt94CT7YBL4" title="Apple’s NEW Space Black M3 Pro MacBook Pro Hands-On!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Dan purchased the M3 Pro MacBook Pro, which is a model that hasn't gotten a lot of attention. Apple provided reviewers with new Macs equipped with M3 and M3 Max chips, but we've heard little about the new M3 Pro. For context, the M3 Pro has 150GB/s memory bandwidth, while the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro had 200GB/s.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also tweaked the 12-core M3 Pro to have six performance cores and six efficiency cores rather than the eight performance cores and four efficiency cores the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chip has, which will impact overall performance. Dan's MacBook Pro is the 16-inch &#36;2,499 version with a 12-core CPU, 18-core GPU, 18GB Unified Memory, and a 512GB SSD.<br/>
<br/>
On Geekbench 6, the M3 Pro earned a single-core score of 3085 and a multi-core score of 15155. Comparatively, the 16-inch MacBook Pro with &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chip that has a 12-core CPU and 19-core GPU earned a single core score of 2643 and a multi-core score of 14206.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 Pro outperforms the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro, but not by a lot. Single-core speed is up 16.7 percent, while multi-core speed is up 6.7 percent. Note that this is one benchmark result so there could be some variance, but it is in line with what we expected.<br/>
<br/>
GPU performance is nearly flat. The M3 Pro MacBook Pro earned an OpenCL score of 51093, while the equivalent &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro version had a score of 50302 for a difference of 1.6 percent.<br/>
<br/>
Other than the M3 chips, there's not much new with the MacBook Pro models. The M3 Pro and M3 Max come in a Space Black color, which is much darker than expected in person, and it is indeed resistant to fingerprints as Apple promised.<br/>
<br/>
The only other new feature is a slight change to the brightness of the display, which is 600 nits for SDR content, up from 500 nits. You won't see any other changes, with the machine offering the same design and internal specs.<br/>
<br/>
We'll have a video of the M3 Max MacBook Pro coming up in the future, as those machines will start delivering to customers later this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-hands-on/">Hands-On With the New M3 Pro MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-m3-pro-macbook-pro.2410222/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.1.1 With Bug Fixes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1-with-bug-fixes.2410219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:52:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1.1, a minor update to the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; operating system that came out in September. &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1.1 comes a few weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1/">release of macOS Sonoma 14.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898568" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-feature-purple-green.jpg" alt="" width="2585" height="1454" /><br/>
The ‌‌&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1‌.1 update can be downloaded for free on all eligible Macs using the Software Update section of System Settings.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update includes bug fixes and security updates according to Apple.<blockquote>This update provides important bug fixes and security updates and is recommended for all users.<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices. For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222">https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</a></blockquote><br/>
More information on the features in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; can be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">found in our macOS Sonoma roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1/">Apple Releases macOS Sonoma 14.1.1 With Bug Fixes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-1-1-with-bug-fixes.2410219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases HomePod 17.1.1 Software With Fix for Siri Response Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-homepod-17-1-1-software/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-17-1-1-software-with-fix-for-siri-response-bug.2410215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:35:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-homepod-17-1-1-software/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside iOS 17.1.1, Apple released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.1.1 software to fix a bug that could cause some &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; speakers to respond slowly or fail to complete requests.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-783453" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/HomePodandMini-feature-green.jpg" alt="" width="1436" height="808" /><br/>
Today's update comes a couple of weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-homepod-software-17-1/">release of the HomePod 17.1 update</a>, which added Enhance Dialogue for the original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ software is installed automatically on the ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌‌ unless the feature is disabled‌‌‌‌, but the ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ can also be manually updated in the Home app by following the instructions in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/homepod-software-update/">HomePod‌‌ update how to</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-homepod-17-1-1-software/">Apple Releases HomePod 17.1.1 Software With Fix for Siri Response Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-17-1-1-software-with-fix-for-siri-response-bug.2410215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Fit Pro and Powerbeats Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/beats-fit-pro-powerbeats-pro-firmware-update-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-fit-pro-and-powerbeats-pro.2410214/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:27:20 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/beats-fit-pro-powerbeats-pro-firmware-update-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware for the Beats Fit Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/powerbeats-pro/">Powerbeats Pro</a> earbuds. The Beats Fit Pro and &zwnj;Powerbeats Pro&zwnj; can now be updated to firmware version 6B27, up from the prior 5B66 firmware that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/02/beats-fit-pro-powerbeats-pro-firmware-update/">came out in May</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/beats-fit-pro-feb23-open.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-885885" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what's included in firmware updates for the Beats Fit Pro and &zwnj;Powerbeats Pro&zwnj;, so we don't know what improvements or bug fixes the firmware offers.<br/>
<br/>
There's no standard way to upgrade the ‌Beats‌‌ software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the earbuds are connected to an iOS device. Putting the Beats‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting them to a power source, and then pairing them‌‌‌‌‌ to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> should force the update after a short period of time.<br/>
<br/>
If we find any notable changes after the firmware update is installed, we'll share details, but the software likely includes performance improvements and bug fixes rather than outward-facing changes.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/beats-fit-pro-powerbeats-pro-firmware-update-2/">Apple Releases New Firmware for Beats Fit Pro and Powerbeats Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-beats-fit-pro-and-powerbeats-pro.2410214/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases WatchOS 10.1.1 With Fix for Apple Watch Battery Drain Bug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1-with-fix-for-apple-watch-battery-drain-bug.2410213/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:14:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released watchOS 10.1.1, a bug fix update for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> operating system that first came out in September. watchOS 10.1.1 comes two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-watchos-10-1/">launch of watchOS 10.1</a>, an update that brought Double Tap and NameDrop support.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912513" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/watchOS-10-Launch-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" /><br/>
‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌‌.1.1 can be downloaded for free through the Apple Watch app on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or later by opening it up and going to General &gt; Software Update. To install the new software, the Apple Watch needs to have at least 50 percent battery and it needs to be placed on a charger.<br/>
<br/>
Today's update addresses an issue that is causing some Apple Watch models to drain battery more quickly than expected. Complaints about Apple Watch battery started after the launch of watchOS 10.1, and Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/04/watchos-update-to-fix-battery-drain-issue/">confirmed in a memo</a> over the weekend that the battery problems would be fixed in a software release.<blockquote>This update provides important bug fixes and addresses an issue that could cause the battery to drain more quickly for some users.</blockquote>Apple is already <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-1-to-developers/">testing watchOS 10.2</a>, an update that is expected to be released alongside iOS 17.2 in December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1/">Apple Releases WatchOS 10.1.1 With Fix for Apple Watch Battery Drain Bug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-1-with-fix-for-apple-watch-battery-drain-bug.2410213/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases iOS 17.1.1 With Bug Fixes for BMW Wireless Charging and Weather Widget</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1-with-bug-fixes-for-bmw-wireless-charging-and-weather-widget.2410212/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 13:12:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released iOS 17.1.1 and iPadOS 17.1.1, minor updates to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> operating systems that first came out in September. iOS 17.1.1 and iPadOS 17.1.1 come roughly two weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-releases-ios-17-1/">Apple released iOS 17.1</a>, an update that brought new AirDrop, StandBy, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> features.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.1.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignleft size-full wp-image-920500" /><br/>
iOS 17.1.1 and iPadOS 17.1.1 can be downloaded on eligible iPhones and iPads over-the-air by going to Settings &gt; General &gt; Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 17.1.1 update addresses a BMW wireless charging problem and a bug with the Weather Lock Screen widget. There have also been issues with Wi-Fi connectivity and device shutdowns, but it's unclear if anything in iOS 17.1.1 is intended to address those. Apple's full release notes for the update are below.<br/>
<blockquote>This update provides bug fixes for your iPhone including:<br/>
<br/>
- In rare circumstances, Apple Pay and other NFC features may become unavailable on iPhone 15 models after wireless charging in certain cars<br/>
- Weather Lock Screen widget may not correctly display snow</blockquote><br/>
Apple is already testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2</a>, updates that are expected to be released in December.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">Apple Releases iOS 17.1.1 With Bug Fixes for BMW Wireless Charging and Weather Widget</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1-with-bug-fixes-for-bmw-wireless-charging-and-weather-widget.2410212/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iMac Supports High-Impedance Headphones</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/new-imac-supports-high-impedance-headphones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-imac-supports-high-impedance-headphones.2410206/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:30:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/new-imac-supports-high-impedance-headphones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new 24-inch iMac with the M3 chip supports high-impedance headphones, according to an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212856">Apple support document</a> updated today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/iMac-power-speaker-heaphones-copy.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-795404" /><br/>
The built-in 3.5mm headphone jack on the left side of the new iMac features impedance detection and adaptive voltage output, and the computer <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212854">now has an improved digital-to-analog converter</a> with support for sample rates of up to 96 kHz, allowing for users to listen to high-fidelity, full-resolution audio with supported headphones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's list of all Macs that support high-impedance headphones:<ul><li>iMac introduced in 2023</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Air introduced in 2022 or later</li><br/>
<li>MacBook Pro introduced in 2021 or later</li><br/>
<li>Mac mini introduced in 2023</li><br/>
<li>Mac Studio introduced in 2022 or later</li><br/>
<li>Mac Pro introduced in 2023</li></ul>The new iMac launched today after being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/apple-announces-imac-with-m3-chip/">introduced at Apple's event</a> last week. Key new features include the M3 chip, Wi-Fi 6E, and Bluetooth 5.3. The all-in-one desktop computer has the same design as the 2021 model with the M1 chip.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/new-imac-supports-high-impedance-headphones/">New iMac Supports High-Impedance Headphones</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-imac-supports-high-impedance-headphones.2410206/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Briefly Paused Work on New Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15 to Clean Up Bugs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-engineers-ios-18-bug-fix-focus/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-briefly-paused-work-on-new-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15-to-clean-up-bugs.2410180/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 09:40:41 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-engineers-ios-18-bug-fix-focus/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple briefly paused work on upcoming iOS 18, macOS 15, watchOS 11, and tvOS 18 updates last week in order to make a serious effort to address bugs in the future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple Watch, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> and Mac releases, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-11-07/apple-delays-work-on-ios-18-macos-15-watchos-11-due-to-problems-with-bugs"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-18-Mock-Feature-Baubles.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909207" /><br/>
Employees were told about a development pause last week, with engineers asked to focus on fixing flaws and boosting software performance.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's software chief Craig Federighi has been making an effort in recent years to ensure that software bugs are addressed, sometimes resulting in features that need to be delayed. Sources that spoke to Gurman said that with the upcoming software updates, the software engineering management team working under Federighi found too many bugs that were missed in internal testing, leading to a week-long sprint to address the issues.<br/>
<br/>
During that week period, all development on future features was stopped to allow engineers to work solely on improving the existing software. Apple is lifting the pause this week so that work on new capabilities for iOS 18 and its sister updates can continue.<br/>
<br/>
Apple last month finished the first "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a>" versions of iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS 15. Work on further development was paused, with Apple also taking a brief break from working on iOS 17.4, expected to be released next March. Given that work on future software was only paused for a week, no release delays are expected next year. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-engineers-ios-18-bug-fix-focus/">Apple Briefly Paused Work on New Features for iOS 18 and macOS 15 to Clean Up Bugs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-briefly-paused-work-on-new-features-for-ios-18-and-macos-15-to-clean-up-bugs.2410180/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Silicon Buyer&#039;s Guide: Which Chip Should You Choose?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon-buyers-guide/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-buyers-guide-which-chip-should-you-choose.2395320/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:50:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon-buyers-guide&#038;post_date=1699386600/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>Mac Studio</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 13&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		<category>Mac mini</category>
		<category>Mac Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Choosing a new Mac often involves consideration of the many Apple silicon chips now on offer, so our comprehensive guide covers their generations, variations, and performance benchmarks to help you decide which is best for you.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Mac-Chip-Comparison-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-902570" /><br/>
After iterating for over a decade in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple in 2020 brought its custom silicon chip technology to the Mac, enabling major performance and power efficiency improvements. Since then, Apple silicon has expanded to every Mac model, spurring new designs and capabilities that were previously impossible.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Apple-M3-chip-series.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920046" /><br/>
<br/>
Understanding the distinctions between Apple silicon chips will help you make an informed decision when selecting the right Mac for your needs. There have been three generations of Apple silicon for the Mac, each with up to four different chip variants. The main differences between the four different chip variants are as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>M1, M2, and M3</strong>: Standard Apple silicon chip with a balance of performance and power-efficiency. </li><br/>
<li><strong>M1 Pro, M2 Pro, and M3 Pro</strong>: Apple silicon chip with additional high-performance CPU cores. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-pro/">M1 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> Pro feature twice the memory bandwidth of the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3 chips (200GB/s), while the M3 Pro features 50% more memory bandwidth than the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3 chips (150GB/s).</li><br/>
<li><strong>M1 Max, M2 Max, and M3 Max</strong>: Doubles the GPU cores of the &zwnj;M1 Pro&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro, or M3 Pro and features up to twice the memory bandwidth (400GB/s) of the &zwnj;M1 Pro&zwnj; or &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chips for better graphics performance. M3 Max also adds extra CPU cores.</li><br/>
<li><strong>M1 Ultra and M2 Ultra</strong>: Encompasses two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1-max/">M1 Max</a> or &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Max chips for double overall CPU and GPU performance, as well as twice the memory bandwidth (800GB/s).</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="apple_silicon_generations">Apple Silicon Generations</h3><br/>
With the introduction of the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; series of chips in 2022 and M3 series of chips in 2023, Apple made some key improvements over the initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> series from 2020.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Apple-M3-chip-series-architecture.jpg" alt="" width="2400" height="1350" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920045" /><br/>
The below table provides a comparison between the &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, and M3 series, highlighting differences in the chips they are based on, node, CPU clock speed, Neural Engines, and more:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj; Series</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; Series</th><br/>
 <th>M3 Series</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Based on A14 Bionic chip from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12 (2020)</td><br/>
 <td>Based on A15 Bionic chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> (2021)</td><br/>
 <td>Based on A17 Pro chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> (2023)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5nm node (N5)</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced 5nm node (N5P)</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> node (N3B)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>3.20 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 <td>3.49 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 <td>4.05 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>40% faster Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>15% faster Neural Engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Video decode engine</td><br/>
 <td>Higher-bandwidth video decode engine</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for AV1 decode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>New GPU architecture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dynamic Caching</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated mesh shading</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Image signal processor (ISP)</td><br/>
 <td>New image signal processor (ISP)</td><br/>
 <td>Same ISP as &zwnj;M2&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Launched November 2020 to March 2022</td><br/>
 <td>Launched June 2022 to early 2024</td><br/>
 <td>Launched starting November 2023</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The performance improvements seen with each iteration of Apple's Neural Engine is indicative of the generation-over-generation improvements that the company has been able to achieve with its custom silicon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/M3-chip-series-Neural-Engine-performance.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920048" /><br/>
<br/>
The standard &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip also features several additional changes over the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip, its direct predecessor, that are worth noting:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>68.25GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 <td>100GB/s memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Media engine for hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC</td><br/>
 <td>Media engine for hardware-accelerated H.264, HEVC, ProRes, and ProRes RAW</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>ProRes encode and decode engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
All Apple silicon chips other than the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip contain media engines for hardware-accelerated H.264, HEVC, ProRes, and ProRes RAW video. The M3 chip also adds support for AV1 decode.<br/>
<br/>
Thanks to use of more advanced fabrication processes and larger surface areas, Apple has added more transistors to its M-series chips with each generation:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>16 billion</td><br/>
 <td>33.7 billion</td><br/>
 <td>57 billion</td><br/>
 <td>114 billion</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>20 billion</td><br/>
 <td>40 billion</td><br/>
 <td>67 billion</td><br/>
 <td>134 billion</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>25 billion</td><br/>
 <td>37 billion</td><br/>
 <td>92 billion</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="devices">Devices</h3><br/>
Each Apple silicon chip is only available in a select number of Apple devices. The standard &zwnj;M1&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chips are present in a large number of laptop and desktop devices, several &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models, and even the upcoming Vision Pro headset, owing to their requirement for a balance of performance and efficiency. On the other hand, the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Ultra, Apple's most powerful custom silicon chip to date, is only available in the high-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> (2020)<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> (2020)<br/>
MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2020)<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> (2021)<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> (2021)<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> (2022)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, 2021)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, 2021)<br/>
&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2022)</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2022)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (2022, 2023)<br/>
MacBook Pro (13-inch, 2022)<br/>
&zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; (2022)<br/>
Mac Mini (2023)<br/>
Vision Pro (2024)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, early 2023)<br/>
&zwnj;Mac mini&zwnj; (2023)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, early 2023)<br/>
&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2023)</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj; (2023)<br/>
&zwnj;Mac Pro&zwnj; (2023)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch, late 2023)<br/>
&zwnj;iMac&zwnj; (2023)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, late 2023)</td><br/>
 <td>MacBook Pro (14-inch and 16-inch, late 2023)</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cpu_and_gpu_cores">CPU and GPU Cores</h3><br/>
CPU cores are individual processing units within a Central Processing Unit (CPU) responsible for executing instructions and performing general-purpose tasks, while GPU cores are specialized units within a Graphics Processing Unit (GPU) designed for parallel processing and graphics-intensive tasks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/m1-max-chip.jpg" alt="" width="2143" height="1248" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-821786" /><br/>
The number of CPU and GPU cores in an Apple silicon chip impacts the performance and multitasking capabilities of a Mac, with more cores leading to faster and more efficient execution of tasks, especially in intensive workloads. The table below presents a comparison of the core configurations and GPU specifications for the different variants of the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chips:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>4 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
7- or 8-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>6 or 8 high-performance cores<br/>
2 energy-efficient cores<br/>
14- or 16-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>8 high-performance cores<br/>
2 energy-efficient cores<br/>
24- or 32-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>16 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
48- or 64-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>4 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
8- or 10-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>6 or 8 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
16- or 19-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>8 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
30- or 38-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>16 high-performance cores<br/>
8 energy-efficient cores<br/>
60- or 76-core GPU</td><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>4 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
8- or 10-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>5 or 6 high-performance cores<br/>
6 energy-efficient cores<br/>
16- or 19-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>10 or 12 high-performance cores<br/>
4 energy-efficient cores<br/>
30- or 40-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Deciding how many CPU cores you need depends on the specific tasks and workflows you intend to perform on your Mac. For example, if you primarily engage in basic tasks like web browsing, document editing, and media consumption, an eight-core CPU should suffice. On the other hand, if you work with demanding workloads like software development, opting for a higher core count can provide significant performance benefits. Similarly, graphics-intense workflows like video editing, 3D modeling, or gaming will benefit from additional GPU cores.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="benchmarks">Benchmarks</h3><br/>
Computer benchmark scores are standardized measurements that evaluate the performance of chips, providing a numerical representation for comparing capabilities and assessing performance against industry standards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/M3-chip-series-performance-cores-comparison.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920049" /><br/>
<br/>
The data on the below table is calculated from Geekbench 6 <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/mac-benchmarks">results users uploaded to Geekbench</a>. Geekbench 6 scores are calibrated against a baseline score of 2,500 (which is the score of an Intel Core i7-12700 performing the same task).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/M3-chip-series-efficiency-cores-comparison.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-920047" /><br/>
<br/>
The below Geekbench 6 scores show the range from the lowest specification chip in the least powerful Mac to the highest specification chip in the most powerful Mac it is offered in. All scores are rounded to the nearest 10 for simplicity.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Single-Core Benchmarks</strong><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>2,330–2,350</td><br/>
 <td>2,360–2,370</td><br/>
 <td>2,380–2,400</td><br/>
 <td>2,384</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>2,570–2,630</td><br/>
 <td>2,640–2,650</td><br/>
 <td>2,740–2,800</td><br/>
 <td>2,760–2,770</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>3,010</td><br/>
 <td>3,120</td><br/>
 <td>3,120</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Multi-Core Benchmarks</strong><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>8,250–8,390</td><br/>
 <td>10,300–12,200</td><br/>
 <td>12,180–12,430</td><br/>
 <td>17,810</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>9,630–9,650</td><br/>
 <td>12,100–14,250</td><br/>
 <td>14,500–14,810</td><br/>
 <td>21,180–21,320</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>11,763</td><br/>
 <td>14,010–14,410</td><br/>
 <td>19,160–21,215</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Metal Benchmarks</strong><br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>29,450–32,030</td><br/>
 <td>61,870–65,910</td><br/>
 <td>103,120–112,940</td><br/>
 <td>154,190</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>41,300–45,550</td><br/>
 <td>72,360–81,430</td><br/>
 <td>137,530–144,380</td><br/>
 <td>202,640–220,080</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>47,430</td><br/>
 <td>68,330–77,070</td><br/>
 <td>124,060–157,120</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;M1&zwnj;, &zwnj;M2&zwnj;, and M3 chips demonstrate performance improvements in single-core and multi-core tasks as you move from the base to the Ultra variants, with the M3 chip showcasing even higher performance across the board. Nevertheless, it is worth noting that benchmarks do not tell the whole story. Benchmarks focus on specific tasks and synthetic workloads, and do not always accurately capture real-world usage scenarios and variations.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="unified_memory">Unified Memory</h3><br/>
Apple silicon chips have a unified memory architecture, meaning that the RAM is tied directly to the processor for maximum speed and efficiency. This means that the chip you choose determines what memory option are available, and it is not upgradable at a later date. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th></th><br/>
 <th>(Standard)</th><br/>
 <th>Pro</th><br/>
 <th>Max</th><br/>
 <th>Ultra</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M1&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>8GB<br/>
16GB</td><br/>
 <td>16GB<br/>
32GB</td><br/>
 <td>32GB<br/>
64GB</td><br/>
 <td>64GB<br/>
128GB</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <td>8GB<br/>
16GB<br/>
24GB</td><br/>
 <td>16GB<br/>
32GB</td><br/>
 <td>32GB<br/>
64GB<br/>
96GB</td><br/>
 <td>64GB<br/>
128GB<br/>
192GB</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>M3</th><br/>
 <td>8GB<br/>
16GB<br/>
24GB</td><br/>
 <td>18GB<br/>
36GB</td><br/>
 <td>36GB<br/>
48GB<br/>
64GB<br/>
96GB<br/>
128GB</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Deciding how much RAM you need depends on your specific tasks and usage patterns. 8GB should be enough for most users, but upgrading to 16GB or 24GB could be sensible for users with more intense multitasking requirements. Amounts of memory beyond 32GB are generally reserved for seriously demanding workflows.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="final_thoughts">Final Thoughts</h3><br/>
Overall, if you are new to Apple silicon and are still not sure which chip to buy, use the following rationale:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Buy M1, M2, or M3 if...</strong> you need a good balance of price, performance, and battery life and have normal day-to-day computing requirements.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Buy M1 Pro, M2 Pro, or M3 Pro if...</strong> you need a performance-focused chip for slightly more intense workflows.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Buy M1 Max, M2 Max, or M3 Max if...</strong> you need additional graphics performance for working with images, videos, graphic design, or games.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Buy M1 Ultra or M2 Ultra if...</strong> you need the best possible overall performance for extremely intense professional workflows.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
It is generally not worth upgrading from any of the individual &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chips to their direct successors and it may be better to wait for Apple to launch the M4 series of chips at some point in the next couple of years before upgrading if you are already an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; user.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro-13/">MacBook Pro 13"</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-pro/">Mac Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac-Studio">Mac Studio (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_13">13" MacBook Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Mini">Mac Mini (Neutral)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Mac_Pro">Mac Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-studio.237">Mac Studio</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-mini.146">Mac mini</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/mac-pro.1">Mac Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon-buyers-guide/">Apple Silicon Buyer&#039;s Guide: Which Chip Should You Choose?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-silicon-buyers-guide-which-chip-should-you-choose.2395320/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>12.9-Inch iPad Pro With Mini-LED Display Expected to Be Discontinued Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/12-9-inch-ipad-pro-discontinued-2024-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/12-9-inch-ipad-pro-with-mini-led-display-expected-to-be-discontinued-next-year.2410171/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:43:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/12-9-inch-ipad-pro-discontinued-2024-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to discontinue the 12.9-inch iPad Pro with mini-LED backlighting in 2024, according to a recent report from <a href="https://www.trendforce.com/presscenter/news/20231103-11903.html">Taiwanese research firm TrendForce</a>, suggesting that the tablet will not remain in the lineup for a reduced price following the launch of the rumored 13-inch iPad Pro with an OLED display next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/ipad-pro-m1-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1780" height="1001" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800056" /><br/>
TrendForce:<blockquote>The shipment volume for Mini LED notebooks is estimated to decrease by approximately 39% YoY. Meanwhile, with the 12.9-inch iPad Pro expected to be discontinued in 2024, the shipment volume of Mini LED tablets is expected to decrease by about 15.6% YoY, making these two the only applications expected to decline.</blockquote>In December 2022, oft-accurate display industry analyst Ross Young was first to report that the 12.9-inch iPad Pro would be succeeded by a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/29/oled-ipads-2024/">slightly larger 13-inch model</a> with an OLED display. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman expects new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro models with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">OLED displays, an M3 chip, and an aluminum Magic Keyboard</a> to launch next year.<br/>
<br/>
OLED display technology would allow for the next iPad Pro models to offer increased brightness, higher contrast ratio, greater color accuracy, and lower power consumption compared to the existing models with LCD panels. Young said Apple would be using very thin hybrid OLED displays with a combination of flexible and rigid materials, which could allow for the next iPad Pro models to have a slightly thinner design.<br/>
<br/>
iPad Pro models released since 2017 support ProMotion, allowing for a variable refresh rate between 24Hz and 120Hz. The switch to OLED would likely allow for the refresh rate to drop down even further to 10Hz or lower to save battery life. iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro models can reach as low as 1Hz while in always-on display mode.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/05/all-ipads-expected-to-be-updated-in-2024/">expected to update the iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad</a> in 2024, but none of those models are expected to switch to OLED next year. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/12-9-inch-ipad-pro-discontinued-2024-report/">12.9-Inch iPad Pro With Mini-LED Display Expected to Be Discontinued Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/12-9-inch-ipad-pro-with-mini-led-display-expected-to-be-discontinued-next-year.2410171/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>High Power Mode Expands to 14-Inch MacBook Pro With M3 Max Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-max-high-power-mode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/high-power-mode-expands-to-14-inch-macbook-pro-with-m3-max-chip.2410165/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 08:12:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-max-high-power-mode/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>High Power Mode</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has expanded High Power Mode to the new 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 Max chip, according to <a href="https://sixcolors.com/post/2023/11/m3-macbook-pro-review-peak-performance/"><em>Six Colors</em> editor-in-chief Jason Snell</a>. The feature was previously only available on the 16-inch MacBook Pro with the M1 Max and M2 Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/High-Power-Mode-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921421" /><br/>
"For some tests, I switched the MacBook Pro into High Power Mode, which is now available on both 14- and 16-inch models in the M3 Max configuration," wrote Snell, in his review of the new MacBook Pros. "I didn't actually find it made much of a difference in the tests I was running, but it sure did make the fans kick in at a very loud volume."<br/>
<br/>
In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT212852">support document</a>, Apple says High Power Mode allows a MacBook Pro's fans to run at higher speeds, and this additional cooling may allow the system to deliver higher performance for "intensive sustained workloads," such as 8K video color grading.<br/>
<br/>
On macOS Ventura and later, High Power Mode can be enabled in the System Settings app under Battery by clicking on the dropdown menus next to "On battery" or "On power adapter" and selecting the "High Power" option.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/07/macos-high-power-mode-macbook-pro-settings/"><em>9to5Mac</em></a> was first to report this news.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/high-power-mode/">High Power Mode</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-max-high-power-mode/">High Power Mode Expands to 14-Inch MacBook Pro With M3 Max Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/high-power-mode-expands-to-14-inch-macbook-pro-with-m3-max-chip.2410165/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Black Friday iPad Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals.2410156/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 07:30:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals&#038;post_date=1699381856/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday is right around the corner, and deals on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/">AirPods</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/">iPhones</a> have already begun cropping up in early November. Today, we're taking a look at all of the best early Black Friday iPad deals you can already get.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921376" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Of course, there is a chance that we could see better deals on these iPads arrive as Black Friday gets closer. This is a risk anyone has to take while shopping during the holidays, so with that in mind, many of the deals shared below are currently their best prices ever seen. More information on these sales can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday Roundup</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
Unless otherwise noted, all the deals in this guide will be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_ipad_deals">Best iPad Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi)</strong></a> for &#36;249.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLC5CPN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>12.9-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi)</strong></a> for &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,199.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>11-inch Magic Keyboard</strong></a> for &#36;229.00, down from &#36;299.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="best_black_friday_deals">Best Black Friday Deals</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</strong></a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-airpods-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday AirPods Deals</strong></a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-iphone-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday iPhone Deals</strong></a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2 id="9th_gen_ipad">9th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/9th-ipad-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921381" /><br/>
We've been tracking a great all-time low discount on the ninth generation iPad since Prime Day, and the deal is still around in November. You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;249.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;329.00. At this price, the iPad is a perfect entry-level tablet for a kid or family member who doesn't need the tablet for work-intensive projects.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FPHY6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>10.2-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><h2 id="10th_gen_ipad">10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-snowflakes-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921383" /><br/>
<br/>
The upgraded iPad from 2022 also has a nice discount on Amazon right now, with the 64GB Wi-Fi model on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;449.00. This model comes with a bigger 10.9-inch Liquid Retina display, A14 Bionic chip for a performance boost, Wi-Fi 6, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10.9-inch iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><h2 id="6th_gen_ipad_mini">6th Gen iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-mini-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921380" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple's 8.3-inch iPad mini 6 is down to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9BXKF5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This iPad mini has an 8.3-inch Liquid Retina display, A15 Bionic chip, USB-C, and more. Perhaps more notably, Amazon has the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9LPNLG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;529.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;649.00, which is a new all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9BXKF5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9LPNLG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;529.99</div></a></div><h2 id="5th_gen_ipad_air">5th Gen iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-air-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921382" /><br/>
<br/>
Switching to iPad Air models, the 2022 64GB Wi-Fi tablet has hit <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;499.99</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;599.00. That's a solid all-time low price on this model, and you can also find a few other storage configurations at record lows this time around. Note that for the majority of colors, you'll need to clip an on-page coupon to see these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3KXJPB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><h2 id="12.9-inch_ipad_pro">12.9-inch iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ipad-pro-snowflakes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921384" /><br/>
<br/>
The 256GB Wi-Fi 12.9-inch iPad Pro dropped to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLC5CPN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;999.99</strong></a> on Amazon this week, down from &#36;1,199.00. This is a new record low price on the high-end tablet, and one of the only notable iPad Pro discounts around right now.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLC5CPN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;199 OFF</div>12.9-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;999.99</div></a></div><h2 id="accessories">Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLG69QR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil 1 with USB-C Charging Adapter</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil 2</a> - &#36;109.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">11-inch Magic Keyboard</a> - &#36;229.00, down from &#36;299.00</li></ul> We've begun tracking all of the season's best deals in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Black Friday Roundup</a>, so be sure to bookmark the page and visit it throughout the season as you do your online shopping. Our roundup mainly focuses on Apple products and related tech accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/best-black-friday-ipad-deals/">The Best Early Black Friday iPad Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-black-friday-ipad-deals.2410156/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Pro Ships With macOS Ventura, Can&#039;t Yet Be Updated to macOS Sonoma Over the Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-macos-sonoma-update-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-pro-ships-with-macos-ventura-cant-yet-be-updated-to-macos-sonoma-over-the-air.2410150/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 06:21:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-macos-sonoma-update-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>macOS Ventura</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's new entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the standard M3 chip <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/06/first-m3-mac-orders-australia-nz/">began arriving to customers</a> over the past day, and some early adopters have discovered that the laptop cannot currently be updated to macOS Sonoma over the air.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/No-13-Inch-M3-MacBook-Pro-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921296" /><br/>
As <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1721742053170684065">noted by @aaronp613 on X</a>, at least some 14-inch MacBook Pro models with the M3 chip shipped with an unreleased build of macOS Ventura 13.5 installed. When users attempt to update to macOS Sonoma in the System Settings app, macOS Ventura 13.5 is listed as the latest version available instead of macOS Sonoma 14.1.<br/>
<br/>
One user who experienced this issue is <a href="https://twitter.com/ZONEofTECH/status/1721868285732344224">Daniel Rotar</a>, host of the <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@ZONEofTECH/">YouTube channel ZONEofTECH</a>, according to a post he shared on X today. Additional users across <a href="https://twitter.com/nacookan/status/1721867659963412668">X</a> and the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-orders-begin-arriving-to-customers.2410091/post-32702848">MacRumors Forums</a> have mentioned the issue.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ok, here’s something weird. <br><br>Our M3 MacBook Pro shipped with Ventura and can’t seem to update to Sonoma at all. Version not compatible. <br><br>Our M3 Pro MacBook Pro shipped with Sonoma. <br><br>Did anyone else get an M3 that shipped with Ventura? <a href="https://t.co/me0kLZjk6f">pic.twitter.com/me0kLZjk6f</a></p>&mdash; Daniel (@ZONEofTECH) <a href="https://twitter.com/ZONEofTECH/status/1721868285732344224?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 7, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Given that macOS Ventura 13.5 was released in July, it seems that Apple began stockpiling the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M3 chip several months ago. <br/>
<br/>
It's unclear when Apple will address this problem, but in the meantime, software researcher <a href="https://twitter.com/nicolas09F9">Nicolás Álvarez</a> <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-m3-macbook-pro-and-imac-orders-begin-arriving-to-customers.2410091/post-32702982">said</a> that affected users can <a href="https://swcdn.apple.com/content/downloads/54/11/042-41700-A_6GDS7ETYNV/zxpkgymp3w9bm3py7ybs9n9ud27qwnwx7u/InstallAssistant.pkg">download the Install Assistant</a> for the M3-compatible version of macOS Sonoma 14.1 and manually install the update. It is also possible to enable macOS public betas to get the update to appear.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> As noted <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/07/m3-macbook-pro-imac-sonoma-fails/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>, this issue appears to affect the new iMac with the M3 chip as well.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-ventura.239">macOS Ventura</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/14-inch-macbook-pro-m3-macos-sonoma-update-issue/">M3 MacBook Pro Ships With macOS Ventura, Can&#039;t Yet Be Updated to macOS Sonoma Over the Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-pro-ships-with-macos-ventura-cant-yet-be-updated-to-macos-sonoma-over-the-air.2410150/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 iMac and MacBook Pro Models Now Available for Same-Day Pickup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-imac-macbook-pro-now-available/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-imac-and-macbook-pro-models-now-available-for-same-day-pickup.2410137/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 03:16:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-imac-macbook-pro-now-available/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>M3</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting today, Apple's refreshed M3 iMac and MacBook Pro models with M3 and M3 Pro chips are available for same-day or next-day pickup at Apple Stores, with no pre-order required. Online orders are also beginning to arrive to customers today. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-imac.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919460" /><br/>
Customers across the United States, Canada, Europe, Asia, and other regions can now place an order on Apple's website or in the Apple Store app and arrange for in-store pickup at a local retail location.<br/>
<br/>
To order a product with Apple Store pickup, add the product to your bag on Apple.com, proceed to checkout, select the "I'll pick it up" option, enter your ZIP code, choose an available Apple Store location, and select a pickup date. Payment is completed online, and a valid government-issued photo ID and the order number may be required upon pickup.<br/>
<br/>
The refreshed 24-inch iMac includes an Apple-designed M3 Arm-based chip that replaces the M1 chip and brings significant speed and efficiency improvements. The iMac with M3 chip is up to 2x faster than the M1 iMac, with support for up to 24GB of unified memory, Bluetooth 5.3 and Wi-Fi 6E. There are no major external design changes to the M3 iMac, which is available in a range of bright colors, including green, blue, pink, silver, orange, yellow, and purple. <br/>
<br/>
The 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models can be purchased today with the M3 and M3 Pro chips, while models with the new M3 Max chip won't become available until later in November. The MacBook Pro models have slightly brighter display levels when viewing SDR content, and also include support for Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3. Apple offers the MacBook Pro in silver, space gray, and space black aluminum color options, depending on chip configuration.<br/>
<br/>
Pricing for the MacBook Pro starts at &#36;1,599 for the 14-inch model and &#36;2,499 for the 16-inch model, while the iMac starts at &#36;1,299.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m3/">M3</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/m3-imac-macbook-pro-now-available/">M3 iMac and MacBook Pro Models Now Available for Same-Day Pickup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-imac-and-macbook-pro-models-now-available-for-same-day-pickup.2410137/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
