<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:11:24 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Models Have Up to 54% Better 5G Download Speeds Than iPhone 14 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-up-to-54-better-5g-download-speeds-than-iphone-14-models.2411097/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 16:09:55 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>5G</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models are equipped with Qualcomm's X70 modem chip that promises faster 5G speeds than the X65 in the prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models, and testing <a href="https://www.ookla.com/articles/iphone-15-samsung-fold5-performance-q3-2023">shared by Ookla</a> confirms that download speeds have notably improved.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ookla-5g-iphone-15-speed.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="826" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922751" /><br/>
Using data collected from its online Speedtest for measuring connection speeds, Ookla has been able to determine that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models support download speeds that are up to 54 percent faster than the download speeds available on the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to their equivalent &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus saw 54 percent faster download speeds, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; had 45 percent better download speeds, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max was 27 percent faster, and the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; had a 25 percent better download speed.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models had the fastest download speeds out of all the Apple and Samsung devices included on Ookla's results list. Median download speeds on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max were at 285Mb/s, and the other iPhones weren't far behind.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; had the slowest median download speed out of Apple's lineup at 249Mb/s, but it still came out ahead of Samsung's latest smartphones, including the Galaxy Z Fold5 and the Galaxy Z Flip5.<br/>
<br/>
Note that Ookla's data covers median download speeds across the entire United States, and connectivity could vary depending on location, proximity to a major city, location of the closest cellular tower, carrier, and more. Data shared for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> was collected from September 22 to October 30.<br/>
<br/>
5G download speeds also improved in multiple other countries, including Australia, Brazil, Canada, France, India, South Korea, Spain, the UK, and the UAE, with full results <a href="https://www.ookla.com/articles/iphone-15-samsung-fold5-performance-q3-2023">available on the Ookla website</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/5g/">5G</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-15-5g-download-speeds/">iPhone 15 Models Have Up to 54% Better 5G Download Speeds Than iPhone 14 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-models-have-up-to-54-better-5g-download-speeds-than-iphone-14-models.2411097/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Six Months of Free Apple Music Available to PlayStation 5 Owners</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-months-of-free-apple-music-available-to-playstation-5-owners.2411092/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 15:15:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As part of an effort to promote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> on the PlayStation, Apple is <a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/deals/apple-music-playstation-offers">offering PlayStation 5 owners</a> up to six months of free access to the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; streaming service.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-music-playstation-5.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="878" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922759" /><br/>
PlayStation 5 owners will need to sign into the PlayStation Network, download the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app, and follow the on-screen instructions to accept the offer. Users will need to sign in with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> or create one.<br/>
<br/>
The PlayStation website suggests that gamers use &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; to create a personalized gaming playlist to listen to before, during, and after gameplay sessions.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; promotion is only available on the PlayStation 5, and it has to be redeemed on a PlayStation 5 console. Only new and qualified returning subscribers to &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; can get free access, so this is not a deal that is available to current subscribers. New subscribers will receive six months of &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;, while returning subscribers will get five months.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will be <a href="https://www.playstation.com/en-us/deals/apple-music-playstation-offers">offering the deal</a> until 11/15/24. After the six-month period expires, a subscription can be continued for &#36;10.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-music-ps5-trial/">Six Months of Free Apple Music Available to PlayStation 5 Owners</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/six-months-of-free-apple-music-available-to-playstation-5-owners.2411092/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 183 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2411091/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 14:55:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser Apple <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed the &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to test features that may be introduced into future release versions of Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-785724" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/Safari-Technology-Preview-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2368" height="1332" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 183 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, AutoFill, CSS, Forms, HTML, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, Scrolling, SVG, URLs, Web API, Web Inspector, and WebGL.<br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running macOS Ventura and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a>, the latest version of macOS that Apple released in September 2023.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a>. Full release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 183 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-183-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2411091/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTuber Explains How to Watch Spatial Videos From iPhone 15 Pro on VR Headsets</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-explains-how-to-watch-spatial-videos-from-iphone-15-pro-on-vr-headsets.2411087/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 13:53:52 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the iOS 17.2 beta, Apple added a feature that allows the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max to record Spatial Video that's designed for the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. As the Vision Pro is not yet available, there's no way to watch Spatial Video in its 3D form on an Apple device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Vision-Pro-Spatial-Video.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922277" /><br/>
Spatial Video content can, however, be watched on the Meta Quest 3 and other 3D devices thanks to a workaround shared by YouTuber Hugh Hou. Earlier this week, Hou described <a href="https://www.threads.net/@hugh.hou">how to manipulate Spatial Video</a> to get it to run on Meta's VR headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Spatial Video in 3D! Shot on iPhone 15 Pro for Vision Pro &amp; Meta Quest 3" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/x3v-0XbWI2s" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
An &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; running the iOS 17.2 beta is required, of course, in order to record Spatial Video in the first place. The beta is available to both developers and public beta testers, and downloading it is as simple as going to the Software Update section in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Settings app and toggling on beta updates.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial Video recording needs to be enabled in the Camera settings after the iOS 17.2 update, and from there, Hou instructs users to <a href="https://testflight.apple.com/join/EEFFsOzJ">get the "Spatialify" app</a> on TestFlight.<br/>
<br/>
The app has instructions on decoding and exporting Spatial Video in a format that the Meta Quest 3 or other 3D headsets and TVs can view, and there is an extra step involving encoding 3D metadata.<br/>
<br/>
It is not the most straightforward process, but it may be of interest to &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; users who have a VR headset or 3D TV and want to try viewing Spatial Video ahead of when the Vision Pro headset comes out.<br/>
<br/>
Spatial Video is designed to allow Vision Pro headset wearers to view video in a more immersive 3D format. Along with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, the headset will also be able to be used to record Spatial Video content.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/spatial-video-iphone-15-vr-headset/">YouTuber Explains How to Watch Spatial Videos From iPhone 15 Pro on VR Headsets</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtuber-explains-how-to-watch-spatial-videos-from-iphone-15-pro-on-vr-headsets.2411087/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Adds New Filters, Support for Custom Stickers From Photos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-new-filters-support-for-custom-stickers-from-photos.2411078/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 12:32:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular social network Instagram <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/11/new-ways-to-create-content-on-instagram/">was today updated</a> with a number of improvements that are designed to give users more ways to edit their content before sharing it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/03/Instagram-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-786418" /><br/>
Instagram has added more than 20 new filters that can be used to tweak the look of images, and this is the first time in several years that filters have been updated. Some of the filters add subtle color changes, while others change the look entirely by adding blur and other effects. All of the filters have an intensity slider to tweak the final look.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside the new filters, the posting interface has been simplified. It's easier to find specific images from the camera roll thanks to improved previews and the ability to zoom and search by keyword.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram is using its Segment Anything AI model to give users the ability to create custom stickers from their own photos and videos, or from eligible photos and videos shared on Instagram. These features are being tested, and may not be accessible to everyone.<br/>
<br/>
For Reels, Instagram is testing options for scaling, cropping, and rotating individual clips, plus there are options to add from the clip hub for creating "more memeable content." The Reels interface is being updated to make it easier to locate tools like Voiceover, and undo and redo functionality is being added.<br/>
<br/>
There are 10 new English text-to-speech voices to choose from to have Instagram read text content, and there are six new text fonts and styles to work with. Note that these features are rolling out and are not available to all users at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram is a free app, and more information on the changes can be <a href="https://about.fb.com/news/2023/11/new-ways-to-create-content-on-instagram/">found on the Instagram blog</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/instagram-new-filters-stickers/">Instagram Adds New Filters, Support for Custom Stickers From Photos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-adds-new-filters-support-for-custom-stickers-from-photos.2411078/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Includes Mystery Boxes With Hundreds in Savings</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-includes-mystery-boxes-with-hundreds-in-savings.2411077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:59:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Anker's <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">Black Friday Early Access</a> sale is winding down this week, so we're again highlighting all of the best deals from the event before it ends on November 16. With this sale, when you buy two or more Anker products sitewide you can get 25 percent off your entire order. There are also a few "mystery boxes" that can include hundreds of dollars in savings, if you're willing to risk not knowing what you're buying ahead of time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/anker-new-gold.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922736" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Anker. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In terms of the base sale, there are plenty of great accessories that you can buy to take advantage of the bundle savings, including the new MagSafe-compatible <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/y1811?ref=black-friday-sale">Anker 3-in-1 Charging Cube</a> (&#36;149.95). This device has space to simultaneously charge an iPhone, Apple Watch, and AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
There's also the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1336-20000mah-power-bank?ref=black-friday-sale&amp;variant=42691854925974">Anker Prime 20,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> (&#36;129.99). Although this one is on sale at &#36;110.49 without the bundle deal, if you buy this and the 3-in-1 Cube together, you'll net a bigger discount. The Power Bank will be knocked down to &#36;97.50 and the 3-in-1 Cube will go down to &#36;112.46 thanks to the 25 percent savings.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">25% OFF</div>Anker Black Friday Early Access</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
At the <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/black-friday-sale?ref=naviMenu">bottom of the Black Friday Early Access sale page</a>, Anker also has a few blind boxes on sale, priced at &#36;19.99 (up to &#36;219.99 in value) and at &#36;59.99 (up to &#36;799.99 in value). These mystery boxes include one Anker accessory, but you won't know what you're getting until they arrive. All items in the &#36;19.99 box are worth more than &#36;19.99, and all items in the &#36;59.99 box are worth more than &#36;59.99, so no matter what you'll be getting a deal.<br/>
<br/>
All mystery box items are non-returnable (with the exception of quality issues). They are also excluded from the 25 percent off promotion when purchasing two or more items. These could net you a huge discount with a collection of solid stocking stuffers for the holidays, if you're willing to take the blind box risk.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Wall Chargers</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2668?variant=41974350315670">65W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;37.99, down from &#36;59.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2669-3-port-wall-charger">67W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;45.00, down from &#36;59.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1MTQQ9ONIG1WQ_1697469063005">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2340?variant=41974288777366">150W 4-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;87.99, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a2342-240w-gan-charger?variant=42691851550870">Prime 240W 4-Port Desktop Charger</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Portable Batteries</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1653-usb-c-portable-charger-5000mah">Nano Power Bank with Foldable USB-C Connector</a> - &#36;25.50, down from &#36;29.99 [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6XK77HJ">Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1268">PowerCore 20,000 mAh</a> - &#36;36.52, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1651">PowerCore 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1289">PowerCore 24,000 mAh Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;159.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/b1291">PowerCore 26,000 mAh</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<strong>Portable Power Stations</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1751">PowerHouse 535</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1761">SOLIX C1000 Power Station</a> - &#36;749.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1770111">PowerHouse 757</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,099.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https://www.anker.com/products/a1780">PowerHouse 767</a> - &#36;1,599.00, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul> You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/anker-black-friday-sale/">Anker Black Friday Early Access Sale Includes Mystery Boxes With Hundreds in Savings</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/anker-black-friday-early-access-sale-includes-mystery-boxes-with-hundreds-in-savings.2411077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Black Friday 2023: Deals on Macs, iPhones, iPads, and Apple Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/</link>
		<comments></comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:21:02 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday&#038;post_date=1700086862/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Arnold Kim</dc:creator>
		<category>Roundup</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Black Friday is approaching and we have started updating our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday 2023 roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We've got everything organized by store, and we'll be highlighting some of the best deals to be had.]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Offering New Accessories From Mophie, Scosche, Hue and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-online-store-accessory-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-offering-new-accessories-from-mophie-scosche-hue-and-more.2411074/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 11:08:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-online-store-accessory-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today updated its online store to add a range of new accessories from companies that include Mophie, Scosche, Philips Hue, Yale, and others. Some of the accessories are limited to online purchases, while others are available in Apple retail locations worldwide.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/scosche-baselynx-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-879602" /><br/>
Apple is now selling <a href="https://www.apple.com/us/search/baselynx?src=globalnav">Scosche's BaseLynx 2.0 modular charging system</a>, which allows customers to purchase individual charging modules for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac. There is an all-in-one kit that is priced at &#36;279, with the kit able to wirelessly charge the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and AirPods, fast charge the Apple Watch, and charge multiple iPads or MacBooks using the vertical USB-C charging dock.<br/>
<br/>
Up to 60W is available for one &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, 30W when two devices are being charged, and 20W when three devices are plugged in to the USB-C ports. Apple is also offering individual modules at prices ranging from &#36;500 to &#36;100.<br/>
<br/>
Also new to Apple's website is Mophie's latest 3-in-1 Travel Charger, priced at &#36;150. It features the same design as Mophie's prior-generation model, but this time with Apple Watch fast charging capabilities. It can wirelessly charge an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; using <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>, charge AirPods over Qi, and charge the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/mophie-charger-2.jpg" alt="" width="1801" height="1013" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833690" /><br/>
The charger folds down into a compact shape when it is not in use, making it ideal for travel, with Mophie also including a travel charger case. It comes with the cable and 30W power adapter needed to use it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/mophie-charger.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1124" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922704" /><br/>
As for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> devices, Apple is now selling the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRBP2ZM/A/yale-assure-lock-2-plus-home-key-lock">&#36;210 Yale Assure Lock 2 Plus</a>, which supports Apple's home keys feature. With home keys, a digital key is added to the Apple Wallet app and the lock can be opened over NFC by tapping an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or Apple Watch to the lock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/yale-home-key-lock.jpg" alt="" width="1510" height="848" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914168" /><br/>
The lock can be opened and accessed using &zwnj;HomeKit&zwnj;, and with DoorSense, the door automatically locks behind you. Note that a separate Yale Wi-Fi Smart Module is required for remote access as the lock is designed to work over Bluetooth.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also offers the latest Philips Hue product from Signify, the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR872ZM/A/philips-hue-festavia-65-foot-250-led-smart-string-lights">Hue Festavia LED string lights</a>. Priced at &#36;220, the Hue Festavia is a 65-foot strand of lights with 250 LEDs, ideal for decorating a tree or for use outdoors during the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/hue-festavia.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-908253" /><br/>
These are gradient string lights that can be set to multiple colors that blend into one another, and they work with the Philips Hue Bridge.<br/>
<br/>
Other new products available from the Apple online store include SanDisk's latest <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HPSU2ZM/B/sandisk-ixpand-flash-drive-luxe-usb-type-c-flash-drive-256gb">256GB iXpand Flash Drive</a>, Belkin's &#36;80 <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1G2ZM/A/belkin-boost-charge-pro-2-in-1-wireless-charger-pad-with-magsafe">Boost Charge Pro 2-in-1 Charger Pad</a> in a range of colors, the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HRDG2ZM/A/backbone-one-mobile-gaming-controller-usb-c">Backbone One Mobile Gaming Controller</a>, and other cases, cables, and accessories. The full list can be <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/accessories/all/whats-new?page=1&amp;s=newest">found on Apple's online store</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-online-store-accessory-update/">Apple Now Offering New Accessories From Mophie, Scosche, Hue and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-offering-new-accessories-from-mophie-scosche-hue-and-more.2411074/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2411068/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 10:24:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third public beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update, allowing non-developers to test out the software ahead of its release. The third public beta comes two weeks after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/macos-sonoma-14-2-public-beta-1/">the second public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds Messages sticker reactions, which make it quicker to add a sticker or an emoji to an iMessage. It also includes support for collaborative <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> playlists, allowing multiple people to add songs to a single playlist. <br/>
<br/>
There's a new Favorites &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; playlist as well, better support for Messages in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> syncing, and iMessage Contact Key Verification for people who face extraordinary digital threats.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2/">Apple Seeds Third Public Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2.2411068/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app-and-more.2411067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 10:24:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to try out the software ahead of its release. The third iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 public betas come two weeks after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-1/">second public betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918853" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.2 adds the Journal app, designed to let <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users record their daily activities and thoughts. Apple offers prompts that can be used as inspiration, and journal entries can be outfitted with images, voice recordings, location tags, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Collaborative playlists are now available in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> so you can create playlists that multiple people contribute to, and there's also now a Favorites playlist that has all the music you've favorited. Stickers can be used as tapback reactions in the Messages app, the Action Button on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models can now be set to a new Translate function, and Apple has implemented support for iMessage Contact Key Verification.<br/>
<br/>
There are new Weather and Clock widgets, tweaks to the TV app, updates to Message syncing across devices, new Memoji options, and more, with the full list of features we've found so far available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">iOS 17.2 beta features article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-public-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Public Beta of iOS 17.2 With Journal App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-public-beta-of-ios-17-2-with-journal-app-and-more.2411067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Nearly &#36;200 Off Apple&#039;s M2 13-Inch MacBook Air in Best Buy&#039;s Black Friday Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-m2-13-inch-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-nearly-200-off-apples-m2-13-inch-macbook-air-in-best-buys-black-friday-sale.2411064/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 10:21:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-m2-13-inch-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy is offering <a href="https://howl.me/ck0ENeWZv3b">nearly &#36;200 off the 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air</a>, coming within just a few dollars of the all-time low price for the 256GB model. This sale requires you to be a <a href="https://howl.me/ck0EO9eTiUj">My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total member</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/macbook-air-holiday-green.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-873085" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Without a membership, you can get the <a href="https://howl.me/ck0ENeWZv3b">256GB 13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air</a> for &#36;949.00, down from &#36;1,099.00. Members can add an extra &#36;47.45 off that price and get it for &#36;901.55, which is just about &#36;2 more than the all-time low price on this model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/ck0ENeWZv3b"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;197.45 OFF</div>13.6-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;901.55</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has plenty of more deals going on right now <a href="https://howl.me/ck0GTqIImxe">for early Black Friday shoppers</a>, including deals on laptops, video games, Bluetooth speakers, TVs, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-m2-13-inch-macbook-air/">Get Nearly &#36;200 Off Apple&#039;s M2 13-Inch MacBook Air in Best Buy&#039;s Black Friday Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-nearly-200-off-apples-m2-13-inch-macbook-air-in-best-buys-black-friday-sale.2411064/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First Qi2 Wireless Chargers Coming Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon.2411058/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 09:27:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		<category>Qi2</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first wireless chargers that support the new Qi2 charging standard are set to launch in time for the holiday season, according to an announcement shared today by the <a href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20231115984149/en">Wireless Power Consortium</a> (WPC).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/magsafe-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911511" /><br/>
Announced earlier this year, Qi2 is a next-generation Qi charging technology that incorporates a Magnetic Power Profile. Qi2 devices will work like Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> feature, using magnets for alignment and speedier charging.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models are the first of Apple's smartphones that support the Qi2 standard. More than 100 Qi2 device are in testing, according to the WPC, including chargers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/mophie-unveils-qi2-accessories/">from companies like</a> Belkin, Mophie, Anker, and Aircharge.<br/>
<br/>
The Magnetic Power Profile was designed based on &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; contributions from Apple, and it is being combined with the new Extended Power Profile (EPP) to form what is considered "Qi2."<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 is meant to ensure that phones and other battery-powered mobile products are perfectly aligned with chargers for improved energy efficiency and faster charging. It will allow for new accessories that would not be chargeable wirelessly using existing flat surface-to-flat surface devices.<br/>
<br/>
Qi2 chargers that have already been announced promise to charge devices at up to 15W, but it is not yet clear if Apple's &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models will support faster wireless charging with Qi2 accessories. Apple's technical specifications page for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; says that the devices support Qi wireless charging "up to 7.5W," with no mention of faster charging.<br/>
<br/>
MagSafe-enabled &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models charge at 7.5W on the current Qi standard, and 15W when using Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; chargers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qi2/">Qi2</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon/">First Qi2 Wireless Chargers Coming Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-qi2-wireless-chargers-coming-soon.2411058/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacBook Pro Black Friday Deals Arrive for Apple&#039;s New M3 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/macbook-pro-black-friday-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-black-friday-deals-arrive-for-apples-new-m3-models.2411046/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:45:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/macbook-pro-black-friday-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-new-m3-imac-discount/">pair of deals on the M3 iMac</a> we shared this morning, now B&H Photo is also discounting Apple's new M3 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro. Every discount in this sale represents a new all-time low price for each M3 MacBook Pro model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/m3-macbook-pro-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-920810" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with B&H Photo. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>14-Inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
Starting with the 512GB M3 14-inch MacBook Pro, you can get this computer for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793630-REG/apple_mtl73ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330378/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;1,449.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.00. This one requires you to add the notebook to your cart and head to checkout before you see the deal price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793630-REG/apple_mtl73ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330378/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3, 512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
B&H also has the 512GB M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Profor <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793624-REG/apple_mrx33ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330385/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;1,799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,999.00. You won't see this record low sale price until you add the computer to your cart and head to the checkout screen.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793624-REG/apple_mrx33ll_a_14_macbook_pro_with.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330385/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Next, the 1TB M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro has hit <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793625-REG/apple_mrx43ll_a_14_macbook_pro_pro.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330386/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;2,199.00</strong></a> on B&H Photo, down from &#36;2,399.00. This one doesn't require you to head to the checkout screen in order to see the deal, as it's been applied automatically on the product page.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793625-REG/apple_mrx43ll_a_14_macbook_pro_pro.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330386/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 1TB) for &#36;2,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2>16-Inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
B&H Photo only has one discount on the larger display models. You can get the 512GB M3 Pro 16-inch MacBook Pro for <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793618-REG/apple_mrw13ll_a_16_macbook_pro_m3.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330380/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;2,299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;2,499.00. This is another one that requires you to add the computer to your cart before you'll see the deal price, and it's also another all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793618-REG/apple_mrw13ll_a_16_macbook_pro_m3.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330380/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro, 512GB) for &#36;2,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/macbook-pro-black-friday-deals/">MacBook Pro Black Friday Deals Arrive for Apple&#039;s New M3 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macbook-pro-black-friday-deals-arrive-for-apples-new-m3-models.2411046/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Series Rumored to Have These 16 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-16-series-16-rumored-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-rumored-to-have-these-16-new-features.2411041/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 07:17:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-16-series-16-rumored-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series is at least 10 months away, and yet there are 16 rumors already circulating about the devices. Below, we've recapped all of the new features and changes we have covered here at <em>MacRumors</em> so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922664" /><br/>
The following key changes have been rumored for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup as of November 2023:<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>Larger Displays</strong>: The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and Pro Max are expected to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, respectively. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro will have a display that's 6.27 inches in size (rounded to 6.3), while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max is expected to have a display that's 6.85 inches in size (rounded to 6.9).</li><br/>
<li><strong>Camera Layout</strong>: The standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are rumored to have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/22/iphone-16-vertical-camera-lenses-rumor/">vertical camera layout</a> that's similar to the camera layout used in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a>. Apple used a diagonal layout for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, and it's not entirely clear why Apple would revert, but one theory is that it could allow the devices to record <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/spatial-videos-on-vision-pro-first-impressions/">spatial video for Apple Vision Pro</a>.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Capture Button</strong>: A new physical "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">Capture Button</a>" is rumored for all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. What its purpose is remains a mystery at this point.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>48-Megapixel Ultra Wide Lens</strong>: The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro models are expected to feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">upgraded 48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera lens</a> for higher-resolution photos with more detail when shooting in 0.5× mode.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Super Telephoto Camera</strong>: The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max could be the first to feature a super telephoto periscope camera for dramatically increased optical zoom, allowing Apple to maintain differentiation between the two "Pro" devices next year.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Wi-Fi 7 Support</strong>: The Pro models are expected to get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">Wi-Fi 7 in the Pro models</a>, enabling data transfer over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. .</li><br/>
    <li><strong>A18 Pro Chip</strong>: Apple's next-generation A18 Pro chip is expected to be manufactured with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">TSMC's second-generation 3nm process</a>, known as N3E.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>5G Advanced</strong>: Pro models may feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">Qualcomm's Snapdragon X75 modem</a> for faster and more power efficient 5G connectivity over networks supporting "5G Advanced".</li><br/>
    <li><strong>5x Optical Zoom</strong>: Both &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro models are expected to feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">5x optical zoom</a>, which is currently exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Solid-State Buttons</strong>: Apple may finally introduce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/12/iphone-16-pro-solid-state-buttons/">solid-state volume, power, and mute buttons</a> to the Pro models. Apple originally wanted to replace the physical buttons on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, but pulled them due to "unresolved technical issues."</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Micro-Lens Technology</strong>: &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; OLED display panels might use brighter <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">micro-lens technology</a> and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/">more power-efficient material set</a>.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Action Button</strong>: The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models include an Action Button, and in 2024, the Action Button could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-capture-button/">expanded to the standard iPhone 16 models</a>.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>A17 Chips</strong>: The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/iphone-16-first-chip-designed-for-standard/">expected to use an A17 chip</a>, but rumors suggest it won't be the same A17 Pro chip that's in the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.</li><br/>
	<li><strong>AI Capabilities</strong>: New <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">powered by large language models</a> are expected in iOS 18, but on-device AI features could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/iphone-16-exclusive-ai-features-ios-18/">remain exclusive to the iPhone 16 models</a>.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Stacked Battery Technology</strong>: Rumors suggest the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro models will use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/25/iphone-15-hybrid-lens-rumor/">stacked battery technology</a>, which can result in higher capacity and a longer lifespan.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Ultra Model</strong>: Apple could introduce a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-ultra/">high-end iPhone 16 "Ultra"</a> that would be sold alongside the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro, and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max. The device could feature additional camera improvements, a bigger display, and perhaps even a portless design.</li><br/>
</ul>Apple is expected to announce the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models around its usual September timeframe in 2024. More details about the devices will likely emerge before then, so be sure to bookmark MacRumors.com and of course keep tabs on our regularly updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16 roundup</a> for the latest information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/iphone-16-series-16-rumored-new-features/">iPhone 16 Series Rumored to Have These 16 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-rumored-to-have-these-16-new-features.2411041/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s New M3 iMac Gets First Major Discounts of Up to &#36;200 Off for Black Friday</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-new-m3-imac-discount/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-new-m3-imac-gets-first-major-discounts-of-up-to-200-off-for-black-friday.2411035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:32:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-new-m3-imac-discount/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're tracking a pair of discounts on Apple's brand new M3 iMac today, with as much as &#36;200 off these computers from <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793634-REG/apple_mqr93ll_a_24_imac_with_m3.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330375/SID/DFF">B&H Photo</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/M3-iMac-Feature-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921466" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The first discount is on the 8-Core GPU, 256GB iMac at B&H Photo, priced at <a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793634-REG/apple_mqr93ll_a_24_imac_with_m3.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330375/SID/DFF"><strong>&#36;1,199.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,299.00. This sale is only available in the Silver color option, and will last through November 18.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/1793634-REG/apple_mqr93ll_a_24_imac_with_m3.html/BI/2696/KBID/3612/DFF/d10-v21-t1-x1330375/SID/DFF"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-Core GPU, 256GB) for &#36;1,199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Secondly, Amazon has the 10-Core GPU, 256GB M3 iMac for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,499.00. This one is also only available in Silver, and it's another new record low price for the brand new M3 24-inch iMac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-Core GPU, 256GB) for &#36;1,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-new-m3-imac-discount/">Apple&#039;s New M3 iMac Gets First Major Discounts of Up to &#36;200 Off for Black Friday</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-new-m3-imac-gets-first-major-discounts-of-up-to-200-off-for-black-friday.2411035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Discontinues the Last macOS Install DVDs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-discontinues-the-last-macos-install-cds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-the-last-macos-install-dvds.2411034/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:24:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-discontinues-the-last-macos-install-cds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has officially ceased the sale of its last optical disc installers for older operating systems including OS X Lion 10.7 and Mountain Lion 10.8. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/os-x-mountain-lion-disc-page.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922637" /><br/>
The change was spotted by <a href="https://twitter.com/ClassicII_MrMac/status/1724458867696795856">@ClassicII_MrMac</a> on X, formerly Twitter. The era of Apple's optical discs began to wane with the introduction of OS X Lion in July 2011, which was the first version of macOS to be available exclusively through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mac-app-store/">Mac App Store</a>. OS X Lion introduced several features like Mission Control, Launchpad, full-screen apps, and significant improvements to Mail and other core apps.<br/>
<br/>
Due to customer demand, Apple briefly reverted to offering physical installation media for Lion and Mountain Lion, primarily to accommodate users with limited internet access or older machines without access to the &zwnj;Mac App Store&zwnj;. Mountain Lion, released in July 2012, followed suit with a focus on digital distribution, introducing features like the Notification Center, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> mirroring, and the Messages app. The first version of macOS to completely forego a physical release was OS X Mavericks (version 10.9), released in October 2013, and the digital update process remains similar to this day.<br/>
<br/>
While the physical install discs are now no more, Apple continues to offer <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/DL2077?locale=en_GB">OS X Lion</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/kb/DL2076?locale=en_GB">OS X Mountain Lion</a> as free digital downloads for those who still need them.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-discontinues-the-last-macos-install-cds/">Apple Discontinues the Last macOS Install DVDs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-discontinues-the-last-macos-install-dvds.2411034/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s MagSafe Duo Charger Hits Record Low &#36;79.99 Price in New Black Friday Sale</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-magsafe-duo-charger/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-magsafe-duo-charger-hits-record-low-79-99-price-in-new-black-friday-sale.2411033/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 06:17:34 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-magsafe-duo-charger/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Woot has been holding a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout">massive Apple accessory blowout sale</a> since the beginning of November, including deals on products like chargers, Apple Watch bands, iPhone cases, and more. They expanded the sale today and are now offering the MagSafe Duo Charger in new condition at <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"><strong>&#36;79.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/magsafe-duo-charger-gold-holiday-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922671" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is a new all-time low price on the accessory, and it beats the previous deal we tracked earlier in the month by about &#36;15. Woot is selling the MagSafe Duo Charger in new condition with a one year Apple manufacturer limited warranty.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;79.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The rest of <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Fplus%2Fnew-apple-accessory-blowout">Woot's Apple accessory sale</a> is worth checking out. You can get rock bottom prices on Apple Watch Series 4 and Series 6 models in new condition, USB-C chargers, Siri Remotes, and more. As of right now, the regular MagSafe Charger is not on sale any longer.<br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apples-magsafe-duo-charger/">Apple&#039;s MagSafe Duo Charger Hits Record Low &#36;79.99 Price in New Black Friday Sale</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-magsafe-duo-charger-hits-record-low-79-99-price-in-new-black-friday-sale.2411033/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro Onboarding Videos Unearthed in visionOS Beta 6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-vision-pro-onboarding-videos-visionos-beta-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-onboarding-videos-unearthed-in-visionos-beta-6.2411019/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 03:09:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-vision-pro-onboarding-videos-visionos-beta-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Tuesday seeded a sixth beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, the software designed to run on the Vision Pro headset, and it includes two new tutorial videos shown to the user during the setup process.   <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-vision-pro-eye.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922615" /><br/>
The first 36-second onboarding video, shared by <a href="https://x.com/M1Astra/status/1724506943425757367?s=20">@M1Astra</a>, is called "Input Training" and demonstrates how the user interacts with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; by looking at UI elements and selecting them using a double-tap gesture. The narrator says the following:<br/>
<blockquote>Your eyes and hands are how you navigate Apple Vision Pro. You browse the system by looking, and it responds to your eyes. Simply look at an element and tap your fingers together to select it. It's like a click on your Mac. To scroll, pinch your fingers together, and gently flick. You can keep your hands where they're comfortable, such as resting on your lap.</blockquote><div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">New onboarding video added in visionOS beta 6!<br><br>&quot;Input Training&quot; <a href="https://t.co/ThKGBL4FbA">pic.twitter.com/ThKGBL4FbA</a></p>&mdash; M1 (@M1Astra) <a href="https://twitter.com/M1Astra/status/1724506943425757367?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 14, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset, the built-in cameras create a customized "Persona" that resembles the user, and this Persona is used in video chat apps like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>. In a second, 50-second video also shared by <a href="https://x.com/M1Astra/status/1724539857752519028?s=20">@M1Astra</a>, "Persona Enrollment," Apple demonstrates how Personas are set up by using the EyeSight display to guide the user: <br/>
<blockquote>To set up your Persona, you'll remove Apple Vision Pro to capture your appearance. Take your time getting ready, and ensure nothing is covering your face. To start capturing, hold Apple Vision Pro at eye level. Keep your arms and shoulders relaxed. Then, follow the instructions. <br/>
<br/>
Turn your head to the right, to the left, and tilt up, and down. Then you'll capture your facial expressions. Smile with your mouth closed, smile showing your teeth, raise your eyebrows, and close your eyes. When you're done, put Apple Vision Pro back on to see your Persona.</blockquote><div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">New video tutorial showing Persona Enrollment for Apple Vision Pro added in visionOS beta 6!<br><br>The enrollment uses the EyeSight display to guide the user. <a href="https://t.co/cGfsdTuIaY">pic.twitter.com/cGfsdTuIaY</a></p>&mdash; M1 (@M1Astra) <a href="https://twitter.com/M1Astra/status/1724539857752519028?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 14, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
As we <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/05/apple-vision-pro-persona-glasses/">previously reported</a>, the 3D capture process requires users to remove anything that covers the face, such as glasses. There does not appear to be any kind of secondary scanning mechanism to separately capture a user's glasses, and instead, Apple will allow users to "Select Eyewear" from a variety of options.<br/>
<br/>
Personas are one aspect of ‌&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;‌ that Apple is working on perfecting before the launch of the Vision Pro headset. In September, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-vision-pro-developer-survey/">began surveying developers</a> who have the Vision Pro about their Personas, soliciting opinions on facial expressions, appearance matching, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro headset is set to launch in early 2024 in the United States, and it will be priced at &#36;3,500. The headset will likely be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/07/apple-vision-pro-launch-uk-canada-end-of-2024/">released in the UK and Canada later the same year</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/apple-vision-pro-onboarding-videos-visionos-beta-6/">Apple Vision Pro Onboarding Videos Unearthed in visionOS Beta 6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-onboarding-videos-unearthed-in-visionos-beta-6.2411019/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Rolls Out Voice Chats for Large Groups</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/whatsapp-rolls-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups.2411014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 01:48:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/whatsapp-rolls-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp is rolling out a new voice chats feature in groups that lets users start voice calls without disturbing everyone in the group.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/whatsapp-voice-chats.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922605" /><br/>
Previously in WhatsApp group chats, the only option was to start a voice call, which rings every member in the group. If no-one joins, the call doesn't go ahead. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, voice chats can be initiated in a group without anyone joining, and users are prompted to join discreetly via a silent push notification. The feature is available for those WhatsApp groups with 33 to 128 members.<br/>
<br/>
Group members not participating in the voice chat can see who is active in the call from the chat header and the Calls tab, and people can join or leave at any time. If the encrypted chat remains empty for 60 minutes, it automatically ends.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <a href="https://wabetainfo.com/whatsapp-is-rolling-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups-on-android-and-ios/">WABetaInfo</a>, the feature is now appearing for users on iOS and Android who have installed the latest WhatsApp update from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and Google Play Store, respectively.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/whatsapp-rolls-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups/">WhatsApp Rolls Out Voice Chats for Large Groups</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-voice-chats-for-large-groups.2411014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 14 Users Get Free Emergency SOS via Satellite for Another Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/emergency-sos-extra-year-iphone-14/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-users-get-free-emergency-sos-via-satellite-for-another-year.2411010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:22:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/emergency-sos-extra-year-iphone-14/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/apple-extends-emergency-sos-via-satellite-for-an-additional-free-year/">announced</a> that its Emergency SOS via satellite service is being extended for an additional free year for existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> users. Apple originally gave new &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; owners two free years after device activation, which would have expired in November 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/11/Emergency-SOS-via-Satellite-iPhone-YT.jpg" alt="" width="3564" height="1996" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-873000" /><br/>
Emergency SOS via Satellite is now free for two more years starting today or at the time of activation of any &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; model. Apple says the free trial will be extended for &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; users who have activated their device in <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213426">any country that supports Emergency SOS via satellite</a> prior to 12 a.m. Pacific Time on November 15, 2023. <br/>
<blockquote>"Emergency SOS via satellite has helped <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=b19w5cHUnPg">save lives around the world</a>. From a man who was rescued after his car plummeted over a 400-foot cliff in Los Angeles, to lost hikers found in the Apennine Mountains in Italy, we continue to hear stories of our customers being able to connect with emergency responders when they otherwise wouldn't have been able to," said Kaiann Drance, Apple's vice president of Worldwide iPhone Product Marketing. "We are so happy iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 users can take advantage of this groundbreaking service for two more years for free."</blockquote>Available on all &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, the feature enables users to send text messages to emergency services via satellite when cellular and Wi-Fi coverage is not available. Users can also share their location via satellite in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> app.<br/>
<br/>
With the service, Apple says users can send and receive messages in as little as 15 seconds in clear conditions. Users are prompted to complete a short questionnaire with vital information, and the interface then shows users where in the sky to point their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to connect and send the initial message. This message includes the user's questionnaire responses, location, altitude, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; battery level, and Medical ID info if set.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the service is designed to work outdoors with a clear view of the sky. Apple warns that foliage or other obstructions can result in emergency messages taking longer to send or failing to send, and satellite connectivity might not work in places above 62° latitude, such as northern parts of Canada and Alaska. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/15/emergency-sos-extra-year-iphone-14/">iPhone 14 Users Get Free Emergency SOS via Satellite for Another Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-users-get-free-emergency-sos-via-satellite-for-another-year.2411010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
