<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 04:04:20 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17: Five Features Apple Plans to Save for 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-five-features-apple-plans-to-save-for-2025.2414853/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 02:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhone development roadmap runs several years into the future and the company is continually working with suppliers on several successive iPhone models concurrently, which is why we sometimes get rumored feature leaks so far ahead of launch. The iPhone 17 series is no different, and already we have some idea of what to expect from Apple's 2025 smartphone lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-17-Five-Features-Header.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927358" /><br/>
If you plan to skip next year's iPhone 16, or if you're just plain curious, here are five rumored features that we are expecting to arrive in time for its successor, the iPhone 17 series, which is likely to be released in September 2025.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    1. Larger Standard Devices</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 17 & iPhone 17 Plus</span><br><br/>
Next year's iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/30/iphone-16-pro-to-feature-taller-aspect-ratio/">rumored</a> to be getting bigger display sizes, going from 6.12- and 6.69-inches to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. With the ‌iPhone‌ 17 and ‌iPhone‌ 17 Plus in 2025, Apple is expected to also bring the larger 6.27- and 6.86-inch display sizes to its two standard ‌iPhone‌ models. As a result, expect the entire iPhone 17 lineup to use a taller aspect ratio of 19.6:9, suggesting the devices will be slightly taller, rather than wider. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    2. 120Hz ProMotion (Always-on Display)</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 17 & iPhone 17 Plus</span><br><br/>
Apple intends to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/promotion-standard-iphones-2025/">expand</a> ProMotion to its standard models in 2025, allowing them to ramp up to a 120Hz refresh rate for smoother scrolling and video content when necessary. Notably, ProMotion would also enable the display on the iPhone 17 and iPhone 17 Plus to ramp down to a more power-efficient refresh rate as low as 1Hz, allowing for an always-on display that can show the Lock Screen's clock, widgets, notifications, and wallpaper even when the device is locked.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">3. Under-Display Face ID</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 17 Pro & iPhone 17 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 17 Pro is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/03/under-display-face-id-to-debut-on-iphone-17-pro/">expected</a> to be the first ‌iPhone‌ to feature under-panel Face ID technology. The only external indication of the under-display ‌Face ID‌ technology will likely be a circular cutout for the front-facing camera. This will probably be Apple's last premium model to include a circular cutout for the front-facing camera. Apple is then <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/06/iphone-under-display-camera/">expected</a> adopt under-display cameras in 2027's "Pro" ‌iPhone‌ models for a true "all-screen" appearance.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">4. Apple-Designed Wi-Fi 7 Chip</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 17 Pro & iPhone 17 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
Apple's premium models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/iphone-17-pro-apple-wifi-7-chip-rumor/">expected</a> to be equipped with an Apple-designed Wi-Fi 7 chip for the first time. Wi-Fi 7 support would allow the "Pro" models to send and receive data over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously with a supported router, resulting in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. The Wi-Fi chip would also allow Apple to further reduce its dependance on external suppliers like Broadcom, which currently supplies Apple with a combined Wi-Fi and Bluetooth chip for iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;">5. 48MP Telephoto Lens</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 17 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
An upgraded 48-megapixel Telephoto lens on Apple's largest premium device is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto-lens-rumor/">expected</a> to be optimized for use with Apple's upcoming Vision Pro headset, set to be released in the U.S. in early 2024. (The current iPhone 15 Pro models feature 48-megapixel main, 12-megapixel ultra wide, and 12-megapixel telephoto lenses.) That would make 2025's "Pro Max" the first iPhone to have a rear camera system composed entirely of 48-megapixel lenses, making it capable of capturing even more photographic detail.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/28/iphone-17-five-rumored-features-2025/">iPhone 17: Five Features Apple Plans to Save for 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-five-features-apple-plans-to-save-for-2025.2414853/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple in 2023: The Biggest News Stories and Surprises of the Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/the-biggest-apple-news-stories-of-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-in-2023-the-biggest-news-stories-and-surprises-of-the-year.2414830/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 16:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/the-biggest-apple-news-stories-of-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[2023 was a relatively iterative year for Apple product releases, but there were still many notable announcements and surprises throughout the year. Apple previewed its upcoming Vision Pro headset, the full-sized HomePod made a comeback, the iPhone finally switched to USB-C, leather accessories were discontinued, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Apple-in-2023-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928075" /><br/>
Below, we recap some of the most noteworthy Apple news stories of 2023, in no particular order.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Behold the Vision Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
After several years of rumors about Apple planning an augmented reality/virtual reality headset, the company <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/05/apple-reveals-vision-pro-headset/">officially unveiled the Vision Pro</a> in June. Apple says the headset will be available in the U.S. starting in early 2024, with pricing set at a staggering &#36;3,499.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro will allow you to interact with apps as if they are floating in the air. The headset is powered by an all-new operating system called visionOS, and it can be controlled with your eyes and hands. It has an Apple Watch-like Digital Crown for switching between virtual reality and augmented reality, and it is powered by an external battery pack.<br/>
<br/>
Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro roundup</a> for more details about the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>The Return of the HomePod</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-White-and-Midnight-Feature-Purple-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-881772" /><br/>
The full-sized HomePod made a comeback this year, as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-announces-new-homepod/">Apple announced a new model</a> in January.<br/>
<br/>
The second-generation HomePod features a virtually identical design as the full-sized model that was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/12/apple-discontinuing-homepod/">discontinued in 2021</a>. However, it has two fewer tweeters and two fewer microphones compared to the original model, and it has an added sensor that can measure temperature and humidity in indoor environments. Many early reviews of the latest HomePod said it has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/homepod/">very similar sound quality</a> as the original model. <br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., the HomePod is priced at &#36;299, with white and midnight color options available.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone Goes USB-C — Finally!</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
It finally happened. After years of hopes and rumors, all iPhone 15 models are equipped with a USB-C port instead of Lightning.<br/>
<br/>
While the USB-C port on iPhones is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-usb-c-port-completely-standard/">completely standard</a>, only the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/">support USB 3.2</a> data transfer speeds of up to 10 Gbps. The lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-usb-port-limited-to-lightning-speeds/">limited to USB 2.0 data transfer speeds</a> of up to 480 Mbps, which is equal to Lightning speeds on previous iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
All iPhone 15 models can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-usb-c-port-apple-watch-airpods-charging/">charge an Apple Watch, AirPods case, and other small accessories</a> connected to the USB-C port, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/">support DisplayPort for up to 4K HDR video mirroring and video output</a> to an external display or TV.<br/>
<br/>
Apple still sells a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/">handful of devices and accessories with Lightning ports</a>, all of which will likely be updated with USB-C or discontinued in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Green Bubble Dreams</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
In November, Apple announced that it will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS</a> in the Messages app on the iPhone starting "later next year." Based on that timeframe, RCS support will likely be added as part of iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
RCS support should result in the following improvements to the default messaging experience between iPhones and Android devices:<ul><br/>
 <li>Higher-resolution photos and videos</li><br/>
 <li>Audio messages</li><br/>
 <li>Typing indicators</li><br/>
 <li>Read receipts</li><br/>
 <li>Wi-Fi messaging between iPhones and Android devices</li><br/>
 <li>Improved group chats, including the ability for iPhone users to leave a conversation that includes Android users</li><br/>
 <li>Improved encryption compared to SMS</li><br/>
</ul>These modern features are already available for iPhone-to-iPhone conversations with blue bubbles, via iMessage, and many of the features are also available in third-party messaging apps, such as WhatsApp and Telegram. RCS support on the iPhone will extend the features to green bubbles in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
Google had been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/02/google-again-pushes-apple-to-adopt-rcs/">urging Apple to adopt RCS</a> for a few years.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>All the Apple Wallet News</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-card-savings-account-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892213" /><br/>
2023 was a big year for the Apple Wallet app on the iPhone, as several new features launched, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/apple-card-savings-account-launching-today/">Apple Card savings account</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-pay-later-launches/">Apple Pay Later financing option</a>, and more. However, it wasn't all good news on this front, as it was reported that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/28/apple-goldman-sachs-partnership-ending/">Apple Card's financial partner Goldman Sachs will be out</a> in the next year or so.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M3 Trio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
During its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/30/everything-apple-announced-october-2023-event/">Halloween-themed "Scary Fast" event</a> in October, Apple announced the M3, M3 Pro, and M3 Max chips for the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro all at once, rather than holding the Pro and Max chips for a later time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple updated the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with M3 Pro and M3 Max chips, and there is also an entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the standard M3 chip. Other new features for the laptops include a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/space-black-macbook-pro-hands-on-videos/">Space Black finish</a> for M3 Pro and M3 Max configurations, and 20% brighter displays for standard content.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Goodbye Leather, Hello FineWoven</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913676" /><br/>
As part of its efforts to be environmentally friendly, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-finewoven/">discontinued all of its leather accessories</a> this year, including iPhone cases, Apple Watch bands, AirTag holders, the MagSafe Wallet, and more. Apple unveiled a new FineWoven material as a replacement for leather, but <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/25/finewoven-iphone-case-continued-criticism/">customers complained about quality issues</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s Jessica Nix referred to FineWoven as Apple's "<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-25/apple-s-finewoven-fabric-emerges-as-its-biggest-misfire-of-2023">biggest dud of 2023</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Final Cut Pro for iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-iPad-Final-Cut-Pro-Logic-Pro-hero-feature-actual-icons.jpg" alt="" width="2499" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896926" /><br/>
YouTubers rejoiced this year when Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/23/apple-releases-final-cut-pro-logic-pro-for-ipad/">expanded its video creation app Final Cut Pro to the iPad</a>. The app was previously only available on the Mac.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says Final Cut Pro for the iPad is optimized for the device's touch-first interface, providing the "ultimate mobile studio for video and music creators." The app is priced at &#36;4.99 per month or &#36;49 per year in the U.S., after a one-month free trial, and it is compatible with iPad models equipped with the M1 chip or newer.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also released its music creation app Logic Pro for the iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next-Generation CarPlay Teaser</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
Apple said that the first vehicles with support for its next-generation CarPlay system would be announced in late 2023, and it delivered on that promise with just days to spare. Earlier this month, Aston Martin and Porsche <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/20/first-next-generation-carplay-vehicles-announced/">previewed what the next-generation CarPlay experience will look like</a> in some of their upcoming vehicles.<br/>
<br/>
Aston Martin confirmed that it will release its first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay in 2024, but there is no specific timeframe and details remain slim.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first previewed the next-generation CarPlay experience in June 2022, promising deeper integration with the instrument cluster and climate controls, support for multiple displays across the dashboard, a dedicated FM radio app, widgets, and more. The interface can be tailored to each specific vehicle model and automaker's brand identity.<br/>
<br/>
When first unveiling next-generation CarPlay last year, Apple said committed automakers included Acura, Audi, Ford, Honda, Infiniti, Jaguar, Land Rover, Lincoln, Mercedes-Benz, Nissan, Polestar, Porsche, Renault, and Volvo. Beyond the addition of Aston Martin, it's unclear if this list has changed since that initial announcement.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Sales Ban</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/apple-watch-series-6-blood-oxygen-monitoring-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="897" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-759072" /><br/>
Earlier this month, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-pausing-series-9-ultra-2-sales-in-us/">paused sales of the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 in the U.S.</a> due to a patent dispute with medical tech company Masimo, which has accused Apple of poaching its employees and stealing trade secrets in order to develop the blood oxygen sensing feature available on the Apple Watch Series 6 and newer.<br/>
<br/>
In January, the U.S. International Trade Commission ruled that Apple had infringed on a Masimo patent related to blood oxygen sensing, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/27/us-trade-tribunal-apple-watch-ban-masimo/">ordered an import and sales ban</a> for Apple Watch models offering the feature. However, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">Apple appealed the decision</a> in court and was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">granted a temporary stay</a>, so the ban is lifted for now.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/the-biggest-apple-news-stories-of-2023/">Apple in 2023: The Biggest News Stories and Surprises of the Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-in-2023-the-biggest-news-stories-and-surprises-of-the-year.2414830/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Available in Apple Stores Starting Today, Online Sales to Resume Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-available-in-stores-today/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-available-in-apple-stores-starting-today-online-sales-to-resume-tomorrow.2414825/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 14:28:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-available-in-stores-today/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>ITC</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> are back in some of Apple's retail stores in the United States today, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1740133644835164569"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. Select stores will have availability today, while all stores will have the Apple Watch models back in stock by December 30. Online sales of the devices are set to resume tomorrow by 12:00 p.m. Pacific Time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
Apple is able to begin selling the Apple Watch models again after the U.S. Court of Appeals temporarily paused the import ban levied by the U.S. International Trade Commission. It's likely that Apple will be able to sell the Apple Watch models through most of January, and perhaps longer depending on what the court decides.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">import ban has been halted</a> while the appeals court determines whether a longer pause should be implemented while the full ITC vs. Apple appeal plays out. If that happens, the import ban will be stayed for several months, but if the appeals court decides not to stay the ban during the appeals process, Apple will need to stop sales again.<br/>
<br/>
The U.S. ITC has until January 10 to argue its case for the import ban to restart immediately, and the appeals court is accepting letters supporting or opposing the import ban through January 15. After that, the court will make a final ruling on the stay.<br/>
<br/>
Apple paused &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 sales <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-watch-removed-from-online-store/">online on December 21</a> and in stores after December 24 to comply with an ITC ruling. The ITC banned imports of Apple Watch components related to blood oxygen monitoring technology after it decided the Apple Watch infringes on patents owned by medical device company Masimo.<br/>
<br/>
The temporary stay on the ban not only allows Apple to resume sales for now, but it also gives Apple time to provide adequate stock to third-party retailers in case the ban is reinstated. Apple retail stores in the United States will have to stop selling the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and Ultra 2 if that happens, but the ban does not extend to retailers like Best Buy, Walmart, and Target.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itc/">ITC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-available-in-stores-today/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Available in Apple Stores Starting Today, Online Sales to Resume Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-available-in-apple-stores-starting-today-online-sales-to-resume-tomorrow.2414825/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get the Best Prices of the Season on Popular Apple Accessories Including AirTag, Apple Pencil, and MagSafe Charger</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/accessories-airtag-pencil-best-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-best-prices-of-the-season-on-popular-apple-accessories-including-airtag-apple-pencil-and-magsafe-charger.2414800/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 10:42:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/accessories-airtag-pencil-best-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a collection of deals on Apple accessories, many of which are at all-time low prices this week. This includes AirTag, MagSafe Charger, Apple Pencil 2, MagSafe Duo Charger, and the Pro Display XDR. All of these deals can be found on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/magsafe-xmas.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-923177" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights include the AirTag at &#36;23.99 (&#36;6 off) and AirTag 4-Pack at &#36;78.99 (&#36;20 off), both of which are just a few dollars away from their previous all-time low prices and are the best prices we've tracked during the holiday season.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0933BVK6T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;6 OFF</div>AirTag 1 Pack for &#36;23.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>AirTag 4 Pack for &#36;78.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For MagSafe products, there's the MagSafe Charger at &#36;29.00 (&#36;10 off) and MagSafe Duo Charger at &#36;98.50 (&#36;30 off). These are also just a few dollars short of their record low prices, and certainly the best deals you'll find for the remainder of 2023.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>MagSafe Charger for &#36;29.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08MWR2NXZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;98.50</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Amazon has the Apple Pencil 2 at &#36;89.00 (&#36;40 off) and there's also a record low price on the Pro Display XDR (Standard Glass), priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB082LZTDX5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;4,399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;4,999.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB082LZTDX5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;599 OFF</div>Pro Display XDR for &#36;4,399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/accessories-airtag-pencil-best-prices/">Get the Best Prices of the Season on Popular Apple Accessories Including AirTag, Apple Pencil, and MagSafe Charger</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-the-best-prices-of-the-season-on-popular-apple-accessories-including-airtag-apple-pencil-and-magsafe-charger.2414800/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Sales Ban Paused by US Appeals Court</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused-by-us-appeals-court.2414792/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 08:49:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">ban on imports</a> of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> models has today been temporarily paused, meaning that the devices can now go back on sale for a short while longer in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
Apple filed an emergency request to the United States Court of Appeals following President Biden's decision to decline a veto on the sales ban, allowing it to take effect earlier this week. The Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cafc.21094/gov.uscourts.cafc.21094.19.0_1.pdf">today accepted</a> an interim stay while the court reviews Apple's request for a full stay for the length of the appeal, effectively pausing the ban on Apple Watch imports for a brief period. <br/>
<br/>
The International Trade Commission (ITC) now has until January 10 to file its response to Apple's request for a full stay while the appeal plays out. The ITC initiated proceedings against Apple after Masimo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/19/masimo-ceo-on-apple-watch-ban/">accuses Apple</a> of hiring away its employees to steal technology related to blood oxygen monitoring in the Apple Watch.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Sales Ban Paused by US Appeals Court</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-sales-ban-paused-by-us-appeals-court.2414792/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Future HomePod Again Rumored to Add Curved LCD Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/future-homepod-again-rumored-to-add-curved-lcd-display.2414776/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:42:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>Kosutami</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing work on a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> model that features a curved LCD display, according to the Apple leaker and prototype collector known as "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a>."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/homepod-b720.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928024" /><br/>
The device, codenamed B720, apparently features the same design as the current &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; but with a curved, convex LCD screen at the top to display content.<br/>
<br/>
In October, Kosutami shared <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/21/images-show-new-homepod-with-screen/">images of component parts</a> that allegedly belong to a prototype touch screen &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;. Other reports at the time claimed to verify the legitimacy of these images with other sources.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">More details on HomePod B720<br>Same panel size and same design with HomePod 2. Screen were bit curved, looks great after got assembled.<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/appleinternal?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#appleinternal</a> <a href="https://t.co/z8mYgeI3O2">pic.twitter.com/z8mYgeI3O2</a></p>&mdash; Kosutami (@KosutamiSan) <a href="https://twitter.com/KosutamiSan/status/1739573100604477766?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 26, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple is believed to be working to adapt <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-podcasts/">Apple Podcasts</a> to be compatible with the new display, which will show a blurred animation based on the colors of the album art when a song or podcast is playing. The screen could also potentially show important notifications. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> was first to suggest in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/22/apple-speakers-with-screens-and-cameras-report/">2021</a> that Apple is working on new HomePods with displays and cameras. Earlier this year, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> claimed Apple plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">redesigned HomePod with a 7-inch display</a> in the first half of 2024. <br/>
<br/>
In the long term, Apple is believed to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/08/08/apple-engineers-pessimistic-apple-tv-strategy/">rethinking its smart home strategy</a>, and is working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/28/gurman-combined-homepod-apple-tv-in-development/">combined Apple TV and HomePod device</a>, as well as a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/04/12/homepod-ipad-with-robotic-arm/">screen mounted on a robotic arm</a>, according to a Gurman.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/kosutami/">Kosutami</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/">Future HomePod Again Rumored to Add Curved LCD Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/future-homepod-again-rumored-to-add-curved-lcd-display.2414776/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AliveCor Praises Apple Watch Ban Amid Its Own Health Tech Patent Dispute With Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/alivecor-praises-apple-watch-ban/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alivecor-praises-apple-watch-ban-amid-its-own-health-tech-patent-dispute-with-apple.2414774/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 05:11:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/alivecor-praises-apple-watch-ban/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AliveCor</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Health technology company AliveCor has praised the International Trade Commission (ITC)'s ban on sales of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/apple-watch-ecg-wrist.jpg" alt="" width="1119" height="630" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-781502" /><br/>
AliveCor, like Masimo, accuses Apple of violating its patents related to heath technology used in the Apple Watch. While Masimo's fight focuses on the Apple Watch's blood oxygen sensing capabilities, AliveCor contends that Apple is in breach of patent with its ECG technology.<br/>
<br/>
AliveCor demonstrated a prototype Apple Watch band with a built-in ECG sensor to Apple in 2015. Apple then unveiled its own built-in ECG technology in 2018 with the Apple Watch Series 4, leading AliveCor to argue that Apple had stolen its technology and request that the ITC bans Apple Watch sales in the United States. AliveCor also initiated an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/05/26/alivecor-apple-watch-antitrust-lawsuit/">antitrust lawsuit</a> against Apple, alleging that it was making it needlessly difficult for third-party apps to access the Apple Watch's heart rate data.<br/>
<br/>
In a statement to <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/12/26/alivecor-apple-watch-ban-patents/"><em>9to5Mac</em></a>, AliveCor expressed its support for Masimo and praised the move to ban Apple Watch sales:<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>This is the second time in less than 12 months President Biden has allowed an International Trade Commission Limited Exclusion Order (LEO) to stand against imports of Apple Watches that violate the patents of small U.S. innovators. Earlier this year, AliveCor's patent for its FDA-cleared personal electrocardiogram (ECG) technology was similarly affirmed and we share our support today for Masimo's tenacity in its face off with Apple. Innovator companies and health consumers alike should be encouraged that industry giants are increasingly being held accountable for anticompetitive practices that would ultimately limit access to potentially life-saving technology.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The ITC <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/22/biden-admin-upholds-apple-watch-patent-ruling/">ruled in favor of AliveCor</a>'s patent infringement claims, but the case did not result in a ban on Apple Watch sales as AliveCor hoped. Unlike AliveCor, Masimo argues that Apple actively hired its engineers and key executives to steal technology. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alivecor/">AliveCor</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/alivecor-praises-apple-watch-ban/">AliveCor Praises Apple Watch Ban Amid Its Own Health Tech Patent Dispute With Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/alivecor-praises-apple-watch-ban-amid-its-own-health-tech-patent-dispute-with-apple.2414774/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Video to Feature Ads From January 29, With &#36;2.99 Fee to Avoid Them</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/amazon-prime-video-to-feature-ads-from-january-29/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-video-to-feature-ads-from-january-29-with-2-99-fee-to-avoid-them.2414771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 04:15:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/amazon-prime-video-to-feature-ads-from-january-29/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		<category>Amazon Prime Video</category>
		<category>Amazon Prime</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Video will introduce limited ads to its content starting on January 29, offering an ad-free option for an additional fee.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/prime-video-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928010" /><br/>
In an email to subscribers, Amazon confirmed that movies and TV shows on Prime Video will soon feature "limited advertisements" starting on January 29, 2024. The company assured users that Prime Video will have "meaningfully fewer ads than linear TV and other streaming TV providers."<br/>
<br/>
The current price of Amazon Prime subscriptions will not change, but members who prefer to avoid ads can opt for a new ad-free version at an extra cost of &#36;2.99 per month. Amazon's email to subscribers reads:<blockquote>Dear Prime member, <br/>
<br/>
We are writing to you today about an upcoming change to your Prime Video experience. Starting January 29, Prime Video movies and TV shows will include limited advertisements. This will allow us to continue investing in compelling content and keep increasing that investment over a long period of time. We aim to have meaningfully fewer ads than linear TV and other streaming TV providers. No action is required from you, and there is no change to the current price of your Prime membership. We will also offer a new ad-free option for an additional &#36;2.99 per month...</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Amazon already operates Freevee, a free, ad-supported streaming service. Competitor streaming services like Disney+, Hulu, and Netflix have also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/30/netflix-ad-plan-apple-tv/">introduced ad-supported options</a> amid rising subscription costs.<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon-prime-video/">Amazon Prime Video</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon-prime/">Amazon Prime</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/amazon-prime-video-to-feature-ads-from-january-29/">Amazon Prime Video to Feature Ads From January 29, With &#36;2.99 Fee to Avoid Them</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-video-to-feature-ads-from-january-29-with-2-99-fee-to-avoid-them.2414771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Official Vision Pro Cover Accessory Emerges in New Apple Design Patent</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/official-vision-pro-cover-accessory-emerges/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/official-vision-pro-cover-accessory-emerges-in-new-apple-design-patent.2414768/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 03:43:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/official-vision-pro-cover-accessory-emerges/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[An official <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> cover has emerged in new design patent filings from Hong Kong, revealing the first-party headset accessory for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/vision-pro-case.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-928003" /><br/>
Apple was granted 70 more design patents in Hong Kong related to its Vision Pro headset on Friday, December 22. The filings, first spotted by <em><a href="https://www.patentlyapple.com/2023/12/apple-has-won-another-70-design-patents-for-apple-vision-pro-including-one-for-a-new-headset-cover-a-new-magsafe-battery.html">PatentlyApple</a></em>, include a never-before-seen Vision Pro accessory with a range of accompanying images showing various angles of it.<br/>
<br/>
The accessory's design seems to match the Vision Pro's headband, using a soft-touch woven fabric to cover the entire front and sides of the headset. It does not cover the back of the headset or Light Seal in any way, likely being designed to help protect the headset's EyeSight display from scratches and other damage. The cover also features a tab on the left-hand side to help remove it from the headset easily.<br/>
<br/>
The other notable design patent won by Apple in the latest batch of filings is a Vision Pro battery, incorrectly identified by some websites as a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> battery pack, showing a recessed port. This is worth highlighting as it confirms that the battery unit's cable is removable.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/official-vision-pro-cover-accessory-emerges/">Official Vision Pro Cover Accessory Emerges in New Apple Design Patent</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/official-vision-pro-cover-accessory-emerges-in-new-apple-design-patent.2414768/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Japan Preparing EU-Style Law to Force Apple to Allow App Sideloading and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/japan-preparing-eu-style-law/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/japan-preparing-eu-style-law-to-force-apple-to-allow-app-sideloading-and-more.2414767/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 03:11:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/japan-preparing-eu-style-law/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Japan</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Japan is preparing antitrust legislation to force Apple to allow app sideloading and alternative payment methods for in-app purchases, <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/Japan-to-crack-down-on-Apple-and-Google-app-store-monopolies"><em>Nikkei Asia</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iOS-App-Store-General-Feature-Desaturated.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-833991" /><br/>
The plans by Japan's Fair Trade Commission focus on combating Apple and Google's dominance in app stores and payments, search, browsers, and operating systems. The regulation could encompass a wide range of changes to Apple's practices, such as an obligation to allow users to utilize alternative app stores, effectively allowing sideloading on iPhones and iPads in Japan.<br/>
<br/>
The regulation also looks to impose fines for violations of the rules amounting to around six percent of revenue earned from "problematic activities." The Fair Trade Commission's work on the legislation is ongoing, with plans to finalize it in the spring. The legislation will have to be approved by parliament in 2024 before coming into effect.<br/>
<br/>
Japan's proposed regulation bears a strong resemblance to the European Union's Digital Markets Act (DMA), which is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">set to force Apple</a> to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/17/app-sideloading-support-coming-ios-17/">enable app sideloading</a> in the EU by March 2024 among other significant changes.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/japan/">Japan</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/japan-preparing-eu-style-law/">Japan Preparing EU-Style Law to Force Apple to Allow App Sideloading and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/japan-preparing-eu-style-law-to-force-apple-to-allow-app-sideloading-and-more.2414767/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Another Apple Designer Joins Jony Ive to Work on Hardware for OpenAI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/another-apple-designer-to-work-on-openai-hardware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/another-apple-designer-joins-jony-ive-to-work-on-hardware-for-openai.2414765/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2023 02:45:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/another-apple-designer-to-work-on-openai-hardware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Jony Ive</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>LoveFrom</category>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's vice president of product design Tang Tan is set to join Sir Jony Ive's LoveFrom to design hardware products for OpenAI, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-12-26/apple-iphone-design-head-tang-tan-to-work-with-jony-ive-sam-altman-on-ai-tech"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/chatgpt-for-iphone-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-896306" /><br/>
Tan will become the latest Apple designer to join LoveFrom, a design company founded by Jony Ive after he departed Apple in 2019. A total of 14 members of Ive's former design team at Apple have now left the company. Only around six designers who once reported to Ive still remain at Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Ive took more Apple designers with him to LoveFrom than remain at Apple. To date, more than 20 former Apple employees have joined Ive's new design firm, including Marc Newson and Shota Aoyagi.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> says that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/28/jony-ive-iphone-artificial-intelligence-openai/">Ive's work for OpenAI</a> marks one of his "most ambitious efforts" since he left Apple, and he apparently hopes to turn the work into a new company, with current efforts focused on hiring talent and creating concepts.<br/>
<br/>
At Apple, Tang Tan is vice president of product design and reports to senior vice president of hardware engineering John Ternus. Tan is responsible for the design of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, Apple Watch, accessories, and acoustic devices like AirPods. News of his departure emerged <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/iphone-product-design-vp-leaves-apple/">earlier this month</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Tan will lead hardware engineering on the OpenAI project while working at LoveFrom. Little is known about OpenAI's hardware ambitions, but <em>Bloomberg</em> claims that projects in the concept stage include devices for the home. Tan officially departs Apple in February, but his responsibilities have already been divided up among successors.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/jony-ive/">Jony Ive</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lovefrom/">LoveFrom</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/another-apple-designer-to-work-on-openai-hardware/">Another Apple Designer Joins Jony Ive to Work on Hardware for OpenAI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/another-apple-designer-joins-jony-ive-to-work-on-hardware-for-openai.2414765/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reveals Annual Japanese New Year Promotion With Special AirTag</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-annual-japanese-new-year-promotion-with-special-airtag.2414723/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 11:05:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In celebration of the Japanese New Year, Apple will be <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/gifts/new-year">holding a promotion</a> that offers customers in Japan a free Apple gift card worth up to ¥30,000 with the purchase of an eligible Apple product from January 2 through January 5.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Japanese-New-Year-Apple-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927987" /><br/>
Gift card values range from ¥4,000 for products like the iPhone SE and third-generation AirPods to ¥30,000 for the 15-inch MacBook Air.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to a gift card, the first 50,000 customers in Japan who purchase a new iPhone 14, iPhone 14 Plus, iPhone 13, or third-generation iPhone SE from Apple during the promotion will receive a limited-edition AirTag with a "Year of the Dragon" engraving.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has shared <a href="https://www.apple.com/jp/shop/gifts/new-year/terms-conditions">terms and conditions</a> for the promotion with additional details. Notably, iPhone orders placed through the Apple Store app will not qualify for a limited-edition AirTag, so make sure to complete your purchase on Apple's website or at a physical Apple Store in Japan if you are interested in receiving one.<br/>
<br/>
Apple holds a Japanese New Year promotion on an annual basis, and this is the third consecutive year it has offered a special AirTag.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apples-japanese-new-year-promotion-2024/">Apple Reveals Annual Japanese New Year Promotion With Special AirTag</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reveals-annual-japanese-new-year-promotion-with-special-airtag.2414723/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Lowe&#039;s Retail Stores Now Accept Apple Pay</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lowes-retail-stores-now-accept-apple-pay.2414712/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:52:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pay</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Lowe's home improvement stores across the United States have finally started accepting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>. &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; has been available in the Lowe's app and the Lowe's website for some time, but the company has been a longtime &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; holdout for its retail store locations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-pay-feature-dynamic-island.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-921515" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/18k2k1u/tap_and_pay_and_apple_pay/">On Reddit</a>, Lowe's employees said in late December that they had received a memo about the upcoming &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; and contactless payment rollout, which was set to begin on December 20.<br/>
<br/>
A Lowe's customer on the <em>MacRumors</em> forums said that he was able to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-pay-lowes.2388023/page-2">successfully use Apple Pay</a> at two different Lowe's stores in Texas, confirming the rollout.<br/>
<br/>
The Lowe's employees on Reddit said they were glad to hear about the rollout due to the <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/14uj8vt/do_you_guys_take_apple_pay/">number of customers</a> asking to use contactless payment options. There have also been many complaint threads from Lowe's customers about the lack of &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Lowes/comments/1005132/apple_pay/">on Reddit</a> and the <em>MacRumors</em> forums.<br/>
<br/>
Lowe's has more than 2,000 stores in the United States, making it the second largest home improvement store after Home Depot. Accepting &zwnj;Apple Pay&zwnj; could lure customers to Lowe's over Home Depot, as Home Depot does not accept the payment technology at this time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-music-apple-pay-card-icloud-fitness.134">Apple Music, Apple Pay/Card, iCloud, Fitness+</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/lowes-apple-pay/">Lowe&#039;s Retail Stores Now Accept Apple Pay</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lowes-retail-stores-now-accept-apple-pay.2414712/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Import Ban Now Official, Apple Appeals Decision</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-import-ban-now-official-apple-appeals-decision.2414706/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 07:18:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ITC</category>
		<category>Patent Lawsuits</category>
		<category>Masimo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is now officially unable to sell the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> in the United States as the International Trade Commission's import ban has become final. This morning, the Biden administration announced that it would not veto the ban.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/apple-watch-9-red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922237" /><br/>
The Office of the United States Trade Representative <a href="https://www.ustr.gov/about-us/policy-offices/press-office/press-releases/2023/december/ustr-statement-section-337-review">said that</a> after "careful consultations" it was opting not to reverse the ITC's decision.<blockquote>"On October 26, 2023, the U.S. International Trade Commission found that Apple, Inc. infringed two patents owned by Masimo Corporation and Cercacor Laboratories, Inc, both based in the United States. Since 2005, the Office of the United States Trade Representative has been delegated the President's authority under Section 337 of the Trade Act of 1930 to review the ITC's decision for a 60-day period. After careful consultations, Ambassador Tai decided not to reverse the ITC's determination and the ITC's decision became final on December 26, 2023."</blockquote>Apple in a statement to <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/biden-administration-allows-us-trade-tribunals-ban-apple-watch-imports-2023-12-26/">Reuters</a></em> said that it is "taking all measures" to get the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; back on store shelves as soon as possible.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has filed an appeal with the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit in Washington, and it has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-watch-import-ban-software-fix/">working on a software solution</a> that it hopes will allow it to resume sales.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; and the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; are not able to be sold by Apple in the United States at this time because the ITC ruled that the devices violate blood oxygen monitoring technology owned by medical device company Masimo.<br/>
<br/>
The ban is limited to Apple Watch models that have a blood oxygen sensor, so the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> is still on sale. It also only applies to Apple retail stores in the United States, so all Apple Watch models are still available in other countries. Stores like Target, Best Buy, and Walmart are able to continue Apple Watch sales as long as supplies hold out, but Apple is not able to bring more units into the United States from overseas.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will not be able to sell the &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; or the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; unless the appeal is successful, it settles with Masimo, or it finds a way to change the blood oxygen sensor so it is not using Masimo's patented technology.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/itc/">ITC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/patent-lawsuits/">Patent Lawsuits</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/masimo/">Masimo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/apple-watch-import-ban-official/">Apple Watch Import Ban Now Official, Apple Appeals Decision</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-import-ban-now-official-apple-appeals-decision.2414706/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>6 Essential iPhone Camera Tips for Taking Great Photos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-essential-iphone-camera-tips-for-taking-great-photos.2414690/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 03:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iPhones include several headline camera features that are worth using, such as Portrait Mode and Photographic Styles. But if all you want to use is the standard photo mode, there are still several tools and settings that can improve the composition of your pictures and help you capture the perfect shot using more traditional techniques.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Blue-Three-Quarters-Perspective-Camera-Closeup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909012" /><br/>
Whether you are the owner of a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> or a longtime user looking to up your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; photography game, here are six camera tools and settings in iOS that are worth checking out and experimenting with.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">1. Use the Rule of Thirds</h2><br/>
For a while now, Apple's Camera app has included a few optional settings that can help you line up your shots. Foremost in these settings is the Grid tool, which should be used when applying the rule of thirds. It divides the frame of your photo into a grid with two horizontal lines and two vertical lines, creating nine equal parts. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/grid-camera-tool.jpg" alt="" width="2716" height="1339" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927774" /><br/>
The rule of thirds helps guide the viewer's eye to the most important parts of your photo and creates a more harmonious composition. Here's how to overlay a grid on the viewfinder.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap Camera. </li><br/>
<li>In the "Composition" section, toggle on the switch next to Grid.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/camera-grid-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="2738" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927655" /><br/>
<br/>
Here are five things to keep in mind when using the grid to apple the rule of thirds.<br/>
<ul><br/>
    <li><strong>Identify the Key Elements</strong>: First, identify the main subjects or elements in the scene you want to photograph. These could be a person, a building, a tree, or any focal point.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Positioning the Subjects</strong>: Place these key elements along the lines or at the points where the lines intersect. For instance, if you're taking a photo of a person, you might position them along one of the vertical lines, rather than in the center of the frame.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Horizontal Elements</strong>: For horizontal elements like the horizon in a landscape, align them with one of the horizontal lines. For a more dramatic sky, place the horizon on the lower line. For more emphasis on the land or sea, place it on the upper line.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Balancing the Image</strong>: Use the rule of thirds to balance your photo. If you place a subject on the left, consider having something of lesser importance on the right to create a sense of balance.</li><br/>
    <li><strong>Experimentation</strong>: While the rule of thirds is a guideline, it's not a strict rule. Feel free to experiment with it and see how shifting elements in your frame changes the photo's impact.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">2. Straighten Top-Down Shots</h2><br/>
If you're taking a picture of something from above like a plate of food or an ornament on the ground, consider using the camera level, as it helps you capture a balanced shot without having to use a tripod arm or mount. It's also useful for taking a shot of something directly above you, like an object on the ceiling or in the sky.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/level-camera-tool-setting.jpg" alt="" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927776" /><br/>
The camera level tool used to be part of the Grid overlay, but Apple separated out the function in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, and it now has its own switch: Open the Settings app on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, select Camera, then toggle on the switch next to Level. Now you are ready to use it.<br/>
<ol><br/>
<li>Open the Camera app, and set the capture mode to <strong>Photo</strong>, <strong>Portrait</strong>, <strong>Square</strong>, or <strong>Time Lapse</strong>, using the sliding menu above the shutter button.</li><br/>
<li>Point the camera straight down above your subject (or straight up if the subject/scene you want to capture is above you).</li><br/>
<li>Line up the floating crosshair with the fixed crosshair in the center of the screen by adjusting the angle of your phone's camera. The crosshairs will both glow yellow when in perfect alignment. </li><br/>
<li>Tap the shutter button to capture the shot.</ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/camera-level-tool-in-action.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1058" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927779" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>The aligned crosshairs turn yellow (right), indicating the lens is parallel with the ground.</em></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">3. Straighten Your Horizontal Shots</h2><br/>
By making the Level tool an individual option in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, Apple has also included an additional horizontal level for more traditional straight-on photos.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/ios-17-camera-level-no.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899126" /><br/>
Turning the Level option on makes a broken horizontal line appear on the screen when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; senses that you're lining up for a straight-on shot and you tilt your device slightly out of horizontal. The line appears white while your phone is out of level and then turns yellow once you achieve a level orientation to indicate success.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/ios-17-camera-level.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-899127" /><br/>
With the Level setting enabled (Settings ➝ Camera ➝ Level), try it for yourself. Open the Camera app and try shooting a subject at a straight angle, and you should see the broken horizontal lines in the center of the viewfinder. Straighten your angle up to connect the lines and make a single yellow line.<br/>
<br/>
The leveling pop-up only appears briefly and only within a narrow range of angles close to horizontal (in either portrait or landscape orientation), so it won't intrusively pop up when you're intentionally trying to take a photo at an angle.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">4. Take Burst Photos</h2><br/>
Burst Mode refers to when the camera on your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; captures a series of photos in rapid succession, at a rate of ten frames per second. It's a great way to shoot an action scene or an unexpected event, since you're always more likely to end up with the picture you were aiming for.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2013/09/burstmode.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="460" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-386450" /><br/>
To shoot in Burst Mode, simply long press on the Volume Up button and your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; will take a series of photos in quick succession. Notice that a counter increases inside the on-screen shutter button for as long as you hold down the volume button. This indicates how many shots are being captured in the current burst. Simply take your finger off the volume when you want to end the burst of shots.<br/>
<br/>
When you take a series of burst photos, they automatically appear in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app under the Album name Bursts. You'll also find them in your main Photo Library. Follow the link to learn <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/delete-redundant-burst-mode-photos-iphone-ipad/">how to view and select the best of your Burst photos</a> in the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">5. Mirror Your Selfies</h2><br/>
When you take a selfie with your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; using the Camera app, it automatically flips – or mirrors – the image so that it's an inverted version of the mirror image you see in the preview before you take the shot.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/stop-flipped-selfie-iphone-ipad.jpg" alt="selfie" width="2710" height="2616" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757877" /><br/>
This can look odd, since it makes a big difference to how selfies look. It can also be annoying, since most third-party social media apps automatically take mirrored selfies, which means you're more likely to be used to the mirroring functionality than the flipped selfies that your ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ takes.<br/>
<br/>
Fortunately, you can change this default behavior of the Camera app, meaning that you can get the mirrored selfie you're probably more accustomed to seeing. Here's how.<br/>
<ol><li>Launch the <strong>Settings</strong> app, then scroll down and select <strong>Camera</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Toggle the switch next to <strong>Mirror Front Camera</strong> to the green ON position.</li></ol><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/mirror-front-camera-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927784" /><br/>
That's all there is to it. From now on when you use the Camera app to shoot a selfie, you'll capture the same shot that you saw in the app's preview mode.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 20px; color: #4A90E2;">6. View Outside the Frame</h2><br/>
On &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 and later models, there is an optional camera setting that allows you to see what is outside the bounds of your photo's frame, so you can correct the alignment of photos (and videos) without having to resort to cropping.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/capture-shot-outside-frame-iphone-11-camera-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="1544" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927787" /><br/>
With the "View Outside the Frame" setting enabled, when shooting using the wide lens or the telephoto lens, the camera will simultaneously shoot using the next widest sensor. So the wide lens is active when you shoot with the telephoto lens, and the ultra-wide is active when you shoot with the wide. <br/>
<ol><li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
<li>Scroll down and tap Camera.</li><br/>
<li>Under the "Composition" section, toggle on the switch next to View Outside the Frame.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/view-outside-frame-setting.jpg" alt="settings" width="1338" height="700" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927786" /><br/>
<br/>
You may have to play around with zoom levels to switch between lenses, but you'll know the feature is active when the camera interface turns semi-transparent to reveal the surroundings outside of the viewfinder.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/26/6-iphone-camera-tips-great-photos/">6 Essential iPhone Camera Tips for Taking Great Photos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/6-essential-iphone-camera-tips-for-taking-great-photos.2414690/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10 Ways to Spend an Apple Gift Card You Received for Christmas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-ways-to-spend-an-apple-gift-card-you-received-for-christmas.2414637/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 06:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you received an Apple gift card for Christmas this year, here are 10 ways to spend it, with all of the options priced under &#36;100 in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/11/apple-gift-card-blue-holiday.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-826644" /><br/>
The all-in-one gift card "for everything Apple" can be used towards purchases on Apple.com and at physical Apple Stores, iTunes Store music, App Store apps and games, subscriptions to services like Apple Music and Apple TV+, and more.<br/>
<br/>
To redeem an Apple gift card on an iPhone or iPad, open the App Store, tap your profile photo in the top-right corner, and tap "Redeem Gift Card or Code."<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What to Buy With an Apple Gift Card</h2><br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUYG3AM/A/magsafe-charging-case-usb%E2%80%91c-for-airpods-pro-2nd-generation">USB-C Case for AirPods Pro 2</a> (&#36;99)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911678" /><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/13/apple-selling-standalone-usb-c-airpods-pro-case/">now selling</a> a USB-C charging case for the second-generation AirPods Pro separately for &#36;99. Keep in mind that if you want your AirPods Pro earbuds to have lossless audio support with Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro headset</a>, and added IP54-rated dust resistance, you will need to purchase the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTJV3AM/A/airpods-pro">AirPods Pro with a USB-C case</a> altogether. <br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUWA3AM/A/apple-pencil-usb-c">Apple Pencil With USB-C Port</a> (&#36;79)</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
Apple this year released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">more affordable Apple Pencil</a> with a hidden USB-C port for charging and pairing. Priced at &#36;79, it has a similar design as the second-generation Apple Pencil, but it lacks wireless charging, pressure sensitivity, a double-tap gesture for switching between drawing tools, and the option for personal engraving at the time of purchase.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-airtag/airtag">AirTag</a> (&#36;29)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/airtag-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-849630" /><br/>
Keep track of your belongings with Apple's item tracker, which integrates with the Find My app on the iPhone, iPad, and Mac. A four-pack is also available for &#36;99.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNWM3AM/A/35w-dual-usb-c-port-compact-power-adapter">Apple's 35W Dual USB-C Charger</a> (&#36;59)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Apple-35W-Charger-feeature.jpg" alt="" width="2080" height="1171" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850450" /><br/>
Apple last year released 35W power adapters with dual USB-C ports, with standard and compact versions of the charger available for &#36;59 each. Both adapters feature foldable prongs and can be used to charge or power multiple lower-power Apple devices simultaneously, such as an iPhone, iPad, Apple Watch, and HomePod mini.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNC73AM/A/siri-remote">Apple TV Remote With USB-C Port</a> (&#36;59)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/siri-remote-1.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-800838" /><br/>
Apple last year released a new version of the Siri Remote for the Apple TV with a USB-C port instead of Lightning for charging. If you already own an Apple TV model released in 2015 or later, the remote can be purchased separately for &#36;59.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MM6F3AM/A/polishing-cloth">Apple Polishing Cloth</a> (&#36;19)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/10/apple-polishing-cloth-green-feature.jpg" alt="" width="3036" height="1708" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-821771" /><br/>
Clean your iPhone, iPad, Mac, Apple Watch, Studio Display, and other devices with Apple's official polishing cloth, released in 2021.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-one/">Apple One</a></h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/Apple-One-Apps-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1012" height="601" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-760995" /><br/>
Redeem your Apple gift card and use the balance towards Apple One, which lets you subscribe to multiple Apple services at a discount. The base Apple One plan includes Apple Music, Apple TV+, Apple Arcade, and iCloud+ with 50GB of storage for &#36;19.95 per month, which is &#36;9 less per month compared to subscribing to these services separately.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HNNT2ZM/A/twelve-south-airfly-pro-bluetooth-transmitter">Twelve South's AirFly Pro</a> (&#36;54.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirFly-Pro-Twelve-South-feature.jpeg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878316" /><br/>
Twelve South's popular AirFly Pro accessory lets you use AirPods or Beats wireless headphones with an airplane's in-flight entertainment system. Simply plug AirFly Pro into the headphone jack on a plane to watch or listen with your AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQGM2ZM/A/Nanoleaf%20Essentials%20Matter%20A19%20Smart%20Bulb%20-%20Thread%20&%20Matter-Enabled%20Smart%20LED%20Light%20Bulb%20-%20White%20and%20Color">Nanoleaf's Essentials A19 Light Bulb</a> (&#36;19.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Nanoleaf-A19.jpeg" alt="" width="800" height="480" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-878315" /><br/>
Nanoleaf's smart color-changing LED bulb is compatible with HomeKit, allowing it to be controlled in the Home app and with Siri. A three-pack is also available for &#36;49.95.<br/>
<br/>
<h3><a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ642ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-notebooks">Belkin's iPhone Mount for Continuity Camera</a> (&#36;29.95)</h3><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/continuity-camera.jpg" alt="" width="1930" height="1276" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848371" /><br/>
Belkin sells an iPhone mount for use with Continuity Camera, a feature that allows an iPhone to be used as a Mac's webcam. Priced at &#36;29.95, the mount attaches to the iPhone with MagSafe and can then be affixed to the top lid of a MacBook Air or MacBook Pro for use with Continuity Camera. Belkin also offers a desktop version of the mount <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ652ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-desktops-and-displays">compatible with the 24-inch iMac and the Studio Display</a> for &#36;39.95.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/apple-gift-card-spending-ideas/">10 Ways to Spend an Apple Gift Card You Received for Christmas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-ways-to-spend-an-apple-gift-card-you-received-for-christmas.2414637/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Vision Pro Mass Shipments Begin Next Week, Launch by February</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-vision-pro-mass-shipments-begin-next-week-launch-by-february.2414633/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 05:18:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mass shipments of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Vision Pro</a> to Apple will begin in the first week of January, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Vision-Pro-Person.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913199" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/2024%E5%B9%B4%E6%B6%88%E8%B2%BB%E9%9B%BB%E5%AD%90%E7%94%A2%E6%A5%AD%E4%B8%89%E5%A4%A7%E9%97%9C%E9%8D%B5%E6%8A%95%E8%B3%87%E8%B6%A8%E5%8B%A2-android%E5%BA%AB%E5%AD%98%E5%9B%9E%E8%A3%9C-vision-pro%E8%88%87ai-pc-%E6%89%8B%E6%A9%9F-three-key-consumer-electronics-investment-42e680eb253b">Christmas Eve note</a>, Kuo said the Vision Pro will most likely hit shelves in late January or early February based on this schedule.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo estimates that Vision Pro shipments in 2024 will reach approximately 500,000 units.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced the Vision Pro at WWDC in June, and said it would launch in the U.S. in early 2024, followed by more countries later in the year.<br/>
<br/>
Happy Holidays!<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/25/vision-pro-mass-shipments-timing-kuo/">Kuo: Vision Pro Mass Shipments Begin Next Week, Launch by February</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-vision-pro-mass-shipments-begin-next-week-launch-by-february.2414633/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares iPhone 15 Plus Ad Highlighting Device&#039;s Long Battery Life</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-iphone-15-plus-ad-highlighting-devices-long-battery-life.2414578/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 10:10:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>Apple Ads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a short <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=07cKD8GK__c">iPhone 15 Plus ad</a> on its YouTube channel that highlights the device's long-lasting battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/07cKD8GK__c?si=04fBHbahr4x4VHTL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the video, an electrical outlet becomes sentient and sings the song "Way Too Long" by rapper Doe Boy. The outlet is sad that the iPhone 15 Plus lasts so long between charges, resulting in the device being plugged in less often.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's tech specs say the iPhone 15 Plus can provide up to 26 hours of offline video playback, and up to 100 hours of audio playback. Like the iPhone 14 Plus, the iPhone 15 Plus offers the longest advertised battery life of any iPhone ever.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's video description:<blockquote>Big screen. Big battery life. iPhone 15 Plus is here. Dynamic Island. New 48MP Main camera. 2x Telephoto. Next-generation portraits. Water resistant (IP68). USB-C. Durable color-infused glass. Aluminum design. You don't want to miss it.</blockquote>The ad was also shared as a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/OFP0c6zBVHs">YouTube Short</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-ads/">Apple Ads</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/iphone-15-plus-battery-life-ad/">Apple Shares iPhone 15 Plus Ad Highlighting Device&#039;s Long Battery Life</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-iphone-15-plus-ad-highlighting-devices-long-battery-life.2414578/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2414545/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 02:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the holiday season, capturing photos and videos of the festivities with family and friends is an important activity for many. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> has a suite of camera features that can significantly elevate the quality and creativity of your holiday photos and videos. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Five-iPhone-Camera-Features-to-Try-This-Holiday-Season-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-927844" /><br/>
It's easy to forget about many of the individual camera features the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; has to offer, and many capabilities go unused by most users, so the holidays is the perfect time to revisit them and try something new. For users of Apple's latest models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> takes things even further with several exclusive camera features. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Spatial Video</h3><br/>
For <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> users, the holiday season presents an ideal opportunity to experiment with Spatial Video capture feature. Available on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max running iOS 17.2 or later, the feature allows users to record videos in a three-dimensional format, bringing a new level of depth and realism to holiday memories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
While Apple's Vision Pro or a device like the Meta Quest 3 is required for the best experience when playing back Spatial Video, this should not deter users from exploring the feature. Spatial Video capture is available now to help users begin creating a library of immersive videos right away. Spatial Videos can also be played back as normal 2D content on other devices.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/record-spatial-video-iphone/">iOS 17.2: How to Record Spatial Video on iPhone 15 Pro</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The technology behind Spatial Video Capture involves using the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s Main and Ultra Wide cameras. When recording, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; seamlessly combines inputs from these cameras to create a single video file that encapsulates a three-dimensional perspective. This is achieved through sophisticated computational videography techniques, which intelligently scale the field of view from the Ultra Wide camera to match that of the Main camera.<br/>
<br/>
The result is a video that, while technically 2D in format, contains depth information that can be utilized by compatible devices to produce a 3D viewing experience. The spatial dimension added to these videos creates a sense of immersion and presence that far surpasses traditional video, supposedly making the viewer feel as if they are actually part of the captured moment.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Cinematic Mode</h3><br/>
The holiday season is a good time for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> and newer model users to try out Cinematic mode, a feature that adds a depth-of-field effect to videos. Cinematic mode uses advanced computational algorithms to automatically focus on subjects and creatively blur the background, akin to what you would see in high-end cinematography. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Cinematic-Mode-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-900525" /><br/>
Cinematic mode allows users to focus on details in a creative way, by shifting focus smoothly from one subject to another. Cinematic mode also simplifies capturing these moments by automatically adjusting focus when people enter or leave the frame, or when the subject of the video looks in a different direction. <br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/shoot-video-in-cinematic-mode-iphone-13-iphone-14/">How to Shoot Video in Cinematic Mode</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Ultra Wide-Angle Lens for Group Shots</h3><br/>
The holiday season presents the perfect opportunity to utilize the often under-utilized Ultra Wide camera lens. This lens, available on most &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models starting from the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11, offers unique advantages that are particularly useful during the holidays.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2019/12/iphone-11-pro-ultra-wide.jpg" alt="" width="2264" height="1186" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-722975" /><br/>
The Ultra Wide lens is particularly adept at photographing in confined spaces that would be difficult to capture fully with a standard Wide lens. One of the most significant advantages of the Ultra Wide lens is its ability to fit more into the frame without needing to move back. This is especially helpful during family gatherings where you might want to capture a large group of people in one photo.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Portrait Mode</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup introduced some substantial improvements to Portrait mode. Now, users can adjust the focus of an image or add background blur after its capture, even if Portrait mode isn't initially selected. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-portrait-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2503" height="1401" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-912809" /><br/>
Post-shot editing capability allows you to experiment with different focal points, ensuring that each portrait captures the subject in the most flattering and interesting way. This improvement is especially useful for snapping quick, candid shots of family members and pets over the holiday period. The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s Portrait mode has also been refined to perform better in low-light conditions.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/iphone-15-how-to-take-portrait-mode-photos/">iPhone 15: How to Take Portrait Mode Photos</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Photographic Styles</h3><br/>
Photographic Styles, a feature introduced in the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; series, offers a personalized photography experience that can help enhance holiday photos. The feature allows users to choose and customize a photographic style that automatically applies to their photos, ensuring that every shot reflects their preferred aesthetic. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/photographic-styles-iphone-13.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-817882" /><br/>
Photographic Styles are not one-size-fits-all filters. Instead, they are smart adjustments that apply selectively to different parts of the photo, such as skin tones and sky. Photographic Styles intelligently adapt to the lighting conditions in each shot, adjusting to preserve natural-looking skin tones and textures.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-photographic-styles-iphone-13-pro/">How to Use Photographic Styles in the Camera App</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Users can choose from preset styles like Rich Contrast, Vibrant, Warm, and Cool, each offering a unique look. During the holidays, this means you can select a style that best suits the festive mood and give your images a distinctive look.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out/">5 iPhone Camera Features to Try Out This Holiday Season</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/5-iphone-camera-features-to-try-out-this-holiday-season.2414545/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2414541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Dec 2023 01:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you been good this year? Then you may be interested to learn that Google today launched its annual <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">Santa tracking feature</a>, allowing Santa to be tracked in real time on his journey to the North Pole as he prepares to deliver presents to kids around the world.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/12/santa-tracker-1.jpg" alt="" width="2096" height="1066" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-830800" /><br/>
Google's Santa Tracker continues a two-decade tradition for the company, allowing excited children (and grown-ups!) to keep up with the jolly gift-giver's travels throughout December 24. On this day, Santa's Village transforms into a tracking experience where children can follow Santa and his reindeer as they merrily go about their important work.<br/>
<br/>
Santa can be tracked using a web browser on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac by visiting Google's <a href="https://santatracker.google.com/">official Santa Tracking website</a>. The site features a live map of Santa's current location, his next stop, a live video feed of his journey, and the estimated time that he will arrive in each specific location.<br/>
<br/>
The Santa site provides pictures of locations that Santa has already visited, a live count of gifts that have been delivered, and Santa's current distance from your location. There are also a selection of games to play, creative things to do, and videos to watch.<br/>
<br/>
Other Santa tracking services are also available, such as the <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/norad-tracks-santa-claus/id1181633163">NORAD Tracks Santa Claus app</a> and website, but Google's site is often the most interactive and detailed. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/24/track-santas-journey-from-north-pole-2/">Track Santa&#039;s Journey From the North Pole Using Google&#039;s Santa Tracker</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/track-santas-journey-from-the-north-pole-using-googles-santa-tracker.2414541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
