<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 04:04:18 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED iPad Pro Price Hikes May Be Lower Than Early Reports Suggested</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/oled-ipad-pro-price-lower-than-first-thought/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-price-hikes-may-be-lower-than-early-reports-suggested.2418631/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 03:52:18 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/oled-ipad-pro-price-lower-than-first-thought/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>DigiTimes</category>
		<category>OLED iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's price increases for its upcoming iPad Pro models with OLED displays could be up to &#36;160, which is substantially lower than early reports have predicted, claims <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240205PD224/ipad-apple-tablet-sales.html">DigiTimes</a></em>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
Apple's current 11-inch iPad Pro starts at &#36;799, while the 12.9-inch model with a mini-LED display starts at &#36;1,099. Previous reports have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/09/2024-oled-ipad-pro-starting-prices/">claimed</a> that the pricing for the next-generation 11-inch ‌OLED ‌iPad‌ Pro‌ could start at &#36;1,500, while the 13-inch model might start at &#36;1,800.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/08/oled-ipad-prices-to-start-1500-dollars/">One report</a> even quoted up to &#36;2,000 for the larger model, although this could be referring to a higher storage tier available for the 13-inch.<br/>
<br/>
<em>DigiTimes</em> does not cite a source for the &#36;160 price increase figure, but if it is accurate or even approximately correct, that could see the starting price of Apple's 11-inch OLED iPad Pro remain under &#36;1,000, with the 13-inch variant starting at around &#36;1,200 to &#36;1,300.<br/>
<br/>
The increase in cost is attributed to the OLED panels, which Apple has not used in iPads before. OLED panels are more expensive to source than LCD panels, and Apple's specific requirements for the screens, such as a very thin design using a tandem-stack design, contribute to the higher cost of these OLED panels compared to others on the market.<br/>
<br/>
On the plus side, OLED technology not only improves display longevity and efficiency but also allows for higher brightness levels. Apple is sourcing these OLED panels from Samsung and LG Display, who are rumored to be developing these special two-stack tandem OLED panels specifically for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
The new iPad Pro models are expected to be powered by Apple's latest M3 chips. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ipad-pro-magsafe-charging/">MagSafe charging</a> is a possibility for the upcoming devices, and they are also likely to be accompanied by a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/27/new-ipad-pro-and-redesigned-magic-keyboard/">refreshed version of the Magic Keyboard</a> that includes a larger trackpad to make the ‌iPad Pro‌ look more like a laptop than the current models.<br/>
<br/>
New ‌iPad Air‌ and ‌‌iPad Pro‌‌ models and accompanying accessories are expected to launch around the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/28/gurman-new-ipads-and-macs-in-late-march/">end of March</a>, which is also when Apple plans to release iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4. For everything else we know about the forthcoming ‌iPad Pro‌ models, be sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/digitimes-com/">DigiTimes</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/oled-ipad-pro-price-lower-than-first-thought/">OLED iPad Pro Price Hikes May Be Lower Than Early Reports Suggested</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-ipad-pro-price-hikes-may-be-lower-than-early-reports-suggested.2418631/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Vision Pro to Launch in China &#039;No Later Than May,&#039; Claims Report</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-vision-pro-launch-china-may/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-no-later-than-may-claims-report.2418625/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 03:03:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-vision-pro-launch-china-may/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's Vision Pro headset will be released in China as early as April and "no later than May," according to supply chain sources quoted by Asia's <em>Wall Street News</em> (via <em><a href="https://www.ithome.com/0/749/243.htm">IT Home</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
According to the report, the registration process for the device at China's Ministry of Industry and Information Technology is nearing completion, which will pave the way for the Vision Pro's launch in the country, although unit availability is initially expected to be tight.<br/>
<br/>
Officially, Apple has said that following its recent U.S. launch on February 2, Apple Vision Pro will be coming to more countries later in the year, though the company has so far stopped short of saying which countries and when exactly.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/gurman-vision-pro-launch-imminent/">insider sources</a> at Apple cited by <em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman, the launch of Vision Pro in other countries around the world will not "actually be that much later" than its release in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is discussing the United Kingdom and Canada as two of the first international markets to get the mixed reality headset this year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/07/apple-vision-pro-launch-uk-canada-end-of-2024/">according to Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Soon after, Apple is said to be looking at bringing the Vision Pro to the rest of Europe as well as Asia, with Apple engineers working to localize the device for France, Germany, Australia, China, Hong Kong, Japan, and Korea.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/16/vision-pro-to-launch-internationally-before-wwdc/">claims</a> that Apple will likely launch its Vision Pro headset outside the United States before Apple's Worldwide Developers Conference in June 2024. Kuo bases his prediction on information that suggests Apple plans to share new details about visionOS – the device's operating system – with developers around the globe at its upcoming developers conference.<br/>
<br/>
China-based companies account for over 60% of Apple's Vision Pro supply chain, according to <em><a href="https://www.digitimes.com/news/a20240205PD226.html">DigiTimes</a></em>. Luxshare is said to be the exclusive assembler of the Vision Pro, with Chinese lens manufacturer Lens Technology being the exclusive supplier of the headset's laminated front glass. Batteries, speakers, and sensor modules are also all sourced from China.<br/>
<br/>
Significantly, Apple may be forced to change the name of its new mixed reality headset in China unless it can come to an agreement with Huawei, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/13/vision-pro-trademark-owned-huawei-china/">already owns the "Vision Pro" trademark</a> in the country. The trademark was originally granted to Huawei on May 16, 2019, and gives the company exclusive rights to its use in China from November 28, 2021 to November 27, 2031.<br/>
<br/>
Huawei actively uses the trademark in China, and offers a number of products under the Vision name, including smart TVs and smart glasses. If Apple intends to sell its headset in China and call it Vision Pro, it may have to enter into negotiations with Huawei to release the trademark for a price.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-vision-pro-launch-china-may/">Apple Vision Pro to Launch in China &#039;No Later Than May,&#039; Claims Report</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-vision-pro-to-launch-in-china-no-later-than-may-claims-report.2418625/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MicroLED Apple Watch Ultra May Be Delayed Due to Supply Chain Issues</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/2026-microled-apple-watch-ultra-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microled-apple-watch-ultra-may-be-delayed-due-to-supply-chain-issues.2418622/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 02:19:45 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/2026-microled-apple-watch-ultra-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Micro-LED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		<category>microLED Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is widely expected to bring a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED display to the Apple Watch Ultra</a>, but a new report out of Korea suggests the company may not have the supply chain configured early enough to launch the device by 2026.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-ultra-adventures.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-864664" /><br/>
Throughout last year, Taiwanese research firm TrendForce predicted a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/04/apple-watch-ultra-microled-delayed-early-2026/">2026 launch timeframe</a> for the device. That's later than several other sources, which have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/10/microled-apple-watch-2025/">centered on 2025</a>. However, according to <em><a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=25793">The Elec</a></em>, problems relating to high manufacturing costs and production yields remain the biggest obstacles to mass production of the microLED Apple Watch Ultra and could even delay the release beyond 2026.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has reportedly been working on custom microLED display technology for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/06/apple-microled-struggle-led-to-reliance-on-samsung/">almost a decade</a>. The advanced display offers improved brightness, color reproduction, dynamic range, viewing angles, and efficiency, making images look more like they are "painted" atop the display glass. <br/>
<br/>
The current Apple Watch Ultra has a display size of 1.93-inches, whereas the upcoming microLED model is expected to feature a 2.12-inch screen. Apple's problem is that the cost of manufacturing a screen with such a high pixel density is still considered prohibitive for a device that currently sells for &#36;799. According to the report, simulation yields indicate a 2.12-inch screen costs as much as &#36;150, which is four times the cost of producing the existing OLED display (&#36;38). As a benchmark, consumer sales of products with a panel price of &#36;150 are usually around &#36;1,500.<br/>
<br/>
For example, &#36;150 is more expensive than it costs to make the OLED displays for the 6.1-inch and the 6.7-inch iPhone 15, which are &#36;80 and &#36;120, respectively. In terms of the cost of the panel right now, the microLED Apple Watch Ultra would have a higher price tag than Apple's latest premium iPhones. The issue is so problematic that even a 2027 release for the device could be overly optimistic, claims today's report.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is said to have plans to replace all of its existing LCD, OLED, and mini-LED panels with microLED in the long term, with the technology being designed to be scaled up from the Apple Watch to the iPhone, iPad, Mac, and Vision Pro headset. The project is part of Apple's plan to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/06/apple-microled-struggle-led-to-reliance-on-samsung/">reduce its reliance on Samsung</a> as a supplier while reaping benefits from engineering its own displays in-house. But unless the company can get all its ducks in a row on the component supply chain side, microLED adoption could still be some way off.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/micro-led/">Micro-LED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microled-apple-watch/">microLED Apple Watch</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/2026-microled-apple-watch-ultra-delays/">MicroLED Apple Watch Ultra May Be Delayed Due to Supply Chain Issues</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/microled-apple-watch-ultra-may-be-delayed-due-to-supply-chain-issues.2418622/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PSA: You&#039;ll Have to Visit an Apple Store If You Forget Your Vision Pro Passcode</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-passcode-apple-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-youll-have-to-visit-an-apple-store-if-you-forget-your-vision-pro-passcode.2418592/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 17:24:43 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-passcode-apple-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> owners who forget the passcode they set will need to take the device to an Apple retail location to get it reset, reports <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-05/forgot-your-apple-vision-pro-s-passcode-you-may-have-to-take-it-back-to-store"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>. There is apparently no on-device way to reset a Vision Pro passcode if it is forgotten.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Purple-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929938" /><br/>
By default, the Vision Pro asks for a six-digit passcode when it is being set up, which must be entered twice. Customers can opt for a longer or shorter passcode. Optic ID can be used in lieu of a passcode, but it works like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>, and the passcode is required after a restart and in certain other situations.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who have forgotten their Vision Pro passcodes have been told by Apple that they will need to visit a retail store for a fix or will need to ship the headset to Apple if there isn't a nearby store. Like Apple's iOS devices, the incorrect passcode cannot be entered too many times or the device will be disabled, with a waiting period before a passcode can be entered again. Removing the passcode requires erasing all content on the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> also must be erased to get rid of a passcode, but it is a process that can be done at home with a Mac or PC. The Apple Watch, which cannot connect to a Mac or PC, can be reset on the device itself using the Digital Crown or on a connected &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
There is an erase content setting on the Vision Pro, but there is no way to get into the reset mode using a combination of button presses. Erasing Vision Pro can only be done through the Settings app.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-selling-vision-pro-developer-strap/">the &#36;300 Developer Strap</a> may be able to wipe the device from a Mac, but most users will not be able to get this accessory as it is limited to registered developers in the United States.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-passcode-apple-store/">PSA: You&#039;ll Have to Visit an Apple Store If You Forget Your Vision Pro Passcode</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-youll-have-to-visit-an-apple-store-if-you-forget-your-vision-pro-passcode.2418592/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Preparing iOS 17.3.1 Update for iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-preparing-ios-17-3-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-17-3-1-update-for-iphone.2418584/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 15:51:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-preparing-ios-17-3-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple appears to be internally testing an iOS 17.3.1 update for the iPhone, based on evidence of the software version in our website's analytics logs this week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/General-iOS-17-Feature-Orange-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898582" /><br/>
Our logs have revealed the existence of several iOS 17 versions before Apple released them, ranging from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/apple-preparing-ios-17-0-3/">iOS 17.0.3</a> to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/apple-preparing-ios-17-2-1/">iOS 17.2.1</a>, so there is a good chance that Apple will follow through with releasing iOS 17.3.1.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.3.1 should be a minor update that addresses software bugs and/or security vulnerabilities. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/13/apple-releases-ios-16-3-1/">iOS 16.3.1</a> was released on February 13 last year, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/10/apple-releases-ios-15-3-1/">iOS 15.3.1</a> was released on February 10 in 2022, so it is likely that iOS 17.3.1 will be released within the next week or so if Apple sticks to a similar timeframe as in the past few years.<br/>
<br/>
A larger iOS 17.4 update remains <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/30/apple-releases-ios-17-4-public-beta/">in beta testing</a> with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/">many new features</a>, including major changes to the App Store in the EU, Apple Podcasts transcripts, SharePlay for the HomePod, new emoji, preparations for the launch of next-generation CarPlay later this year, and more. In a press release, Apple confirmed that iOS 17.4 will be released in March.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-preparing-ios-17-3-1/">Apple Preparing iOS 17.3.1 Update for iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-preparing-ios-17-3-1-update-for-iphone.2418584/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Honda Offering Wireless Apple CarPlay Upgrade for 2018-2022 Accords</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/honda-accord-wireless-carplay-upgrade/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/honda-offering-wireless-apple-carplay-upgrade-for-2018-2022-accords.2418569/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 13:22:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/honda-accord-wireless-carplay-upgrade/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>CarPlay</category>
		<category>Honda</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Honda <a href="https://hondanews.com/en-US/releases/honda-enhances-ownership-experience-with-upgrade-to-wireless-apple-carplay-and-android-auto-for-2018-2022-accord-models">recently announced</a> that owners of 2018-2022 Accord models in the U.S. are now eligible for a wireless Apple CarPlay upgrade option for a fee.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-CarPlay-Dash.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934995" /><br/>
The update can be completed at any Honda dealership in the U.S. for a suggested price of &#36;112, plus a labor fee, according to the announcement. Eligible customers can book a service appointment on their local Honda dealership's website.<br/>
<br/>
Approximately 631,000 Accords with wired-only CarPlay are eligible for the upgrade, said Honda.<br/>
<br/>
"Enhancing the ownership experience and market value of Honda vehicles already in use is a key strategy in pursuit of our goal to have zero environmental impact by 2050," said Honda's sustainability vice president Jay Joseph.<br/>
<br/>
The upgrade also adds wireless Android Auto.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/carplay/">CarPlay</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/honda/">Honda</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/honda-accord-wireless-carplay-upgrade/">Honda Offering Wireless Apple CarPlay Upgrade for 2018-2022 Accords</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/honda-offering-wireless-apple-carplay-upgrade-for-2018-2022-accords.2418569/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube Claims an Apple Vision Pro App is On the Roadmap</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/youtube-vision-pro-app-on-roadmap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-claims-an-apple-vision-pro-app-is-on-the-roadmap.2418560/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 11:57:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/youtube-vision-pro-app-on-roadmap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> launched <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/youtube-spotify-vision-pro/">without a few key apps</a>, such as Netflix, YouTube, and Spotify. A YouTube app could be coming in the future, though, according to a statement the company gave to <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/5/24062425/youtube-vision-pro-app-360-vr-video">The Verge</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/General-YouTube-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-814336" /><br/>
YouTube says that it is "excited" by the Vision Pro launch and that an app is on the company's roadmap, but no timing was provided. YouTube's full statement:<br/>
<blockquote>We're excited to see Vision Pro launch and we're supporting it by ensuring YouTube users have a great experience in Safari. We do not have any specific plans to share at this time, but can confirm that a Vision Pro app is on our roadmap.</blockquote><br/>
YouTube and parent company Google have sometimes taken <em>years</em> to adopt new Apple features, so it is entirely unclear when we might actually see a YouTube app for the device. In the meantime, Apollo developer Christian Selig <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/juno-app-youtube-apple-vision-pro/">has created an app</a> called "Juno" for watching YouTube on the Vision Pro. Alternatively, YouTube videos can be watched from the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
Neither Juno nor YouTube on the web work allow Vision Pro owners to watch YouTube's collection of 360 and 3D videos. An Apple spokesperson told <em>The Verge</em> that this is because the content "was created for devices that do not deliver a high-quality spatial experience."<br/>
<blockquote>In some cases, this content could also cause motion discomfort. We've focused our efforts on delivering the best spatial media experience possible including spatial photos and videos, Apple Immersive Video, and 3D movies available on Apple TV.</blockquote><br/>
There is no word on whether YouTube's eventual app will work with its 3D content.<br/>
<br/>
Apple did say that it is working on supporting WebXR content which could eventually allow for YouTube VR videos to be viewable on the web using Safari, but it is still a new standard. WebXR doesn't yet "take full advantage of the power, performance and interaction capabilities of &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>," but Apple is contributing to W3C web standards including WebXR.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/youtube-vision-pro-app-on-roadmap/">YouTube Claims an Apple Vision Pro App is On the Roadmap</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-claims-an-apple-vision-pro-app-is-on-the-roadmap.2418560/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Valentine&#039;s Day Deals: Get All-Time Low Prices on AirPods, iPad, iPhone, MacBook Air, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/valentines-day-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/valentines-day-deals-get-all-time-low-prices-on-airpods-ipad-iphone-macbook-air-and-more.2418557/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 11:12:50 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/valentines-day-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[We're just over one week away from Valentine's Day, which falls on Wednesday, February 14, this year. Similar to years past, many third-party Apple resellers and accessory companies have opened up notable discounts on Apple products and accessories to coincide with the holiday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/Valentines-Deals-2022-Hero.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836658" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Additionally, there are a few solid discounts on Apple products like the iPhone 15, AirPods, Apple Watch, MacBook Pro, MacBook Air, and iPad. In this article you'll find deals from third-party retailers collected first, including special Valentine's Day themed sales from AT&T, ZAGG, Belkin, eBay, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Valentine's Accessory Sales</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clzwZ4g39av">Best Buy</a> - Purchase &#36;100 Apple gift card, get a &#36;10 Best Buy e-gift card</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=592977.24&subid=0&type=4">Anker</a> - Bundle gifts up to 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a> - Save up to &#36;340 on soundbars, speakers, and subwoofers</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">AT&T</a> - iPhone 15 Pro at no cost with eligible trade-in</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clzuN6ondRm">Samsung</a> - Get up to &#36;750 instant trade-in credit with purchase of new Galaxy S24 smartphones</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1654433&u=63177&m=102921&urllink=&afftrack=">Twelve South</a> - Buy one, get one 20% off</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11043124-1465418060000">ZAGG</a> - Save 30% off your entire cart when you purchase two or more products</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://belkin.evyy.net/c/153062/214281/3736">Belkin</a> - Save 20% sitewide with code VDAY24</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1592498&u=63177&m=100061">Casely</a> - Save up to 50% sitewide</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://rover.ebay.com/rover/1/711-53200-19255-0/1?icep_ff3=1&pub=5575340917&toolid=10001&campid=5338201023&customid=&ipn=psmain&icep_vectorid=229466&kwid=902099&mtid=824&kw=lg">eBay</a> - Save up to 60% on tech, home, and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1200223&u=63177&m=80610">ESR</a> - Buy two, get 20% off</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/AirPods-Valentine-Deal.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-782131" /><br/>
<br/>
There are quite a few AirPods deals going on in early February on Amazon, including big savings on the AirPods 2, AirPods 3, and AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C. Starting with the cheapest model, the AirPods 2 are available for &#36;89.99, down from &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The AirPods 3 have dropped to &#36;139.99 on Amazon, down from &#36;169.00. This is the model with the Lightning Charging Case, and this sale is a match of the all-time low price on the AirPods 3.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99, down from &#36;249.00. This is another match of an all-time low price, and an overall great deal on the newest model of AirPods.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/02/watch-heart-valentines-deal.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-836619" /><br/>
<br/>
The best Apple Watch-related deals you can find right now are on the second generation Apple Watch SE. The 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE has hit &#36;189.00 on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00, while the 44mm GPS model is available for &#36;219.00, down from &#36;279.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Series 9 deals aren't as steep, but are still notable if you're shopping for an Apple Watch this month. You can get the 41mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for &#36;329.00 on Amazon, down from &#36;399.00, and the 45mm GPS model for &#36;359.00, down from &#36;429.00. <a href="https://howl.me/clztYrRobwN">These prices are being matched at Best Buy</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1RVMT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX6SF1J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;359.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally for Apple Watches, it's worth noting the Apple Watch Ultra 2 is down to an all-time low price of &#36;737.99 on Amazon, down from &#36;799.00. Only the Indigo Alpine Loop in Medium is available at this price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;61 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;737.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
As of last month, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">sales ban was reenacted</a> in the United States on any Apple Watch model sold by Apple that has blood oxygen sensing. While Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models purchased directly from Apple currently come with blood oxygen sensing disabled, retailers like Best Buy are able to continue selling through their existing stocks that include the feature.<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/iPad-Valentine-Deal.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-782130" /><br/>
<br/>
Right now Amazon has Apple's 9th and 10th generation iPad at numerous record low prices, starting at just &#36;249.00 for the 64GB Wi-Fi 9th generation iPad. You can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;379.00, which is &#36;100 off and an all-time low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 9th Gen iPad for &#36;249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G96TFF7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 9th Gen iPad for &#36;379.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are even more 10th generation iPads on sale on Amazon, with nearly every model getting a best-ever price. This includes both Wi-Fi and cellular tablets, starting at &#36;349.00 for the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi 10th Gen iPad for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi 10th Gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDWX34%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>64GB Cellular 10th Gen iPad for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDLYXP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>256GB Cellular 10th Gen iPad for &#36;649.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, there are a few iPad mini models on sale on Amazon, but only on the 64GB Wi-Fi model. You can get this tablet in multiple colors for &#36;399.99, down from &#36;499.00, a solid second-best price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9FW785%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><h2>MacBook</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/02/MacBook-Pro-Valentine-Deal.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-782132" /><br/>
<br/>
There aren't many MacBook Pro and MacBook Air deals right now, but if you're shopping for a new Apple notebook you can still find some solid discounts on Amazon. The most notable MacBook Pro markdown is the 14-inch M3 512GB MacBook Pro for &#36;1,399.00, down from &#36;1,599.00, as well as the M3 Pro 512GB model for &#36;1,799.00, down from &#36;1,99.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 512GB) for &#36;1,399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro 512GB) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch M1 MacBook Air is available for &#36;749.99 in all three colors on Amazon, which is &#36;249 off and an all-time low price. This is a great entry-level MacBook and perfect for anyone who needs a notebook for simple Internet browsing and checking email.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08N5M7S6K%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;249 OFF</div>13-inch MacBook Air (M1 256GB) for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><h2>Apple Accessories</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/airtag-heart-valentines-deal.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934918" /><br/>
<br/>
We're tracking a few notable discounts on Apple accessories on Amazon below, as well as a great deal on the MagSafe Duo Charger at Woot.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0933BVK6T%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirTag 1 Pack</a> - &#36;24.00, down from &#36;29.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08L5NP6NG%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">MagSafe Charger</a> - &#36;32.99, down from &#36;39.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirTag 4 Pack</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil USB-C</a> - &#36;69.00, down from &#36;79.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLG69QR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil 1</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-duo-fast-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_1">MagSafe Duo Charger</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3T1WX%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;18.69, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1652P%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Silicone Case</a> - &#36;25.55, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX9FJTK%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;30.94, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Plus-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX47H6D%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Plus Silicone Case</a> - &#36;17.23, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX2XFLN%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Silicone Case</a> - &#36;33.64, down from &#36;49.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-FineWoven-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX1HZST%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">iPhone 15 Pro Max FineWoven Case</a> - &#36;51.99, down from &#36;59.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-iPhone-15-Pro-Max-Silicone-Case-MagSafe%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3TW92%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26ref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">iPhone 15 Pro Max Silicone Case</a> - &#36;35.16, down from &#36;49.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/valentines-day-deals-2024/">Valentine&#039;s Day Deals: Get All-Time Low Prices on AirPods, iPad, iPhone, MacBook Air, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/valentines-day-deals-get-all-time-low-prices-on-airpods-ipad-iphone-macbook-air-and-more.2418557/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17 Adoption is Slower Than iOS 16 Adoption</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-shares-ios-17-adoption-numbers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-adoption-is-slower-than-ios-16-adoption.2418553/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:48:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-shares-ios-17-adoption-numbers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> is installed on 76 percent of iPhones released in the last four years, according to <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/app-store/">newly released iOS 17 adoption statistics</a> provided today by Apple. This is the first time that Apple has given us &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; installation numbers since the operating system was released last September.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iOS-17-Adoption-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-934949" /><br/>
20 percent of iPhones released in the last four years are still running iOS 16, while four percent run an earlier operating system. Of all active iPhones, 66 percent are running &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, 23 percent are running iOS 16, and 11 percent are running an earlier version of iOS.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also shared iPadOS installation numbers. 61 percent of iPads introduced in the last four years have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> installed, while 29 percent have iPadOS 16, and 10 percent are running an earlier version of iPadOS.<br/>
<br/>
Among all active iPads, 53 percent have &zwnj;iPadOS 17&zwnj;, 29 percent have iPadOS 16, and 18 percent run an earlier version of the iPadOS software.<br/>
<br/>
Around this time last year, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/16/ios-16-adoption-stats-from-apple/">81 percent of all iPhones</a> introduced in the last four years had iOS 16 installed, so &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; adoption has been slower. Only 53 percent of iPads were running iPadOS 16 in February 2023, however, so the pace of &zwnj;iPadOS 17&zwnj; adoption has been faster than iPadOS 16 adoption.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; was first released in September, and Apple has released three major updates so far. A fourth major update, iOS 17.4, is set to come out in March.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-shares-ios-17-adoption-numbers/">iOS 17 Adoption is Slower Than iOS 16 Adoption</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-adoption-is-slower-than-ios-16-adoption.2418553/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 Swift Student Challenge Now Live</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-2024-swift-student-challenge/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-swift-student-challenge-now-live.2418547/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 10:18:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-2024-swift-student-challenge/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		<category>Swift Playgrounds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=vn4toshi">today began accepting submissions</a> for its 2024 Swift Student Challenge. Apple's annual challenges ask students to create an innovative coding project using the Swift Playgrounds app.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932478" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/swift-student-challenge-2024.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/08/swift-student-challenge-february-2024/">first announced plans</a> for an early 2024 launch in November 2023, giving students plenty of time to prepare for this year's event.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will select 350 winners for this year's challenge, and there will be a category that recognizes a total of 50 Distinguished Winners for standout submissions. The Distinguished Winners will be invited to Apple's headquarters in Cupertino, California, where they will be able to connect with their peers and the Apple team, and all 350 winners will be granted a free one-year membership in the Apple Developer program, a complimentary voucher to take an App Development with Swift certification exam, and a special gift from Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been holding an annual Swift Student Challenge for several years now, but it is typically announced when Apple provides dates the Worldwide Developers Conference. Past winners have been invited to attend WWDC, and Apple says that this year's 50 Distinguished Winners will be invited to Cupertino "next summer," so the planned invite could again be tied to WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
Students will have three weeks to submit their app playgrounds to Apple, and applications must be submitted by February 25. Apple judges entries on technical accomplishment, creativity of ideas, and content of written responses explaining the project.<br/>
<br/>
Eligible students include those enrolled in an accredited academic institution (or an official homeschool equivalent), a STEM organization's educational curriculum, or an Apple Developer Academy. Apple also accepts applications from developers who have graduated from high school or the equivalent in the past six months and are awaiting acceptance to an accredited academic institution.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/swift-playgrounds/">Swift Playgrounds</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-2024-swift-student-challenge/">Apple&#039;s 2024 Swift Student Challenge Now Live</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-swift-student-challenge-now-live.2418547/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Previews 2024 Lineup of Shows and Films</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-tv-plus-2024-shows-and-films/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-previews-2024-lineup-of-shows-and-films.2418544/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 09:37:58 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-tv-plus-2024-shows-and-films/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-unveils-a-sneak-peek-at-star-studded-lineup-of-new-and-returning-original-series-set-to-debut-in-2024/">previewed new and returning series and films</a> that will be available on its TV+ streaming service this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-TV-Plus-Constellation.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1104" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934926" /><br/>
Here's what's new or upcoming this year, according to Apple:<ul><li>The New Look</li><br/>
<li>Sugar</li><br/>
<li>Killers of the Flower Moon</li><br/>
<li>Masters of the Air</li><br/>
<li>Franklin</li><br/>
<li>Napoleon</li><br/>
<li>Girls State</li><br/>
<li>Lady in the Lake</li><br/>
<li>Presumed Innocent</li><br/>
<li>Constellation</li><br/>
<li>Manhunt</li><br/>
<li>The Dynasty: New England Patriots</li><br/>
<li>Dark Matter</li><br/>
<li>Palm Royale</li><br/>
<li>The Completely Made-Up Adventures of Dick Turpin</li><br/>
<li>Land of Women</li><br/>
<li>Messi's World Cup: The Rise of a Legend</li><br/>
<li>Snoopy Presents: Welcome Home, Franklin</li><br/>
<li>Loot (Season 2)</li><br/>
<li>The Big Door Prize (Season 2)</li><br/>
<li>The Reluctant Traveler With Eugene Levy (Season 2)</li><br/>
<li>Fraggle Rock: Back to the Rock (Season 2)</li><br/>
<li>Acapulco (Season 3)</li><br/>
<li>Trying (Season 4)</li></ul><a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/02/apple-tv-unveils-a-sneak-peek-at-star-studded-lineup-of-new-and-returning-original-series-set-to-debut-in-2024/">Apple's press release</a> provides more details about each of the series and films, so be sure to check that out for a deeper dive into the content.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also shared a teaser video:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/s6jZTQ3oc7w?si=kA8JL5diCyfiTTRO" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen data-thumb-size="hqdefault"></iframe></div><br/>
Apple TV+ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-tv-price-increasing-significantly/">received a price increase in October</a>, and the service now costs &#36;9.99 per month in the U.S. for new and existing subscribers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-tv-plus-2024-shows-and-films/">Apple TV+ Previews 2024 Lineup of Shows and Films</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-previews-2024-lineup-of-shows-and-films.2418544/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Demo Appointments Begin Today at All Apple Stores in U.S.</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-vision-pro-demo-appointments/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-demo-appointments-begin-today-at-all-apple-stores-in-u-s.2418536/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 08:55:31 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-vision-pro-demo-appointments/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting today, you can receive a free Vision Pro demo at any Apple Store in the U.S. on an appointment basis. You can reserve a time slot up to seven days in advance <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/instore-shopping-session/session-selection/?topic=visionpro">on Apple's website</a>, or by using the Apple Store app on your iPhone or iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Michael-Steebers-Brother.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934914" /><br/>
During the 30-minute demo experience, guided by an Apple retail employee, you will learn how to navigate the visionOS operating system as you explore a few built-in apps, including Apple TV, Photos, and Safari. The employee will make sure the Vision Pro properly fits you, and provide the correct ZEISS optical inserts for vision correction if necessary.<br/>
<br/>
At select stores, Apple has created a special "Demo Zone" with curved sofas and rugs to create a more comfortable and homey feel. Apple Store expert Michael Steeber provided more details about the demo experience <a href="https://michaelsteeber.substack.com/p/the-big-demo">in his Tabletops newsletter</a> today. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Vision-Pro-availability-demo-zone_big.jpg.large_2x.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934899" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Demo Zone at Apple Fifth Avenue in New York City</em></div><br/>
Vision Pro launched in the U.S. on Friday, and Apple plans to release the headset in additional countries at some point later this year.<br/>
<br/>
"The era of spatial computing has arrived," said Apple CEO Tim Cook. "Apple Vision Pro is the most advanced consumer electronics device ever created. Its revolutionary and magical user interface will redefine how we connect, create, and explore."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/apple-vision-pro-demo-appointments/">Vision Pro Demo Appointments Begin Today at All Apple Stores in U.S.</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-demo-appointments-begin-today-at-all-apple-stores-in-u-s.2418536/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Discounts 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE to Just &#36;189</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/amazon-apple-watch-se-189/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-to-just-189.2418519/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:18:26 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/amazon-apple-watch-se-189/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE has dropped to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, which is just &#36;10 higher compared to its all-time low price. This deal is only available in the Silver Aluminum Case with Winter Blue Sport Loop option of the Apple Watch SE, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's available in Midnight, Silver, and Starlight Aluminum options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX5W8YM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for a more high-end Apple Watch, Amazon also has the Apple Watch Ultra 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX7J5Z3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;737.99</strong></a> in the Indigo Alpine Loop (Medium) model, down from &#36;799.00. This is the lowest price we've ever tracked for the Ultra 2, and right now Amazon only has one model on sale.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/amazon-apple-watch-se-189/">Amazon Discounts 2nd Gen Apple Watch SE to Just &#36;189</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-discounts-2nd-gen-apple-watch-se-to-just-189.2418519/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Videos: Apple Vision Pro Tested for Work, Gaming, Flying, and Sports</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-videos-for-work-gaming-flying-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/videos-apple-vision-pro-tested-for-work-gaming-flying-and-sports.2418518/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 07:08:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-videos-for-work-gaming-flying-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-launch-day/">launched in the U.S. on Friday</a>, and there are already several YouTube videos that demonstrate using the headset for remote work, gaming, in-flight entertainment, watching sports, and more. We have rounded up these videos below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Vision-Pro-Airplane.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934834" /><br/>
If you want to experience the Vision Pro for yourself, you can <a href="https://www.apple.com/retail/instore-shopping-session/?topic=visionpro">book an appointment for a free Vision Pro demo</a> at any Apple Store in the U.S. on Apple's website. During the demo, which can take up to 30 minutes, you will learn how to navigate the visionOS operating system, and explore built-in apps such as Apple TV, Photos, and Safari.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Working at Home</h2><br/>
Himels Tech demonstrated using the Vision Pro at home for work, entertainment, and more:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/BV9Xy6L_rlM?si=AcSvV-nJ7It3R8wC" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In the video, he walks around and shows off several visionOS app windows pinned at his desk, in the living room, and in the kitchen.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro can be used as an external display for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-can-display-intel-macs/">any Mac compatible with macOS Sonoma</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Gaming</h2><br/>
Wynnsanity tested gaming on the Vision Pro:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xmYNLndZZIs?si=0Qw6L-A7MgWnKqU1" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Most controllers that are compatible with the iPhone or iPad also work with the Vision Pro, including wireless PlayStation and Xbox controllers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Traveling on Airplane</h2><br/>
Gravel took the Vision Pro on an airplane and used the headset as a virtual seat-back screen:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5bbQC2YSshM?si=d94_CLzxxG7a74r-&amp;start=564" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-travel/">features a Travel Mode</a> that adapts to the "unique motion and environment of commercial air travel" to give you the "best experience while traveling on an airplane," according to Apple. Travel Mode can be turned on in Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says the Vision Pro should not be worn during taxiing, takeoff, and landing, and while a flight has turbulence. Apple also says to avoid looking out an airplane's windows, as this could affect the headset's ability to track your surroundings.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Watching Sports</h2><br/>
In his excellent Vision Pro review last week, Brian Tong showed what it is like to use the NBA app:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GkPw6ScHyb4?si=pPkaXKS9lG_2F_5t&amp;start=898" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
With the NBA app and an NBA League Pass subscription, you can watch up to five basketball games live or on demand at once. You can also view real-time player stats, game scores, and other information at a glance.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>In Public</h2><br/>
Casey Neistat wore the Vision Pro on the New York City subway and at Times Square:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UvkgmyfMPks?si=3kXBFlAKxg5nByK4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1KZ2Ejg3mWA">Many</a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P161APUiLCk">other</a> <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JJ4R0yJ9-vg">YouTubers</a> also used the Vision Pro in public.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/05/vision-pro-videos-for-work-gaming-flying-more/">Videos: Apple Vision Pro Tested for Work, Gaming, Flying, and Sports</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/videos-apple-vision-pro-tested-for-work-gaming-flying-and-sports.2418518/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releasing iOS 17.4 in March With These New Features and Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releasing-ios-17-4-in-march-with-these-new-features-and-changes.2418427/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 08:56:17 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple last month confirmed that iOS 17.4 will be released in March, and the update includes several new features and changes for the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932462" /><br/>
Key new features in iOS 17.4 include major App Store changes in the EU, Apple Podcasts transcripts, SharePlay for the HomePod, and new emoji. The update also includes preparations for the launch of next-generation CarPlay later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/01/apple-announces-changes-to-ios-safari-and-the-app-store-in-the-european-union/">press release</a> confirmation that iOS 17.4 will be released in March:<blockquote>Inevitably, the new options for developers' EU apps create new risks to Apple users and their devices. Apple can't eliminate those risks, but within the DMA's constraints, the company will take steps to reduce them. These safeguards will be in place <strong>when users download iOS 17.4 or later, beginning in March</strong>.</blockquote>More details about the new features and changes in iOS 17.4 follow.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>App Store Changes in EU</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-ios-app-store-safari-changes.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933983" /><br/>
To comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act, Apple announced major changes to the App Store, Apple Pay, Safari, and more. These changes will be implemented with iOS 17.4 for iPhone users who reside in the <a href="https://www.netherlandsworldwide.nl/eu-eea-efta-schengen-countries">27 countries</a> that belong to the EU.<br/>
<br/>
First and foremost, Apple now allows <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">alternative app marketplaces</a> and alternative payment options on the App Store in the EU. Other changes in the EU include a new default web browser selection screen in Safari, the ability for third-party web browsers to use web engines other than Apple's WebKit on the iPhone, the ability for third-party mobile wallet apps to access the iPhone's NFC chip for contactless payment functionality, and more.<br/>
<br/>
For more details, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/iphone-changes-coming-to-eu-users/">recap of all of the EU changes in iOS 17.4</a> and <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/dma-and-apps-in-the-eu/">Apple's overview</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Podcasts Transcripts</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Podcasts-Transcriptions.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934710" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 17.4, the Apple Podcasts app now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/view-search-transcripts-podcasts-app/">offers transcripts for podcasts</a>, allowing listeners to read the full text of an episode, search for a specific word or phrase, and tap on the text to jump to a certain part of the episode. As an episode plays, each word is highlighted, similar to Apple Music song lyrics.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://podcasters.apple.com/support/5316-transcripts-on-apple-podcasts">Apple says</a> it automatically generates transcripts after a new episode is published. Transcripts are available for podcasts in English, French, German, and Spanish, and they will be added for older episodes in a podcast's catalog over time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>SharePlay for HomePod</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/SharePlay-Music-Control-Expanding-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-933114" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 17.4, Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/shareplay-music-control-homepod-apple-tv/">expanded SharePlay music control to HomePod speakers</a>.<br/>
<br/>
This feature allows family and friends to control the music that is playing on your HomePod, if you approve their request. For now, it is limited to the Music app, and the other people do not require an Apple Music subscription in order to participate.<br/>
<br/>
While playing a song on your iPhone, tap the SharePlay icon at the bottom of the screen to bring up a QR code, which another person can scan with their iPhone or Android smartphone's camera to request access to music playback controls. Even a screenshot of the QR code suffices, allowing you to remotely grant access to people around the world.<br/>
<br/>
Apple already rolled out a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/13/whats-new-carplay-ios-17/">similar feature for CarPlay</a> last year, allowing anyone in a car to control music playback via SharePlay with permission.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Emoji</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-New-Emoji-Feature-2.5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1077" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932812" /><br/>
iOS 17.4 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-adds-new-emoji/">adds new emoji</a>, including a broken chain, a brown mushroom, a head shaking horizontally, a head shaking vertically, a lime, and a phoenix.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Next-Generation CarPlay Preparations</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/Next-Generation-CarPlay-Porsche-1.png" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927534" /><br/>
The first iOS 17.4 beta includes code for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">eight new CarPlay apps</a>:<ul><li><strong>Auto Settings:</strong> This app will let you manage paired iPhones and adjust vehicle settings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Car Camera:</strong> This app will display the vehicle's rear-view camera feed.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Charge:</strong> For electric vehicles, this app will display battery level, charging status, time remaining until the battery is fully charged, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Climate:</strong> This app will provide access to a vehicle's climate controls within CarPlay, allowing you to adjust the temperature of the A/C or heating system, fan speed, heated seats, heated steering wheel, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Closures:</strong> This app will display if any of the vehicle's doors are opened, and it might also display vehicle warning symbols.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Media:</strong> This app will provide access to FM and AM radio station controls within CarPlay, along with other media options like SiriusXM. It is unclear if SiriusXM will offer satellite connectivity, or remain limited to internet streaming. Users will be able to select from a list of music genres, such as Top 40 and Rock.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Tire Pressure:</strong> This app will display air pressure for each of the vehicle's tires, and provide low pressure, high pressure, and flat tire warnings.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Trips:</strong> This app will provide a variety of driving-related data, including the vehicle's average speed, fuel efficiency or energy efficiency, the total time elapsed and distance traveled on a trip, and more.</li></ul>Apple recently confirmed that the first U.S. vehicle models with next-generation CarPlay will be released at some point in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More</h2><br/>
Read our <strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1-changes/">full list of iOS 17.4 features</a></strong> to learn about more changes, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/ios-17-4-stopwatch-live-activity/">Live Activities support for the Clock app's stopwatch</a>, and the "Listen Now" tab being renamed to "Home" in the Apple Music and Apple Podcasts apps.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/ios-17-4-new-features-and-changes/">Apple Releasing iOS 17.4 in March With These New Features and Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releasing-ios-17-4-in-march-with-these-new-features-and-changes.2418427/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods 3 Available for Record Low &#36;139.99 Price Alongside Discounts on AirPods 2 and AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/airpods-3-record-low-139-99/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-available-for-record-low-139-99-price-alongside-discounts-on-airpods-2-and-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c.2418414/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 07:21:01 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/airpods-3-record-low-139-99/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is back with all-time low prices on two AirPods models, including the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C and the AirPods 3 with Lightning Charging Case. You can also find a solid discount on the AirPods 2 in these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-2-and-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895354" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This is a match of the record low price on these AirPods, which feature a new USB-C port as well as improved dust resistance and 20-bit 48kHz lossless audio when paired with the Apple Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The AirPods 3 are on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;139.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;169.00. This is another match of an all-time low price, and for the AirPods 3 this is the first time in 2024 that we're tracking a best-ever price on the model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;29 OFF</div>AirPods 3 for &#36;139.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, Amazon has the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;89.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;129.00. Although we've tracked this model lower in the past, particularly during the holidays, this is the lowest price we've seen in weeks and overall the best deal so far in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;39 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/04/airpods-3-record-low-139-99/">AirPods 3 Available for Record Low &#36;139.99 Price Alongside Discounts on AirPods 2 and AirPods Pro 2 With USB-C</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-3-available-for-record-low-139-99-price-alongside-discounts-on-airpods-2-and-airpods-pro-2-with-usb-c.2418414/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Shares Apple Vision Pro Teardown</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/ifixit-apple-vision-pro-teardown/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-shares-apple-vision-pro-teardown.2418368/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 14:40:08 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/ifixit-apple-vision-pro-teardown/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The well-known repair website iFixit today shared a <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/90137/vision-pro-teardown-why-those-fake-eyes-look-so-weird">written teardown</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JVJPAYwY8Us">video teardown of the Apple Vision Pro</a>, offering a look inside the mixed reality headset.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/JVJPAYwY8Us?si=rslK4MNOQW_qMDrZ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
iFixit's disassembly of the Vision Pro reveals several internal components, including an array of cameras and sensors, fans, lens motors, and more. Unsurprisingly, it appears that opening and repairing the headset will be difficult.<br/>
<br/>
"The EyeSight seems like a repair Achilles' heel—so many points of failure for a slightly creepy feature," said iFixit, in an email. "But we'll give Apple credit where it's due: the easily replaceable speakers and battery are big repairability wins."<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro is powered by an M2 chip with an 8-core CPU, a 10-core GPU, a 16-core Neural Engine, and 16GB of unified memory. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/apple-vision-pro-tech-specs/">Other specs include</a> up to 1TB of storage, and an all-new R1 chip that "processes input from 12 cameras, five sensors, and six microphones to ensure that content feels like it is appearing right in front of the user's eyes."<br/>
<br/>
The publication <em>Wallpaper*</em> <a href="https://www.wallpaper.com/tech/apple-vision-pro-review">had already shared</a> an image of the Vision Pro's internals on Friday, as part of an exclusive Vision Pro design interview with Apple's vice president of software design Alan Dye and vice president of hardware design Richard Howarth.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Vision-Pro-Internals-1.jpg" alt="" width="1360" height="784" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934630" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Image Credit: Wallpaper*</em></div><br/>
Howarth said Apple designed the Vision Pro with "a lot of flexible materials and soft textures" like the Solo Knit Band so that people "would not only feel physically comfortable wearing it, but also enjoy wearing it around others too."<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro launched on Friday in the U.S., and Apple said the headset will be available in additional countries later this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/ifixit-apple-vision-pro-teardown/">iFixit Shares Apple Vision Pro Teardown</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-shares-apple-vision-pro-teardown.2418368/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Vision Pro User Guide and Dozens of Support Documents With Useful Tips</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-support-documents/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-vision-pro-user-guide-and-dozens-of-support-documents-with-useful-tips.2418359/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 12:26:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-support-documents/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple on Friday shared a wealth of information about its new Vision Pro headset, including a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/apple-vision-pro/welcome/visionos">detailed user guide</a> and dozens of support documents.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
We have already highlighted many topics separately, such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-optic-id/">Optic ID</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-vision-pro-guest-mode/">Guest User</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-travel/">Travel Mode</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-persona-tips/">Personas</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-gestures/">supported gestures</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-bluetooth-accessories/">compatible Bluetooth accessories</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-syncs-data-battery-light/">charging</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/vision-pro-battery-management-system/">battery management</a> details, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-explains-how-to-clean-vision-pro-headset/">cleaning instructions</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-lacks-find-my-tracking/">lack of Find My tracking</a>, using the Vision Pro  <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-can-display-intel-macs/">as an external display for a Mac</a>, and more.<br/>
<br/>
With assistance from <em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613">Aaron Perris</a>, we have created a list with nearly every Apple support document related to the Vision Pro.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214043">About Activation Lock on Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214018">About Automatic Display Alignment</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214051">About Optic ID advanced technology</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213947">About the materials used in Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214071">About visionOS 1 Updates</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213946">About visual discomfort with Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213955">Apple Vision Pro Battery and Performance</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213959">Attach and pair your ZEISS Optical Inserts</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213908">Before you begin an immersive experience</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213949">Close an app on Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/117740">Connect and charge Apple Vision Pro battery</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213999">Create a workspace in Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214014">Delete apps from your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213976">Factory reset your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213973">Find your Apple Vision Pro serial number</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213952">Get your Apple Vision Pro ready for service</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213964">How to clean Apple Vision Pro and accessories</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213945">How to get the best fit wearing Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213994">How to remove and replace your Apple Vision Pro Audio Strap for service</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213963">How to remove or attach your Apple Vision Pro head band</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214013">How to remove your Apple Vision Pro battery or power cable for service</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213944">How to safely use your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214024">How to send your Apple Vision Pro Enclosure to Apple for service</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214025">How to send your ZEISS Optical Inserts in for replacement</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213962">How to set up Optic ID</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213980">How to set up your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213934">If you experience motion sickness while using Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214019">If you need help with eye setup on Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213960">If you need to order or replace your ZEISS Optical Inserts</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213953">If your Apple Vision Pro doesn't fit properly</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213900">If your eyes are too close or too far from your Apple Vision Pro displays</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/117742">Let another person use your Apple Vision Pro with Guest User</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213968">Liquid damage to Apple Vision Pro and accessories not covered by warranty</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213950">Restart Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214002">Set up your Persona (beta) on Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214004">Store your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214009">Update visionOS on your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213920">Use AirPods with Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214045">Use Apple Vision Pro on an airplane with Travel Mode</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213998">Use Bluetooth accessories with your Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/117741">Use gestures with Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT213971">Use your Mac with Apple Vision Pro</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://support.apple.com/HT214044">What to do before you sell, give away, or trade in your Apple Vision Pro</a></li></ul>Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/apple-vision-pro-support-videos/">shared video overviews</a> of the Settings app, Control Center, Guest User, accessibility features, and more on visionOS.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-support-documents/">Apple Shares Vision Pro User Guide and Dozens of Support Documents With Useful Tips</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-vision-pro-user-guide-and-dozens-of-support-documents-with-useful-tips.2418359/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Optic ID: Apple Explains Vision Pro&#039;s Iris Authentication System</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-optic-id/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/optic-id-apple-explains-vision-pros-iris-authentication-system.2418352/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 11:22:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-optic-id/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>Optic ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the launch of the Vision Pro, Apple has <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT214051#416">shared additional details</a> about the headset's Optic ID iris authentication option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-eye-tracking.jpg" alt="" width="2080" height="1170" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898908" /><br/>
Optic ID can recognize the uniqueness of your irises, the colored part of your eyes, allowing you to quickly unlock your Vision Pro, authorize Apple Pay purchases, sign in to many third-party apps, access sensitive personal data, and more. Apps that support Face ID and Touch ID on the iPhone and iPad automatically support Optic ID. After setting up Optic ID, it also becomes a requirement in order use your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-persona-tips/">Persona</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"In the same way that Touch ID revolutionized authentication using a fingerprint and Face ID revolutionized authentication using facial recognition, Optic ID revolutionizes authentication using iris recognition," says Apple. "Optic ID provides intuitive and secure authentication that uses the uniqueness of your iris, made possible by Apple Vision Pro's high-performance eye-tracking system of LEDs and infrared cameras."<br/>
<br/>
Optic ID scans both of your eyes by default. Given that the size of your irises and pupils change in various lighting conditions, Apple says Optic ID adapts by updating your enrolled template after each successful authentication. Apple ensures that <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/privacy/data/en/optic-id#416">all biometric data is encrypted</a> and never backed up to iCloud or anywhere else.<br/>
<br/>
There is an accessibility option for using Optic ID with one eye only that can be turned on in the Settings app under Accessibility → Eye Input. Optic ID can also be kept off entirely, in which case you authenticate with a passcode only.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Apple-Vision-Pro-Optic-ID.jpg" alt="" width="1178" height="663" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934569" /><br/>
For users who require vision correction, Optic ID works with the Vision Pro's ZEISS optical inserts and prescription soft contact lenses.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says Optic ID uses "advanced hardware and software" for iris recognition.<br/>
<br/>
"When you set up Optic ID, spatiotemporally modulated eye-safe near-infrared light illuminates the eye, so that the Apple Vision Pro eye cameras can capture images of your iris," says Apple. "This iris image data is sent to and processed on the Secure Enclave and a portion of the Apple M2 chip's neural engine that's protected within the Secure Enclave, where it is transformed into a mathematical representation for enrollment. When you authenticate with Optic ID, the authentication attempt uses the same process to compare your iris to the enrolled biometric data to determine whether there is a match."<br/>
<br/>
Optic ID complies with international safety standards and "won't cause harm to the eyes or skin due to the low output of the emitters," according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says that a probability that a random person could unlock your Vision Pro using Optic ID is less than one in a million, similar to Face ID. The company explains that Optic ID matches against "detailed iris structure in the near-infrared domain," which "reveals highly unique patterns independent of iris pigmentation."<br/>
<br/>
Optic ID allows a maximum of five unsuccessful match attempts before a passcode is required. As an additional layer of protection, you can set the Vision Pro to <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/guide/apple-vision-pro/tanf79745605/visionos#416">erase all information, media, and personal settings</a> after 10 consecutive failed passcode attempts.<br/>
<br/>
You also need to enter your passcode when:<ul><li>The device has just been turned on or restarted.</li><br/>
<li>The device hasn't been unlocked for more than 48 hours.</li><br/>
<li>The passcode hasn't been used to unlock the device in the last six-and-a-half days and Optic ID hasn't unlocked the device in the last 4 hours.</li></ul>You may still be able to use Optic ID in these cases if your iPhone is nearby, as Apple explains in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213962#416">support document about setting up and using Optic ID</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/optic-id/">Optic ID</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-vision-pro-optic-id/">Optic ID: Apple Explains Vision Pro&#039;s Iris Authentication System</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/optic-id-apple-explains-vision-pros-iris-authentication-system.2418352/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 Drops to Record Low &#36;299 Price at Best Buy [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-watch-series-9-drops/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-drops-to-record-low-299-price-at-best-buy-updated.2418335/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2024 09:38:23 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-watch-series-9-drops/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy kicked off <a href="https://howl.me/clunu1dvWgW">a new Apple Watch sale</a> this weekend, and in it you can get the 41mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for the all-time low price of <a href="https://howl.me/clyFscY8CSo"><strong>&#36;299.00</strong></a> in all aluminum colors, down from &#36;399.00. According to Best Buy's website, these deals will only last for the remainder of today, so if you've been waiting for great Apple Watch deals, now is the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/series-9-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-926442" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://howl.me/clyFs3reElo"><strong>&#36;329.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00, which is another record low price. Best Buy has every aluminum model of the GPS Apple Watch Series 9 on sale, so you can get the Starlight, Pink, Midnight, Silver, and PRODUCT(RED) colors on sale at these record low prices. This also includes both S/M and M/L band sizes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clyFscY8CSo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clyFs3reElo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has cellular models of the Apple Watch Series 9 at best-ever prices. You can get the 41mm Cellular model for <a href="https://howl.me/clyFvTgMURf"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a> and the 45mm Cellular model for <a href="https://howl.me/clyFvAK7DJA"><strong>&#36;429.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;100 markdowns and available in all aluminum colors.<br/>
<br/>
As of last month, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">sales ban was reenacted</a> in the United States on any Apple Watch model sold by Apple that has blood oxygen sensing. While Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models purchased directly from Apple currently come with blood oxygen sensing disabled, retailers like Best Buy are able to continue selling through their existing stocks that include the feature.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> These deals have expired, although Best Buy still has all Apple Watch Series 9 models at solid second-best prices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/03/apple-watch-series-9-drops/">Apple Watch Series 9 Drops to Record Low &#36;299 Price at Best Buy [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-drops-to-record-low-299-price-at-best-buy-updated.2418335/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
