<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:04:07 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>VR Games Job Simulator and Vacation Simulator Launch on Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/job-simulator-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vr-games-job-simulator-and-vacation-simulator-launch-on-apple-vision-pro.2427621/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 17:09:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/job-simulator-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular VR games <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/job-simulator/id6477550490">Job Simulator</a> and <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/vacation-simulator/id6475732786">Vacation Simulator</a> are now available for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Job Simulator I Apple Vision Pro Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uD5RQbGkGzI" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Job Simulator is a VR game where automation and robots have replaced all human jobs. Players can relive what it was like to work as a human with not-so historically accurate recreations of jobs that include an office worker, gourmet chef, and store clerk.<br/>
<br/>
The game uses hand tracking for control purposes, which means no controller is required. Hands can be used for interacting with, throwing, and smashing objects.<br/>
<br/>
Vacation Simulator is similar to Job Simulator, but it provides a simulated vacation experience. Activities include ice sculpting, swimming, knitting mittens, building snowhumans, doing yoga, painting, taking selfies, and more in forest, mountain, and beach scenes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Vacation Simulator I Apple Vision Pro Trailer" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O6m4PrvA_R8" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Vacation Simulator and Job Simulator have previously been available on Steam VR, Oculus devices, and PlayStationVR, and were released in 2019 and 2016, respectively. <br/>
<br/>
Job Simulator is available from the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> for &#36;19.99, while Vacation Simulator is priced at &#36;29.99.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/job-simulator-vision-pro/">VR Games Job Simulator and Vacation Simulator Launch on Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vr-games-job-simulator-and-vacation-simulator-launch-on-apple-vision-pro.2427621/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>T-Mobile Announces UScellular Acquisition, Promises Improved Connectivity in Rural Areas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/tmobile-uscellular-acquisition/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-uscellular-acquisition-promises-improved-connectivity-in-rural-areas.2427618/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:43:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/tmobile-uscellular-acquisition/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[T-Mobile <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/news/business/uscellular-acquisition-operations-assets">today announced plans</a> to purchase UScellular's wireless operations for &#36;4.4 billion, a deal that includes UScellular's wireless customers, stores, and select cellular spectrum.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/T-Mobile-Generic-Feature-Pink-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951944" /><br/>
According to T-Mobile, the purchase will provide millions of UScellular customers access to the T-Mobile network, improving connectivity in underserved rural areas. T-Mobile also plans to use the spectrum and wireless assets from UScellular to expand its home broadband offerings.<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile's press release suggests that wireless customers across the United States will "benefit from enhanced choice and competition," wording aimed at the federal regulators who will need to approve the deal. UScellular will retain ownership of some of its spectrum and its towers, with T-Mobile planning to lease space on approximately 2,000 towers.<br/>
<br/>
UScellular customers will have the option to stay on their existing plans or move to an unlimited T-Mobile plan with no switching costs.<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile has previously acquired MetroPCS and Sprint, with the latter merger <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/11/06/fcc-approves-t-mobile-sprint-merger/">occurring in 2020</a> after it was previously <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/11/04/sprint-t-mobile-call-off-merger/">called off in 2014</a>. U.S. regulators have been concerned with the lack of a fourth major carrier in the United States and could be hesitant to approve yet another T-Mobile purchase.<br/>
<br/>
T-Mobile says that the deal should close in mid-2025.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/tmobile-uscellular-acquisition/">T-Mobile Announces UScellular Acquisition, Promises Improved Connectivity in Rural Areas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/t-mobile-announces-uscellular-acquisition-promises-improved-connectivity-in-rural-areas.2427618/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>YouTube Launches &#039;Playables&#039; Mobile Games for iOS</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/youtube-playables/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-launches-playables-mobile-games-for-ios.2427617/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:15:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/youtube-playables/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>YouTube</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[YouTube is the latest company to introduce mobile games that are available outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, today announcing <a href="https://blog.youtube/news-and-events/youtube-playables/">the official launch</a> of "Playables" in the YouTube app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/youtube-playables.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952517" /><br/>
Playables are free games that can be played on the YouTube website or in the YouTube app for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. There are more than 75 games available, including Angry Birds Showdown and Cut the Rope.<br/>
<br/>
YouTube is focusing on "lightweight, entertaining games," so many of the options are games that are meant to be played for a short period of time rather than longer games that you might find on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Game progress is saved, and YouTube keeps track of all-time best scores.<br/>
<br/>
Playables have been available for a small number of users in select markets as YouTube has tested the feature, but as of today, the games are rolling out to everyone and are more widely available. Playables can be accessed in the iOS app by going to the Explore menu and choosing the Playables section.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix has offered a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/14/netflix-games-tvs-macs-pcs/">selection of in-app games</a> since 2021, and has started testing games on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> as well. Other companies like The New York Times also offer dedicated games.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/youtube/">YouTube</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/youtube-playables/">YouTube Launches &#039;Playables&#039; Mobile Games for iOS</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/youtube-launches-playables-mobile-games-for-ios.2427617/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Check Out This LEGO Apple Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/lego-apple-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-lego-apple-store.2427611/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:21:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/lego-apple-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>LEGO</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LEGO has an "Ideas" website that allows fans to submit mockups and suggestions for future LEGO sets, and one fan recently <a href="https://ideas.lego.com/projects/798c9236-c87f-40be-a740-3166f919c8b6">designed a detailed Apple Store</a> that any Apple enthusiast would love to build.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/lego-apple-store.jpg" alt="" width="1350" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952512" /><br/>
The LEGO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a>'s design isn't made to resemble a specific store, but instead uses the design elements that Apple has incorporated into many of its locations. There's an all-glass facade with trees in pots, minifigures in classic Apple blue shirts, and an upstairs area reached by a set of stairs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/lego-apple-store-exterior.jpg" alt="" width="1350" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952513" /><br/>
Inside, there are tables with different iPhones and Macs on display, a section for headphones, and product boxes on shelves. There's also a colorful display upstairs, a big white Apple logo at the front of the store, and exterior area housing large versions of some of Apple's most iconic products.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/lego-apple-store-inside.jpg" alt="" width="1350" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952514" /><br/>
If the LEGO &zwnj;Apple Store&zwnj; gets 10,000 "supporters" or votes on the LEGO ideas site, LEGO will review it and will consider it for an official retail set. It is unclear if Apple would approve such a set, and it is unknown if it will pass LEGO's review. LEGO evaluates submissions based on existing products, products already in development, brand fit, expected demand, licensing possibilities, build quality, and more.<br/>
<br/>
The set comes from Legotruman, who has had several other ideas reviewed by LEGO staff, and who was responsible for <a href="https://ideas.lego.com/projects/acc7c4c8-3967-4563-8fb5-a49859fa7755">the Starry Night LEGO</a> set that is now available for sale.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lego/">LEGO</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/lego-apple-store/">Check Out This LEGO Apple Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/check-out-this-lego-apple-store.2427611/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.5, Downgrading No Longer an Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-5-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2427610/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:07:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 17.5, preventing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS. The update is no longer being signed after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">May 20 release of iOS 17.5.1</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Green-and-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940351" /><br/>
It is not unusual for Apple to stop signing an older version of iOS, and it typically happens a week or two after a new version of iOS comes out. When an update is no longer signed, it means it is no longer able to be installed on an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; per a server side software verification check.<br/>
<br/>
Apple prevents users from installing older versions of iOS to encourage customers to keep their operating systems up to date with the latest security improvements.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.5.1 addressed a corruption bug that could cause <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">deleted photos to reappear on an iPhone</a>. The update is now the only publicly released version of iOS available.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-5/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.5, Downgrading No Longer an Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-5-downgrading-no-longer-an-option.2427610/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nomad Launches Qi-Rechargeable Find My Tracking Card to Prevent Lost Wallets</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/nomad-tracking-card/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-qi-rechargeable-find-my-tracking-card-to-prevent-lost-wallets.2427603/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 12:34:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/nomad-tracking-card&#038;post_date=1716935666/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Nomad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Nomad today announced the launch of the <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/tracking-card">Tracking Card</a>, a super thin Find My-enabled card that is designed to be carried in a wallet so that it's trackable with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/nomad-tracking-card.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952503" /><br/>
The Tracking Card is about the thickness of two credit cards (2mm), so it doesn't take up too much space in a wallet. It's also credit card sized, which means it can be carried right alongside other cards. There are several <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> cards on the market now, and 2mm is among the thinnest that are available. The Eufy SmartTrack, Chipolo CARD Spot, and Tile Slim are all a bit thicker.<br/>
<br/>
One side of the black plastic card is largely plain except for a logo, and the other side has a second subtle Nomad logo with light gray lines representing the hardware that's inside the card. It's not identifiable as a &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; tracking card, so if someone steals your wallet, it won't immediately tip the thief off that it's trackable. It actually looks a lot like a key card.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/nomad-tracking-card-2.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952504" /><br/>
There's a hidden button on the card that's pressed to add it to &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, and adding it to the app is as simple as opening it up, pressing the "+" button, and then holding down the pairing button on the Tracking Card. From there, it can be given a name and an icon, and it's trackable right alongside other &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; items and also Apple devices with &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad's Tracking Card connects to the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; over Bluetooth, but it is also able to take advantage of the full &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network, utilizing nearby Apple devices if it is out of range of your own &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; provides the current location if it's with you, or the Tracking Card's last known location if it's been located with the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network.<br/>
<br/>
When nearby, the Tracking Card can play a sound via &zwnj;Find My&zwnj;, which is helpful for locating your wallet if it's been misplaced in the home or nearby. There is no Precision Finding as there is with Apple devices, so the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app can't lead you directly to the Tracking Card. The beeping is not loud enough to hear it from another room in most cases, especially if it's buried in couch cushions or similarly hidden, but it should be loud enough if you're in the same room with the card.<br/>
<br/>
You can set the Tracking Card to notify you if it's left behind, which means it sends an alert when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; gets out of range. That's perhaps the most useful feature of the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; network because it lets you know right away if you've misplaced or dropped something.<br/>
<br/>
There are options to get directions to the Tracking Card in the &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; app, plus you can share it with family members so they can track it and Lost Mode is available for adding your contact information should your wallet be lost. As with other &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; accessories, Nomad is able to deliver firmware updates should new software be needed.<br/>
<br/>
Perhaps the best feature of the Tracking Card is the battery. The battery inside can be recharged by putting the card on a Qi-based charger, and the markings on the card show the alignment. I tested the card with several Qi/<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> chargers and they were all able to provide power, with charging indicated by a small red LED on the card. The light turns green when it's fully charged, and turns off when there's no charger connected. There is a small amount of metal inside, but it's enough that it's able to be attached to upright chargers as well as flat chargers. There isn't a magnet in the card so it's not going to affect the magnetic stripe on credit and debit cards. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/nomad-tracking-card-3.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952505" /><br/>
According to Nomad, a single charge should last for around five months, so it isn't going to need to be charged often. Nomad says IPX7 waterproofing is included, so if the card happens to get wet, it'll survive.<br/>
<br/>
Many of the wallet-sized Bluetooth trackers on the market do not have a rechargeable or replaceable battery inside, so it's nice that Nomad has designed the Tracking Card to last more than a couple of years. With the Chipolo Card Spot or Eufy SmartTrack, the entire device needs to be thrown out when the built-in battery dies.<br/>
<br/>
At &#36;40, Nomad's Tracking Card is about &#36;10 more expensive than some competing products from well-known companies like Chipolo, but it does have built-in wireless charging and a slim design. There are some &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; wallet tracking cards <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FReyke-Tracker-Wireless-Charging-Passports%2Fdp%2FB0CT38WDJC%2F">on Amazon</a> with the same Qi technology for around &#36;10 to &#36;15 less, so Qi charging for trackers isn't a totally new idea. Of course, these are not known Apple accessory makers so quality and functionality is unverified, plus the reviews are mixed, but there are other options out there.<br/>
<br/>
Note that like all &zwnj;Find My&zwnj; Bluetooth tracking accessories, the Tracking Card from Nomad only works with Apple devices. It cannot be used on the Android platform.<br/>
<br/>
Nomad's Tracking Card can be <a href="https://nomadgoods.com/products/tracking-card">purchased from the Nomad website</a> as of today.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Nomad provided MacRumors with a Tracking Card for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nomad/">Nomad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/nomad-tracking-card/">Nomad Launches Qi-Rechargeable Find My Tracking Card to Prevent Lost Wallets</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nomad-launches-qi-rechargeable-find-my-tracking-card-to-prevent-lost-wallets.2427603/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-airpods-pro-firmware-6f7/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2427600/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:46:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-airpods-pro-firmware-6f7/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released new firmware update for both the Lightning and USB-C versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2. The new firmware is version 6F7, up from the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/05/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware-6b34/">6B34 firmware</a> released in November.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-867348" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/airpods-pro-2-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Apple does not provide details on what features might be included in the refreshed firmware beyond "bug fixes and other improvements," so it is unclear what's new in the update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple does not give customers instructions on how to upgrade AirPods software, but firmware is generally installed over-the-air while the ‌‌AirPods‌‌ are connected to an iOS device. Putting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ in the case, connecting the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to a power source, and then pairing the ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌ to an iOS device or Mac should force the update.<br/>
<br/>
You can check your ‌‌‌AirPods‌‌ firmware by following these steps:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Connect your ‌‌‌‌‌‌&zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;‌‌‌‌‌‌ to your iOS device.</li><br/>
 	<li>Open the Settings app.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap General.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap About.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap ‌‌‌‌‌AirPods‌‌‌‌‌.</li><br/>
 	<li>Look at the number next to "Firmware Version."</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
If we learn more about what's new in the firmware release, we'll update this article.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-airpods-pro-firmware-6f7/">Apple Releases New AirPods Pro 2 Firmware</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-airpods-pro-2-firmware.2427600/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next Apple Watch Activity Challenge to Take Place on June 5 to Celebrate Global Running Day</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-watch-activity-global-running-day/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-apple-watch-activity-challenge-to-take-place-on-june-5-to-celebrate-global-running-day.2427599/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:32:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-watch-activity-global-running-day/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a new Apple Watch activity challenge for June 5, which is Global Running Day. This is an Apple Watch activity challenge that Apple has not offered in the past, so it is a new day and a new award.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/running-day-2024-apple-watch.jpg" alt="" width="669" height="376" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952490" /><br/>
To complete the challenge, Apple Watch owners will need to record a running workout of at least five kilometers on June 5.<br/>
<blockquote>Hit the road, trail, track, or tread for Global Running Day! Record a running workout and go at least 5 km on June 5 to earn this special badge.</blockquote><br/>
Those who complete the challenge will unlock a dedicated badge in the Fitness app along with animated stickers that can be used in the Messages and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/running_day_2024_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952488" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/running_day_2024_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952487" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/running_day_2024_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952486" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/running_day_2024_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952485" /><br/>
The World Running Day challenge is the second new challenge that Apple has introduced in 2024, and it follows the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-watch-activity-challenge-meditation-day/">May 21 Meditation Day challenge</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-watch-activity-global-running-day/">Next Apple Watch Activity Challenge to Take Place on June 5 to Celebrate Global Running Day</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-apple-watch-activity-challenge-to-take-place-on-june-5-to-celebrate-global-running-day.2427599/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Design Award Finalists Announced Ahead of WWDC 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/2024-apple-design-award-finalists/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-design-award-finalists-announced-ahead-of-wwdc-2024.2427598/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:20:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/2024-apple-design-award-finalists/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Apple Design Awards</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we prepare for the 2024 Worldwide Developers Conference, Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/design/awards/">today announced</a> its finalists for the Apple Design Awards. Apple chooses the best apps and games annually, announcing the winners at WWDC.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/2024-apple-design-award.jpg" alt="" width="1580" height="890" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952483" /><br/>
The Apple Design Awards are meant to highlight apps with outstanding design, innovation, ingenuity, and technical achievement. Apps have been selected in the following categories: Delight and Fun, Inclusivity, Innovation, Interaction, Social Impact, Visuals and Graphics, and Spatial Computing. The last category is a new addition this year that's focused on Vision Pro apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Delight and Fun</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Dudel Draw</li><br/>
 	<li>Bears Gratitude</li><br/>
 	<li>Rooms</li><br/>
 	<li>WHAT THE CAR?</li><br/>
 	<li>NYT Games</li><br/>
 	<li>Hello Kitty Island Adventure</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Inclusivity</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Oko</li><br/>
 	<li>Complete Anatomy 2024</li><br/>
 	<li>Tiimo</li><br/>
 	<li>Unpacking</li><br/>
 	<li>Quadline</li><br/>
 	<li>Crayola Adventures</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Innovation</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Copilot Money</li><br/>
 	<li>SmartGym</li><br/>
 	<li>Procreate Dreams</li><br/>
 	<li>Call of Duty: Warzone Mobile</li><br/>
 	<li>Lost in Play</li><br/>
 	<li>Wavelength</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Interaction</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Procreate Dreams</li><br/>
 	<li>Arc Search</li><br/>
 	<li>Crouton</li><br/>
 	<li>Little Nightmares</li><br/>
 	<li>Rytmos</li><br/>
 	<li>finity.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Social Impact</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>How We Feel</li><br/>
 	<li>Ahead: Emotions Coach</li><br/>
 	<li>Gentler Streak Fitness Tracker</li><br/>
 	<li>The Wreck</li><br/>
 	<li>Cityscapes: Sim Builder</li><br/>
 	<li>The Bear</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Visuals and Graphics</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Sunlitt</li><br/>
 	<li>Meditate</li><br/>
 	<li>Rooms</li><br/>
 	<li>Death Stranding Director's Cut</li><br/>
 	<li>Lies of P</li><br/>
 	<li>Honkai: Star Rail</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Spatial Computing</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Sky Guide</li><br/>
 	<li>NBA</li><br/>
 	<li>djay</li><br/>
 	<li>Synth Riders</li><br/>
 	<li>Blackbox</li><br/>
 	<li>Loona: Cozy Puzzle Games</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
One app and one game will be chosen in each category, with Apple to announce winners during the 2024 Worldwide Developers Conference. Winners will receive a physical award and hardware to help them continue to create apps and games.<br/>
<br/>
Links to all of the apps that are nominated <a href="https://developer.apple.com/design/awards/">can be found on Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-design-awards/">Apple Design Awards</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/2024-apple-design-award-finalists/">Apple Design Award Finalists Announced Ahead of WWDC 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-design-award-finalists-announced-ahead-of-wwdc-2024.2427598/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Confirms Time for June 10 WWDC Keynote, Shares Full Schedule</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-time-for-june-10-wwdc-keynote-shares-full-schedule.2427595/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 10:21:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>WWDC</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared details on the <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apples-worldwide-developers-conference-to-kick-off-june-10-with-keynote-address/">schedule that it has prepared</a> for the 2024 Worldwide Developers Conference, which is set to take place from June 10 to June 14.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/wwdc-2024-main-image-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944281" /><br/>
While WWDC always includes a keynote, Apple has confirmed that it will be held on June 10 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time. Apple is expected to announce <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, iPadOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-15/">macOS 15</a>, tvOS 18, watchOS 11, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 2, and at this time, we have not heard rumors of hardware.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will follow the keynote with the Platforms State of the Union, and the Apple Design Awards are typically also held on the same day.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>10:00 a.m. PDT</strong> - Apple Keynote, which provides a first look at "groundbreaking updates" coming to Apple platforms later in the year.</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>1:00 p.m. PDT</strong> - Platforms State of the Union, which will take a deeper dive into the latest advances across iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;, and watchOS, and new tools that will further empower Apple developers.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The keynote event will be available to stream on Apple's website, the Apple Developer App, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, and YouTube. The Platforms State of the Union will be available on the Apple Developer app and the Apple Developer website.<br/>
<br/>
A select number of developers have been invited to a viewing party at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-park/">Apple Park</a> campus in Cupertino, California, and they will be able to watch the keynote and the Platforms State of the Union in person.<br/>
<br/>
Throughout WWDC week, Apple is hosting online labs and consultations for developers to get advice on implementing the new features that Apple plans to announce at WWDC, plus there will be more than 100 technical sessions from Apple engineers, designers, and other experts.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recommends that developers download the Apple Developer app to keep up with the WWDC announcements.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">WWDC 2024</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-inc-and-tech-industry.8">Apple, Inc and Tech Industry</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">Apple Confirms Time for June 10 WWDC Keynote, Shares Full Schedule</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-confirms-time-for-june-10-wwdc-keynote-shares-full-schedule.2427595/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Review: Belkin&#039;s 2-in-1 Qi2 Magnetic Charging Pad Powers Up Your iPhone, AirPods, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/review/belkin-boostcharge-pro-2-in-1-qi2-charging-pad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-belkins-2-in-1-qi2-magnetic-charging-pad-powers-up-your-iphone-airpods-and-more.2427588/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:26:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/review/belkin-boostcharge-pro-2-in-1-qi2-charging-pad&#038;post_date=1716924380/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Belkin</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Back at CES in January, Belkin confirmed that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/07/ces-2024-belkin-chargers-auto-tracking-stand/">several wireless chargers using the Qi2 standard</a> based on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> would soon be rolling out, and I've recently been able to spend some time testing out the <a href="https://belkin.evyy.net/QyM9GP">BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad</a> from that lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/belkin-2-in-1-pad-parts.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952178" /><br/>
As the name suggests, the BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad with Qi2 15W is a flat pad-style charger offering two surfaces on which to charge devices. One side has a Qi2 wireless charging pad supporting recent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models at up to their maximum of 15 watts, while the other is a 5-watt Qi pad intended to work with AirPods models with wireless charging cases. Other devices which support Qi wireless charging like phones can also be charged on the pad, though they will not align magnetically and will charge at a much slower speed compared to using the Qi2 pad.<br/>
<br/>
In my testing, I found that the Qi2 pad didn't charge my <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max quite as quickly as Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Charger does, but it was fairly close and definitely faster than an original Qi pad which is limited to 7.5 watts for iPhones. The pad was able to boost my &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s battery from 30% to around 70% in an hour, though as with all other charging methods, the rate began to slow significantly beyond about 80% to prevent overheating and overcharging as the battery began approaching a full charge.<br/>
<br/>
In addition to the two wireless charging pads, the BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad includes an additional USB-C port supporting up to 5 watts of output, allowing for wired charging of other devices such as an Apple Watch with an appropriate cable. (If you prefer integrated Apple Watch charging, Belkin also offers a <a href="https://belkin.evyy.net/KjM6Pn">BoostCharge 3-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad</a> with an Apple Watch charging puck already included to attach to that USB-C port.)<br/>
<br/>
The BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad is available in either black or white, and the unit is powered by a color-matched 30-watt power adapter and 5-foot (1.5-meter) USB-C to USB-C cable, with both thankfully included in the box. The U.S. power adapter is similar in size and shape to Apple's 20-watt USB-C adapter and unfortunately does not include folding prongs, which would have been convenient for travel. You're of course free to use any USB-C power source of 30 watts or more, so it's easy enough to substitute something that better fits your needs, but I would have liked to see a more travel-friendly adapter right in the box.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/belkin-2-in-1-pad-top.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952179" /><br/>
The pad design itself is ideal for travel as its minimal thickness allows it to fit nicely in a computer bag or backpack. It is on the heavy side though at around 11 ounces (310 grams) plus the cable and power adapter, which might hamper portability a bit. That heft does, however, contribute to stability on surfaces and makes it easier to detach an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sitting on the magnetic pad. At around 6.4 x 3.2 x 0.6 inches (16.3 x 8.2 x 1.5 cm), the unit is pretty close to the size of an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max but somewhat thicker due to the slightly elevated Qi2 pad.<br/>
<br/>
The body of the charger is a matte plastic with some arcs of rubber-like material on the bottom to protect surfaces and limit sliding. The Qi2 charging pad on the left has a similar rubber-like surface to protect your phone from scratches, while the lower-power Qi pad on the right is simply a shallow depression in the smooth, hard plastic to help with accurate placement of an AirPods case for charging. Some magnets would have been nice to ensure easy alignment of AirPods cases supporting that feature, but I didn't have any trouble getting my AirPods to register properly with the charger.<br/>
<br/>
The extra USB-C output port is on the right side of the unit, while the USB-C input port is on the rear. There's no status light for the Qi2 pad, but the AirPods pad has a small LED status light in front of it that shines white while a device is charging or orange if there is a charging error. It also briefly flashes white upon plugging the pad in, confirming the unit is receiving power.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/belkin-2-in-1-pad-ports.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="703" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952180" /><br/>
Overall, I've found the BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad to be a reliable wireless charging accessory with some nice features but also some minor drawbacks. It has a relatively travel-friendly design, features a clean, unobtrusive look, and reliably charges devices, but the lack of magnetic alignment for the AirPods charging spot and lack of folding prongs on the power adapter are missed opportunities in my opinion.<br/>
<br/>
While the pad design is simple and convenient for travel, some may prefer an angled charging surface for better visibility of the screen while their phone is charging on a desk or nightstand. Fortunately, Belkin offers chargers with that design as well, and even some that convert between the two, so you've got options.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://belkin.evyy.net/QyM9GP">Belkin's BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad</a> is priced at &#36;79.99 in either black or white on both Belkin's site and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FBelkin-BoostCharge-MagSafe-Compatible-Wireless-Additional%2Fdp%2FB0CRSVJQMD">Amazon</a>. One of the anticipated advantages of Qi2 was the ability to have &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging performance without the need for Apple's &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; licensing that drives costs up, but Belkin's similar <a href="https://belkin.evyy.net/vNJK0d">BoostCharge Pro 2-in-1 Wireless Charging Pad with Official MagSafe Charging</a> is priced at the exact same &#36;79.99. It does lack the extra USB-C output port that the Qi2 model has, but still, I've been hoping for bigger cost savings with Qi2 over &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; than I've seen so far.<br/>
<br/>
As I mentioned previously, in addition to the 2-in-1 model, <a href="https://belkin.evyy.net/KjM6Pn">Belkin also offers a 3-in-1 model</a> that includes an Apple Watch fast charger which mounts directly to the extra USB-C port on the main body of the unit. But due in part to licensing and sourcing of official Apple Watch charging components, moving to the 3-in-1 model adds a whopping &#36;50 to the price, bringing it to &#36;129.99.<br/>
<br/>
Alternatively, you could get the 2-in-1 model and then spend just &#36;29 for an official USB-C Apple Watch charging cable to plug into that USB-C port. It's not as clean a solution as the direct-attach module from Belkin, but it'll save you &#36;20, or there are other multi-device charging solutions available to fit your particular needs.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: Belkin provided MacRumors with the BoostCharge 2-in-1 Magnetic Charging Pad with Qi2 15W for the purpose of this review. No other compensation was received. MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Belkin and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/belkin/">Belkin</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/review/belkin-boostcharge-pro-2-in-1-qi2-charging-pad/">Review: Belkin&#039;s 2-in-1 Qi2 Magnetic Charging Pad Powers Up Your iPhone, AirPods, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/review-belkins-2-in-1-qi2-magnetic-charging-pad-powers-up-your-iphone-airpods-and-more.2427588/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Hits New Low Price of &#36;299.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-10th-gen-ipad-hits-new-low-price-of-299-99-on-amazon.2427572/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:36:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 10th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad has hit a new all-time low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.99</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;349.00. You can also find another record low price on the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and both of these deals <strong>require you to clip an on-page coupon</strong> in order to see the deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/10th-gen-ipad-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951776" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad, you can get this tablet for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;499.00. Both tablets are available to be delivered as soon as this week, if you are a Prime member (or pay for the fastest delivery option), and early next week otherwise.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple cut the prices of this iPad lineup earlier in the month, and each model is now &#36;100 cheaper. After this, we quickly saw discounts measuring about &#36;20-&#36;30 on Wi-Fi models, and today marks the first time we've tracked steeper &#36;49 markdowns on the new prices of the 10th generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/">Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Hits New Low Price of &#36;299.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-10th-gen-ipad-hits-new-low-price-of-299-99-on-amazon.2427572/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hearing Study Reveals New Insights on Tinnitus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hearing-study-reveals-new-insights-on-tinnitus.2427570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:02:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-hearing-study-shares-preliminary-insights-on-tinnitus/">shared an update</a> on the Apple Hearing Study that reveals new insights into the hearing condition tinnitus.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-hearing-study.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-952448" /><br/>
In one of the largest surveys on tinnitus to date, researchers from the University of Michigan examined data from over 160,000 participants using Apple devices. Tinnitus, defined as the perception of sound without an external source, can manifest as ringing, buzzing, or other sounds and can impact quality of life by disrupting sleep, concentration, and clear hearing.<br/>
<br/>
The study found that 77.6% of participants had experienced tinnitus at some point in their lives. The prevalence of daily tinnitus increased with age, with those aged 55 and older being three times more likely to experience it daily compared to younger participants aged 18-34. Male participants reported a slightly higher incidence of daily tinnitus, at 2.7% more than females, but a higher percentage of males stated they had never experienced tinnitus.<br/>
<br/>
Participants reported employing various methods to manage their tinnitus. The most common strategies included using noise machines, listening to nature sounds, and practicing meditation. Regarding the causes of tinnitus, the study highlighted that noise trauma or exposure to excessively high noise levels was the primary reported cause, cited by 20.3% of participants. Apple highlighted several ways in which its devices can help support hearing health:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li><b>Noise app</b>: The Noise app on the Apple Watch can notify users when environmental noise levels may impact their hearing health. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s Health app tracks a user's history of sound level exposure and indicates if headphone audio or environmental noise levels exceed World Health Organization standards.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Environmental sound levels</b>: Users can view environmental sound levels over the course of a week on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and check noise levels in decibels on the Apple Watch, ensuring their exposure remains within safe limits.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Active Noise Cancellation and Loud Sound Reduction mode</b>: Active Noise Cancellation on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> uses built-in microphones to detect and counter external sounds with anti-noise, effectively canceling them before they reach the user's ears. For those who still wish to hear surrounding sounds, the Loud Sound Reduction mode on &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; (2nd generation) reduces loud noises while maintaining sound quality.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Reduce loud audio</b>: To set a headphone volume limit, users can navigate to Settings, tap "Sounds & Haptics" (on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 7 and later) or "Sounds" (for earlier models), then tap "Headphone Safety" to enable "Reduce Loud Audio" and adjust the slider to the desired decibel level.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Hearing Study, conducted in collaboration with the University of Michigan, seeks to advance understanding of sound exposure and its impact on hearing health. The study has already accumulated approximately 400 million hours of calculated environmental sound levels, supplemented by lifestyle surveys, to analyze how sound exposure affects hearing, stress, and related health aspects. The data collected is also being shared with the World Health Organization as part of its Make Listening Safe initiative. See Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-hearing-study-shares-preliminary-insights-on-tinnitus/">full press release</a> for more information.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/">Apple Hearing Study Reveals New Insights on Tinnitus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hearing-study-reveals-new-insights-on-tinnitus.2427570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Beats Pill Speaker Listed on Apple&#039;s Regulatory Website as Launch Approaches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-listed-on-apples-regulatory-website-as-launch-approaches.2427568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:58:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After appearing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">alongside athletes</a> and celebrities, in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-beats-pill-ios-17-5/">iOS 17.5 code</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/">in the FCC database</a> over the past month or so, a next-generation Beats Pill speaker has now been <a href="https://regulatoryinfo.apple.com/cwt/api/ext/file?fileId=eurocompliance%2FA3211_V1_V0.zip">listed on Apple's regulatory compliance website</a> for Europe.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/New-Beats-Pill-iOS-17.5-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949655" /><em>The new Beats Pill speaker</em></div><br/>
The original Beats Pill was a wireless Bluetooth speaker introduced in 2012, prior to Apple's acquisition of Beats. The speaker received a few updates in its first several years on the market, with the final revision being a redesigned Beats Pill+ with a Lightning charging port, introduced under Apple's ownership in 2015. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">discontinued the Beats Pill+ in early 2022</a>, but a new version now appears to be on the horizon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/beats-pill-f1-daniel-ricciardo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949043" /><em>The new Beats Pill speaker</em></div><br/>
The new Beats Pill is likely to feature a USB-C charging port, upgraded Bluetooth, and more. Leaked images revealed a built-in lanyard, which was not available on previous models, along with red, black, and gold color options.<br/>
<br/>
Beats is releasing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">new Solo Buds earbuds</a> in June, so perhaps the new Beats Pill will launch next month too, but Apple has yet to formally announce the speaker. The previous Beats Pill+ was originally priced at &#36;229.95 in the U.S. when it launched in 2015, but it had been available for &#36;179.95 prior to being discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The listing on Apple's regulatory website was spotted by MacRumors contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a>.</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/">New Beats Pill Speaker Listed on Apple&#039;s Regulatory Website as Launch Approaches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-listed-on-apples-regulatory-website-as-launch-approaches.2427568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Green-Lights iPhone 16 Pro Display Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-green-lights-iphone-16-pro-display-production.2427561/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:13:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung Display and LG Display have been granted approval for mass production of OLED screens for Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, Korea's <a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=28125"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-iPhone-15-Pro-lineup-Action-button-230912.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910375" /><br/>
Both suppliers apparently received approval earlier this month, paving the way for the commencement of mass production of screens for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models. While Samsung Display will supply OLED screens for all four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, LG Display will supply screens exclusively for the Pro models. Additionally, BOE is expected to help supply OLED displays for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus.<br/>
<br/>
The development is particularly noteworthy for LG, which has historically struggled to meet Apple's production deadlines. Last year, LG Display received approval for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> OLED screens several months after Samsung Display, allowing Samsung to increase its market share and secure higher prices. <br/>
<br/>
Samsung Display is expected to undergo the approval process for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max's OLED screens by the end of this month, with LG Display scheduled to follow in the middle of June. Currently, Samsung Display has received approval for the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, with the Plus and Pro Max models soon to follow. <br/>
<br/>
<em>The Elec</em> claims that differences between the OLED displays for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; are minimal, but the bezels <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/iphone-16-even-thinner-bezels/">may be slightly thinner</a> thanks to Border Reduction Structure (BRS) technology. The entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to launch in the fall. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/">Apple Green-Lights iPhone 16 Pro Display Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-green-lights-iphone-16-pro-display-production.2427561/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Next-Gen Chip Technology on Track for 2025 Debut</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025-debut.2427559/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:06:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple chip supplier TSMC is on track to deliver 2nm chip technology next year, <a href="https://www.businesskorea.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=217935"><em>BusinessKorea</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
Apple is expected to move its custom silicon to the 2nm process next year to leverage TSMC's advancements. TSMC is said to be confidently progressing with the 2nm node. The chipmaker's Vice President of Process Development, Zhang Xiaogang, announced that "the development of the 2nm process is progressing smoothly" and mass production is on track for 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Some rumors suggested that TSMC may be forced to delay full-scale mass production of its 2nm process until 2026 due to technical challenges associated with the first-time application of Gate-All-Around (GAA) technology. These rumors were dispelled by Zhang, who confirmed that "the yield when applying GAA has reached 90 percent of the target," indicating substantial progress. Jeff Williams, Apple's Chief Operating Officer, recently made a discreet <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-coo-jeff-williams-secures-2nm-chips/">visit to Taiwan</a> to meet with TSMC President Wei Zhejia and secure supply of 2nm chips.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> is powered by the A17 Pro chip, which is manufactured with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process. This process allows for more transistors to be packed into a smaller space, delivering improvements in performance and efficiency. Apple's M4 chip, which just debuted in the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, uses an enhanced version of this ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ technology. The transition to 2nm chips should bring further improvements, with projected performance gains of 10 to 15 percent and power consumption reductions of up to 30 percent compared to the ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ process.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC remains the only company capable of manufacturing 2nm and &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips at the scale and quality Apple requires. For its ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ chips, Apple booked all of TSMC's available chipmaking capacity, and the chipmaker plans to triple its production capacity for the node by the end of the year to meet soaring demand. 2nm chips could first appear in 2025's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 lineup.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/">Apple&#039;s Next-Gen Chip Technology on Track for 2025 Debut</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025-debut.2427559/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED MacBook Pro Could Launch as Soon as 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026.2427558/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 04:20:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>Omdia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is "highly likely" to introduce new MacBook Pros featuring OLED displays in 2026, market research firm <a href="https://omdia.tech.informa.com/pr/2024/may/omdia-forecasts-oleds-for-mobile-pc-market-to-grow-37-cagr-by-2031">Omdia</a> claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/New-MacBook-Pros-Launching-Tomorrow-With-These-4-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921192" /><br/>
According to Omdia's Display long-term demand forecast tracker, demand for OLED displays in mobile devices is projected to grow by 37 percent from 2023 to 2031. This substantial growth reflects a significant shift as many tech companies, including Apple, are increasingly incorporating OLED panels into their high-end notebooks and tablets. Ricky Park, Senior Principal Analyst in Omdia's Display research practice, said:<blockquote>Apple is highly likely to incorporate OLED into its MacBook Pro models as early as 2026. This move could spark a significant surge in OLED demand within the notebook market, potentially reaching over 60 million units by 2031.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
OLED panels can individually control each pixel, resulting in more precise color reproduction and deeper blacks compared to other common display technologies. They also provide superior contrast, faster response times, better viewing angles, and greater design flexibility. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's move to offer OLED displays on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> for the first time is projected to triple demand for OLED tablets in 2024 compared to the previous year. The company is expected to bring OLED display technology to most of its tablet lineup, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>. This decision is expected to influence competitors' OLED adoption strategies and drive tablet OLED demand to exceed 30 million units by 2029.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-developing-oled-ipad-mini-for-2026/">report from last week</a> claimed that Samsung has started developing a new 8-inch OLED display panel for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;. The same report predicted that Apple would update the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with OLED technology in 2026. Last year, Samsung was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/04/macbook-pro-not-getting-oled-until-2026/">rumored</a> to be investing &#36;3.14 billion into its facility in Asan, South Korea to produce OLED panels for upcoming 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with OLED displays.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/omdia/">Omdia</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/">OLED MacBook Pro Could Launch as Soon as 2026</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026.2427558/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sales Recover in China Amid Surge in Smartphone Demand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-recover-in-china-amid-surge-in-smartphone-demand.2427556/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:45:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China surged by 52% in April, reflecting a significant rebound driven by aggressive price cuts and renewed consumer demand, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-28/apple-s-china-iphone-shipments-jump-52-as-rebound-gains-steam"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series-store.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913490" /><br/>
The surge in shipments from 2.3 million units in April 2023 to 3.5 million units in April 2024, revealed in data from the China Academy of Information and Communications Technology (CAICT), follows a series of strategic price reductions from Apple aimed at boosting sales in the region. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s recovery in China is part of a broader resurgence in the smartphone market, which saw overall sales rise by 25.5% to 22.7 million units in April. The CAICT data revealed that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales contributed significantly to this growth.<br/>
<br/>
This change comes after a challenging start to the year for Apple in China, where the company experienced a 37% slump in sales during the first two months of 2024. The recovery began in March with a 12% increase in shipments, continuing into April.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's comeback strategy in China involved substantial discounts on iPhones, with price cuts reaching up to 2,300 yuan (approximately &#36;318) on its official Tmall site. These discounts, which are double those initially offered in February, were part of an aggressive campaign to compete with local companies like Huawei. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> noted that Apple's market share in China may soon stabilize, as consumer interest in upgrading to new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is increasing. A recent survey indicated that more than half of Chinese consumers are willing to spend over 4,000 yuan (approximately &#36;550) on their next phone, a significant rise from the 33% who currently use premium handsets. This trend toward "premiumization" is expected to benefit Apple just four months away from the debut of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/">iPhone Sales Recover in China Amid Surge in Smartphone Demand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-recover-in-china-amid-surge-in-smartphone-demand.2427556/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Future iPads Could Feature Landscape Apple Logo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-future-ipads-could-feature-landscape-apple-logo.2427494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:31:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[French website <em>Numerama</em> <a href="https://www.numerama.com/tech/1747904-rencontre-avec-lequipe-design-dapple-lipad-est-une-feuille-de-verre-magique.html">interviewed three senior Apple employees</a> about the new iPad Pro models that launched earlier this month. While the discussion did not reveal many new details, it did mention one potential change for future iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPad-Pro-Landscape-Apple-Logo-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-952476" /><br/>
While the Apple logo on the back of iPads is positioned so that it appears upright in vertical orientation, the devices are often used in landscape orientation with a keyboard attached, which results in the Apple logo appearing on its side. Apple even moved the front camera to the longer right-side edge on the new iPad Pro and iPad Air models, so that it appears at the top-center when the devices are in landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
With landscape usage becoming increasingly popular, Apple product designer Molly Anderson said a landscape Apple logo is a possibility on future iPads.<br/>
<br/>
"I think it could change," said Anderson, per a computer translation of the French-language interview. "We are thinking about it. The iPad has long been a product that is used in portrait mode, but we are using it more and more in landscape mode."<br/>
<br/>
On the software side, Apple already began showing the Apple logo that appears when an iPad is booting up in a landscape position starting with iPadOS 14.5, when the device is in landscape orientation. With Apple seemingly open to making the change on the hardware side too, it will be something to look for on future iPads.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/">Apple Says Future iPads Could Feature Landscape Apple Logo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-future-ipads-could-feature-landscape-apple-logo.2427494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: These 10 New AI Features Are Coming in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-these-10-new-ai-features-are-coming-in-ios-18.2427453/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:57:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 and macOS 15 will offer an array of new AI features such as auto-generated emojis, suggested replies to emails and messages, and more, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
A significant portion of Apple's Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) is expected to focus on AI features. Writing his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that Apple's AI strategy emphasizes providing practical tools for ordinary users, with new features for core apps like Safari, Photos, and Notes. Apple will apparently use AI to deliver the following new features:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>Photo retouching.</li><br/>
	<li>Voice memo transcription.</li><br/>
	<li>Suggested replies to emails and messages.</li><br/>
	<li>Auto-generated emojis based on the content of a user's messages, providing all-new emoji for any occasion beyond the existing catalog.</li><br/>
	<li>Improved Safari web search.</li><br/>
	<li>Faster and more reliable searches in Spotlight.</li><br/>
	<li>More natural interactions with Siri.</li><br/>
	<li>More advanced version of Siri designed for the Apple Watch, optimized for "on-the-go tasks."</li><br/>
	<li>Smart recaps of missed notifications and individual messages, web-pages, news articles, documents, notes, and more.</li><br/>
	<li>Developer tools for Xcode.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
AI features that require less processing power will run entirely on-device, but more demanding tools will operate via the cloud. Apple will apparently tout the privacy advantages of this plan.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is purportedly considering marketing many of its new AI tools as a "preview," at least in beta versions of iOS 18 before its official launch in September, to make it clear that the technology is unfinished.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">Report: These 10 New AI Features Are Coming in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-these-10-new-ai-features-are-coming-in-ios-18.2427453/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
