<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 21:02:41 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Investigating Display Flickering Issue Affecting Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-display-flicker-issue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-investigating-display-flickering-issue-affecting-apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2.2407904/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 17:52:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-display-flicker-issue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is investigating an issue where the display brightness briefly flickers or "pulses" on some Apple Watch models when Always On mode is enabled, according to an internal service memo shared with Apple Authorized Service Providers today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
The memo does not indicate which Apple Watch models are affected, but the issue appears to be most prevalent on the Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models released last month. There are complaints from customers about this issue across the <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-flickering-when-raising-to-wake-on-10-0-2.2407076/">MacRumors Forums</a>, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AppleWatch/comments/16y6ssa/apple_watch_ultra_2_screen_flickering/">Reddit</a>, and the <a href="https://discussions.apple.com/thread/255165682">Apple Support Community website</a>. The issue appears to be present on all watchOS 10 versions, including the latest watchOS 10.0.2 release.<br/>
<br/>
Apple says service providers should not repair affected watches, and instead advise customers to keep their Apple Watch software up to date, suggesting that Apple will eventually make a fix available in a watchOS update. It's unclear if Apple has addressed the issue in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-rc/">watchOS 10.1</a>, which is expected to be released to the public next week.<br/>
<br/>
As a temporary solution, Apple says customers can turn off Always On mode in the Settings app under Display & Brightness → Always On.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Watch-Pink-Complications.jpg" alt="" width="1274" height="826" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917427" /><br/>
Apple is also investigating an issue where complications like Activity rings on a watch face might "temporarily turn pink," according to the memo. This is another issue that has been <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/applewatchultra/comments/16r3wxs/awu2_complications_flicker_to_pink_after_waking_up/">reported by some customers</a> online in recent weeks.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-display-flicker-issue/">Apple Investigating Display Flickering Issue Affecting Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-investigating-display-flickering-issue-affecting-apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2.2407904/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>X Tests &#039;Not A Bot&#039; Program That Charges New Users &#36;1/Year to Post</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/x-not-a-bot-program/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-tests-not-a-bot-program-that-charges-new-users-1-year-to-post.2407901/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 17:28:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/x-not-a-bot-program/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Twitter</category>
		<category>Elon Musk</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[X, the social network formerly known as Twitter, <a href="https://help.twitter.com/en/using-x/not-a-bot">today announced</a> that it is testing a "Not A Bot" program that charges new, unverified users &#36;1 per year to post and interact with content on X.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/X-twitter-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904140" /><br/>
Not A Bot is being tested in New Zealand and the Phillipines at the current time, and it only applies to new users. The X support account says that existing users are not affected "within this test."<br/>
<br/>
Charging users &#36;1 per year is meant to "reduce spam, manipulation of [the X] platform, and bot activity." X claims that subscription options have "proven to be the main solution that works at scale" to combat these issues.<blockquote>This new program aims to defend against bots and spammers who attempt to manipulate the platform and disrupt the experience of other X users. We look forward to sharing more about the results soon.</blockquote>All new accounts in New Zealand and the Philippines will be required to verify a phone number and then pay a &#36;1 USD fee to create posts, reply, repost, quote posts, and bookmark posts. New users who do not pay the fee will only be able to read posts, watch videos, and follow accounts.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word yet on whether Not A Bot will be expanded to additional countries and to users who have already signed up for X but have declined to pay the monthly fee for a premium subscription.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/twitter/">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/elon-musk/">Elon Musk</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/x-not-a-bot-program/">X Tests &#039;Not A Bot&#039; Program That Charges New Users &#36;1/Year to Post</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/x-tests-not-a-bot-program-that-charges-new-users-1-year-to-post.2407901/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Expands Vision Pro Test Labs to New York City and Sydney</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-vision-pro-lab-new-york-sydney/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-vision-pro-test-labs-to-new-york-city-and-sydney.2407889/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 13:03:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-vision-pro-lab-new-york-sydney/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Developer Program</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=wztdeypy">today announced</a> that it is expanding its Vision Pro developer labs to New York City, New York and Sydney, Australia to give developers additional locations where the new headset can be tested with their apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898552" /><br/>
Vision Pro developer labs <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/28/vision-pro-developer-lab-invites/">first launched</a> in August, giving developers a chance to try out the Vision Pro headsets to refine <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> apps ahead of when the device launches next year.<br/>
<br/>
The first Vision Pro developer labs were limited to Cupertino, London, Munich, Shanghai, Singapore, and Tokyo, meaning some developers had to travel long distances if they wanted to be able to try the Vision Pro in person. Apple was criticized for only offering one Vision Pro test spot in the United States, for example, as people from the east coast were required to travel all the way to Cupertino.<br/>
<br/>
With a Vision Pro developer lab now in New York, developers on the east coast of the United States will not need to travel as far, nor will developers in Australia. Any developer can apply to attend a Vision Pro lab, but Apple is not reimbursing for travel.<br/>
<br/>
At the Vision Pro developer labs, developers are provided with hands-on time with the Vision Pro headset as well as help from Apple engineers. The labs provide opportunities for testing and optimization for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also sent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/24/apple-vision-pro-developer-kits-now-available/">Vision Pro developer kits</a> to some developers, but the developer kits are available in limited quantities and Apple is prioritizing apps that best take advantage of the Vision Pro features and capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
Developers still have several months to work on &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; apps before the headset launches, as it is set to come out in early 2024 in the United States. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-developer-program/">Apple Developer Program</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-vision-pro-lab-new-york-sydney/">Apple Expands Vision Pro Test Labs to New York City and Sydney</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-expands-vision-pro-test-labs-to-new-york-city-and-sydney.2407889/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces Updated iPad 10 With eSIM Support in China</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ipad-10-with-esim-support-mainland-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-updated-ipad-10-with-esim-support-in-china.2407886/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 12:45:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ipad-10-with-esim-support-mainland-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com.cn/newsroom/2023/10/apple-introduces-new-apple-pencil-bringing-more-value-and-choice-to-the-lineup/">announced</a> an updated version of the cellular 10th-generation iPad with eSIM support in mainland China. Apple says the device will be available to pre-order in mainland China starting October 19 and released on October 25.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Fanned-Gray.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869881" /><br/>
China Unicom is currently the only supported eSIM carrier for the iPad in mainland China, according to a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213954">new Apple support document</a>. eSIM support in mainland China requires a 10th-generation iPad (Wi-Fi + Cellular) with model number A3162. All other iPad and iPhone models do not have eSIM support in mainland China.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's support document offers more details on how to set up an eSIM on the updated 10th-generation iPad in mainland China, and how to activate eSIM cellular data plans on the device from carriers in other countries while traveling.<br/>
<br/>
An eSIM is a digital SIM that allows users to activate a cellular plan without having to use a physical nano-SIM card.<br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks, <a href="https://twitter.com/ApolloZhaoD/status/1714346620140073343">Apollo</a>!)</em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ipad-10-with-esim-support-mainland-china/">Apple Announces Updated iPad 10 With eSIM Support in China</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-updated-ipad-10-with-esim-support-in-china.2407886/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Upcoming 17.1 Software Brings Enhance Dialogue to Original HomePod and HomePod mini</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/homepod-software-17-1-enhance-dialogue/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/upcoming-17-1-software-brings-enhance-dialogue-to-original-homepod-and-homepod-mini.2407885/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 12:40:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/homepod-software-17-1-enhance-dialogue/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> software 17.1 update that is set to be released in the near future, Apple is bringing support for Enhance Dialogue to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> and the original &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-793543" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/AppleTV-and-HomePod-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
Enhance Dialogue is a feature that is meant to boost the volume of spoken voices to make dialogue easier to hear over effects, action, and music in a movie or TV show. The feature works when a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; or &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; is paired to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> and used as the audio output option.<br/>
<br/>
Prior to now, Enhance Dialogue was available on the second-generation &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, and it was a feature that was first introduced in tvOS 17. With tvOS 17.1 and &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; software 17.1, Enhance Dialogue can be enabled on any &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; (or set of HomePods) paired to an &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K.<br/>
<br/>
Enabling Enhance Dialogue can be done by playing a TV show or movie, bringing up the playback controls with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> Remote, and choosing the Enhance Dialogue feature from the Audio Options button. It can be enabled for all content by going to Settings &gt; Video and Audio &gt; Enhance Dialogue.<br/>
<br/>
Apple today seeded the final beta version of the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.1 software, and it should see a release as soon as next week alongside iOS 17.1 and tvOS 17.1.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/homepod-software-17-1-enhance-dialogue/">Upcoming 17.1 Software Brings Enhance Dialogue to Original HomePod and HomePod mini</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/upcoming-17-1-software-brings-enhance-dialogue-to-original-homepod-and-homepod-mini.2407885/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>32-Inch iMac With Mini-LED Display Rumored to Launch in 2025</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/32-inch-imac-with-mini-led-display-rumored-to-launch-in-2025.2407881/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:58:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A higher-end <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> with a mini-LED 32-inch display will come out in 2025, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1714350456565350625">Apple analyst Ming-Chi</a> Kuo. Kuo does not specify, but this machine could be positioned as an "&zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro" to replace the 2017 model that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/19/imac-pro-officially-discontinued/">discontinued two years ago</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/iMac-Pro-2022-27-and-24-iMac.jpg" alt="" width="1626" height="914" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833952" /><br/>
There have been multiple rumors of a larger &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; over the last couple of years, but the information has been confused with standalone display options and products that Apple ultimately shelved, leading to some confusion over if and when we would see a larger &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; option. The 27-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; was also nixed in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
After the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; Pro was discontinued, Apple replaced it with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> and its matching 27-inch Studio Display, and there has been no sign of a larger &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; since then. It sounds like that is set to change in 2025, with Apple using the same mini-LED technology that has been introduced in the more expensive Pro Display XDR.<br/>
<br/>
At 32 inches, a larger &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; would offer the same dimensions as the 6K Pro Display XDR, which Apple sells for &#36;5,000. As for the design, we could perhaps see slimmer bezels and a machine that is ultimately modeled after the Studio Display, with Apple eliminating the chin, but rumors are not clear on this point.<div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">32-Inch iMac With Mini-LED Display Rumored to Launch in 2025</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/32-inch-imac-with-mini-led-display-rumored-to-launch-in-2025.2407881/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: New 24-Inch iMac Coming in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/24-inch-imac-2024-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-24-inch-imac-coming-in-2024.2407880/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:47:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/24-inch-imac-2024-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will release a new 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> in 2024, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1714350456565350625">Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo</a>. Kuo's prediction is in line with previous rumors from <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, who has also said that a new &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is likely to come in 2024.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iMac-M3-Blue-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917291" /><br/>
Kuo does not mention which chip Apple will use, but Gurman has claimed that Apple will use the M3 chip in the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;. The M3 chip is expected to feature an 8-core GPU and 10-core GPU, and because it is built on a new 3-nanometer process, it will have performance and efficiency improvements. <br/>
<br/>
The current 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; came out in 2021, and it is equipped with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip. Apple has opted not to update the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; since the debut of the &zwnj;M1&zwnj; chip, so it is overdue for a refresh.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman has long maintained that Apple has no intention of introducing an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> version of the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, which would be accurate with Kuo's projected timeline. Last week, Japanese site <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></em> said that Apple would release a 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; with &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; Pro chips i<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/imac-m2-and-m2-pro-rumor/">n the near future</a>, but that appears to be inaccurate. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/24-inch-imac-2024-launch/">Kuo: New 24-Inch iMac Coming in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-new-24-inch-imac-coming-in-2024.2407880/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Veterans Day Apple Watch Activity Challenge Taking Place November 11</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/veterans-day-activity-challenge-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/veterans-day-apple-watch-activity-challenge-taking-place-november-11.2407878/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 11:34:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/veterans-day-activity-challenge-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple plans to launch its next Apple Watch Activity Challenge on Saturday, November 11, to honor the upcoming Veterans Day holiday in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-868640" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/veterans-day-2022-activity-badge.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Apple Watch owners can earn the Veterans Day award by doing any workout for 11 minutes or more on November 11.<blockquote>Earn this special award on November 11 by doing any workout for 11 minutes or more. Record your time with the Workout app or any app that adds workouts to Health.</blockquote>Like all Activity Challenges, the Veterans Day challenge will be accompanied by an award that can be viewed in the Fitness app and a series of animated stickers that can be used in the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/veterans_day_2023_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917280" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/veterans_day_2023_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917281" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/veterans_day_2023_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917282" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/VeteransDay_Sticker_animated.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917283" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple offers a Veterans Day Activity Challenge annually, and the challenge is usually joined by other Veterans Day-themed content in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app, Books app, and more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/veterans-day-activity-challenge-2023/">Veterans Day Apple Watch Activity Challenge Taking Place November 11</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/veterans-day-apple-watch-activity-challenge-taking-place-november-11.2407878/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Fixes iPhone Display Image Retention Issue</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-display-image-retention-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-fixes-iphone-display-image-retention-issue.2407869/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:44:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-display-image-retention-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The iOS 17.1 update that Apple is set to release in the near future addresses an issue that "may cause display image persistence," according to Apple's feature notes for the software.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/05/iphone-15-sizes.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912524" /><br/>
Since the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, there have been sporadic <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/severe-burn-in-on-my-iphone-15-pro-max.2406278/">reports of severe screen burn-in</a> impacting the new devices. There <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/iphone/comments/174k2jr/comment/k4b93ic">was speculation</a> that it might be a hardware issue with the OLED display, but based on the iOS 17.1 update, Apple has found and addressed a software problem that mimicked screen burn-in.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iphone-15-display-burn-in.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="4032" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917271" /><em><div class="center-wrap">Image via MacRumors reader Josh</div></em><br/>
While most of the reports of display problems were coming from &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; users, there were also some users with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> Pro and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 12 Pro devices that saw similar issues, which is likely why Apple's release notes do not mention the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; specifically.<br/>
<br/>
Those who have noticed "burn-in" on their iPhones should update to iOS 17.1 to ensure that it solves the problem.<br/>
<br/>
The iOS 17.1 update also addresses a number of other bugs. It fixes an issue that could cause the Significant Location privacy setting to reset when transferring or pairing an Apple Watch for the first time, plus it addresses a bug that could cause custom and purchased ringtones not to appear as options for a text tone.<br/>
<br/>
There is a fix for an issue that could cause the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; keyboard to be less responsive, and Apple says that it has added crash detection optimizations for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models to further refine how the iPhones respond when a vehicle crash event is detected.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-display-image-retention-fix/">iOS 17.1 Fixes iPhone Display Image Retention Issue</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-fixes-iphone-display-image-retention-issue.2407869/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.1 Improves Screen Time Syncing Across Apple Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-improves-screen-time-syncing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-improves-screen-time-syncing-across-apple-devices.2407868/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:34:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-improves-screen-time-syncing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>Screen Time</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 17.1 improves syncing of Screen Time settings across Apple devices, according to the release notes for the upcoming software update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/Screen-Time-iOS-16.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905106" /><br/>
Screen Time provides parents with settings to remotely manage a child's device, allowing them to restrict device usage to certain times, set time limits for apps, and block inappropriate content. However, some parents had complained that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/30/apple-promises-further-updates-to-screen-time/">Screen Time settings sometimes reset or failed to sync across all devices</a> within a Family Sharing group.<br/>
<br/>
"We are aware that some users may be experiencing an issue where Screen Time settings are unexpectedly reset," an Apple spokesperson said, in a statement shared with <em>The Wall Street Journal</em> in July. "We take these reports very seriously and we have been, and will continue, making updates to improve the situation."<br/>
<br/>
Apple already attempted to improve Screen Time settings syncing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-16-5-features/">with iOS 16.5</a>, but the issue persisted for some users on later software versions.<br/>
<br/>
Screen Time launched in 2018 as part of iOS 12, providing parents with a built-in option for the type of controls that previously required third-party apps.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 should be released next week. A final beta version <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-rc/">known as the Release Candidate</a> was made available to developers for testing today.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/screen-time/">Screen Time</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/ios-17-1-improves-screen-time-syncing/">iOS 17.1 Improves Screen Time Syncing Across Apple Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-1-improves-screen-time-syncing-across-apple-devices.2407868/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 Release Candidates to Developers and Public Beta Testers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-release-candidates-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407863/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:09:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate versions of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 to developers and public beta testers for testing purposes, with the betas coming one week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-beta-3-to-developers/">released the third betas</a> of iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912331" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iOS-17.1-Feature-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta. Public beta testers will need to follow the same steps after opting in to the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1 adds the option to favorite songs, albums, playlists, artists, and more, with favorited content added to the Library and used for suggestions. Favoriting can be done from the Lock Screen using the Now Playing widget, plus when starting a playlist, you'll now see Song Suggestions.<br/>
<br/>
AirDrop transfers can be finished over the internet so close proximity does not need to be maintained, and an Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 can now use NameDrop with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> running iOS 17.1. On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, iOS 17.1 ensures you won't activate the Camera or Flashlight in your pocket.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include a flashlight indicator in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a> for non &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, and a Wallet feature that lets U.S. Discover card users and those in the UK connect their banks to see balances and transactions. Apple's release notes for the update are below:<br/>
<blockquote><strong>AirDrop</strong><br/>
- Content continues to transfer over the internet when you step out of AirDrop range<br/>
<br/>
<strong>StandBy</strong><br/>
- New options to control when the display turns off (iPhone 14 Pro, iPhone 14 Pro Max, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max)<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Music</strong><br/>
- Favorites expanded to include songs, albums, and playlists, and you can filter to display your favorites in the library<br/>
- New cover art collection offers designs that change colors to reflect the music in your playlist<br/>
- Song suggestions appear at the bottom of every playlist, making it easy to add music that matches the vibe of your playlist<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following improvements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Option to choose a specific album to use with Photo Shuffle on the Lock Screen<br/>
- Home key support for Matter locks<br/>
- Improved reliability of Screen Time settings syncing across devices<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause the Significant Location privacy setting to reset when transferring an Apple Watch or pairing it for the first time<br/>
- Resolves an issue where the names of incoming callers may not appear when you are on another call<br/>
- Addresses an issue where custom and purchased ringtones may not appear as options for your text tone<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause the keyboard to be less responsive<br/>
- Crash detection optimizations (all iPhone 14 and iPhone 15 models)<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may cause display image persistence<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions or on all Apple devices. For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>On the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the update also adds support for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">new USB-C Apple Pencil</a>. <br/>
<br/>
More information on some of the unmentioned features in iOS 17.1 can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">available in our iOS 17.1 features article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-rc/">Apple Seeds iOS 17.1 and iPadOS 17.1 Release Candidates to Developers and Public Beta Testers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-ios-17-1-and-ipados-17-1-release-candidates-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407863/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.1 Release Candidate to Developers and Public Beta Testers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-release-candidate-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407862/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:09:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.1 update to developers and public beta testers for testing purposes, with the update coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-beta-3/">launch of the third 14.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the Sonoma Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the developer beta. Public beta testers will need to follow the same steps after opting in to the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.1 includes updates for the Music app, introducing an option to favorite songs, albums, artists, and more, plus there's a new Coverage section in System Settings for keeping track of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+. No other major new additions have been found in the beta as of yet, and Apple's release notes don't add much.<blockquote>This update provides enhancements, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac including:<br/>
- Favorites expanded in Music to include songs, albums, and playlists, and you can filter to display your favorites in the library<br/>
- Apple warranty status for Mac, AirPods, and Beats headphones and earbuds are available in System Settings<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the System Services settings within Location Services may reset<br/>
- Fixes an issue that may prevent encrypted external drives from mounting<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.<br/>
For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>macOS Sonoma is likely to see a public launch next week following a week of RC testing. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-fourth-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-1-rc/">Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.1 Release Candidate to Developers and Public Beta Testers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-1-release-candidate-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407862/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds watchOS 10.1 Release Candidate to Developers and Public Beta Testers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-release-candidate-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407864/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:08:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming watchOS 10.1 update to developers and public beta testers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/10/apple-releases-watchos-10-1-beta-3/">release of the third watchOS 10.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>‌.1 update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the ‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌.1 Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required. Public beta testers will need to follow the same steps after opting in to the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, ‌watchOS 10.1‌ can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.1 adds NameDrop support for sharing contact information with another Apple Watch or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, plus it includes Double Tap.<br/>
<br/>
NameDrop can be used by tapping into the Apple Watch Contacts app, selecting your profile, and tapping on the "Share" option. From there, touching the Apple Watch to another Apple Watch running watchOS 10.1 or an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> will initiate a contact transfer.<br/>
<br/>
Double Tap is a gesture exclusive to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and the Apple Watch Ultra, and it allows users to tap their thumb and index fingers together to do things like bring up the Smart Stack, start a call, pause a song, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-rc/">Apple Seeds watchOS 10.1 Release Candidate to Developers and Public Beta Testers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-10-1-release-candidate-to-developers-and-public-beta-testers.2407864/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds tvOS 17.1 Release Candidate to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-release-candidate-to-developers.2407867/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:07:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate of an upcoming tvOS 17.1 to developers and public beta testers, with the software coming a week after the launch of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-beta-3/">third tvOS 17.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can download the tvOS 17.1 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required. Public beta testers will need to follow the same steps after opting in to the beta through Apple's public beta testing website. <br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes. tvOS 17.1 adds a new favoriting option to the Music app on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, along with some other minor Music changes.<br/>
<br/>
Apple shares some information on tvOS releases in its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT207936">tvOS support document</a>, which is updated after each tvOS launch, but Apple does not provide notes during beta testing.<br/>
<br/>
Though we don't often know much about what's new in tvOS betas, we let <em>MacRumors</em> readers know when new updates are available so those who are developers can download new software upon release. Apple has also seeded a new beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.1 software for developers.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-rc/">Apple Seeds tvOS 17.1 Release Candidate to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-1-release-candidate-to-developers.2407867/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Rumor Report Card: New Apple Pencil Announced Instead of New iPads</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-rumor-report-card/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rumor-report-card-new-apple-pencil-announced-instead-of-new-ipads.2407853/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 09:10:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-rumor-report-card/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Over the past four days, there were several conflicting rumors about Apple announcing new iPads, a new Apple Pencil, or a combination of those two things. In the end, the only product announced was a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">lower-cost Apple Pencil with a USB-C port</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/New-iPads-and-Apple-Pencil-Rumor-Report-Card-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917228" /><br/>
Below, we have put together a rumor report card that recaps all of the reports and speculation leading up to Apple's press release today.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Accurate</h2><ul><li><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">would not be any new iPads released this month</a>, a claim that remains accurate.</li><br/>
<li>Last month, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">new iPads were unlikely for the remainder of 2023</a>, a claim that remains accurate.</li><br/>
<li>Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em> said it believed <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">a new Apple Pencil was likely to be announced instead of new iPads</a>, although it was not a third-generation model with interchangeable magnetic tips, as the report suggested it would be.</li><br/>
<li><em>MacRumors</em> contributor Steve Moser found <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/03/ios-17-1-apple-pencil-usb-c/">references to an Apple Pencil with USB-C charging</a> in the second beta of iPadOS 17.1.</li><br/>
<li></li></ul><h2>Inaccurate</h2><ul><li><em>Supercharged</em>'s Sami Fathi reported that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">Apple would announce new iPad Air, iPad mini, and entry-level iPad models today</a>, but there are no new iPads.</li><br/>
<li><em>9to5Mac</em> initially <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20231015085450/https://9to5mac.com/2023/10/15/apple-to-announce-new-ipad-models-this-week-featuring-upgraded-chips/">corroborated the report</a> about new iPads, citing its own sources.</li><br/>
<li>A leaker known as "Majin Bu" on X, formerly known as Twitter, said an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/leaker-claims-low-cost-ipad-launching-tomorrow/">11th-generation entry-level iPad would be announced today</a>.</ul><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-rumor-report-card/">Rumor Report Card: New Apple Pencil Announced Instead of New iPads</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/rumor-report-card-new-apple-pencil-announced-instead-of-new-ipads.2407853/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Deals: Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Drops to &#36;399 in All Colors (&#36;50 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-drops-to-399-in-all-colors-50-off.2407843/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 08:13:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 10th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad is on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;399.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;449.00. Amazon has all four colors at this price, including Blue, Pink, Silver, and Yellow.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/10th-Gen-iPad-Feature-Deals-399-2.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893587" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is an overall second-best price on the 2022 iPad, but an all-time low price has not appeared since late September. Amazon has a delivery estimate ranging from October 19 to October 22 for most models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCL22Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 256GB Wi-Fi model on sale for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;549.00</strong></a> (&#36;50 off), the 64GB cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDWX34%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;549.00</strong></a> (&#36;50 off), and the 256GB cellular model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBH659%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;699.00</strong></a> (&#36;50 off). All of these sales are also second-best prices on the 10th generation iPad, with delivery estimates for late October.<br/>
<br/>
The 10th generation iPad is compatible with Apple's new Apple Pencil, which was just <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">announced</a> today. The new model includes a USB-C port hidden behind a sliding cap and it runs at a cheaper price of &#36;79. The new Apple Pencil won't launch until early November.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-2/">Deals: Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Drops to &#36;399 in All Colors (&#36;50 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/deals-apples-10th-gen-ipad-drops-to-399-in-all-colors-50-off.2407843/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple Pencil Announced With Hidden USB-C Port and More for &#36;79</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-announced-with-hidden-usb-c-port-and-more-for-79.2407830/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 06:06:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/10/apple-introduces-new-apple-pencil-bringing-more-value-and-choice-to-the-lineup/">today unveiled</a> an all-new, more affordable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> model featuring a USB-C port hidden behind a sliding cap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
The new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is a cheaper model that sits below the first- and second-generation Apple Pencils in the lineup with a price tag of just &#36;79. It features a sliding cap at the top that reveals a USB-C port, allowing users to charge and pair via a USB-C cable, with a matte finish and design reminiscent of the second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;. When magnetically attached to the side of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, the new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; enters into a sleep state to preserve battery life. Bob Borchers, Apple's vice president of Worldwide Product Marketing, said:<blockquote>Apple Pencil has revolutionized note taking, sketching, and illustrating, unleashing endless possibilities for productivity and creativity. Combined with the versatility of iPad, the new Apple Pencil unlocks another great option to experience the magic of digital handwriting, annotation, marking up documents, and more.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; features low latency and tilt sensitivity like the other &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; models, but misses out on pressure sensitivity, wireless pairing and charging, double tap to change tools, and free engraving. However, unlike the first-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, it does support &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover on the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models. It is compatible with all &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models that feature a USB-C port. <br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is priced at &#36;79 and launches in early November. The first- and second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; models continue to be available for &#36;99 and &#36;129, respectively.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/new-apple-pencil-with-usb-c-announced/">New Apple Pencil Announced With Hidden USB-C Port and More for &#36;79</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-pencil-announced-with-hidden-usb-c-port-and-more-for-79.2407830/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple CEO Tim Cook Visits China Amid Reports of Lower iPhone 15 Sales</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/cook-visits-china-amid-reports-of-iphone-15-sales/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-visits-china-amid-reports-of-lower-iphone-15-sales.2407825/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 04:55:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/cook-visits-china-amid-reports-of-iphone-15-sales/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>Tim Cook</category>
		<category>Counterpoint</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> has made a surprise visit to China amid reports that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> sales are down in the country compared to last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models (via <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-17/apple-s-cook-cheers-on-tencent-game-gala-in-surprise-china-visit">Bloomberg</a></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Tim-Cook-iPhone-15-launch.jpg" alt="" width="1000" height="520" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-917158" /><br/>
Cook visited an Apple's Taikoo Li store in Chengdu to watch a local gaming tournament for the major Tencent game "Honor of Kings" and talk to shoppers and staff. Cook later posted about the event <a href="https://weibo.com/timcook">on Weibo</a> with a short video, saying that "the energy tonight was off the charts!" Cook then visited a Yucheng elementary school to see how students use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> to support local culture.<br/>
 <br/>
The appearance comes just a day after two <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-10-16/iphone-15-china-sales-disappoint-as-huawei-rises-jefferies-says">Counterpoint Research studies</a> claimed that &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; sales are down 4.5% versus last year's &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; lineup in China, causing Apple's share price to fall. As a result, Cook's visit is being widely associated with concern about &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; sales in China across various mainstream media outlets.<br/>
<br/>
Cook's posts on Weibo during the trip have also aroused a usual amount of ire. For example, Cook shared a photo of Chengdu at night shot on an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max. The post was then "flooded with complaints" about the ostensibly poor quality of the image and unfavorable comparisons to pictures from Chinese devices like Huawei's recently Mate 60 Pro.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/counterpoint/">Counterpoint</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/cook-visits-china-amid-reports-of-iphone-15-sales/">Apple CEO Tim Cook Visits China Amid Reports of Lower iPhone 15 Sales</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ceo-tim-cook-visits-china-amid-reports-of-lower-iphone-15-sales.2407825/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Expect From an Apple Pencil 3 Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-pencil-3-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-an-apple-pencil-3-update.2407788/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 15:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-pencil-3-what-to-expect/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to be introducing a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> as soon as tomorrow, so with a potential announcement on the horizon, we thought we'd round up a list of the features that are said to be coming in the next update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/apple-pencil-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897359" /><br/>
<h2>The Current Rumors</h2><br/>
While we've been hearing about a third-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; for several months now, it was just this weekend that Japanese site <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></em> said that a new model is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">set to launch imminently</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The rumor came in response <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">to another rumor</a> about new iPads. Apparently, Apple has media briefings scheduled for this week with some YouTubers, and those meetings are said to be focused on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. No more specific information has been leaked, so it's unclear whether we're going to get iPads, iPads and an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, or just an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
What seems clear is that some kind of announcement is happening tomorrow via press release.<br/>
<h2>Magnetic Tips</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 3 is said to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">swappable magnetic tips</a> that are for different activities like drawing, sketching, and writing. Apple could go with tips of different thicknesses and shapes.<br/>
<br/>
A thin tip, for example, would be ideal for writing, but those who are sketching and drawing might want the option for something thicker or a tip in a different shape.<br/>
<br/>
Majin Bu, the leaker who shared the rumor, said the tips would be used for different purposes, but there is also a possibility that the tips will be the same, but magnetically detachable to make it easier to swap them out when one wears down.<br/>
<h2>Design Changes</h2><br/>
Way back in 2021, there was a leaked third-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with a shorter length and a glossy, rounded finish, but it is not clear if that is an accurate depiction of the planned third-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; given that it was so long ago.<br/>
<br/>
That model did, however, have a larger tip component that could actually make sense with swappable magnetic tips.<br/>
<h2>Color</h2><br/>
There were rumors that the next &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/06/02/future-apple-pencil-black-color/">available in white and black</a>, but that rumor dates all the way back to 2020, so it's unlikely to be accurate at this point in time.<br/>
<h2>USB-C and Consolidation</h2><br/>
Right now, Apple sells two Apple Pencils, the first-generation model that's compatible with the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, and the second-generation model that works with everything else.<br/>
<br/>
With the transition to USB-C, an update to the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; makes sense. Apple could design a third-generation model that works with all iPads, including future low-cost models to eliminate the need to have two Apple Pencils, or it could design a new version of the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; that charges over USB-C to accommodate the USB-C port that's already been introduced in the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Right now, the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; has a Lightning connector, and charging it with the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; requires an adapter, an unwieldy and inconvenient setup.<br/>
<h2>Will There or Won't There Be an iPad Refresh?</h2><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> and Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, Apple does not have plans to introduce new iPads tomorrow. Gurman <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">said over the weekend</a> that while new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, and entry-level &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models are in the works with faster chips, an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; refresh "won't happen this month." Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/kuo-new-ipads-unlikely-to-launch-this-year/">said back in September</a> that new iPads are "unlikely" to launch in 2023.<br/>
<br/>
Both <em>9to5Mac</em> and <em>Supercharged News</em> have claimed that Apple will announce updated &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, and entry-level &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models this week.<br/>
<br/>
It would be unusual for Apple to debut a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; without introducing new iPads, but Kuo and Gurman often have reliable insight in to Apple's plans, so it doesn't seem out of the question. It is possible that we could see Apple introduce a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; and a new low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, as that is a tablet that is typically refreshed yearly and it is also the sole remaining tablet that uses the original &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Refreshing the low-cost &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; would allow Apple to introduce a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; that works with all &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models, doing away with the split &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; lineup.<br/>
<br/>
If we do get new iPads, there are no major redesigns or flashy features in the works. All of the rumors so far suggest that only minor spec bumps like chip improvements are in the works.<br/>
<br/>
Which source do you think is right? Will we see iPads or an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; tomorrow? Let us know in the comments below.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/apple-pencil-3-what-to-expect/">What to Expect From an Apple Pencil 3 Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-expect-from-an-apple-pencil-3-update.2407788/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Leaker Claims New 11th-Generation Low-Cost iPad Will Launch Tomorrow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/leaker-claims-low-cost-ipad-launching-tomorrow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/leaker-claims-new-11th-generation-low-cost-ipad-will-launch-tomorrow.2407782/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2023 14:27:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/leaker-claims-low-cost-ipad-launching-tomorrow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad (low cost)</category>
		<category>Majin Bu</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will introduce a new low-cost 11th-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> tomorrow, according to <a href="https://twitter.com/MajinBuOfficial/status/1714024008767680536">leaker Majin Bu</a>. Majin Bu claims that the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will have the same design as the 10th-generation model, and that accessories "will be perfectly compatible."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/ipad-green-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-904791" /><br/>
Last week, the same leaker claimed that Apple would debut a third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/02/apple-pencil-3-could-feature-magnetic-tips/">interchangeable magnetic tips</a>, and today's rumor comes following conflicting reports about products that Apple might be introducing tomorrow.<br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said on Sunday that while new iPads are in development, new models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/mark-gurman-on-new-ipads-and-macs/">not expected this month</a>, while reports from <em>9to5Mac</em> and <em>Supercharged News</em> claimed that Apple plans to introduce new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, and &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models as soon as Tuesday. Separately, Japanese site <em><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></em> reported that Apple doesn't have plans to introduce new iPads, but will debut a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/15/apple-pencil-3-magnetic-tips-rumor/">new Apple Pencil 3 instead</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Majin Bu's report of an 11th-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; does not mention the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; or the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, and it also seems to suggest that the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; will be accompanied by compatible accessories, perhaps a new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; as suggested by <em>&zwnj;Mac Otakara&zwnj;</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Majin Bu is known for sharing rumors from Weibo and other sources, but the information that we hear is often hit or miss. At this point, it is unclear whether we're going to get new iPads, an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, or some combination of both, but we'll find out more in the morning.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/majin-bu/">Majin Bu</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad">iPad (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/leaker-claims-low-cost-ipad-launching-tomorrow/">Leaker Claims New 11th-Generation Low-Cost iPad Will Launch Tomorrow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/leaker-claims-new-11th-generation-low-cost-ipad-will-launch-tomorrow.2407782/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
