<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 00:03:45 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Lauds &#36;2 Billion EU Fine, Says Apple Has &#039;Muzzled&#039; Streaming Music Services</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services.2421067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:27:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/eu-fines-apple-2-billion/">was today fined</a> €1.8 billion (&#36;1.95 billion) for anti-competitive conduct against rival streaming music services in the European Union, and following the ruling, Spotify has <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2024-03-04/the-european-commission-confirms-apples-anti-competitive-behavior-is-illegal-and-harms-consumers/">praised the European Commission</a> for its decision.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" /><br/>
For context, the European Commission's investigation into Apple's practices started <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/03/13/spotify-files-complaint-vs-apple-in-europe/">due to a 2019 complaint</a> from Spotify over <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> policies. Spotify has long railed against Apple's 30 percent fee, and has complained that it is unfairly disadvantaged compared to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>.<br/>
<br/>
In a blog post, Spotify says that the European Commission has sent a clear message that "Apple's behavior limiting communications to consumers is unlawful."<br/>
<blockquote>Apple's rules muzzled Spotify and other music streaming services from sharing with our users directly in our app about various benefits--denying us the ability to communicate with them about how to upgrade and the price of subscriptions, promotions, discounts, or numerous other perks. Of course, Apple Music, a competitor to these apps, is not barred from the same behaviour. By requiring Apple to stop its illegal conduct in the EU, the EC is putting consumers first. It is a basic concept of free markets--customers should know what options they have, and customers, not Apple, should decide what to buy, and where, when and how.</blockquote><br/>
It is worth noting that the scope of the investigation in Europe has changed several times. While Spotify complained over Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; fees and the requirement to use in-app purchase, the European Commission was unable to target Apple for those actions. Instead, the investigation ended up pertaining to Apple's anti-steering rules, and the rule that keeps Spotify from informing customers about lower prices on the web within the Spotify app.<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission decided that Apple's restrictions preventing developers from letting iOS users know about alternative and cheaper music subscription services available outside the app is "illegal under EU antitrust rules." The EC claims that Apple caused customers to "pay significantly higher prices for music streaming subscriptions."<br/>
<br/>
Spotify in its blog post further says that Apple has "routinely defied laws and court decisions in other markets," and that it is waiting for the next steps that will "clearly and conclusively address Apple's long-standing unfair practices." Spotify claims that it plans to continue to push against Apple until it is able to secure a "truly fair digital marketplace everywhere."<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been ordered to "remove the anti-steering provisions" and keep from repeating the infringement or adopting similar practices in the future. Apple plans to appeal the decision and has claimed that the EC's view is misguided and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/22/apple-spotify-limitless-access-no-fees/">has been heavily influenced</a> by Spotify's complaints.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify will soon be able to release an app outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; with support for alternative app marketplaces coming to the EU in iOS 17.4, but the streaming music company has complained that Apple's plans <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/01/spotify-epic-games-apple-dma-complaint/">do not comply</a> with the DMA and that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/26/spotify-on-apple-eu-app-changes/">changes coming in Europe</a> are a "complete and total farce."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services/">Spotify Lauds &#36;2 Billion EU Fine, Says Apple Has &#039;Muzzled&#039; Streaming Music Services</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-lauds-2-billion-eu-fine-says-apple-has-muzzled-streaming-music-services.2421067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Vision Pro Personas and EyeSight Improving With visionOS 1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-personas-and-eyesight-improving-with-visionos-1-1.2421065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:33:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will soon release the first major software update for the Vision Pro, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-release-candidate/">new version of visionOS</a> will bring improvements not only to Personas, but also to the EyeSight feature.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
Personas and EyeSight are Vision Pro additions that many people have poked fun at since the headset's release. Personas are a digital representation of the user that's shown in video calls, while EyeSight uses an external display to show the Vision Pro wearer's eyes if there are other people in the room. Personas and EyeSight are aimed at making the Vision Pro less of an isolating experience, but neither has been particularly well-received.<br/>
<br/>
As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/testing-personas-visionos-1-1/">we've previously shared</a>, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 beta makes Personas look more realistic, and Apple's release notes provided with the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 release candidate offer more insight. Specific improvements have been made to hair and makeup appearance and neck and mouth representation, and these tweaks make a big difference.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Vision Pro Persona FIXED in visionOS 1.1?" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xEixxDkYXlo" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The update also apparently improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight, which isn't something that was previously noticed during the beta testing period. EyeSight draws on the Persona feature to capture a person's eyes to show on the external display. Presumably the EyeSight feature now looks somewhat better on the Vision Pro headset, but that it's gone so under the radar suggests Apple still has more work to do.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features in the update include improvements for the virtual keyboard and the Mac virtual display.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 will be officially released as soon as this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-eyesight-personas-improvement/">Vision Pro Personas and EyeSight Improving With visionOS 1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/vision-pro-personas-and-eyesight-improving-with-visionos-1-1.2421065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Siri Will Learn Your Music Preferences With HomePod Software 17.4</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-will-learn-your-music-preferences-with-homepod-software-17-4.2421061/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:32:09 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside iOS 17.4, iPadOS 17.4, and tvOS 17.4, Apple plans to release a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> 17.4 software update that adds a small but meaningful change to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/homepod-blue-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895477" /><br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to learn what a user's preferred media service is, which means that there won't be a need to include an app name when asking &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; to play content or go through the process to set a default third-party app.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; users have been able to play songs, podcasts, audiobooks, and other media using supported third-party apps through a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; request for quite some time now, but this needed to be set up in the Settings section of the Home app. The option was fairly hidden, so some &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; users might have forgotten the feature was even available. From Apple's release notes:<blockquote>This update enables Siri to learn your preferred media service, so you no longer need to include the name of the media app in your request.</blockquote>With &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4, &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will learn preferences and use those preferences to select apps. If you have YouTube Music, for example, you won't need to say "Play [song name] on YouTube Music" to bypass <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, nor will you need to set YouTube Music as your default music service in the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; already works this way on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and asks users for their preferred app when playing content for the first time. As &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; has been updated to set a preference automatically, Apple has removed the Home app option that let users select a default media service.<br/>
<br/>
Third-party apps that work directly with the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; include YouTube Music, Deezer, Pandora, TuneIn, and iHeartRadio. Streaming music services need to support &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; for the feature to work, and not all do. Note that popular music service Spotify can play content through a &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; request on &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, but it uses the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to do so.<br/>
<br/>
Along with &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; support for a preferred music service, the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4 update also includes performance and stability improvements. The &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; 17.4 software will see a release as soon as this week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/homepod-siri-music-preferences-17-4/">Siri Will Learn Your Music Preferences With HomePod Software 17.4</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/siri-will-learn-your-music-preferences-with-homepod-software-17-4.2421061/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has First Discounts on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Air Exclusively for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-first-discounts-on-apples-m3-macbook-air-exclusively-for-members.2421060/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:01:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">announced</a> the newest models of the MacBook Air, which include the M3 chip and come in 13-inch and 15-inch sizes. Just a few hours later, Best Buy now has the <a href="https://howl.me/clLuBIw32S9">first notable discounts</a> on these computers <strong>exclusively for My Best Buy Plus or My Best Buy Total members</strong>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
If you're a Plus/Total member, you can get &#36;50 off both the 13-inch and 15-inch M3 MacBook Air.  My Best Buy Plus and My Best Buy Total begins at &#36;49.99/year, so these new MacBook Air discounts will only make sense for people who already have paid for the service.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: Discounts available only to My Best Buy Plus/Total members.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLur9sCFjw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>13-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLutG0IgBi"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,249.00 </div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With these discounts, the 256GB 13-inch M3 MacBook Air is available from &#36;1,049.00 and the 256GB 15-inch M3 MacBook Air is available from &#36;1,249.00. You'll find every new MacBook Air model on sale with Best Buy's exclusive &#36;50 discounts, including those with increased RAM.<br/>
<br/>
If you're willing to invest in a previous generation model, you can also find the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/">13-inch M1 MacBook Air on sale at Best Buy</a>. We covered this deal earlier today, and it's a good option for anyone willing to sacrifice the internal upgrades of the M3 chip for a much lower price tag of &#36;749.99.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/first-discounts-m3-macbook-air/">Best Buy Has First Discounts on Apple&#039;s M3 MacBook Air Exclusively for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-first-discounts-on-apples-m3-macbook-air-exclusively-for-members.2421060/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Ups Mac Trade-In Prices Following M3 MacBook Air Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ups-mac-trade-in-prices-following-m3-macbook-air-launch.2421047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:24:05 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Trade-In</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today increased the trade-in values for some Macs, with the update coming alongside the launch of new 13-inch and 15-inch M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/mac-studio-thumbnail.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-841118" /><br/>
Mac users who opt to trade in an old machine can get between &#36;120 and &#36;1315, with the values increased from the prior &#36;115 to &#36;1070 range. Most of the trade-in values have seen only minor increases or have stayed the same, but the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-studio/">Mac Studio</a> has driven values up.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is now offering up to &#36;1315 when trading in a &zwnj;Mac Studio&zwnj;, with the prior maximum at &#36;1070.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;1000 (Up from &#36;990)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook Air</strong> - Up to &#36;550 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>MacBook</strong> - Up to &#36;160 (Up from &#36;150)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iMac</strong> - Up to &#36;440 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iMac Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;500 (No change)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac mini</strong> - Up to &#36;400 (Down from &#36;410)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac Studio</strong> - Up to &#36;1315 (Up from &#36;1070)</li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac Pro</strong> - Up to &#36;800 (Down from &#36;900)</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Trade-in values vary based on the condition, year, and configuration of the Mac that's being traded in. Macs can be traded in toward the purchase of a new device or the value can be added toward an Apple Gift Card.<br/>
<br/>
Values for trading in other devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and Apple Watch have not changed.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-trade-in/">Apple Trade-In</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-increases-mac-trade-in-prices/">Apple Ups Mac Trade-In Prices Following M3 MacBook Air Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-ups-mac-trade-in-prices-following-m3-macbook-air-launch.2421047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Pro to Get Multi-Display Support With Software Update</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-pro-multi-display-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-pro-to-get-multi-display-support-with-software-update.2421042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:47:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-pro-multi-display-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a software update that will add multi-display support to the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro model, the company confirmed to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/03/04/14-inch-m3-macbook-pro-multi-display-support/">9to5Mac</a></em>. The M3 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models that were introduced today include support for up to two 5K external displays when used in clamshell mode, a feature that is not currently available on the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the same M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919851" /><br/>
With the two machines using the same M3 chip, it was not clear why the &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; has the feature while the MacBook Pro does not, but it is an issue that Apple plans to rectify. In the near future, a software update will add the option for the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro to drive two external displays when the lid of the machine is closed.<br/>
<br/>
Both the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; and the M3 MacBook Pro offer support for one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz when the display is open, and with the update, the M3 MacBooks will also be able to power two 5K external displays with a resolution of up to 60Hz. That is equivalent to the Studio Display, so users can expect to be able to run two of Apple's 5K displays in clamshell mode.<br/>
<br/>
The higher-end M3 Pro and M3 Max MacBook Pro models are already able to drive multiple displays, so this change only applies to the 14-inch MacBook Pro that has the M3 chip. This machine replaced the prior-generation 13-inch MacBook Pro, which Apple has now done away with.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-pro-multi-display-support/">M3 MacBook Pro to Get Multi-Display Support With Software Update</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-pro-to-get-multi-display-support-with-software-update.2421042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Pay Canadian Customers Up to &#36;150 Following iPhone Battery Controversy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-iphone-battery-settlement-approved-in-canada/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-pay-canadian-customers-up-to-150-following-iphone-battery-controversy.2421040/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:38:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-iphone-battery-settlement-approved-in-canada/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone Slowdown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A court in British Columbia, Canada today approved Apple's settlement related to the iPhone battery throttling controversy in 2018, according to <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/business/apple-settlement-british-columbia-supreme-court-1.7098096"><em>CBC News</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-6s-MacRumors-YouTube.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929156" /><br/>
Apple agreed to pay up to &#36;14.4 million (CAD) to settle a class action lawsuit in Canada that alleged the company secretly throttled the performance of some iPhone models. Each affected customer who submits a claim will receive a payment of between &#36;17.50 and &#36;150 (CAD) from Apple, with the exact payout amount to be dependent on the total number of claims submitted. More information on how to submit a claim will be shared on the <a href="https://www.smartphoneperformancesettlement.ca/">settlement website</a>, but a specific timeframe has yet to be provided.<br/>
<br/>
The class includes any current or former resident of Canada (excluding Quebec) who owned and/or purchased an iPhone 6, iPhone 6 Plus, iPhone 6s, iPhone 6s Plus, and/or iPhone SE with iOS 10.2.1 or later installed or downloaded, and/or an iPhone 7 or iPhone 7 Plus with iOS 11.2 or later installed or downloaded, before December 21, 2017. A serial number will be required for each affected iPhone, according to <em>CBC News</em>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has denied the allegations described in the lawsuit, and the settlement does not represent an admission of fault. The settlement allows for Apple to avoid the additional time and costs involved with continued litigation.<br/>
<br/>
Apple was sued in multiple Canadian provinces over iPhone battery throttling in 2018, including Alberta, British Columbia, Ontario, and Saskatchewan. The cases were filed shortly after Apple revealed that it had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/12/18/geekbench-iphone-6s-slowdowns/">started throttling the maximum performance of some iPhone models with "chemically aged" batteries</a>, when necessary, to prevent the devices from unexpectedly shutting down. Apple introduced this new power management system in iOS 10.2.1, but it initially failed to mention the change in that update's release notes, leading to public outcry. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/12/28/apple-iphone-battery-performance-price-drop/">Apple eventually apologized</a> about its lack of transparency, and temporarily lowered the price of iPhone battery replacements to &#36;29 (USD) until the end of 2018.<br/>
<br/>
Apple agreed to pay up to &#36;500 million (USD) to settle a similar class action lawsuit in the U.S., and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/06/apple-starts-iphone-batterygate-payouts/">payments started going out in January</a> there.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-slowdown/">iPhone Slowdown</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-iphone-battery-settlement-approved-in-canada/">Apple to Pay Canadian Customers Up to &#36;150 Following iPhone Battery Controversy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-pay-canadian-customers-up-to-150-following-iphone-battery-controversy.2421040/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.4 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-release-candidate.2421033/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:06:39 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-5/">release of the fifth beta</a>. The release candidate marks the final version of the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 update that will be provided to the public. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 introduces new emoji characters, podcast episode text, and an option to only show icons for websites in the Safari Favorites Bar. The update also supports the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> models that were introduced today.<blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.4 introduces new emoji as well as other features, bug fixes, and security updates for your Mac.</p><br/>
<br/>
<strong>Emoji</strong><br/>
- New mushroom, phoenix, lime, broken chain, and shaking heads emoji are now available in emoji keyboard<br/>
- 18 people and body emoji support facing the opposite direction<br/>
<br/>
<strong>This update also includes the following improvements and bug fixes:</strong><br/>
- Podcasts Episode text can be read in full, searched for a word or phrase, clicked to play from a specific point and used with accessibility features such as Text Size, Increase Contrast, and VoiceOver<br/>
- Business Updates in Messages for Business let you get updates that you've opted into, like order status, flight notifications, fraud alerts or other transactions from trusted businesses<br/>
- Safari Favorites Bar adds an option to show only icons for websites<br/>
<br/>
Some features may not be available for all regions, or on all Apple devices.<br/>
<br/>
For detailed information about the security content of this update, please visit: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>macOS Sonoma 14.4 could see a public release as soon as this week.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds macOS Sonoma 14.4 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-release-candidate.2421033/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds visionOS 1.1 Release Candidate</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-release-candidate/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-visionos-1-1-release-candidate.2421032/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:05:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-release-candidate/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 update for developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The new update comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-releases-visionos-1-1-beta-4/">release of the fourth beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 brings support for iMessage Contact Key Verification and it adds Apple device management to the Vision Pro. With this functionality, IT departments at companies and educational institutions can manage Vision Pro headsets in the same way they manage iPhones, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's beta notes, users can now reposition volumetric scenes closer than before, enabling easier direct interaction with the volumetric scene content. That means objects can be placed closer to you. Apple also made several improvements to Personas, the virtual keyboard, and the Mac virtual display, with full release notes available below.<blockquote><strong>Mobile Device Management</strong><br/>
- Enables account-driven device and user enrollment using Managed Apple IDs<br/>
- Support for device configuration (Wi-Fi, VPN, email accounts, single sign-on, and more)<br/>
- Support for deploying apps in volume including iPhone and iPad compatible apps, visionOS apps included in a Universal purchase, and proprietary in-house visionOS apps<br/>
- Support for remote erase via MDM and device inventory data<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Messages</strong><br/>
- Adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Accessibility</strong><br/>
- Closed captions can be anchored to the playback control while viewing Apple Immersive Video<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Persona (beta) and EyeSight</strong><br/>
- Adds an option to enroll your Persona hands-free<br/>
- Improves hair and makeup appearance<br/>
- Improves neck and mouth representation<br/>
- Improves rendering of the eyes for EyeSight<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Virtual keyboard</strong><br/>
- Cursor positioning for text input is now more accurate<br/>
- Resolves some instances where the virtual keyboard placement obscures the text input field<br/>
- Fixes an issue where in some cases, the text preview on the virtual keyboard may appear out of sync with the text field in the app<br/>
- Fixes an issue where the edit menu may appear unexpectedly<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Mac Virtual Display</strong><br/>
- Improves the reliability of discovering and connecting to a Mac using Mac Virtual Display<br/>
- Resolves an issue where Universal Control may stop working<br/>
- Addresses a connectivity issue that occurs when a previously paired Bluetooth device cannot be found<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Captive Network Support</strong><br/>
- Ability to set up your device while using a captive WiFi network such as those found at hotels, cafes and airports<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website:<br/>
https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>With the RC now available, the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 beta will likely be released to the public in less than a week. <br/>
<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/visionos-1-1-release-candidate/">Apple Seeds visionOS 1.1 Release Candidate</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-visionos-1-1-release-candidate.2421032/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds watchOS 10.4 Release Candidate to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-release-candidate-to-developers.2421034/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming watchOS 10.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-4-to-developers/">release of the fourth watchOS 10.4 beta</a>. The RC is the finalized version of watchOS 10.4 that will see a public launch next week. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.4‌ update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.4 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 includes new emoji characters such as a lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake). There is also a Setting to disable the Double Tap feature on Apple Watch when using Vision Pro, as the Double Tap gestures might be accidentally activated when controlling Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's release notes for the update are below:<blockquote>watchOS 10.4 includes new features, improvements, and bug fixes, including:<br/>
- Tap to Show Full Notification setting now allows you to double tap to expand the notification<br/>
- Using Apple Pay with Confirm with AssistiveTouch will require a passcode for additional security and will not support double clicking the side button<br/>
- Resolves an issue that causes some users to experience false touches on the display<br/>
- Fixes an issue that prevents contacts from syncing to Apple Watch for some users<br/>
<br/>
For information on the security content of Apple software updates, please visit this website: https://support.apple.com/kb/HT201222</blockquote>watchOS 10.4 will likely see a public release in the near future alongside iOS 17.4. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-rc/">Apple Seeds watchOS 10.4 Release Candidate to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-release-candidate-to-developers.2421034/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds tvOS 17.4 Release Candidate to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-rc/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-release-candidate-to-developers.2421035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 10:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-rc/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the release candidate version of an upcoming tvOS 17.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-5/">release of the fifth tvOS 17.4 beta</a>. The RC is the final version of tvOS 17.4 that will be provided to the public as long as no bugs are found in the software. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.4 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes.<br/>
<br/>
Early tvOS 17.4 betas added support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> SharePlay on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;, but the feature was removed in later betas and it is not clear if it is coming. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-rc/">Apple Seeds tvOS 17.4 Release Candidate to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-release-candidate-to-developers.2421035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Instagram Gains Direct Message Editing, Pinned Chats and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/instagram-dm-editing-pinned-chats/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-gains-direct-message-editing-pinned-chats-and-more.2421029/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:32:24 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/instagram-dm-editing-pinned-chats/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Instagram <a href="https://about.instagram.com/blog/announcements/new-dm-improvements">today announced several updates</a> for its direct messaging feature, including message editing and pinned chats. Direct messages sent on Instagram can now be edited for up to 15 minutes after sending.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/instagram-dm-editing-option.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939508" /><br/>
To edit a message, long press on it and then choose the "Edit" option. Users will see that the content has been edited, and the feature brings Instagram in line with Facebook and with Apple's own iMessage editing feature.<br/>
<br/>
Up to three chats will soon be able to pinned to the top of the message inbox, with support for both group messages and one on one conversations. Swipe left or tap and hold on a chat and choose the "pin" option to pin it to the top of the messaging interface.<br/>
<br/>
Instagram added a new toggle for disabling read receipts, which can be done for all chats or just for certain chats. The account-wide setting can be turned on in the settings section by going to Messages and then story replies.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these updates, Instagram introduced several new themes that can be activated on a per-chat basis, plus there is now an option to save favorite stickers in DMs for quicker access. Pressing and holding on a sticker allows it to be saved.<br/>
<br/>
These new features are rolling out to Instagram users starting today, and it can take some time for the options to be available for everyone.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/instagram-dm-editing-pinned-chats/">Instagram Gains Direct Message Editing, Pinned Chats and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/instagram-gains-direct-message-editing-pinned-chats-and-more.2421029/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air-buyers-guide-all-differences-compared.2421026/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 09:18:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air&#038;post_date=1709583493/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">today</a> brought the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> up to date with its latest-generation Apple silicon. The company has reworked the lineup and its pricing, phasing out the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> machine from 2020 and discontinuing the 15-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; introduced in June 2023, so which model should you buy?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/M2-MBA-vs-M3-MacBook-Air-Buyers-Guide-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939499" /><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-macbook-air/">2024 MacBook Air</a> is available in 13.6- and 15.3-inch display sizes just like its predecessor, with the smaller model starting at &#36;1,099 and the larger model starting at &#36;1,299. The 13.6-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; with the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip from 2022 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m2-macbook-air-under-1000/">remains in the lineup</a>, now at a price of &#36;999. This means that buyers have the choice between the 2022 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, its 2024 successor, and a big-screen variant of the 2024 model. It is also worth remembering that it is possible to shave at least &#36;100 off the price of a new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; directly from Apple with education pricing.<br/>
<br/>
Read on to find out about all of the differences between the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; and M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; models to help you decide which model is best for you, as well as if it may be worth upgrading. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="m2_vs._m3_chip">M2 vs. M3 Chip</h3><br/>
The main upgrade offered by the &zwnj;2024 MacBook Air&zwnj; models is the M3 chip. In benchmark tests, the M3 outperforms the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ by about 17% in single-core tasks and approximately 21% in multi-core tasks. In GPU performance measured by Metal benchmarks, the M3 exhibits a notable improvement of around 15% over the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; Chip</th><br/>
 <th>M3 Chip</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Based on A15 Bionic chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> (2021)</td><br/>
 <td>Based on A17 Pro chip from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> (2023)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Enhanced 5nm node (N5P)</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> node (N3B)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>20 billion transistors</td><br/>
 <td>25 billion transistors</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>3.49 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 <td>4.05 GHz CPU clock speed</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>15% faster Neural Engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for AV1 decode</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>New GPU architecture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dynamic Caching</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated ray tracing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hardware-accelerated mesh shading</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The M3 chip introduces an all-new GPU architecture. This architecture includes Dynamic Caching, a breakthrough feature that optimizes GPU memory allocation and utilization, adapting in real-time to varying task demands. This enhancement not only boosts graphics performance for intensive applications but also bolsters the chip's overall energy efficiency. This is particularly beneficial for graphics-heavy tasks like advanced video editing, 3D rendering, and gaming. It also features support for AV1 video decode to provide more efficient and higher-quality video from streaming services.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon-buyers-guide/">Apple Silicon Buyer's Guide: Which Chip Should You Choose?</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Despite similarities in the 16-core Neural Engine between the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ and M3, the M3's adoption of a ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ fabrication process leads to more efficient execution of machine learning and AI tasks. Additionally, the M3 maintains up to 24GB of unified memory, just like the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌, but leverages the new process for more efficient memory bandwidth utilization.<br/>
<br/>
One other notable difference between the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ and M3 chips is their energy efficiency. The ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ fabrication process enables the M3 to achieve higher performance without a proportional increase in power consumption, making the chip particularly appealing for laptop users who value a balance between power and battery life.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/how-much-better-really-is-m3/">M2 vs. M3 Buyer's Guide: How Much Better Really Is M3?</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the M3 chip is a considerable upgrade from the ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌, distinguished by its higher transistor count, improved performance in CPU and GPU tasks, and superior energy efficiency. While the M3 offers clear advancements, the extent of its superiority does not necessitate an immediate upgrade for current ‌&zwnj;M2&zwnj;‌ users, especially if their existing workflows are still completed comfortably. For new buyers or those upgrading from older models, the M3's improvements in performance and efficiency will be much more pronounced.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_differences">Other Differences</h3><br/>
There are a number of other notable differences between the two &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; generations beyond their chips. While these upgrades are fairly small, they are worth bearing in mind when contemplating whether to get the latest model.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (2022 and 2023)</th><br/>
 <th>M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; (2024)</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available with 13.6-inch display only, 15.3-inch model discontinued</td><br/>
 <td>Available with both 13.6- and 15.3-inch display size options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for one external display</td><br/>
 <td>Support for up to two external displays when the lid is closed</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Voice Isolation and Wide Spectrum microphone modes</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced voice clarity in audio and video calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 support</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anodization seal to reduce fingerprints with Midnight finish</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;999</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;1,099</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="final_thoughts">Final Thoughts</h3><br/>
Overall, the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is a minor upgrade over its predecessor, largely focusing on enhanced performance rather than new capabilities. Its main target audience is those who have an older &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj;, such as an &zwnj;M1&zwnj; or Intel-based model, or no &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; at all.<br/>
<br/>
Unless you can leverage the specific advantages of the M3 chip and require maximum performance from its highly portable form factor, it is likely not worth buying the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; over the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; for most users. However, if future-proofing is a major priority because you tend to keep your computer for many years, the extra &#36;100 to get the latest model will probably be warranted. The M3 model's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-two-displays-lid-closed/">support for two external displays</a> may also justifiably swing your buying decision if you have multiple monitors.<br/>
<br/>
If you plan to buy a new &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; from Apple and want the larger, 15.3-inch model, then the latest M3 model is your only option as the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; 15.3-inch machine has now been discontinued. That being said, the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; 15.3-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; is still readily available second-hand, refurbished, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#macbook_air">from third-party retailers</a> for prices well below the &#36;1,299 price of the latest model. If you want the larger model, it may be worth seeking out one of these <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/#macbook_air">deals</a> on an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; model before opting for the latest M3 machine directly from Apple. <br/>
<br/>
It is certainly not worth upgrading from the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; to the M3 &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; for the overwhelming majority of customers. Upgrading from an &zwnj;M2&zwnj; 13-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; to an M3 15-inch &zwnj;MacBook Air&zwnj; may be more justifiable owing to the display size increase, but there is little that the latest generation meaningfully offers over its predecessor.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air/">M2 vs. M3 MacBook Air Buyer&#039;s Guide: All Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m2-vs-m3-macbook-air-buyers-guide-all-differences-compared.2421026/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Apple&#039;s Magic Keyboard for Just &#36;179.99 and Pair it With the iPad Air at the Record Low Price of &#36;449.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/magic-keyboard-for-179-99/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apples-magic-keyboard-for-just-179-99-and-pair-it-with-the-ipad-air-at-the-record-low-price-of-449-99.2421019/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 08:08:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/magic-keyboard-for-179-99/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has Apple's Magic Keyboard for the 11-inch iPad Pro and fourth/fifth generation iPad Air at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0863BQJMS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;179.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.00. This is the first time we've tracked a deal on the keyboard in 2024, and it's a solid second-best price on the accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/04/Magic-Keyboard-Side-Anlge-Red.jpg" alt="" width="1328" height="747" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-738387" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Specifically, the Magic Keyboard is compatible with the 11-inch iPad Pro (first, second, third, and fourth generations) and the iPad Air (fourth and fifth generations). Amazon only has the black color option at this &#36;179.99 price tag, and it's currently the only retailer offering such a low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0863BQJMS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>Apple Magic Keyboard for &#36;179.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for an iPad to pair with the Magic Keyboard, Best Buy has every model of the 5th generation iPad Air on sale at an all-time low price right now. Prices start at <a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> for the 64GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;599.00. These are &#36;150 off across the board, and also include best-ever prices on both cellular models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxkYXiXGKb"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk0ZOm0OM"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2jeyYSK"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;599.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clxk2RAFUDo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/magic-keyboard-for-179-99/">Get Apple&#039;s Magic Keyboard for Just &#36;179.99 and Pair it With the iPad Air at the Record Low Price of &#36;449.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-apples-magic-keyboard-for-just-179-99-and-pair-it-with-the-ipad-air-at-the-record-low-price-of-449-99.2421019/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Belkin Releases MagSafe Mount for Using iPhone Camera With Apple TV</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/belkin-iphone-magsafe-mount-for-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-releases-magsafe-mount-for-using-iphone-camera-with-apple-tv.2421016/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:22:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/belkin-iphone-magsafe-mount-for-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Belkin</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began selling Belkin's new <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HR1V2ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-apple-tv-4k">iPhone Mount with MagSafe for Apple TV 4K</a> on its online store in the U.S. and other countries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Belkin-Apple-TV-MagSafe-Mount.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939490" /><br/>
This accessory allows you to mount your iPhone to the top of your TV, or it can be placed on the stand below. Then, you can conveniently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-iphone-facetime-camera-apple-tv/">use your iPhone's rear camera for FaceTime video calls</a> on any Apple TV 4K model running tvOS 17 or later.<br/>
<br/>
Key features of the mount, as listed on Apple's online store:<blockquote>Mount directly to your TV or display up to 4 inches (10.1 cm) in depth<br/>
<br/>
Works as standalone mount on desktop or a TV stand<br/>
<br/>
Tilt from –20 to +30 degrees to adjust to your environment<br/>
<br/>
Easily flip iPhone orientation to stream or record in portrait or landscape<br/>
<br/>
Keyhole mounts and mounting bracket included for added stability<br/>
<br/>
Designed for Continuity Camera–supported apps</blockquote>Belkin already offered a very similar version of this mount for use <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ652ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-desktops-and-displays">with the iMac and Apple's external displays</a>, but it is currently listed as unavailable on Apple's online store. Apple continues to sell a version of the mount <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/HQ642ZM/A/belkin-iphone-mount-with-magsafe-for-mac-notebooks">for MacBooks</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Priced at &#36;49.95 in the U.S., the TV version of the mount ships in one business day.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/belkin/">Belkin</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/belkin-iphone-magsafe-mount-for-apple-tv/">Belkin Releases MagSafe Mount for Using iPhone Camera With Apple TV</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/belkin-releases-magsafe-mount-for-using-iphone-camera-with-apple-tv.2421016/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Has Apple&#039;s Just-Discontinued 13-Inch M1 MacBook Air for Only &#36;749.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-apples-just-discontinued-13-inch-m1-macbook-air-for-only-749-99.2421014/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 07:05:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this morning <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">announced</a> new models of the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air, now with the M3 chip. With Apple moving onto the next generation of MacBook Air models, we're looking back at the original 13-inch M1 MacBook Air, which is at a great all-time low price on Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/M1-MacBook-Air-Deals-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2125" height="1195" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850533" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 256GB 13-inch M1 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/clLm50orOos"><strong>&#36;749.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.99. Best Buy has this notebook in all three colors, and offers free two-day shipping to all customers. Although nearly four years old, this version of the MacBook Air still has an Apple silicon chip and should be perfect for anyone who wants to prioritize saving money over having the latest and greatest product.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clLm50orOos"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>13-inch M1 MacBook Air for &#36;749.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
With the launch of the new MacBook Air models, this M1 device from late 2020 has now been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-discontinues-m1-macbook-air/">discontinued</a> from Apple's official lineup. Additionally, Apple has discontinued the 15-inch M2 MacBook Air, so we'll likely be tracking last-chance deals on those notebooks soon. Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/best-buy-13-inch-m1-macbook-air/">Best Buy Has Apple&#039;s Just-Discontinued 13-Inch M1 MacBook Air for Only &#36;749.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-has-apples-just-discontinued-13-inch-m1-macbook-air-for-only-749-99.2421014/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All-New Apple Watch Hermès &#039;Tricot&#039; Knitted Band Released</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-watch-hermes-tricot-released/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-new-apple-watch-hermès-tricot-knitted-band-released.2421011/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:33:36 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-watch-hermes-tricot-released/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Hermès</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple and Hermès today released an all-new knitted "Tricot" Apple Watch band, available in four color options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Hermès-Tricot-Single-Tour-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939425" /><br/>
Apple describes the Tricot Single Tour as "a knitted textile band that comfortably hugs the wrist like a glove." It is available as a single tour band only.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>Patterned on 1930s-era Hermès gloves created for driving, sailing, and golf, the Tricot band takes what was old and makes it new again. The continuous textile knit comfortably hugs the wrist, imparting both a freedom of movement and a sense of élan.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Hermès already sells a number of "Tricot" luxury accessories such as neckties. Unlike its main selection Tricot accessories, which tend to be made of 100% silk, the Apple Watch Hermès Tricot Single Tour is made of polyamide yarn. Polyamide is waterproof and enables the band to be used when swimming, just like all of the other non-leather Apple Watch Hermès bands.<br/>
<br/>
The Tricot Single Tour band is available in Bleu Jean, Jaune de Naples, Orange, and Beige de Weimar. It is only compatible with 38mm, 40mm, and 41mm Apple Watch models. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/hermes-tricot.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939444" /><br/>
<br/>
The Tricot Single Tour replaces the both the single and double tour Apple Watch Hermès Bridon bands on the company's main Apple Watch band webpage. The Apple Watch Hermès Bridon bands are knitted just like the Tricot, suggesting that the new band could replace it when stock runs out.<br/>
<br/>
The Bridon band is <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTHQ3AM/A/apple-watch-hermès-45mm-noir-bridon-single-tour?">still available</a>, but it may only be while stocks last as a result. Apple tends to allow discontinued Apple Watch Hermès bands to sell out over a longer period of time rather than outright de-listing them. The Navy/Gris/Ciel Bridon band also continues to be available directly from Hermès, but now on a separate webpage, just like many of the leather Apple Watch Hermès bands that Apple stopped selling in September last year.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/">refresh of iPhone and Apple Watch band color options</a> earlier today, Apple and Hermès added Bleu Céleste/Écru and Framboise/Écru Color options to the Hermès Toile H Single Tour band, Bleu Céleste/Bleu Jean and Jaune d'Or/Bleu Jean color options to the Hermès Twill Jump Single Tour and, and Blanc and Bleu Céleste color options to the Hermès Kilim Single Tour band.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Watch Hermès Tricot Single Tour band is <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MWP93AM/A/apple-watch-hermès-41mm-orange-tricot-single-tour?fnode=2f8bb64ea4e2bafcdc01e949ab01260e2f27c6d3f637fe18cb1f10a46f8c1b133a041375d7e3ed4eef9ead783a04a78fa7cfd974ffb9147f87779a78f3a3bc24c30e2a1f4f3c5d29b2f5ee07827b36fb">now available to order</a> for &#36;349.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-hermes/">Apple Watch Hermès</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-watch-hermes-tricot-released/">All-New Apple Watch Hermès &#039;Tricot&#039; Knitted Band Released</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-new-apple-watch-hermès-tricot-knitted-band-released.2421011/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>M3 MacBook Air Supports More External Displays Than M3 MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-more-external-displays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-supports-more-external-displays-than-m3-macbook-pro.2421010/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:32:19 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-more-external-displays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[If you frequently work with external displays, it's worth noting that Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">just-announced</a> M3 MacBook Air models support two external displays – one more than the 14-inch MacBook Pro with the same M3 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/Apple-MacBook-Air-2-up-hero-240304-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939443" /><br/>
Launched last October, the 14-inch MacBook Pro with M3 chip simultaneously supports one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz. <br/>
<br/>
In contrast, both the 13-inch and 15-inch MacBook Air with M3 chip support one external display with up to 6K resolution at 60Hz, and two external displays with up to 5K resolution at 60Hz when the laptop lid is closed, also known as clamshell mode.<br/>
<br/>
Given that the machines use identical chips, it could be that the additional external display support on the MacBook Airs has been made at the software level. If so, there would seem to be no reason that it could not be added to the M3 MacBook Pro in a future software update. However, it could also be a hardware-based change, and we might not know for sure until a teardown is performed on the new laptops.<br/>
<br/>
The new M3-powered MacBook Air models start from &#36;1,099 and can be pre-ordered on Apple's website, with availability beginning on Friday, March 8. The 14-inch MacBook Pro with M3 chip starts at &#36;1,599.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m3-macbook-air-more-external-displays/">M3 MacBook Air Supports More External Displays Than M3 MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/m3-macbook-air-supports-more-external-displays-than-m3-macbook-pro.2421010/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Refreshes Silicone Case and Watch Band Colors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-refreshes-silicone-case-and-watch-band-colors.2421006/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 06:01:22 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		<category>iPhone Accessories</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Accessories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">announcement of the new MacBook Air</a>, Apple today refreshed the color options available with many of its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> cases and Apple Watch bands.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/3-4-24-iPhone-Case-Refresh-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939420" /><br/>
Apple's Silicone Case with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a> for &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/iphone/accessories/cases-protection">now available</a> with new Soft Mint, Sunshine, Light Blue, and Pink color options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/3-4-24-Sport-Band-Refresh-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-939421" /><br/>
<br/>
Many of the <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/watch/bands">new Apple Watch band colors</a> match up with the refreshed silicone cases, with the exception of Raspberry and Ocean Blue. The new Apple Watch band color options are as follows:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Sport Loop</strong>: Soft Mint and Ocean Blue.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Sport Band</strong>: Soft Mint, Sunshine, and Light Blue.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Braided Solo Loop</strong>: Sunshine, Light Blue, and Raspberry.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Solo Loop</strong>: Pink, Soft Mint, Ocean Blue.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Watch Hermès bands available directly from Apple also today received new color options:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><strong>Hermès Toile H Single Tour</strong>: Bleu Céleste/Écru and Framboise/Écru.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Hermès Twill Jump Single Tour</strong>: Bleu Céleste/Bleu Jean and Jaune d'Or/Bleu Jean.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Hermès Kilim Single Tour</strong>: Blanc and Bleu Céleste.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The refreshed lineup of accessories are <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/watch/bands">available to order</a> immediately.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-accessories/">iPhone Accessories</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-accessories/">Apple Watch Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-refreshes-cases-and-watch-bands/">Apple Refreshes Silicone Case and Watch Band Colors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-refreshes-silicone-case-and-watch-band-colors.2421006/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>13-Inch M2 MacBook Air Now Starts From &#36;999, 15-Inch M2 Model Discontinued</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m2-macbook-air-under-1000/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-m2-macbook-air-now-starts-from-999-15-inch-m2-model-discontinued.2421004/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 05:40:38 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m2-macbook-air-under-1000/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 15&quot;</category>
		<category>MacBook Air 13&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-announces-m3-macbook-air/">announcement</a> of new M3 MacBook Air models, Apple has reduced the starting price of the 13-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip by &#36;100, putting it at under &#36;1,000 for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/m2-macbook-air-image-blue-e1666794320469.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856764" /><br/>
Apple originally launched the 13-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip in June 2022 with a &#36;1,199 starting price, but dropped the price to &#36;1,099 in June 2023 when the 15-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip was launched. The base configuration includes an 8-Core CPU, 8-Core GPU, 8GB of unified memory, and 256GB of internal storage.<br/>
<br/>
Pre-orders of the new MacBook Air models with M3 chip start today, with orders arriving to customers on Friday, March 8. The laptops continue to be available in Midnight, Starlight, Space Gray, and Silver with a starting price of &#36;1,099. Apple today also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/apple-discontinues-m1-macbook-air/">discontinued</a> the MacBook Air with M1 chip and the 15-inch MacBook Air with M2 chip.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#15-MacBook-Air">15" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Air">13" MacBook Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-air.122">MacBook Air</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/04/m2-macbook-air-under-1000/">13-Inch M2 MacBook Air Now Starts From &#36;999, 15-Inch M2 Model Discontinued</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/13-inch-m2-macbook-air-now-starts-from-999-15-inch-m2-model-discontinued.2421004/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
