<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 03:01:19 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Pro Max Will Be First to Feature Three 48MP Camera Lenses</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/11/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-max-will-be-first-to-feature-three-48mp-camera-lenses.2431112/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:20:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/11/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature an upgraded 48-megapixel Tetraprism camera for enhanced photo quality and zoom functionality, according to Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Cameras.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913544" /><br/>
In his <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/水晶光電為iphone四重反射稜鏡升級藍圖的領先受益者-crystal-optech-as-a-leading-beneficiary-in-iphone-tetraprism-upgrade-ca62dd37e364">latest investor note published to Medium</a>, Kuo said the key specification change would be a 1/2.6" 48MP CIS sensor, up from the 1/3.1" 12MP sensor expected to be used in this year's iPhone 16 Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
Both the iPhone 16 Pro and the iPhone 16 Pro Max are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/26/both-iphone-16-pro-models-5x-optical-zoom-rumor/">expected</a> to get Tetraprism telephoto lenses in 2024, instead of the technology being limited to the larger Pro Max, as it is in the iPhone 15 series. (The iPhone 15 Pro has a 12-megapixel telephoto camera that offers 3x zoom, but the iPhone 15 Pro Max uses an upgraded telephoto system that allows for 5x zoom.) That means both iPhone 16 Pro models will feature at least 5x optical zoom and at least 25x digital zoom.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo said he is currently uncertain whether only the iPhone 17 Pro Max will feature the upgraded Tetraprism camera. But if it is exclusive to the model, then both iPhone 18 Pro models will get it in 2026. The upgraded Tetraprism camera requires all-new designed prisms, which must have a shorter form factor to reduce the camera's height, added Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
The analyst's report corroborates a claim made last year by Jeff Pu of Haitong International Securities. Pu in December <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/15/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto-lens-rumor/">said</a> the iPhone 17 Pro Max's upgraded 48MP telephoto lens will be optimized for use with Apple Vision Pro. Current iPhone 15 Pro models can record spatial video with 3D depth for playback on the Vision Pro – when held in landscape orientation, the main and ultra wide lenses combine to record spatial video with added depth. <br/>
<br/>
Pu previously said both iPhone 16 Pro models will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">48MP ultra wide lens</a>, which would make the iPhone 17 Pro Max the first iPhone model to have a rear camera system entirely made up of 48-megapixel lenses. To put that into perspective, current iPhone 15 Pro models have 48MP main, 12MP ultra wide, and 12MP telephoto lenses. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/11/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">iPhone 17 Pro Max Will Be First to Feature Three 48MP Camera Lenses</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-pro-max-will-be-first-to-feature-three-48mp-camera-lenses.2431112/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>10+ Changes to Control Center in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-control-center/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-changes-to-control-center-in-ios-18.2431099/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:43:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-control-center&#038;post_date=1720662213/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple redid the Control Center in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, and it's one of the biggest changes to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> outside of Apple Intelligence. The interface is much more customizable, there are more Control Center options, and controls can be accessed from new places.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Control-Center-Guide-1.jpg" alt="" width="2100" height="1180" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958438" /><br/>
This guide highlights all of the new Control Center changes that Apple added in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; (and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>).<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="reorder_controls">Reorder Controls</h2><br/>
With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, you could choose some of the controls that were available in Control Center, but in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, customization goes much further. For the first time, you can rearrange Control Center quick access buttons into a layout that best suits your needs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-customization.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958441" /><br/>
Apple has designed a Home Screen-style grid for the Control Center, with an 8x4 arrangement of open circular spots where different controls can be placed. You can fill up all the empty circle spots, or choose to leave blank spaces between columns and rows.<br/>
<br/>
None of the Control Center buttons are permanent, and every one that you opt to use can be moved, duplicated, deleted, and rearranged as needed. To move controls, follow these steps.<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Swipe down from the right upper corner of your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; display to open up Control Center.</li><br/>
 <li>Long press on any empty space and hold until the grid shows up, or tap on the "+" button at the upper left of the display.</li><br/>
 <li>Use a finger to grab an icon and move it where you want it to be.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap at the top or the bottom of the display to exit the grid mode.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="resize_and_delete_controls">Resize and Delete Controls</h2><br/>
Control Center controls can be resized, so you can make your most used buttons bigger and easier to press. Single button controls like <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>, Flashlight, Timer, Low Power Mode, Voice Memo, and Remote can be up to four grid circles in size.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-icon-sizing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958442" /><br/>
Options include a single grid circle, a two grid circle that's horizontal, which adds the control's name, and a four grid circle arranged in a square shape. The majority of controls are limited to these sizes.<br/>
<br/>
Some modules like volume and brightness can only be two horizontal circles in size, with Apple not offering an option to modify the shape or size. The aggregated connectivity controls can take up four spots of the grid in a square shape, or the entire thing with no options in between.<br/>
<br/>
Controls like those for multiple smart home accessories and scenes have more sizing options and can be four grid spaces long or four spaces in a grid, eight spaces, sixteen spaces, or 24 spaces at maximum. The Now Playing control has a similar set of options, but can take up the entire grid.<br/>
<br/>
To resize controls, follow these steps:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Long press in an open space in the Control Center or tap the "+" button.</li><br/>
 <li>Grab the bottom right corner of an icon, which has a curved, highlighted marker to indicate that it can be manipulated.</li><br/>
 <li>Drag and pull outward to make a control bigger, or push up and over to make it smaller. There will be minimum and maximum sizes that vary for different controls.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap at the top or bottom of the display to exit the editing menu, or just wait and it will close automatically after a few seconds with no interaction.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
To delete any Control Center control, follow the steps above to enter edit mode and tap on the "-" button.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="controls_gallery">Controls Gallery</h2><br/>
Control Center controls are now organized into a gallery that can be accessed from the Control Center interface. To get to the Control Center gallery, long press on the display or use the "+" button to enter editing mode, and then tap on "Add a Control."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-gallery.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958443" /><br/>
The main part of the gallery has a selection of suggested controls, and if you scroll down, you'll see options organized into the following categories: Accessibility, Capture, Clock, Connectivity, Display and Brightness, Focus, Hearing Accessibility, Home, Motor Accessibility, Notes, Now Playing, Remote, Shortcuts, Sounds, Translate, Utilities, Vision Accessibility, Voice Memos, Wallet, and Watch.<br/>
<br/>
There is a search interface right at the top of the gallery so if you're looking for something specific, you can just search for it rather than having to swipe down to try to locate it manually.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="multiple_screens">Multiple Screens</h2><br/>
Control Center has always been just a single screen, but that's changing in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. You can set up multiple screens for your controls, which means you can have dedicated pages for things like connectivity controls, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/homekit/">HomeKit</a> devices, and Accessibility options.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-pages.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958444" /><br/>
There are multiple pages by default when installing &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, and you can customize them to your liking and add and delete pages. Control Center supports up to 15 separate screens.<br/>
<br/>
Navigating through pages is done by swiping up and down through Control Center, tapping the small icons on the right side of the display, or holding a finger over the icons and scrubbing through them. As you add controls to different pages, Control Center automatically assigns an icon based on what's on the page. You can't customize the icons at this time.<br/>
<br/>
Here's how to add pages:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Swipe down from the right hand side of the display to get into Control Center.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the circle icon at the bottom of the icon list, which denotes a blank page.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Add a Control to select the controls that you want to include on the page.</li><br/>
 <li>When finished, tap anywhere at the top or bottom of the display to exit editing mode.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
If you add more controls than there are space for, or resize something to be larger than will fit, Control Center will automatically add another page and move the control to that page.<br/>
<br/>
There are some limitations to what can be on a single page. Control Center won't allow you to add a single-sized icon to a page and then create another page - the create new page option won't show up while an existing page still has enough space to accommodate icons. It does offer the option when a page is about half full, which provides enough wiggle room to have spacing between icons.<br/>
<br/>
To remove a page, you just need to delete all of the controls on it following the steps up above.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="power_button">Power Button</h2><br/>
At the top right of the Control Center, Apple added a Power Button to make it easier to turn your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; off. To prevent accidental activation, using the Power Button requires a press and hold.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-power-button-control-center.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958450" /><br/>
Pressing and holding brings up the shut down interface where you need to swipe to turn your device off, and it locks your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> will be needed to unlock it again (similar to multiple presses on the side button).<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="third-party_apps">Third-Party Apps</h2><br/>
In &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, Control Center is no longer limited to built-in apps and features. Third-party app developers can create controls for their apps, and those can be added to Control Center through the Control Center gallery.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="lock_screen">Lock Screen</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; brings Control Center to the Lock Screen, allowing you to swap out the default Flashlight and Camera icons for new quick access buttons. There's also an option to remove Lock Screen controls entirely.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-lock-screen-controls.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958445" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>At the Lock Screen, unlock and long press to get into the Lock Screen editing interface.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Customize to customize an existing Lock Screen or tap on the "+" button to create a new Lock Screen.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Lock Screen.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on the "-" buttons on the Flashlight and Camera icons to remove them. Stop here if you don't want to add new controls.</li><br/>
 <li>To swap in something else, tap on the "+" button to open up the Control Center gallery.</li><br/>
 <li>Choose a control from the list or use the search interface.</li><br/>
 <li>When you're finished, tap on Done and then tap on the Lock Screen to exit out of editing mode.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
Many of the Control Center options can be put on the Lock Screen, including those from third-party apps. You can activate everything from &zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj; to Airplane Mode, or open up apps like Notes or Home. There is an option to set any Shortcut to the Lock Screen, or add a control to open any app you have on your device.<br/>
<br/>
With this option in particular, you have a lot of customization options. You can, for example, set a third-party camera app to open instead of the main Camera app, giving you quick access to a non-default camera.<br/>
<br/>
There are some Control Center controls that are not available, such as volume and brightness adjustment, Low Power mode, Bluetooth and Wi-Fi, Focus, and Screen Recording.<br/>
<br/>
For some actions, such as opening an app or activating a Shortcut, &zwnj;Face ID&zwnj; or &zwnj;Touch ID&zwnj; authentication is required for privacy purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="action_button">Action Button</h2><br/>
Control Center controls can also be assigned to the Action Button on devices that support it, which includes the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-action-button-controls.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958446" /><br/>
<ol><br/>
 <li>Open up the Settings app.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Action Button.</li><br/>
 <li>Swipe until you get to the Controls option.</li><br/>
 <li>Tap on Choose a Control.</li><br/>
 <li>Scroll down to select a control or use the search interface to find what you're looking for.</li><br/>
 <li>Swipe up to exit the Settings app.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
After setup, when you press the Action Button, you'll activate the control that you've set.<br/>
<br/>
There are a limited number of options for the Controls Action Button.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Calculator</li><br/>
 <li>Stopwatch</li><br/>
 <li>Alarm</li><br/>
 <li>Home</li><br/>
 <li>Timer</li><br/>
 <li>&zwnj;Dark Mode&zwnj;</li><br/>
 <li>Airplane Mode</li><br/>
 <li>Cellular Data</li><br/>
 <li>Personal Hotspot</li><br/>
 <li>Open Music</li><br/>
 <li>Quick Note</li><br/>
 <li>Remote</li><br/>
 <li>Scan Code</li><br/>
 <li>Wallet</li><br/>
 <li>Tap to Cash</li><br/>
 <li>Ping My Watch</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Some other features that you would normally find in Control Center, such as the Camera, can be added through other Action Button options.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="new_control_center_options">New Control Center Options</h2><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-new-controls.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958449" /><br/>
With these changes, there are Control Center options that were not previously available.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 <li>Open Music</li><br/>
 <li>Activate a Shortcut</li><br/>
 <li>Open any app</li><br/>
 <li>Third-party app controls</li><br/>
 <li>Translate</li><br/>
 <li>Print Center</li><br/>
 <li>Tap to Cash</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
There are also a number of new hearing, motor, and vision accessibility options that can be added. Apple had broader categories for these before, but now there are specifics for things like Voice Control, Assistive Touch, Background Sounds, Live Listen, Headphone Levels, Live Speech, Reduce Motion, Invert, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="settings">Settings</h2><br/>
There were a number of Control Center settings in the Settings app in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, but Apple has eliminated almost all of them because these capabilities are now in the controls gallery. The only option you'll find in the Settings app is Access Within Apps, a toggle for determining whether swiping down on the display brings up Control Center when you're using an app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-control-center-settings.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958447" /><br/>
<h2 id="read_more">Read More</h2><br/>
For more on all of the new features that are coming in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">we have a dedicated iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-control-center/">10+ Changes to Control Center in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/10-changes-to-control-center-in-ios-18.2431099/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Astropad Studio Gains Support for Apple Pencil Pro Controls</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/astropad-studio-apple-pencil-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/astropad-studio-gains-support-for-apple-pencil-pro-controls.2431102/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 15:40:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/astropad-studio-apple-pencil-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Astropad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://astropad.com">Astropad</a> today announced a major update for the Astropad Studio app, introducing new features that work with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro that Apple launched earlier this year. Astropad Studio is designed to turn the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> into a drawing tablet that can be used with PC and Mac creative apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/astropad-studio.jpg" alt="" width="792" height="447" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958453" /><br/>
The 5.4 version of Astropad Studio supports Squeeze Gesture Shortcuts, so you can set custom shortcuts to swap between your preferred tools using the Squeeze feature on the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro.<br/>
It also adds support for barrel rotation, which takes advantage of the gyroscope that Apple added to the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Turning and twirling the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro when using Astropad precisely rotates the brush while drawing, and as of now, Astropad Studio is the only drawing tablet option that supports barrel roll rotation.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these features, there is a new Adaptive Image Rendering video compression algorithm that provides 53 percent clearer image quality during high-motion content like rotating an object in blender or previewing animations. Astropad says that Astropad Studio now has a feature set that puts it on par with the Wacom Cintiq drawing tablets.<br/>
<br/>
A one-year Astropad license is available for &#36;60, while a lifetime license is priced at &#36;120. These are sale prices that can be obtained by entering the promo code SUMMER24 at checkout <a href="https://astropad.com/product/studio/">on the Astropad website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/astropad/">Astropad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/astropad-studio-apple-pencil-pro/">Astropad Studio Gains Support for Apple Pencil Pro Controls</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/astropad-studio-gains-support-for-apple-pencil-pro-controls.2431102/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers.2431081/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 10:10:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of upcoming an upcoming macOS 15 Sequoia update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/24/macos-sequoia-beta-2-iphone-mirroring//">release of the second beta</a>, which added <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring support. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> includes &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Mirroring, which allows you to control your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. You can open and use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, interact with notifications, and drag and drop files between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
There are new options for window tiling, and dragging a window to the edge of the display will suggest a tiled location to make it easier to use multiple apps at once. Apple is adding a Passwords app for managing passwords, Safari can summarize websites and surface key information, and Notes has support for live audio transcription and math equations.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Intelligence features coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will also be available in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, but Apple does not plan to add these until later in the beta testing process. Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools for editing, proofreading, and summarizing text in apps, and an Image Playground allows for AI images to be created from prompts.<br/>
<br/>
Custom emoji or "Genmoji" can be created for any situation and used just like emoji, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting much smarter. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in apps and will better understand requests, especially those made in regard to on-screen content.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; is available to developers right now, but Apple will release a public beta later this month.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers.2431081/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-third-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2431082/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 10:09:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-third-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming macOS 14.6 update to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its launch. Today's public beta comes a week after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta-2/">released the second public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
No new features have been found in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.6 developer betas, so it is not clear what might be included. With Apple now working on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, development on &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; is beginning to wrap up so it's likely a bug fix update.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-third-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta/">Apple Releases Third macOS Sonoma 14.6 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-macos-sonoma-14-6-public-beta.2431082/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Third Public Beta of iOS 17.6</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2431079/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 10:08:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 updates to public beta testers, with the betas coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-2/">second iOS and iPadOS 17.6 public betas</a>. Apple seeded the third betas of iOS 17.6 and iPadOS 17.6 to developers earlier this week. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.6-Feature-Redux.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950716" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
The new features that Apple announced for &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have all been implemented at this point, so it is not clear what will be included in iOS 17.6, and no features have been discovered in the developer betas so far. <br/>
<br/>
With Apple now shifting its focus to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it is likely that iOS 17.6 will include bug fixes and other under-the-hood improvements rather than outward-facing features. <br/>
<br/>
Apple has also seeded the second public betas of upcoming watchOS 10.6 and tvOS 17.6 updates. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-releases-ios-17-6-public-beta-3/">Apple Releases Third Public Beta of iOS 17.6</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-third-public-beta-of-ios-17-6.2431079/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hopes iOS 18 AI Features Will Boost iPhone Shipments by 10% in 2024</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-ai-iphone-16-shipment-boost/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hopes-ios-18-ai-features-will-boost-iphone-shipments-by-10-in-2024.2431077/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 10:02:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-ai-iphone-16-shipment-boost/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple wants to ship a minimum of 90 million <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models in 2024, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-07-10/apple-bets-on-ai-to-drive-demand-for-iphone-16-targets-10-growth-in-shipments">Bloomberg</a></em>. Apple is telling its suppliers and partners that it is aiming for 10 percent shipment growth over 2023, when it shipped approximately 81 million <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Colors.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935159" /><br/>
The upcoming &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will all use next-generation A18 chip technology, which will support Apple Intelligence. As of right now, only the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max are powerful enough for Apple's AI features, so anyone with an older <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> that wants to take advantage of the new capabilities will need to upgrade this year. &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; pricing starts at &#36;799, and that will also likely be the starting price for the entry-level &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model that will support Apple Intelligence. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is expecting Apple Intelligence to increase demand for the new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, which indicates that Apple could see a strong 2024, especially in countries like China. Apple is lagging behind Chinese smartphone manufacturers in AI development, as brands like Xiaomi and Huawei have already shipped AI features.<br/>
<br/>
There is no word yet on how Apple Intelligence will function in China because Apple has not yet established a deal with a Chinese AI company. OpenAI's ChatGPT, which will be available in the United States and other countries, is not able to operate in China. To get similar functionality, Apple needs to ink a deal with a company that operates in China. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-ai-partner-china/">has been holding talks</a> with Baidu, Alibaba group, and Beijing startup Baichuan AI, but there hasn't been news of an agreement.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence will only be available in U.S. English at launch, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/21/apple-intelligence-europe-delay/">will not be launching</a> in the European Union when the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models come out, which could hurt sales in Europe. Apple said in June that it needs more time to figure out how to make Apple Intelligence compatible with the requirements of the Digital Markets Act.<br/>
<br/>
With Apple Intelligence, Apple is introducing a long list of new capabilities, including Writing Tools for proofreading, polishing, and summarizing text, Image Playground for generating images, and Genmoji for creating custom emoji. Apple Intelligence will also be used to overhaul <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, but the new &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; functionality isn't slated to launch until 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-ai-iphone-16-shipment-boost/">Apple Hopes iOS 18 AI Features Will Boost iPhone Shipments by 10% in 2024</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hopes-ios-18-ai-features-will-boost-iphone-shipments-by-10-in-2024.2431077/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Easily Switch From Google Photos to iCloud Photos With This New Tool</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-photos-to-icloud-photos-transfer-tool/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/easily-switch-from-google-photos-to-icloud-photos-with-this-new-tool.2431076/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 09:49:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-photos-to-icloud-photos-transfer-tool/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Google Photos</category>
		<category>iCloud Photos</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today <a href="https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/9666875">released a tool</a> that allows you to transfer photos and videos from Google Photos to iCloud Photos, complete with albums and descriptions.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/icloud-photos.jpg" alt="" width="836" height="470" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897381" /><br/>
Apple released an <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/118257">equivalent tool</a> for moving from iCloud Photos to Google Photos <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/03/03/apple-transfer-icloud-photos-google-photos/">three years ago</a>, so this was a reciprocal move by Google. The companies released the tools as part of the Data Transfer Initiative, which is focused on ensuring that customers can download their data from one online service and upload it to another.<br/>
<br/>
Google's tool merely creates a copy of your photos and videos for another service. The original photos and videos will remain in your Google Photos account following the transfer process, unless they are manually deleted afterwards.<br/>
<br/>
More details can be found in the <a href="https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/9666875">Google</a> and <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/118257">Apple</a> support documents for each tool, and on the <a href="https://dtinit.org/blog/2024/07/10/DTI-members-new-photo-video-tool">Data Transfer Initiative blog</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-photos/">Google Photos</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-photos/">iCloud Photos</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-photos-to-icloud-photos-transfer-tool/">Easily Switch From Google Photos to iCloud Photos With This New Tool</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/easily-switch-from-google-photos-to-icloud-photos-with-this-new-tool.2431076/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Cutesy New Website Pushes Apple Watch for Kids</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-watch-for-kids-website/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-cutesy-new-website-pushes-apple-watch-for-kids.2431074/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 09:22:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-watch-for-kids-website/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-watch-for-your-kids/">is encouraging parents</a> to purchase a cellular Apple Watch for their children with a new "Apple Watch For Your Kids" campaign, which appears to be a more informative rebranding of the Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/family-setup/">Family Setup</a> feature that's been around since 2020.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/apple-watch-for-kids.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958393" /><br/>
The Apple Watch For Your Kids website walks through how the feature works and the perks. An Apple Watch with cellular can be added to and managed by an adult's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, providing kids with a wrist-worn device for phone calls, text messaging, and location tracking.<br/>
<br/>
Apple touts Schooltime, an option that restrictions notifications and apps during school hours through Do Not Disturb. The Schooltime schedule is set by parents and adds a visible yellow circle to an Apple Watch so teachers are aware the device is not usable during classtime.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also promotes Apple Watch durability and water resistance, as well as the built-in activity tracking options that include workouts for children and activity awards.<br/>
<br/>
The newly rebranded Apple Watch For Your Kids feature is being promoted on the Apple Watch pages, but Apple has not yet updated the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/109036">support document</a> that walks parents through setup.<br/>
<br/>
Requirements for providing a child with an Apple Watch include a Series 4 or later with GPS + Cellular and a cellular service plan, an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 6s or later (for the parent), a Family Sharing group setup, and Apple IDs for both the parent and child.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-watch-for-kids-website/">Apple&#039;s Cutesy New Website Pushes Apple Watch for Kids</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-cutesy-new-website-pushes-apple-watch-for-kids.2431074/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Settings Visible in iOS 18 Beta 3 Simulator, But Features Still Not Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-beta-3-simulator-apple-intelligence/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-settings-visible-in-ios-18-beta-3-simulator-but-features-still-not-available.2431073/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:58:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-beta-3-simulator-apple-intelligence/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The latest beta of Apple's app development tool Xcode allows developers to simulate an iPhone running the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-3/">third beta of iOS 18</a>, and this has led to the discovery of some Apple Intelligence settings that are not yet available.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-Intelligence-Settings-in-iOS-18-Beta-3-Simulator-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958352" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a> and <a href="https://x.com/MatthewRodarmel/status/1810777717014732996">Matthew Rodarmel</a> are among those who spotted the settings, which can be seen in the screenshots above. However, Apple Intelligence features are still not available for testing in the third beta of iOS 18, released this week.<br/>
<br/>
During its WWDC keynote last month, Apple said that some Apple Intelligence features would be available to try "this summer," but it did not provide a specific timeframe. The features will be available in U.S. English only at launch, and they require an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, or a Mac or iPad equipped with an M1 chip or newer.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence will be able to summarize text, prioritize notifications and emails, and generate custom emoji and images, while the technology will also power a smarter version of Siri with richer language understanding, deeper per-app controls, on-screen awareness, and more. Apple said some of the features, along with support for additional languages and software platforms, will be added "over the course of the next year."<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 should be widely released in September. Even then, the initial Apple Intelligence features will still be considered a "preview" for all users.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-beta-3-simulator-apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence Settings Visible in iOS 18 Beta 3 Simulator, But Features Still Not Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-settings-visible-in-ios-18-beta-3-simulator-but-features-still-not-available.2431073/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Users Are Keeping Their Devices for Longer as Upgrades Slow</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-users-keeping-their-devices-for-longer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-users-are-keeping-their-devices-for-longer-as-upgrades-slow.2431071/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 08:51:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-users-keeping-their-devices-for-longer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>CIRP</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple users are holding onto their devices for increasingly long periods of time as upgrade cycles slow, data from <a href="https://cirpapple.substack.com/p/aging-apple-apparatus-macs">Consumer Intelligence Research Partners</a> (CIRP) suggests.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/homekit-devices-feature-orange3.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-794441" /><br/>
In recent years, a shift has occurred in the behavior of Apple customers, who are increasingly opting to retain their iPhones, iPads, and Macs for extended periods before upgrading. In the most recent 12-month period, 71% of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> owners and 68% of Mac owners reported that their previous device was over two years old, up from 63% and 59%, respectively, in 2020. <br/>
<br/>
In the specific case of the Mac, CIRP indicates a substantial increase in the length of time users keep their devices. Currently, 56% of Mac customers hold onto their laptops or desktops for three years or more, a significant rise from 40% in 2020. This trend has led to a decline in shorter lifecycle lengths, with fewer users keeping their Macs for less than three years. CIRP's research suggests that the transition to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, which began in 2020 with the introduction of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m1/">M1</a> chip, has played a crucial role in this shift. &zwnj;Apple Silicon&zwnj; has delivered significant performance and energy efficiency improvements, making Macs more capable of handling demanding tasks for several years.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/cirp-2020-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1127" height="827" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-958336" /><em>Age of previous Mac for Apple customers buying a new Mac (12 months ending March of each year)</em></div><br/>
The economic impact of the COVID-19 pandemic also likely influenced consumer behavior. During the early stages of the pandemic, there was a surge in demand for technology to support remote work and online education, but economic uncertainy followed and many consumers became more cautious with their spending, opting to maximize the lifespan of their existing devices rather than investing in new ones. Battery life improvements in MacBooks have also reached a satisfactory threshold for many users, further reducing the incentive to upgrade frequently. <br/>
<br/>
This phenomenon has similarly been <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-30/apple-s-longer-lasting-devices-ios-19-and-apple-intelligence-on-the-vision-pro-ly1jnrw4?srnd=undefined&sref=a7KhiWzs">noted by</a> <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, who recently said that the percentage of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac users whose previous device was older than two years has risen sharply. He attributed the shift to several factors, including fewer significant features in new models, improved durability and reliability of devices, and changing user needs. The increased reliance on streaming services and web-based applications means that for many users, their current devices remain sufficiently powerful and capable for everyday tasks. As a result, the traditional motivations for frequent upgrades, such as the need for better cameras, more storage, or faster processing speeds, have diminished.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/cirp/">CIRP</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-users-keeping-their-devices-for-longer/">Apple Users Are Keeping Their Devices for Longer as Upgrades Slow</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-users-are-keeping-their-devices-for-longer-as-upgrades-slow.2431071/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Early Prime Day Discounts Hit M2 iPad Air Models at Up to &#36;90 Off</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/early-prime-day-m2-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/early-prime-day-discounts-hit-m2-ipad-air-models-at-up-to-90-off.2431066/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:56:12 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/early-prime-day-m2-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's M2 iPad Air models are just a few months old, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WGD6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon has up to &#36;90 off select models</a> this week. We're tracking all-time low prices across the entire Wi-Fi M2 iPad Air lineup, although the steepest discounts will be found on 13-inch models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m2-iPad-Air-Horizontal-Feature-Blue-and-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950735" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
The cheapest model is the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WGD6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;564.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.00. You'll also find deals on the 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB models below, all of which are in stock on Amazon with delivery dates as soon as the end of the week for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WGD6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;35 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;564.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5D33G%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0D3KGR4NB%3F_encoding%3DUTF8%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;654.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J53DNX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;55 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;844.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6VB4J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;75 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,024.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The 13-inch M2 iPad Air models start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;738.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;799.00. Similar to the 11-inch devices, all Wi-Fi models are on sale this week, and for the larger display iPad Airs these discounts reach up to &#36;90 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5XNCT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;61 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;738.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8W54H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;839.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8BD6L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;75 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,024.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J75PYR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,209.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The iPad Air is Apple's middle-tier iPad model, equipped with an LCD Liquid Retina display, True Tone support, four unique color options, Touch ID, relocated front-facing camera, and two new size options with the 11-inch and 13-inch sizes.<br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/early-prime-day-m2-ipad-air/">Early Prime Day Discounts Hit M2 iPad Air Models at Up to &#36;90 Off</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/early-prime-day-discounts-hit-m2-ipad-air-models-at-up-to-90-off.2431066/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Includes Two New Background Sounds to Help You Focus or Rest</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-new-background-sounds/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-includes-two-new-background-sounds-to-help-you-focus-or-rest.2431063/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:42:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-new-background-sounds/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Background Sounds</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iOS 18 update for the iPhone includes two new Background Sounds: Night and Fire.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Control-Center-Background-Sounds.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958281" /><br/>
Introduced on iOS 15, the Background Sounds feature allows you to play ambient background sounds on your iPhone to help you focus or rest. Other available sounds include Balanced Noise, Bright Noise, Dark Noise, Ocean, Rain, and Stream.<br/>
<br/>
Background Sounds is a free feature built into the iPhone that offers similar functionality as apps such as Dark Noise. We have a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/focus-chill-out-iphone-background-sounds/">step-by-step guide</a> that outlines how to turn on the feature in the Settings app or in Control Center.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 18 is currently in beta for developers, and a public beta will be available soon. The update should be widely released in September.<br/>
<br/>
The new Backgrounds Sounds are also included in the iPadOS 18 and macOS Sequoia betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/background-sounds/">Background Sounds</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/ios-18-new-background-sounds/">iOS 18 Includes Two New Background Sounds to Help You Focus or Rest</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-includes-two-new-background-sounds-to-help-you-focus-or-rest.2431063/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Leads Global PC Growth With 21% Shipment Increase</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-leads-global-pc-growth/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leads-global-pc-growth-with-21-shipment-increase.2431055/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 07:08:06 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-leads-global-pc-growth/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>IDC</category>
		<category>Canalys</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is believed to have seen a significant 21% increase in Mac shipments for the second quarter of 2024, the largest growth among global PC manufacturers during this period, as part of an industry-wide recovery.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/apple-silicon-mac-lineup-wwdc-2022-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-878408" /><br/>
According to a <a href="https://www.idc.com/getdoc.jsp?containerId=prUS52428724">report by IDC</a>, an industry research firm, worldwide shipments of desktops and laptops increased by 3% year-over-year for the quarter ending in June 2024. Apple and Acer led the growth among major manufacturers, with Acer showing a 14% increase in shipments. This marked the second consecutive quarter of growth for the PC industry, following a period of decline after the pandemic-driven surge in purchases during 2020 and 2021.<br/>
<br/>
Ryan Reith, group vice president at IDC, noted that the combination of two consecutive quarters of growth, market excitement around AI-focused PCs, and a commercial refresh cycle, provided a much-needed boost to the PC market. AI-focused PCs are anticipated to drive a new wave of upgrades, though IDC reports that only about 3% of PCs shipped this year are said to be optimized for AI tasks. Apple's Mac lineup is likely to see further traction with the integration of Apple Intelligence, which positions the company to capitalize on the growing demand for AI-optimized PCs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's shipments jumped 20.8% from the second quarter of 2023, the largest rise among global PC makers. Acer followed with a 13.7% increase. Dell experienced a 2.4% decline in shipments, making it the only major company to see a decrease during this period. A new report from <a href="https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2024-07-10-gartner-says-worldwide-pc-shipments-increased-1-point-9-percent-in-second-quarter-of-2024">Gartner</a> shows similar figures.<br/>
<br/>
Despite weak demand in China, which held back overall results, excluding China, global shipments grew by more than 5%, according to IDC. Lenovo maintained the highest market share at nearly 23%, while HP saw a 1.8% increase from the previous year, holding 21% of the market.<br/>
<br/>
Canalys, another market research firm, <a href="https://canalys.com/newsroom/global-pc-market-q2-2024">reported</a> a slightly higher global PC market growth of 3.4% year-over-year, with total shipments reaching 62.8 million units in the second quarter of 2024. Apple secured the fourth position with 5.5 million units shipped, translating to a 9% market share, and marking a 6% increase from the same period last year. Lenovo led the market with 14.7 million units shipped, followed by HP with 13.7 million units, and Dell with 10.1 million units.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/idc/">IDC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/canalys/">Canalys</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-leads-global-pc-growth/">Apple Leads Global PC Growth With 21% Shipment Increase</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-leads-global-pc-growth-with-21-shipment-increase.2431055/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacStadium Releases Free Orka Desktop macOS Virtualization Software</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/macstadium-free-orka-desktop-macos-vm-software/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macstadium-releases-free-orka-desktop-macos-virtualization-software.2431054/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:55:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/macstadium-free-orka-desktop-macos-vm-software/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Orka</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Mac cloud services provider MacStadium today unveiled <a href="https://www.macstadium.com/orka-desktop">Orka Desktop</a>, a free virtualization tool that allows Mac users to create and manage macOS virtual machines locally via an easy-to-use admin panel.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/orka-desktop.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958261" /><br/>
Orka users can create or download custom macOS images locally for their own personal use, or to collaborate with team members using a familiar workflow, versioning, audit, and review controls. The tool has been designed for iOS/macOS Developers, DevOps Engineers, and IT Admins, as well as students, hobbyists, technologists, and others.<br/>
<br/>
MacStadium claims it is the "ideal tool" for those who want to learn more about Mac virtualization and learn how an image can be built and tested locally, then uploaded to the cloud.<br/>
<blockquote>"Orka Desktop provides the tools to allow developers to create many different macOS image versions locally, commit those into a shared repository, and pass them around for collaboration. Developers can also scale further by pulling those resources into an Orka Cluster at MacStadium where you can orchestrate workloads with cloud resources," said Chris Chapman, MacStadium's chief technology officer."</blockquote>MacStadium says Orka Desktop achieves near-native performance on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a>, with virtualization overhead as low as 5% in most cases. Orka Desktop also wraps and compresses macOS images with an Open Container Initiative (OCI)-compliant specification, which allows it to reduce a 90GB image by as much as 80%, shrinking it to nearly 15GB, making it much easier to move around. <br/>
<br/>
There are two options for creating a new VM in Orka: Clean Install, where the image is created from an existing IPSW file, and Pull Image, where the image is pulled from an Image Repository. There is also an option to pull the latest IPSW directly from Apple's servers. More information can be found in <a href="https://orkadocs.macstadium.com/docs/desktop-getting-started">Orka's documentation</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/orka-desktop-macos.jpg" alt="" width="3024" height="1964" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958270" /><br/>
The new VM application requires macOS Ventura or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> running on an Apple silicon Mac with at least 8GB of RAM and more than 50GB of free disk space. Orka Desktop can be downloaded for free from the <a href="https://www.macstadium.com/orka-desktop">MacStadium website</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/orka/">Orka</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/macstadium-free-orka-desktop-macos-vm-software/">MacStadium Releases Free Orka Desktop macOS Virtualization Software</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macstadium-releases-free-orka-desktop-macos-virtualization-software.2431054/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Hits Record Low &#36;799 Price at Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/m2-macbook-air-record-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-hits-record-low-799-price-at-best-buy.2431049/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:26:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/m2-macbook-air-record-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today has Apple's 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"><strong>&#36;799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. You'll find all four colors on sale at this price, including Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-m2-13-inch.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939833" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Compared to previous sales, this is a match of the all-time low price on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. Right now, only Best Buy has this steep discount, and we aren't tracking any notable deals on the 512GB model.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Although there are now updated M3 MacBook Air computers, Apple does still sell the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air as an entry-level option. The model on sale today features an 8-core CPU, 8-core GPU, and 8GB RAM, and it should work perfectly for anyone looking for a reliable machine to do basic daily tasks.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/m2-macbook-air-record-low/">Apple&#039;s M2 MacBook Air Hits Record Low &#36;799 Price at Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m2-macbook-air-hits-record-low-799-price-at-best-buy.2431049/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Launches New Galaxy Z Fold6 and Z Flip6 Smartphones, Earbuds, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-launches-new-galaxy-z-fold6-and-z-flip6-smartphones-earbuds-and-more.2431047/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 06:05:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today announced the launch of its latest flagship foldable smartphones, the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN5A3Sx">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> and the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUOtRCKM">Galaxy Z Flip6</a>, plus it introduced new Galaxy earbuds, new smart watches, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fkH7N4DO6Cw?si=i0FKNUfOQzZI3mZi" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN5A3Sx">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> is Samsung's larger foldable device, featuring a 6.3-inch cover display when folded and a 7.6-inch display when opened up. The new model is the slimmest and lightest to date, with a slightly larger cover screen. Samsung designed a new dual rail hinge that is more durable, and there is a strengthened folding edge that better distributes the shock of external impacts. Enhanced layers on the main display improve the crease while boosting strength, and Samsung says it is using Gorilla Glass Victus 2, all of which make this the most durable Galaxy foldable device to date.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958253" /><br/>
There's a 10-megapixel selfie camera, a 4-megapixel under-display camera, and a triple rear camera setup with a 12-megapixel ultra-wide lens, a 50-megapixel wide-angle lens, and a 10-megapixel telephoto lens. Other features include 12GB memory, up to 256GB internal storage, a 4,400mAh battery, a fingerprint sensor, and Qualcomm's Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 mobile chip, which is optimized for AI processing.<br/>
<br/>
Galaxy Z Fold6 AI features include a Notes app with translation, summaries, auto formatting, and Composer for the keyboard that generates suggested text and can mimic your tone by analyzing past content. A sketch to image feature for the S Pen turns sketches into more detailed drawings, similar to how Apple's Image Playground feature works in the Notes app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung partnered with Google to integrate the Google Gemini app into its new smartphones, and accessing Gemini can be done by swiping from the corner of the display. AI photo tools include Portrait Studio for creating a variety of portrait styles for images, and Instant Slow-mo for slowing a video by generating additional frames.<br/>
<br/>
The smaller <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUOtRCKM">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> also has a thinner, more durable display, and the same Snapdragon 8 Gen 3 chip. It features a 3.4-inch FlexWindow that unfolds into a 6.7-inch smartphone. There's a 10-megapixel selfie camera, a 12-megapixel ultra-wide camera, and a 50-megapixel wide-angle camera.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/dan-samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958254" /><br/>
An AI-based suggested replies feature can be used on the Z Flip6 to respond to texts from the cover screen. The feature analyzes your latest text messages to suggest tailored responses. The FlexWindow can take advantage of many Galaxy AI features such as Samsung Health, and there's support for additional widgets. An AI-powered Photo Ambient wallpaper is able to change in real-time based on the time and weather, and the FlexCam has a new Auto Zoom feature for finding the best framing for a shot.<br/>
<br/>
Other Galaxy AI features on the new smartphones include instant translation for PDFs, equation solving much like Apple's Math Notes, browsing assist for providing translations and summaries of webpages, interpreter for one-way or continuous transcription, and real-time phone call translation.<br/>
<br/>
Alongside the new smartphones, Samsung introduced the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN0rdCS">Galaxy Buds3</a> and the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN6mU8k">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a>, which have been redesigned to be more comfortable and more AirPods-like. The Buds3 have an open design, while the Buds3 Pro are in-ear with silicone tips and block out ambient noise.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-galaxy-buds-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958256" /><br/>
Both models have ANC, but the Pro model offers adaptive noise control much like Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>. Samsung says the Buds3 Pro continually identify surrounding sound and adjust the optimal level of noise and sound. Samsung added Blade Lights LED to the Galaxy Buds3 Pro for swipe-based music and volume control.<br/>
<br/>
There are two new Galaxy watches, the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDKH9qQfnk">Galaxy Watch7</a> and the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDKH74fMyN">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a>. The Watch7 is available in 40mm and 44mm sizes, while the Ultra model is larger at 47mm. The Ultra model is equipped with a titanium casing. With the Galaxy Watch7 and Galaxy Watch Ultra, Samsung beat Apple to a rumored Apple Watch feature, sleep apnea detection. The feature is able to check for potential sides of moderate to severe sleep apnea.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-galaxy-watch-7-ultra.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958255" /><br/>
Sleep apnea detection, ECG functionality, and heart rate monitoring use a new BioActive Sensor that Samsung says is more accurate. The Galaxy Watches includes a feature for measuring the production of glycation end products (AGEs) from the wrist using light sensors. Samsung explains that AGEs are a reflection of the overall biological aging process and an indication of metabolic health.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung also provided more detail on the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDKH817tQP">Galaxy Ring</a>, which was first introduced earlier this year. The Galaxy ring is a smart ring that can be used alongside a Galaxy smartphone in lieu of a smart watch. It is made from titanium, comes in black, silver, or gold colors, and is available in nine sizes starting at size five. The ring has a seven day battery life and 10ATM water resistance, so Samsung says it is durable enough to wear anywhere without worry.<br/>
<br/>
The ring tracks several sleep metrics, including movement during sleep, sleep latency, heart rate, and respiratory rate to provide a nightly sleep score, plus it is able to use Galaxy AI to generate an energy score. The energy score uses sleep, activity, sleeping heart rate, and sleeping heart rate variability to provide health insights. Samsung is not charging a subscription fee for the Galaxy Ring, and it has access to all data and insights from the Samsung Health app.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's new product lineup will be available on July 24, with preorders available starting today. The Galaxy Z Fold6 is priced starting at &#36;1,900, while the Galaxy Z Flip6 is priced starting at &#36;1,100. The Galaxy Ring is priced starting at &#36;400, the Galaxy Watch7 is priced starting at &#36;300, and the Galaxy Watch Ultra is priced starting at &#36;650. Samsung's Galaxy Buds3 are priced starting at &#36;180, and the Galaxy Buds3 Pro are priced starting at &#36;250.<br/>
<br/>
As part of the launch, Samsung is offering significant discounts with up to &#36;1,200 in enhanced trade-in credit when purchasing a Z Fold6 or up to &#36;650 when purchasing a Z Flip6, free storage upgrades on both models, a free band with either the Galaxy Watch Ultra or the Galaxy Watch7, plus savings on the Galaxy Buds3 series. Customers purchasing the Z Fold6 through our link also qualify for a bonus &#36;100 in savings for the first 72 hours.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/">Samsung Launches New Galaxy Z Fold6 and Z Flip6 Smartphones, Earbuds, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-launches-new-galaxy-z-fold6-and-z-flip6-smartphones-earbuds-and-more.2431047/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple TV+ Reveals Severance Season 2 Premiere Date in Teaser Video</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-2-date/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-reveals-severance-season-2-premiere-date-in-teaser-video.2431046/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 05:56:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-2-date/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Shows</category>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The critically-acclaimed workplace thriller "<a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/originals/severance/">Severance</a>" returns to Apple TV+ early next year, according to a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ULC9M8CCn28">teaser video</a> released today.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Apple-TV-Plus-Severance-Season-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1104" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958238" /><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.apple.com/tv-pr/news/2024/07/apples-hit-global-phenomenon-workplace-thriller-severance-to-return-for-season-two-on-friday-january-17-2025/">said</a> the 10-episode season will premiere on Friday, January 17, and then one episode will follow every Friday through March 21.<br/>
<br/>
The sci-fi series revolves around the mysterious company Lumon Industries, whose employees cannot recall any memories about their personal lives while they are at work. Similarly, the employees cannot remember anything about the workplace when they are out of the office. The show was created by Dan Erickson, and it has an ensemble cast starring Adam Scott, Britt Lower, Tramell Tillman, Zach Cherry, Christopher Walken, and others.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ULC9M8CCn28?si=x-beVX2jPbvLb0oc" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The first season of Severance ended in April 2022, so fans will have waited around 33 months for the second season, which faced production delays for seven months last year as a result of the Writers Guild of America going on strike.<br/>
<br/>
Severance is one of the most popular shows on Apple TV+. In the U.S., the streaming service costs &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;99 per year following a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">price increase</a> last October, and it is included in all Apple One subscription bundles.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-shows/">Apple TV Shows</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-tv-plus-severance-season-2-date/">Apple TV+ Reveals Severance Season 2 Premiere Date in Teaser Video</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-tv-reveals-severance-season-2-premiere-date-in-teaser-video.2431046/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Google Advanced Protection Program Adds Single Passkey Set-Up Option</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-advanced-protection-program-passkeys/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-advanced-protection-program-adds-single-passkey-set-up-option.2431042/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 04:52:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-advanced-protection-program-passkeys/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google today <a href="https://blog.google/technology/safety-security/google-passkeys-advanced-protection-program/">announced</a> that has added a new passkey set-up option to its <a href="https://landing.google.com/advancedprotection/">Advanced Protection Program</a>, allowing Pixel and iPhone owners to use their device's biometric authentication instead of physical security keys.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/google-advanced-protection-program.jpg" alt="" width="1916" height="1079" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958199" /><br/>
For those unfamiliar with the Advanced Protection Program, it's designed for high-profile Google product users who need maximum protection from hacking attempts. It's a feature aimed at journalists, activists, business leaders, and others who feel vulnerable to targeted security breaches. <br/>
<br/>
When it launched in 2017, Google required users to have two physical security keys to activate it, and one of those keys plus a password to log in. Last year, the company changed the feature so that users could sign in with just a passkey, but the physical security keys were still required to set it up. <br/>
<br/>
From today, that's no longer the case. When users get started with <a href="https://landing.google.com/advancedprotection/">Google's Advanced Protection Program</a>, they will have the option to set up with either a passkey or a physical security key. <br/>
<br/>
Passkeys are easier to use and more secure than passwords because they let users sign in to apps and sites the same way they unlock their devices: With Face ID, Touch ID, or a device passcode. Passkeys are also resistant to online attacks like phishing, making them more secure than things like SMS one-time codes.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/google-advanced-protection-program-passkeys/">Google Advanced Protection Program Adds Single Passkey Set-Up Option</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/google-advanced-protection-program-adds-single-passkey-set-up-option.2431042/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Rumored to Support 40W Fast Charging and 20W MagSafe</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/iphone-16-pro-40w-fast-charging-20w-magsafe/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-rumored-to-support-40w-fast-charging-and-20w-magsafe.2431038/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 03:57:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/iphone-16-pro-40w-fast-charging-20w-magsafe/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's forthcoming iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will support 40W wired fast charging and 20W MagSafe charging, claims a rumor currently swirling around China.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-16-Pro-Front-Update-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953750" /><br/>
Right now, iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models are capable of up to 27W peak charging speeds with an appropriate USB-C power adapter, while official MagSafe chargers from Apple and authorized third parties can wirelessly charge the iPhone 15 models at up to 15W. All four iPhone 15 models can charge up to 50% in around 30 minutes with a 20W or higher power adapter, which is the same as Apple's previous iPhone 13 and iPhone 14 models.<br/>
<br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.ithome.com/0/780/712.htm">ITHome</a></em>, that's set to change for the Pro models in Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 lineup, with a boost to 40W wired and 20W wireless charging in order to "balance and improve the problem of increasing charging time caused by the increase in battery capacity."<br/>
<br/>
This rationale relates to another rumor that – with the exception of the iPhone 16 Plus – models in Apple's ‌iPhone 16 series will feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/09/alleged-iphone-16-battery-details-leaked/">larger batteries than their predecessors</a>.<br/>
<br/>
The claim about increased charging wattage resurrects a similar rumor we covered here at <em>MacRumors</em> almost a year ago, when it was reported that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/iphone-15-could-feature-stacked-battery-technology/">iPhone 16 lineup would adopt stacked battery technology</a>, alongside 40W wired charging and 20W charging via ‌MagSafe‌. Stacked batteries can result in a higher capacity and longer lifespan. <br/>
<br/>
It's unclear why the rumor is again doing the rounds in Asia, but given that we are only two months out from Apple unveiling its new flagship devices, there could be something in it. The iPhone 16 series is expected to be released sometime around mid-September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/iphone-16-pro-40w-fast-charging-20w-magsafe/">iPhone 16 Pro Rumored to Support 40W Fast Charging and 20W MagSafe</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-rumored-to-support-40w-fast-charging-and-20w-magsafe.2431038/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
