<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 08:02:38 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect New AirPods Max to Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/when-to-expect-new-airpods-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-airpods-max-to-launch.2419437/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:52:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/when-to-expect-new-airpods-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/08/airpods-max-announced-three-years-ago/">more than three years</a> since Apple released the AirPods Max, leading some to wonder when the over-ear headphones will be updated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936392" /><br/>
Below, we outline when to expect new AirPods Max, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/airpods-max-2-launch-next-year-what-to-expect/">rumored features</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
In an October 2023 edition of his newsletter, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-10-29/apple-to-unveil-m3-m3-pro-m3-max-chip-macbook-pro-imac-to-reignite-mac-sales-lobgrqad"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said</a> Apple planned to release new AirPods Max in "late 2024," so the headphones are likely around 7-10 months away from being updated based on that timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced the current AirPods Max in a press release <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/airpods-max/">on December 8, 2020</a>, and the headphones launched a week later.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Features</h2><br/>
Apple is only planning minor changes for the AirPods Max, including a USB-C port instead of Lightning for charging and wired audio playback, according to Gurman. He also said the headphones will be available in new color options. The current color options include Green, Pink, Silver, Sky Blue, and Space Gray.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said the updated headphones will still be considered first-generation AirPods Max, signifying how minor the changes will be.<br/>
<br/>
The updated AirPods Max will likely support Bluetooth 5.3, up from Bluetooth 5.0, for more reliable and power-efficient wireless audio connectivity.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/when-to-expect-new-airpods-max/">When to Expect New AirPods Max to Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-new-airpods-max-to-launch.2419437/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Takes &#36;99 Off AirPods Max for First Time in 2024, Available for &#36;449.99</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/amazon-99-off-airpods-max/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-99-off-airpods-max-for-first-time-in-2024-available-for-449-99.2419435/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 07:04:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/amazon-99-off-airpods-max/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has the first &#36;99 discount on Apple's AirPods Max since Black Friday, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> in select colors, down from &#36;549.00. Most models can deliver as soon as February 16 with Prime delivery, but others have slipped into a late February delivery estimate.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Max-Discount-Feature-Red.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895399" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
On Amazon, colors being discounted include Green, Pink, and Silver. You can find a <a href="https://howl.me/clDir4j95E4">matching sale at Best Buy</a> right now, with similar shipping estimates in most colors. Best Buy's sale is depicted as lasting for one day only, but Amazon's should stay up a little longer.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;99 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
There are plenty of other AirPods deals happening right now on Amazon. This includes the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a> (&#36;59 off), the AirPods 3 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BDHB9Y8H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;139.99</strong></a> (&#36;29 off), and the AirPods 2 for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;89.99</strong></a> (&#36;39 off). In regards to the AirPods Pro 2 and AirPods 3, these are both all-time low prices on these models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is rumored to be updating the AirPods Max sometime in 2024, and the new models should be getting a USB-C port and new color options. Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/amazon-99-off-airpods-max/">Amazon Takes &#36;99 Off AirPods Max for First Time in 2024, Available for &#36;449.99</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-takes-99-off-airpods-max-for-first-time-in-2024-available-for-449-99.2419435/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac Audio Balance Bug That Apple Knew About 12 Years Ago Still Exists</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/macos-audio-bug-still-exists-12-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-audio-balance-bug-that-apple-knew-about-12-years-ago-still-exists.2419425/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 05:00:40 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/macos-audio-bug-still-exists-12-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>macOS Monterey</category>
		<category>macOS Ventura</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has still not fixed a bug in macOS that causes the audio balance to drift on Macs under certain conditions, despite having acknowledged the issue 12 years ago.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/sound-balance-bug-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936342" /><br/>
A developer named Fabian highlighted the problem today in a <a href="https://x.com/ffaebi/status/1757669861377949930?s=20">post</a> on X (formerly Twitter), claiming that Apple "still has not fixed the audio left/right balance bug in macOS. I still have to use an app to fix it automatically. The app is from 2015, that means we are approaching the 10 year anniversary [of the bug]."<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.tunabellysoftware.com/balance_lock/">Balance Lock</a> is the app in question, a free download available from Tunabelly Software. The bug's continuing existence was corroborated by other users who responded to the X post and commented on it over on <a href="https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=39367460">Hacker News</a>. However, it seems as though the issue has persisted for even longer than Fabian initially supposed. <br/>
<br/>
Writing in 2013 on <a href="https://apple.stackexchange.com/questions/79384/audio-balance-changes-randomly-in-macbook-pro-retina-15-inch-mid-2012">Stack Exchange</a>, one user claimed to have experienced the same bug on multiple Macs going back to 2003. Whether or not that is the case, what we do know is that Apple acknowledged the bug on February 12, 2012 in a <a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20230419150423/https://support.apple.com/kb/TA22305?locale=nl_BE">Mac OS X 10.2 support document</a>, which is no longer on Apple's website but retrievable via the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine. In it Apple states: <br/>
<blockquote>In some cases the audio balance may unexpectedly drift towards the left or right channel. This can happen if you rapidly press the volume up or down keys while the computer's microprocessor is under heavy load.</blockquote>To rectify the problem, Apple advises users to open the Sound panel in System Preferences (now System Settings) and "Drag the audio balance slider to the desired position."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The year is 2024 and <a href="https://twitter.com/Apple?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@apple</a> still has not fixed the audio left/right balance bug in MacOS. I still have to use an app to fix it automatically. The app is from 2015, that means we are approaching the 10 year anniversary &#x1f389; <a href="https://t.co/QegD5tEvaA">https://t.co/QegD5tEvaA</a> <a href="https://t.co/saoiGubhXV">pic.twitter.com/saoiGubhXV</a></p>&mdash; Fabian (@ffaebi) <a href="https://twitter.com/ffaebi/status/1757669861377949930?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 14, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Given Apple's advice at the time, it sounds like the company had not been able to come up with a proper fix when the support document was published, which begs the question as to whether it <em>still</em> has no solution to the bug, and that is why the company has let it remain in successive versions of Mac OS X and macOS up to this day. <br/>
<br/>
Have you experienced the audio balance drifting on your Mac? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-monterey.234">macOS Monterey</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-ventura.239">macOS Ventura</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/macos-audio-bug-still-exists-12-years/">Mac Audio Balance Bug That Apple Knew About 12 Years Ago Still Exists</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-audio-balance-bug-that-apple-knew-about-12-years-ago-still-exists.2419425/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Latest AI Tool Can Animate an Image Based on Your Description</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/apple-research-ai-tool-animates-images/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-latest-ai-tool-can-animate-an-image-based-on-your-description.2419416/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2024 02:07:10 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/apple-research-ai-tool-animates-images/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has made another addition to its growing AI repertoire with the creation of a tool that leverages large language models (LLMs) to animate static images based on a user's text prompts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-AI-research-dall-e.jpg" alt="" width="1792" height="1024" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936311" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>MacRumors image made with DALL·E</em></div><br/>
Apple describes the innovation in a new research paper titled "<a href="https://arxiv.org/pdf/2402.06071.pdf">Keyframer: Empowering Animation Design Using Large Language Models.</a>" <br/>
<blockquote>"While one-shot prompting interfaces are common in commercial text-to-image systems like Dall·E and Midjourney, we argue that animations require a more complex set of user considerations, such as timing and coordination, that are difficult to fully specify in a single prompt—thus, alternative approaches that enable users to iteratively construct and refine generated designs may be needed especially for animations.<br/>
<br/>
"We combined emerging design principles for language-based prompting of design artifacts with code-generation capabilities of LLMs to build a new AI-powered animation tool called Keyframer. With Keyframer, users can create animated illustrations from static 2D images via natural language prompting. Using GPT-4 3, Keyframer generates CSS animation code to animate an input Scalable Vector Graphic (SVG)."</blockquote>To create an animation, the user uploads an SVG image – of a space rocket, say – then types in a prompt like "generate three designs where the sky fades into different colors and the stars twinkle." Keyframer then generates CSS code for the animation, and the user can then refine it by editing the code directly or by entering additional text prompts. <br/>
<br/>
"Keyframer enabled users to iteratively refine their designs through sequential prompting, rather than having to consider their entire design upfront," explain the authors. "Through this work, we hope to inspire future animation design tools that combine the powerful generative capabilities of LLMs to expedite design prototyping with dynamic editors that enable creators to maintain creative control."<br/>
<br/>
According to the paper, the research was informed by interviews with professional animation designers and engineers. "I think this was much faster than a lot of things I've done," said one of the study participants quoted in the paper. "I think doing something like this before would have just taken hours to do."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ai-model-animates-images-1.jpg" alt="" width="1779" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936312" /><br/>
The innovation is just the latest in a series of AI breakthroughs by Apple. Last week, Apple researchers <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/apple-ai-model-edits-images-natural-language/">released</a> an AI model that harnesses the power of multimodal LLMs to perform pixel-level edits on images. <br/>
<br/>
In late December, Apple also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/21/apple-ai-researchers-run-llms-iphones/">revealed</a> that it had made strides in deploying LLMs on iPhones and other Apple devices with limited memory by inventing an innovative flash memory utilization technique.<br/>
<br/>
Both <em>The Information</em> and analyst Jeff Pu have said that Apple will have some kind of generative AI feature available on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>‌ and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/19/apple-generative-ai-late-2024-jeff-pu/">later in the year</a>, when <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> is released. The next version of Apple's mobile software is said to include an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">enhanced version of Siri</a> with ChatGPT-like generative AI functionality, and has the potential to be the "biggest" update in the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s history, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/ios-18-biggest-update-rumor/"><em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<em>(Via <em><a href="https://venturebeat.com/ai/apple-researchers-unveil-keyframer-an-ai-tool-that-animates-still-images-using-llms/">VentureBeat</a></em>.)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/apple-research-ai-tool-animates-images/">Apple&#039;s Latest AI Tool Can Animate an Image Based on Your Description</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-latest-ai-tool-can-animate-an-image-based-on-your-description.2419416/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says Quest 3 is Better Than Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/meta-quest-3-apple-vision-pro-zuckerberg/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-says-quest-3-is-better-than-apple-vision-pro.2419400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 17:41:06 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/meta-quest-3-apple-vision-pro-zuckerberg/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg today compared the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> to the &#36;500 Meta Quest 3 <a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/C3TkhmivNzt/">in an Instagram video</a>, and provided several reasons why he thinks Meta's headset is better than Apple's.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/meta-quest-3.jpg" alt="" width="1385" height="779" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-914163" /><br/>
According to Zuckerberg, the Quest 3 is better "for the vast majority of things that people use mixed reality for," and here are some of the things he said about the Meta Quest 3:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>It's 7x less expensive than Vision Pro.</li><br/>
 	<li>It does high-quality passthrough with big screens "just like Vision Pro."</li><br/>
 	<li>Quest is a lot more comfortable - it's 120 grams less.</li><br/>
 	<li>There are no wires that get in the way when you move around.</li><br/>
 	<li>The field of view is wider and the screen is brighter.</li><br/>
 	<li>Vision Pro has motion blur when you move around. Quest is a lot crisper.</li><br/>
 	<li>Precision controllers are available, as is hand tracking, and Quest's hand tracking is more accurate.</li><br/>
 	<li>Quest's immersive content library is a lot deeper.</li><br/>
 	<li>You can watch YouTube or play Xbox.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Zuckerberg said that he was surprised at the "tradeoffs" that Apple had to make to provide a higher resolution screen than is offered by the Quest 3, sacrificing "comfort," "ergonomics," and more. He went on to explain that Apple is not always the leader in a new product category, and that he hopes Meta's devices will ultimately "win."<blockquote>Now look, I know that some fanboys get upset whenever somebody dares to question if Apple is going to be the leader in a new category, but the reality is that every generation of computing has an open and a closed model. And yeah, in mobile, Apple's closed model won. It's not always that way. If you go back to the PC era, Microsoft's open model was the winner. In this next generation, Meta is going to be the open model, and I really want to make sure that the open model wins out again. The future is not yet written.</blockquote>The Meta Quest 3 launched back in October. It has two 2K LCD panels compared to the &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;'s 4K microLED displays. It weighs 515 grams while the Vision Pro weighs 600 to 650 grams, and it does not have a separate battery pack. It uses Qualcomm's Snapdragon XR2 Gen 2 chipset, has 8GB RAM, and is equipped with Touch Plus controllers.<br/>
<br/>
Meta has produced several headsets so far, including the Oculus Quest, the Oculus Quest 2, the Quest 3, and the Quest Pro. Apple plans to continue producing headsets, and rumors suggest that the next-generation version will be much more affordable. When explaining the price of the Vision Pro, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/02/tim-cook-on-vision-pro-moment/">Apple CEO Tim Cook said</a> that it was "tomorrow's technology today."<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/meta-quest-3-apple-vision-pro-zuckerberg/">Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg Says Quest 3 is Better Than Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/meta-ceo-mark-zuckerberg-says-quest-3-is-better-than-apple-vision-pro.2419400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Pirated Movie App Disguised as Vision Test Snuck Onto App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/pirated-movie-was-in-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pirated-movie-app-disguised-as-vision-test-snuck-onto-app-store.2419391/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 16:14:25 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/pirated-movie-was-in-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A vision testing app named "Kimi" with a not-so-hidden pirated movie feature recently made its way past Apple's review team, ultimately reaching number eight on the list of top free entertainment apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/kimi-app.jpg" alt="" width="3291" height="1851" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936299" /><br/>
As reported by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/2/13/24071693/kimi-movie-piracy-app-store-trending-apple-iphone-ios">The Verge</a></em>, Kimi's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> listing claimed that it was an app that "tests your eyesight," but when downloaded and installed, it opened right up to a clear TV show and movie interface for downloading and watching pirated content. There was no attempt to hide the app's true purpose behind some kind of vision test interface, which begs the question of how it made its way past the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; review team.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; description mentioned comparing two pictures as an eyesight test, watching scenery, and playing games, but none of those features were present in the app.<br/>
<br/>
For an app focused on pirated content, Kimi had a fleshed out feature set. It offered top movies, search options, recommended suggestions, games, and more, with ads included for monetization purposes. The app was first approved in September, and it was available for several months in the iOS and macOS App Stores without Apple noticing.<br/>
<br/>
Apple pulled the app this morning after <em>The Verge</em> wrote about it, and it is no longer available.<br/>
<br/>
This is the second time in the last week that Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; has made headlines for questionable app approval. Last Thursday, popular password management app LastPass raised the alarm about a fake "LassPass" app that was imitating its design and feature set. Apple pulled the app about a day after the news was shared on media sites.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/pirated-movie-was-in-app-store/">Pirated Movie App Disguised as Vision Test Snuck Onto App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/pirated-movie-app-disguised-as-vision-test-snuck-onto-app-store.2419391/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says There Are Now Over 1,000 Vision Pro Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-more-than-1000-vision-pro-apps/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-there-are-now-over-1-000-vision-pro-apps.2419386/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 15:09:12 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-more-than-1000-vision-pro-apps/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There are more than 1,000 apps available for the Vision Pro, Apple marketing chief Greg Joswiak said today. There are also more than 1.5 million <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> apps that are compatible with the Vision Pro and that are able to run on the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/Apple-Vision-Pro-Dual-Loop-Band-Orange-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-929937" /><br/>
When the Vision Pro launched, Apple said there were more than 600 apps available for the headset, so the number of apps has increased by over 400 in the weeks since the Vision Pro debuted. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A huge thank you to our developers! Their hard work has already resulted in over 1,000 incredible spatial apps designed specifically for Vision Pro, along with over 1.5 million compatible apps. We&#39;re thrilled to see how they&#39;ll continue to push the boundaries for what’s possible.</p>&mdash; Greg Joswiak (@gregjoz) <a href="https://twitter.com/gregjoz/status/1757533581495382496?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 13, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
The Vision Pro is able to run many of the apps that are on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, but the 1,000 app count is for those that have been designed for and optimized for the headset. <br/>
<br/>
We've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/vision-pro-app-list/">rounded up some of the many Vision Pro apps</a> available that are worth checking out.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-more-than-1000-vision-pro-apps/">Apple Says There Are Now Over 1,000 Vision Pro Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-there-are-now-over-1-000-vision-pro-apps.2419386/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Another Longtime Industrial Designer Leaves Apple</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/another-longtime-industrial-designer-leaves-apple/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/another-longtime-industrial-designer-leaves-apple.2419384/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 14:57:54 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/another-longtime-industrial-designer-leaves-apple/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is losing yet another longtime industrial design team members, reports <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-13/apple-s-longest-serving-designer-bart-andre-retiring-from-company">Bloomberg</a></em>. Bart Andre, who has been with Apple for over 30 years, is set to retire this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912516" /><br/>
Andre joined Apple in 1992 alongside Jony Ive, and he is one of the last remaining design team members that worked with Ive to establish the design aesthetic Apple was known for during Ive's tenure.<br/>
<br/>
Andre has been helping run the design team following the 2022 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/21/apple-announces-evans-hankey-leaving/">departure of Evans Hankey</a>, who served as Apple's vice president of industrial design after Ive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/06/27/jony-ive-leaving-apple/">left in 2019</a>. When Ive quit Apple to start LoveFrom, several of the designers he had worked with went with him, and since then, other design team members <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/18/ive-era-designer-leaves-apple/">have departed as well</a>.<br/>
<br/>
After Evans Hankey left, Apple eliminated the Product Design Chief role and restructured the product design team under operations chief Jeff Williams. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>, some of the people on the design team are unhappy with being led by an operations person instead of a designer, and cost cutting efforts have also changed the way the design team operates.<br/>
<br/>
Apple now has only a handful of longtime designers that remain at the company.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/another-longtime-industrial-designer-leaves-apple/">Another Longtime Industrial Designer Leaves Apple</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/another-longtime-industrial-designer-leaves-apple.2419384/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>tvOS 17.4 Allegedly Hints at HomePod With Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-homepod-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-17-4-allegedly-hints-at-homepod-with-display.2419371/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 13:47:56 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-homepod-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The tvOS 17.4 beta that was released today contains code that references a future <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> with a display, according to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/13/references-homepod-screen-tvos-17-4/">9to5Mac</a></em>. The site claims that there is evidence of a device with a "Z314" identifier with an A15 chip inside, with both production and "internal" versions of the device being tested by Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/homepod-blue-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895477" /><br/>
<blockquote>Based on our findings, the unreleased "Z314" device is powered by an A15 Bionic chip, which interestingly is the same as the iPad mini 6. Code reveals that there are internal development and also production versions of this product under test, which suggests that it may have reached an advanced stage of development.</blockquote><br/>
The latest beta also reportedly adds SwiftUI frameworks to the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; firmware to support a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a display.<br/>
<br/>
We've heard multiple rumors about a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a touchscreen display from reliable sources. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said in March 2023 that there was a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/homepod-with-7-inch-display-to-launch-in-2024/">7-inch display in development</a>, and in October 2023, leaker <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/27/future-homepod-to-add-curved-lcd-display/">Kosutami</a> said the next-generation &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; would have a design similar to the current model but with a large LCD touch screen at the top instead of an LED array.<br/>
<br/>
HomePods to date have been equipped with the same chips that Apple uses in the Apple Watch rather than the A-series chips used in Apple devices, so <em>9to5Mac</em>'s finding of an A15 Bionic mention could reflect a shift. The S9 chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> is, however, based on the A15 Bionic, and so that would also make sense for a new &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
In 2023, Kuo claimed that the &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; with display would launch in the first half of 2024, but we have not heard additional release details since then. It is not yet clear when the device might come out, but Apple is planning to debut new iPads and Macs around the March timeframe, so we might also see a new &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; at that time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-homepod-display/">tvOS 17.4 Allegedly Hints at HomePod With Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tvos-17-4-allegedly-hints-at-homepod-with-display.2419371/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17&#039;s AirPlay Feature for Hotel Room TVs Rolling Out &#039;This Spring&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/lg-says-airplay-hotel-tvs-coming-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17s-airplay-feature-for-hotel-room-tvs-rolling-out-this-spring.2419366/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 12:50:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/lg-says-airplay-hotel-tvs-coming-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>AirPlay</category>
		<category>LG</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Starting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/ios-17-3-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">with iOS 17.3</a> and iPadOS 17.3, you can wirelessly stream content from your iPhone or iPad to a compatible hotel room TV via AirPlay, and we have now learned that the feature should begin rolling out at hotels over the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/AirPlay-Hotel-Room-TV.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="892" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936284" /><br/>
A spokesperson for LG today informed <em>MacRumors</em> that the company expects the first hotels to install AirPlay-enabled smart TVs "later this spring," meaning that the feature should be available by mid-June at the latest. LG last year <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/22/lg-airplay-hotel-room-tvs/">announced</a> that it would be the first manufacturer to offer AirPlay on both new hotel room TVs and older models released in "recent years," suggesting the capability could be enabled with a software update on some existing hotel room TVs.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first announced this feature at WWDC 2023 last June, and it said that IHG Hotels & Resorts would be the first to offer it at select hotels. IHG owns many well-known hotel brands in the U.S. and abroad, including Holiday Inn, Crowne Plaza, Kimpton, InterContinental, Candlewood Suites, Staybridge Suites, Hotel Indigo, Avid, and others.<br/>
<br/>
IHG and other major hotel companies, including Hilton, Hyatt, Marriott, Wyndham, and others, did not respond to our requests for comment.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airplay-hotels.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898340" /><br/>
Once available, the feature will allow you to scan a unique QR code on a hotel room TV to establish an AirPlay connection, allowing you to wirelessly stream videos, music, and photos from your iPhone or iPad to the TV. After the pairing process, your device will also automatically be connected to the hotel's Wi-Fi network.<br/>
<br/>
"With no logins or passwords to remember and no separate app to download, this will be the simplest way for a hotel to enable guests to access their personal entertainment apps and accounts on the big screen in their room," LG said last year.<br/>
<br/>
Google already offers a similar Chromecast streaming feature on some hotel TVs that works with both iPhones and Android devices.<br/>
<br/>
With thousands of hotels across the U.S. alone, it will likely take a long time for the AirPlay-enabled TVs to roll out widely. Where it is available, the feature will provide a much improved experience for quickly and seamlessly streaming content.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg/">LG</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/lg-says-airplay-hotel-tvs-coming-soon/">iOS 17&#039;s AirPlay Feature for Hotel Room TVs Rolling Out &#039;This Spring&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17s-airplay-feature-for-hotel-room-tvs-rolling-out-this-spring.2419366/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.1</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/visionos-1-1-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-1.2419356/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:18:53 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/visionos-1-1-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.1 update for developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The second beta comes a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-releases-first-beta-of-visionos-1-1/">release of the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.1 adds an option to reset the Vision Pro in case you <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/visionos-1-1-beta-vision-pro-reset-option/">forget your passcode</a>, a feature that was also just released to the public with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.0.3 yesterday. Previously, a forgotten passcode would require the Vision Pro to be brought to Apple to reset it.<br/>
<br/>
The update brings support for iMessage Contact Key Verification and it adds Apple device management to the Vision Pro. With this functionality, IT departments at companies and educational institutions can manage Vision Pro headsets in the same way they manage iPhones, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
According to Apple's beta notes, users can now reposition volumetric scenes closer than before, enabling easier direct interaction with the volumetric scene content. That means objects can be placed closer to you.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also improved Personas in &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;, making them look more natural and lifelike than before. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/visionos-1-1-beta-2/">Apple Releases Second Beta of visionOS 1.1</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-beta-of-visionos-1-1.2419356/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/ios-17-4-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers.2419351/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:06:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/ios-17-4-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to developers for testing purposes, with the updates coming one week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-seeds-ios-17-4-beta-2/">Apple seeded the second betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-932463" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iOS-17.4-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.4 introduces sweeping changes to the way the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> and apps operate in the European Union, paving the way for alternative app marketplaces, alternative payment systems, third-party browser engine support, and NFC access for banks and third-party payment providers. These features are limited to the EU, and won't be available in other countries.<br/>
<br/>
There are, however, changes to gaming apps, and with the launch of iOS 17.4, Apple will be allowing cloud gaming apps like Xbox Cloud Gaming and Nvidia GeForce NOW. Mini games, chatbots, and plug-ins are also now able to use the in-app purchase system.<br/>
<br/>
Along with these updates, iOS 17.4 adds new emoji characters, transcripts for podcasts in the Podcasts app, support for using SharePlay with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, Stopwatch Live Activities, and more. Full details on everything new in iOS 17.4 can be found in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-beta-1-changes/">our iOS 17.4 features article</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/ios-17-4-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.4 and iPadOS 17.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-4-and-ipados-17-4-to-developers.2419351/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers.2419350/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:05:49 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-2/">release of the second beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.4 introduces some of the features in the iOS 17.4 beta, such as new emoji characters. We don't know what Mac-specific features are included, and little else was found in the first two betas.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/macos-sonoma-14-4-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-4-to-developers.2419350/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/watchos-10-4-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2419352/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:04:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/watchos-10-4-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-seeds-watchos-10-4-beta-2/">release of the second watchOS 10.4 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.4‌ update, developers need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, watchOS 10.4 can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.4 includes new emoji characters such as a lime, an edible brown mushroom, a phoenix, a broken chain, shaking head vertically (as in a "yes" nod), and shaking head horizontally (a "no" head shake).<br/>
<br/>
There is also a Vision Pro setting to disable the Double Tap feature on Apple Watch, as the hand gestures might interfere.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/watchos-10-4-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-4-to-developers.2419352/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2419355/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:03:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.4 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming one week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-seeds-tvos-17-4-beta-2/">release of the second tvOS 17.4 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-856182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/apple-tv-4k-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.4 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS software releases are usually minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on smaller improvements rather than outward-facing changes.<br/>
<br/>
The tvOS 17.4 update adds support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> SharePlay on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj;. The &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; user can pull up an &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; QR code that can be scanned by anyone, which then allows multiple people to contribute to what's playing via &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj;. An &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; subscription is not required.<br/>
<br/>
We've also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/tvos-17-4-homeos-mention/">seen references to homeOS</a> in tvOS 17.4, but it's not yet clear what homeOS is.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 17.4 is expected to see a release in March alongside iOS 17.4.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/tvos-17-4-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.4 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-4-to-developers.2419355/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Shares Overview of Vision Pro&#039;s Privacy and Security Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-vision-pro-privacy-and-security-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-overview-of-vision-pros-privacy-and-security-features.2419334/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:48:07 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-vision-pro-privacy-and-security-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		<category>Apple Privacy</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the launch of the Vision Pro, Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/privacy/docs/Apple_Vision_Pro_Privacy_Overview.pdf">shared a new document</a> outlining various privacy and security measures for the headset.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Privacy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936140" /><br/>
An overview of some of the Vision Pro's privacy policies, according to Apple:<ul><li>Where you look before you interact with content is not shared with Apple or the apps you are using, and does not leave the device.</li><br/>
<li>Apps you use cannot access information about your surroundings by default.</li><br/>
<li>visionOS does not share information about who may be physically nearby with the apps and websites that you use, or with Apple.</li><br/>
<li>Personas are generated entirely on-device, and associated data is encrypted.</li><br/>
<li>Optic ID data for iris authentication is encrypted and never leaves the device.</li><br/>
<li>You can limit the apps that someone else can interact with in Guest User mode to just those currently visible.</li></ul>More details are available in <a href="https://www.apple.com/privacy/docs/Apple_Vision_Pro_Privacy_Overview.pdf">Apple's document</a>, shared earlier <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/02/13/apple-vision-pro-privacy/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple privacy features available on visionOS include App Tracking Transparency, Advanced Data Protection, iCloud Private Relay, Hide My Email, and more. iMessage Contact Key Verification was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/vision-pro-imessage-contact-key-verification/">added in the visionOS 1.1 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro launched in the U.S. earlier this month, and Apple said it plans to release the headset in additional countries later this year.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-privacy/">Apple Privacy</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/apple-vision-pro-privacy-and-security-features/">Apple Shares Overview of Vision Pro&#039;s Privacy and Security Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-shares-overview-of-vision-pros-privacy-and-security-features.2419334/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Takes &#36;90 Off Large Collection of Apple Watch Series 9 Models, Starting at &#36;309</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/best-buy-takes-90-off-apple-watch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-90-off-large-collection-of-apple-watch-series-9-models-starting-at-309.2419332/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 07:18:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/best-buy-takes-90-off-apple-watch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy recently opened up <a href="https://howl.me/clunu1dvWgW">a new Apple Watch sale</a>, and in it you can get the 41mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://howl.me/clyFscY8CSo"><strong>&#36;309.00</strong></a> in all aluminum colors, down from &#36;399.00. These deals will only last for the remainder of today, so if you've been waiting for great Apple Watch deals, now is the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/apple-watch-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-930418" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 45mm GPS Apple Watch Series 9 for <a href="https://howl.me/clCSlnQ3Uf2"><strong>&#36;339.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;429.00. Both of these deals are solid second-best prices that are just &#36;10 higher when compared to their previous all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clyFscY8CSo"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;309.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/clCSlnQ3Uf2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;339.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy has every aluminum model of the GPS Apple Watch Series 9 on sale, so you can get the Starlight, Pink, Midnight, Silver, and PRODUCT(RED) colors on sale at these record low prices. This also includes both S/M and M/L band sizes.<br/>
<br/>
Best Buy also has cellular models of the Apple Watch Series 9 at best-ever prices. You can get the 41mm Cellular model for <a href="https://howl.me/clCSmJRGjPH"><strong>&#36;409.00</strong></a> and the 45mm Cellular model for <a href="https://howl.me/clyFvAK7DJA"><strong>&#36;439.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;90 markdowns. Stock on cellular models is much more strained, so you'll only find a few aluminum colors on sale at these prices.<br/>
<br/>
As of last month, a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/17/apple-watch-sales-ban-reinstated/">sales ban was reenacted</a> in the United States on any Apple Watch model sold by Apple that has blood oxygen sensing. While Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch Ultra 2 models purchased directly from Apple currently come with blood oxygen sensing disabled, retailers like Best Buy are able to continue selling through their existing stocks that include the feature.<br/>
<br/>
If you are looking for cheaper Apple Watches, you can also get the Apple Watch SE on sale at Best Buy, all of which are at &#36;60 off. The 40mm GPS model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clCR9B9mui9"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a>, the 44mm GPS model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clCSfvk0ZUD"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a>, the 40mm cellular model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clCSggfrO9d"><strong>&#36;239.00</strong></a>, and the 44mm cellular model is available for <a href="https://howl.me/clCSgFaNYsz"><strong>&#36;269.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/best-buy-takes-90-off-apple-watch/">Best Buy Takes &#36;90 Off Large Collection of Apple Watch Series 9 Models, Starting at &#36;309</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-takes-90-off-large-collection-of-apple-watch-series-9-models-starting-at-309.2419332/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s iMessage Avoids EU&#039;s Digital Markets Act Regulation</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/imessage-avoids-eu-regulation/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-imessage-avoids-eus-digital-markets-act-regulation.2419320/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 04:07:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/imessage-avoids-eu-regulation/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMessage</category>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's iMessage will avoid regulation requiring interoperability with other messaging platforms under the EU's Digital Markets Act (DMA), following the conclusion of an investigation by the regulator (via <em><em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-13/apple-imessage-microsoft-bing-dodge-eu-s-big-tech-crackdown">Bloomberg</a></em></em>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/General-Apps-Messages.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-808613" /><br/>
The probe concluded that the iMessage platform and Microsoft's Bing do not hold a dominant enough position to be brought under the DMA's strict rules for services provided by big tech's so-called digital "gatekeepers," which include Apple, Meta, Google, Amazon, and TikTok, according to the EU.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Microsoft said they welcomed the decision to not designate them as core platform services in separate statements following the announcement. <br/>
<br/>
The EU has been working on legislation under the DMA that would have required Apple to make changes to iMessage to make it available on other platforms. The interoperability rules would have meant that Meta apps like WhatsApp or Messenger could request to interoperate with Apple's iMessage framework, and Apple would have been forced to comply within the EU. <br/>
<br/>
However, the EU probe found that iMessage falls outside the legislation because it is not widely used by businesses. The reprieve for Apple is part of a five-month market investigation by the European Commission. <br/>
<br/>
Despite the investigation's conclusion into iMessage, the DMA is still forcing Apple to make major changes to its app ecosystem in the European Union. For example, in iOS 17.4, due later next month, Apple is implementing updates that will allow <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> users to download and install apps outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-alternative-app-marketplaces-eu/">alternative app marketplaces</a>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/imessage/">iMessage</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/imessage-avoids-eu-regulation/">Apple&#039;s iMessage Avoids EU&#039;s Digital Markets Act Regulation</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-imessage-avoids-eus-digital-markets-act-regulation.2419320/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Peloton Is Dropping Apple Watch GymKit Support</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/peloton-losing-apple-watch-gymkit-support/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/peloton-is-dropping-apple-watch-gymkit-support.2419319/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:56:35 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/peloton-losing-apple-watch-gymkit-support/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>GymKit</category>
		<category>Peloton</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Peloton is dropping support for Apple GymKit in favor of Peloton One-Tap tracking, the fitness equipment company revealed to users in an email on Monday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/09/peloton-bike-plus-treadmill-gymkit.jpg" alt="" width="921" height="457" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-757966" /><br/>
The change is most likely to irk existing Bike+ owners who originally purchased the &#36;2,495 stationary workout bike based on the premise that GymKit was an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/09/08/peloton-announces-bike-gymkit-support/">exclusive perk</a>. While GymKit has become less important since Peloton rolled out Apple Watch integration to all its fitness equipment in 2022, GymKit offered additional integration with Apple Health that isn't available with Peloton's solution.<br/>
<br/>
Peloton's app does most of the things that GymKit offers, including tracking things like distance, pace, and heart rate metrics, and showing them live on Peloton screens. Only a subset of that data will, however, now sync to Apple Health in the absence of GymKit support.<br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced GymKit as part of watchOS 4.1, which was released back in October 2017.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update</b>: As <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/posts/32935433">noted</a> by forum member Eradik and <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/pelotoncycle/comments/1ape43k/apple_gymkit_no_longer_supported_as_of_227/">others on Reddit,</a> Peloton's app syncs only basic data to Apple Health. Data like cadence and average speed and power are not synced, meaning that the loss of GymKit support may have a substantial impact for some users.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/gymkit/">GymKit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/peloton/">Peloton</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/peloton-losing-apple-watch-gymkit-support/">Peloton Is Dropping Apple Watch GymKit Support</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/peloton-is-dropping-apple-watch-gymkit-support.2419319/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Video&#039;s Ads Tier Loses Dolby Vision HDR and Dolby Atmos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/amazon-prime-video-dolby-vision-atmos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-videos-ads-tier-loses-dolby-vision-hdr-and-dolby-atmos.2419316/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 03:23:37 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/amazon-prime-video-dolby-vision-atmos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Amazon Prime Video</category>
		<category>Amazon Prime</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon Prime Video content no longer includes Dolby Vision HDR or Dolby Atmos surround sound on its ads-supported tier, which is included in all Amazon Prime memberships.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Amazon-Prime-Video-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936178" /><br/>
The news was first reported by German website <em><a href="https://www.4kfilme.de/amazon-prime-video-entfernt-dolby-atmos-und-dolby-vision-im-werbefinanzierten-abo/#google_vignette">4KFilme</a></em> and picked up by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/24071417/amazon-prime-video-no-dolby-vision-atmos">The Verge</a></em>. Instead of the higher fidelity options previously enjoyed for no additional fee, Prime Video is streaming in HDR10 with Dolby Digital 5.1. <br/>
<br/>
That is, unless you pay &#36;2.99 extra for Prime Video's ad-free service, in which case you can retain the higher quality audio experience. The change was confirmed to <em>The Verge</em> by Amazon. <br/>
<br/>
"Dolby Vision and Dolby Atmos capabilities are only available on the ad free option, on relevant titles," said an Amazon spokesperson.<br/>
<br/>
Most Prime Video viewers will be Amazon Prime members, which costs &#36;14.99 per month, or &#36;139 per year if you pay annually. Prime Video is also available as a &#36;9.99-per-month standalone subscription, or &#36;12.99-per-month if you add on the Dolby Vision HDR or Dolby Atmos surround sound surcharge. Ads were introduced across basic Prime Video subscriptions in the United States on January 29.<br/>
<br/>
For comparison, Disney+ costs &#36;9.99 with ads, while Netflix can be had for &#36;6.99 per month with ads, although content is streamed in 1080p. Meanwhile, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> membership costs &#36;9.99, up from the previous &#36;6.99. Apple introduced the increase on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/25/apple-services-price-increases/">October 25</a>, but there are no limits on streaming quality.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon-prime-video/">Amazon Prime Video</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon-prime/">Amazon Prime</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/13/amazon-prime-video-dolby-vision-atmos/">Amazon Prime Video&#039;s Ads Tier Loses Dolby Vision HDR and Dolby Atmos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-videos-ads-tier-loses-dolby-vision-hdr-and-dolby-atmos.2419316/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
