<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:03:22 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17 Launching Tomorrow for iPhones With These 10 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-for-iphones-with-these-10-new-features.2402541/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 12:35:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In June, Apple announced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> with a wide range of new features and changes for the iPhone. Following over three months of beta testing, the free software update will be released this Monday, September 18 for the iPhone XS and newer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-and-iPhones-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1372" height="773" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898529" /><br/>
Below, we have recapped 10 key features coming to the iPhone with iOS 17, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-features-coming-later-this-year/">additional features coming later this year</a>. The update should be released to users around 10 a.m. Pacific Time / 1 p.m. Eastern Time on Monday, and once it is available, it can be installed from the Settings app under General → Software Update.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>StandBy</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/StandBy-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898860" /><br/>
StandBy is a new full-screen view that provides glanceable information designed to be viewed from a distance when an iPhone is on its side and charging, according to Apple. The customizable interface can show a clock in various styles, a calendar, favorite photos, the weather forecast, music playback controls, widgets, and more.  <br/>
<br/>
StandBy is designed for an iPhone charging on a nightstand, kitchen counter, or desk, and it supports Live Activities, Siri, incoming calls, and larger notifications. The feature also works with the iPhone 14 Pro's always-on display.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Contact Posters</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Contact-Posters-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1828" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898862" /><br/>
iOS 17 lets users create a personalized Contact Poster that appears during an incoming phone call on another person's iPhone. The poster can include a photo or Memoji, and the font and background color can also be customized. The feature is available in the built-in Phone app and will also be available for third-party calling apps.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>NameDrop</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/namedrop.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898310" /><br/>
NameDrop allows users to easily share contact information by bringing their iPhones close together. Both individuals can choose the specific phone numbers or email addresses they would like to share, and can also share their Contact Posters.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Live Voicemail</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Live-Voicemail-iOS-17.jpg" alt="" width="1306" height="793" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898863" /><br/>
Live Voicemail provides real-time transcription on the screen as someone leaves a voicemail. If the user considers the voicemail to be important, they can pick up the call while the caller is leaving their message. Apple says calls identified as spam by carriers are not transcribed and will instead be instantly declined.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Swipe to Reply in iMessage</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iMessage-Swipe-to-Reply.jpg" alt="" width="1330" height="794" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898868" /><br/>
In the Messages app, users can now swipe to the right on any message to send an inline reply.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Interactive Widgets</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Interactive-Widgets.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898611" /><br/>
Interactive widgets are now available on the iPhone across the Home Screen, Lock Screen, and the new StandBy view. Apple gave some examples of what interactive widgets can be used for, including marking a reminder as completed, playing or pausing a song or podcast, and controlling accessories in the Home app, and there will be many more possibilities as third-party apps are updated with support in the coming months.<br/>
<br/>
Home Screen widgets offered limited functionality until now, as Apple did not allow developers to include scrolling, buttons, or animations.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Improved Autocorrect</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Autocorrect-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="638" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898562" /><br/>
Apple says iOS 17 includes a state-of-the-art language model for word prediction that will greatly improve autocorrection on the iPhone. When typing, on-device machine learning will intelligently correct mistakes with greater accuracy than ever before. In addition, users will now receive predictive text recommendations inline as they type, allowing for words or complete sentences to be added by tapping the space bar.<br/>
<br/>
Autocorrection has an updated design on iOS 17 that briefly underlines an autocorrected word. Tapping on an underlined word reveals the original word typed, making it easy to quickly revert the change. The system will also learn the user's typing habits over time and avoid some corrections, which Apple's software engineering chief Craig Federighi said is designed for "those moments where you just want to type a ducking word."<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Maps Offline</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Maps-Offline.jpg" alt="" width="1324" height="956" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898866" /><br/>
Apple Maps is catching up on a key Google Maps feature on iOS 17 with the ability to download maps for offline use. Apple says users can download a specific map area and access turn-by-turn navigation, view their estimated time of arrival, find places, and more when an iPhone is not connected to a cellular or Wi-Fi network.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Stickers Drawer</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Sticker-Drawer.jpg" alt="" width="2770" height="1628" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898869" /><br/>
A new stickers drawer on iOS 17 provides access to all stickers, including Live Stickers, emoji, Memoji, and iMessage sticker packs in one place. Live Stickers can be created by touching and holding an object in a photo, such as a cat or a dog.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>"Hey Siri" Shortened to Siri</h3><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Hey-Siri-vs-Siri.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="894" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898361" /><br/>
Apple has simplified the voice command to invoke Siri on the iPhone and other Apple devices, including the iPad, Mac, HomePod, and newest AirPods Pro. Instead of "Hey Siri," users are now simply able to say "Siri" to activate the voice assistant, and can issue multiple commands in succession without having to say "Siri" again.<br/>
<br/>
For more features, read our in-depth <strong><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17 roundup</a></strong>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-feature-list/">iOS 17 Launching Tomorrow for iPhones With These 10 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-launching-tomorrow-for-iphones-with-these-10-new-features.2402541/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Significantly Lowers Repair Fees for iPhone 15 Pro Models With Cracked Back Glass</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-significantly-lowers-repair-fees-for-iphone-15-pro-models-with-cracked-back-glass.2402536/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 11:51:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we reported last week, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-models-more-repairable/">more repairable internal design</a>, with a redesigned frame that allows for the back glass panel to be easily removed from the devices. This change was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/19/ifixit-iphone-14-teardown/">first made to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus</a> last year, and now it extends to the Pro models this year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature-White.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911430" /><br/>
At the time, we said that the removable back glass would likely result in significantly lower repair fees for iPhone 15 Pro models with cracked back glass for customers without AppleCare+ coverage, and this is now confirmed. As noted <a href="https://twitter.com/ianzelbo/status/1703439723400667246">by Ian Zelbo</a>, Apple has <a href="https://support.apple.com/iphone/repair">updated its U.S. website</a> with iPhone 15 repair fees, revealing that it will charge &#36;169 or &#36;199 to repair the iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max with back glass damage. By comparison, these fees are set at &#36;499 or &#36;549 for the iPhone 14 Pro or iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
The lower fees were also reported <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/09/17/replacing-back-glass-iphone-15-pro/">by <em>9to5Mac</em></a>. For customers with AppleCare+ coverage for their iPhone, back glass damage can be repaired for &#36;29.<br/>
<br/>
In the U.S., Apple's battery replacement fee is set at &#36;99 for all four iPhone 15 models, which is unchanged from the iPhone 14 series. For additional iPhone 15 repair fees, such as for the rear camera or other damage, visit <a href="https://support.apple.com/iphone/repair">Apple's website</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-cracked-glass-repair-fees-lower/">Apple Significantly Lowers Repair Fees for iPhone 15 Pro Models With Cracked Back Glass</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-significantly-lowers-repair-fees-for-iphone-15-pro-models-with-cracked-back-glass.2402536/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Models Reportedly Max Out at 27W Charging Speeds Despite 35W Rumor</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-models-reportedly-max-out-at-27w-charging-speeds-despite-35w-rumor.2402528/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 10:57:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Mac Otakara</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models are capable of up to 27W peak charging speeds with an appropriate USB-C power adapter, according to <a href="https://www.macotakara.jp/iphone/entry-45309.html">Japanese blog <em>Mac Otakara</em></a>. It is unclear where the website sourced this information from, but it seems to confirm that the iPhone 15 Pro models have the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/18/iphone-14-and-14-pro-charging-speeds/">same maximum charging speeds as the iPhone 14 Pro models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
In August, <em>9to5Mac</em> reported that at least some iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/17/iphone-15-faster-charging-speeds/">could support up to 35W charging speeds</a>, but this rumor appears to be incorrect.<br/>
<br/>
Just like the iPhone 14 models, Apple says all four iPhone 15 models can charge up to 50% in around 30 minutes with a 20W or higher power adapter.<br/>
<br/>
Last year, the website ChargerLAB determined that Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MY1W2AM/A/30w-usb-c-power-adapter">30W USB-C power adapter</a> was the company's lowest-priced charger that could charge the iPhone 14 Pro models at their maximum charging speeds of up to 27W, and this will likely remain the case for the iPhone 15 Pro models. In the U.S., the adapter is priced at &#36;39 on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
Real-world tests still need to be completed, but for now it appears the 35W rumor was wrong.<br/>
<br/>
All of the new iPhone 15 models launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/macotakara-jp/">Mac Otakara</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-27w-max-charging-report/">iPhone 15 Pro Models Reportedly Max Out at 27W Charging Speeds Despite 35W Rumor</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-models-reportedly-max-out-at-27w-charging-speeds-despite-35w-rumor.2402528/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max Seeing &#039;Robust&#039; Demand, Shipping Estimates Extending Into November</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-seeing-robust-demand-shipping-estimates-extending-into-november.2402511/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 09:12:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There has been "robust" demand for the iPhone 15 Pro Max since the device became <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-preorders-now-available/">available to pre-order</a> on Friday, according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://medium.com/@mingchikuo/iphone-15%E9%A6%96%E9%80%B1%E6%9C%AB%E9%A0%90%E8%B3%BC%E8%A7%80%E5%AF%9F-thoughts-on-the-iphone-15-first-weekend-pre-order-436f33668ad6">post on Medium</a> today, Kuo said iPhone 15 Pro Max demand has outpaced iPhone 14 Pro Max demand during the equivalent period last year. However, he said demand for the iPhone 15 Pro is weaker than it was for the iPhone 14 Pro so far, which he believes could be the result of more customers choosing to buy the Pro Max model this year.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro Max exclusively features an upgraded Telephoto lens with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/">up to 5x optical zoom</a>, compared to up to 3x on the iPhone 15 Pro. In the U.S., pricing for the iPhone 15 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-pricing/">starts at &#36;1,199 for 256GB of storage</a>, with Apple no longer offering the Pro Max with 128GB of storage for &#36;1,099 like it did in years past.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo reiterated that the iPhone 15 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/30/kuo-iphone-15-colors-and-more/">entered mass production later</a> than the other devices in the iPhone 15 series, which has contributed to the device's lengthy shipping delays. In the U.S., some configurations of the iPhone 15 Pro Max are currently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/">estimated for delivery in November</a> on Apple's online store. He said the Pro Max continues to face production challenges that are "more pronounced" than they are for the other models.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes that demand for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus has been "roughly on par" with the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus after the same amount of time.<br/>
<br/>
All four iPhone 15 models will launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-robust-demand/">Kuo: iPhone 15 Pro Max Seeing &#039;Robust&#039; Demand, Shipping Estimates Extending Into November</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-iphone-15-pro-max-seeing-robust-demand-shipping-estimates-extending-into-november.2402511/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: When to Expect USB-C AirPods Max, Magic Mouse, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-magic-mouse-and-more.2402498/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 06:58:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While all four iPhone 15 models are equipped with a USB-C port, Apple continues to sell a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/">handful of products with Lightning</a>. In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-09-17/apple-s-watch-series-9-iphone-15-will-hold-it-over-until-vision-pro-ai-in-2024-lmngtodu">"Power On" newsletter today</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman outlined when some of these products will move to USB-C.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Dark-Red-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877636" /><br/>
First, Gurman said he expects USB-C versions of the Magic Mouse, Magic Trackpad, and Magic Keyboard to be released alongside the next iMac.<br/>
<br/>
Second, he said the standard AirPods should be updated with a USB-C charging case <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/usb-c-airpods-and-airpods-max-2024/">in 2024</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Third, he said the next AirPods Max will be equipped with a USB-C port, but he did not provide a release timeframe for the over-ear headphones. He previously reported that the AirPods Max could be updated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/08/usb-c-airpods-and-airpods-max-2024/">as early as next year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Last, he said that he expects the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger accessories to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/">return with USB-C ports eventually</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-and-more/">Gurman: When to Expect USB-C AirPods Max, Magic Mouse, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-when-to-expect-usb-c-airpods-max-magic-mouse-and-more.2402498/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger Ever Return With USB-C Ports?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-magsafe-battery-pack-and-magsafe-duo-charger-ever-return-with-usb-c-ports.2402494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 06:28:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>MagSafe</category>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>MagSafe Battery Pack</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple quietly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">discontinued the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger</a> immediately after unveiling four new iPhone 15 models with a USB-C port last week. Both accessories were equipped with a Lightning connector.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/07/magsafe-battery-pack-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2820" height="1587" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-807695" /><br/>
Apple has not commented on why the MagSafe accessories were removed from sale, but the move was not surprising given the company is transitioning away from Lightning. The big question is, will they ever return with USB-C ports?<br/>
<br/>
As noted <a href="https://daringfireball.net/linked/2023/09/16/magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo-charger">by <em>Daring Fireball</em>'s John Gruber</a>, Apple has often released battery packs months after new iPhones. Apple released Smart Battery Cases for the iPhone 6s, iPhone XR, and iPhone 11 between two and four months after each of those devices launched, while the MagSafe Battery Pack launched nine months after the iPhone 12.<br/>
<br/>
"So, maybe Apple is simply done selling the MagSafe Battery Pack," said Gruber. "But, even if they have a new USB-C version in the works, I'm not at all surprised that it wasn't released last week. Let's wait for November."<br/>
<br/>
In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2023-09-17/apple-s-watch-series-9-iphone-15-will-hold-it-over-until-vision-pro-ai-in-2024-lmngtodu">"Power On" newsletter today</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said he still expects USB-C versions of the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger to return "eventually." However, he said "don't hold your breath."<br/>
<br/>
In May 2022, prior to the MagSafe Battery Pack being discontinued, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said a USB-C version of the accessory would be released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/05/15/kuo-usb-c-apple-accessories/">in the "foreseeable future,"</a> but it's unclear if he still expects this to happen.<br/>
<br/>
Released in July 2021, the ‌MagSafe Battery Pack‌ was priced at &#36;99 and attaches magnetically to the back of the iPhone 12 and newer, providing hours of additional battery life. The battery pack can be recharged with a Lightning cable.<br/>
<br/>
Released in December 2020, the MagSafe Duo was a &#36;129 foldable charging mat with a MagSafe charger for iPhones and an Apple Watch charging puck.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe Battery Pack</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/will-there-be-a-usb-c-magsafe-battery-pack/">Will the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger Ever Return With USB-C Ports?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-the-magsafe-battery-pack-and-magsafe-duo-charger-ever-return-with-usb-c-ports.2402494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Likely Feels Even Lighter Than It Really Is Due to Inertia Change</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-even-lighter-than-it-really-is-due-to-inertia-change.2402485/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 05:19:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> likely feels considerably lighter than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>, not just due to the switch from stainless steel to titanium, but also a change to the device's moment of inertia, according to calculations by Dr. Drang's <a href="https://leancrew.com/all-this/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-facts-and-estimates/"><em>LeanCrew</em> blog</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Internal-Chassis.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910920" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; weighs 187g, a 9% reduction of the &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj;'s 206g weight. During its announcement, Apple highlighted that the new lightweight feel is facilitated by switching from a stainless steel frame to titanium. Those who have already spent some time with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;, including <em>MacRumors</em>' Dan Barbera, have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">noted</a> just how much lighter the device feels in the hand. Yet new analysis suggests that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; likely feels even lighter than its actual weight reduction due to a change of its moment of inertia. <br/>
<br/>
The moment of inertia, a fundamental concept in physics, measures an object's resistance to rotational motion. Its value is determined by both the amount of mass an object has and how that mass is distributed. Crucially, the further away mass is positioned from an object's axis of rotation, the greater the moment of inertia. Thus, for commonly handled objects like smartphones, this resistance to rotation plays a significant role in how weighty or light they feel during daily use.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's shift from stainless steel to titanium for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s outer band is pivotal in this change since a substantial portion of the phone's weight reduction is localized at its outer edges. Dr. Drang's analysis suggests that by minimizing mass predominantly at the perimeter, Apple achieved a reduction in the phone's moment of inertia that is more significant than would be expected from the sheer weight decrease alone.<br/>
<br/>
<blockquote>This reduction, which is more than the mass reduction, would make the iPhone 15 Pro easier to turn, and that may add to the impression that it's significantly lighter than the 14 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
[...]<br/>
<br/>
Reducing the mass at the perimeter, which the change from stainless steel to titanium has done, has definitely reduced the moment of inertia more than a uniform reduction in mass would have. And that will make the 15 Pro easier to manipulate and will contribute—at least somewhat—to the impression of lightness.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
Based on an analysis of the new phones' dimensions and assuming the mass reduction is mostly around the phone's perimeter, the moment of inertia for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; is estimated to be reduced by 14–15%. Overall this means that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; doesn't just weigh less; its design ensures that its mass is distributed in a manner that makes it resist rotational motion less strongly. This results in a device that feels more agile and nimble, giving an amplified impression of lightness.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-lighter-than-it-really/">iPhone 15 Pro Likely Feels Even Lighter Than It Really Is Due to Inertia Change</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-likely-feels-even-lighter-than-it-really-is-due-to-inertia-change.2402485/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Unlike Apple Watch, Google Will Not Repair Broken Pixel Watches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-apple-watch-google-will-not-repair-broken-pixel-watches.2402480/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 04:03:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Google</category>
		<category>Google Pixel</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Google currently offers no official repair procedure for the Pixel Watch, meaning that broken devices simply become e-waste (via <a href="https://www.theverge.com/23874281/google-pixel-watch-cracks-no-repairs-warranty"><em>The Verge</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/pixel-watch-vs-apple-watch-4.jpg" alt="" width="2560" height="1440" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-868839" /><br/>
This information was recently confirmed by Google spokesperson Bridget Starkey to <em>The Verge</em>. Starkey stated, "At this moment, we don't have any repair option for the Google Pixel Watch. If your watch is damaged, you can contact the Google Pixel Watch Customer Support Team to check your replacement options." Google Support chats add that the company "doesn't have any repair centers or service centers" for the Pixel Watch.<br/>
<br/>
The device's lack of repair options stands in contrast to Google's approach with its Pixel phones, where it partners with iFixit to ensure that spare parts and repair guides are accessible for consumers looking to mend their handsets. An independent <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/Guide/Google+Pixel+Watch+Screen+Replacement/160350">iFixit guide</a> details how to replace the Pixel Watch screen, proving that it is possible to do so. Yet users who wish to undertake such a repair are faced with the challenge of finding a replacement part. Given the Pixel Watch's limited sales compared to mainstream rivals like the Apple Watch, obtaining damaged "donor hardware" with the required intact part remains a difficult proposition.<br/>
<br/>
By comparison, Apple offers repair solutions for the Apple Watch, albeit at different costs depending on the availability of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+. For Apple Watch owners without &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+, the company cites a flat &#36;299 estimate for an Apple Watch Series 8 and &#36;499 for an Apple Watch Ultra. With &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+, this drops to &#36;69 for the Apple Watch Series 8 and &#36;79 for the Apple Watch Ultra, not including the cost of &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj; itself.<br/>
<br/>
The Pixel Watch's screen is particularly vulnerable due to its design, featuring a large glass hemisphere that can easily crack upon impact. Google's hardware warranty does not cover damage resulting from accidents, such as drops or impacts, leaving users without many options other than to simply replace the entire device with a new one. The Pixel Watch 2 is rumored to feature almost exactly the same design.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google/">Google</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/google-pixel/">Google Pixel</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/17/google-will-not-repair-pixel-watches/">Unlike Apple Watch, Google Will Not Repair Broken Pixel Watches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/unlike-apple-watch-google-will-not-repair-broken-pixel-watches.2402480/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15&#039;s USB-C Port: 4.5W Charging for Accessories, USB 3.2 Gen 2 for Pro Models, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-usb-c-port-4-5w-charging-for-accessories-usb-3-2-gen-2-for-pro-models-and-more.2402440/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 20:17:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In a <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213839">support document</a> published on Friday, Apple provided some additional details about the USB-C port found on all iPhone 15 models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Event-Still.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910412" /><br/>
First, Apple said all iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-usb-c-port-apple-watch-airpods-charging/">can charge an Apple Watch, AirPods case</a>, or other small accessories connected to the USB-C port at up to 4.5W. Apple already announced this capability, but it had not provided the wattage information.<br/>
<br/>
Second, the document reveals that the iPhone 15 Pro and Pro Max support USB 3.2 Gen 2 for data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps. Apple had already revealed that the devices support USB 3, but the exact specification is now confirmed. The USB-C cable included with iPhone 15 Pro models supports USB 2 speeds, so a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MU883AM/A/thunderbolt-4-usb%E2%80%91c-pro-cable-1-m">higher-spec cable</a> is needed for faster speeds. <br/>
<br/>
As we previously reported, the document indicates that all iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/">support DisplayPort</a> for up to 4K HDR video mirroring to an external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable, or an adapter. However, unlike select iPad models with Stage Manager, the iPhone lacks an extended display mode.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro models also support recording ProRes video <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-external-storage-prores/">directly to an external storage device</a>, at up to 4K and 60 frames per second.<br/>
<br/>
To connect an iPhone 15 to a vehicle with a USB-A port for wired CarPlay usage, Apple says customers can use a USB-C to USB-A cable.<br/>
<br/>
Additional information is outlined in the <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT213839">support document</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/iphone-15-usb-c-port-details/">iPhone 15&#039;s USB-C Port: 4.5W Charging for Accessories, USB 3.2 Gen 2 for Pro Models, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15s-usb-c-port-4-5w-charging-for-accessories-usb-3-2-gen-2-for-pro-models-and-more.2402440/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Event Recap With iPhone 15, New Apple Watches, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-recap-with-iphone-15-new-apple-watches-and-more.2402352/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[What a week! Things are finally beginning to settle down after a flurry of announcements at Tuesday's event involving the usual suspects of iPhone and Apple Watch. All of the new hardware is now available to order, with launches happening next Friday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/top-stories-16sep2023-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911682" /><br/>
Don't forget about Apple's software updates, with iOS 17, watchOS 10, and tvOS 17 all coming on Monday and macOS Sonoma debuting on September 26. Read on below for all the details on the biggest announcements from this week's event!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything Announced at Apple's Event in Six Minutes</h2><br/>
Apple hosted its annual iPhone event this week, and it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">packed with announcements as usual</a>. New products unveiled include the iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15 Pro Max, Apple Watch Series 9, Apple Watch Ultra 2, and USB-C AirPods Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Everything-Announced-at-Apples-Wonderlust-Event-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910543" /><br/>
There are also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/every-iphone-15-case/">new iPhone cases</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/every-apple-watch-band-2023/">Apple Watch bands</a> with a "FineWoven" material instead of leather, wired EarPods with a USB-C connector, and several other new accessories, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">check out our recap of everything announced at Apple's event</a> to learn more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iPhone 15 Pro With Titanium Design, Action Button, A17 Pro Chip, and More</h2><br/>
As widely expected, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro models</a> are equipped with a USB-C port instead of Lightning, providing users with a more universal charging standard and faster data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Lineup-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911423" /><br/>
Other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">new features for the Pro models</a> include a lightweight titanium frame, the A17 Pro chip, a customizable Action button, slimmer bezels around the screen, Wi-Fi 6E support, increased RAM, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus With USB-C Port, Dynamic Island, and More</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">lower-end iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a> models also feature a USB-C port, and the Dynamic Island first added to iPhone 14 Pro models last year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Colors-pink.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911680" /><br/>
Other <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">new features for the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus</a> include an upgraded 48-megapixel main camera lens with a new 2x Telephoto zoom option, the A16 Bionic chip, a frosted glass back, brighter displays, a second-generation Ultra Wideband chip, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Series 9 Unveiled With S9 Chip, 'Double Tap' Gesture, and More</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-unveiled/">next-generation Apple Watch Series 9 is official</a>, with new features including a faster S9 chip, a "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watch without touching the screen, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-64gb-storage/">increased 64GB of storage</a>, a pink color option for the aluminum case, a brighter display, faster on-device Siri, Precision Finding for iPhone, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
For the first time, Apple said customers can choose a carbon-neutral variant of any Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Features Faster S9 Chip, Brighter Display, and More</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-apple-watch-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 is here</a>, with a handful of new features added, including the same S9 chip and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-double-tap/">Double Tap gesture</a> from the Series 9, a brighter display with peak brightness of 3,000 nits, expanded altitude range, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-feature-white.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911671" /><br/>
Unfortunately, the rumor that the Apple Watch Ultra 2 would be available in a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/01/apple-watch-ultra-2-black-titanium-rumor/">new Black Titanium finish</a> was incorrect, with only Natural Titanium offered.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Introduces Updated AirPods Pro and EarPods With USB-C and More</h2><br/>
In addition to the iPhone 15 models getting a USB-C port, Apple announced that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">second-generation AirPods Pro are now available to order with a USB-C charging case</a> for &#36;249, and the wired EarPods headphones now come in a USB-C version as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-USB-C-Port-Purple-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911676" /><br/>
On an accessory-related note, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">Apple discontinued the MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger</a>, both of which used Lightning, following the iPhone 15 event.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/sep-14-2023">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/top-stories-iphone-15-event-recap/">Top Stories: Apple Event Recap With iPhone 15, New Apple Watches, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-event-recap-with-iphone-15-new-apple-watches-and-more.2402352/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>There Is No iPhone 15 Mini: Here&#039;s Why</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/there-is-no-iphone-15-mini/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/there-is-no-iphone-15-mini-heres-why.2402241/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:50:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/there-is-no-iphone-15-mini/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> lineup noticeably lacks a model with a display size below six inches, just two years after Apple extolled the virtues of a 5.4-inch device. So why did Apple eliminate the "mini" device that some <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> customers had come to love?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/iPhone-mini-wonder-feature-yellow.jpg" alt="" width="1444" height="812" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-794050" /><br/>
Apple debuted the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12 mini</a> in 2020 following years of calls from &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; fans for the company to offer a small-screen device with the latest features. When Apple did so, it was assumed that the small form factor would persist for several years, but the device came to a seemingly premature end upon the release of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> lineup in 2022. Upon the release of the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; lineup, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-iphone-13-mini/">retired the last remaining device</a> with the "mini" form factor.<br/>
<br/>
Concerns first arose when the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; appeared to not be selling as well as Apple had hoped, making up just six percent of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12</a> sales in the U.S. in October and November 2020, according to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/05/iphone-12-mini-sales-lackluster-cirp/">data gathered by Consumer Intelligence Research Partners</a> (CIRP). <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/09/iphone-12-mini-low-january-sales/">Counterpoint Research</a> reported that the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; accounted for only five percent of all &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; sales in the U.S. in the first half of January 2021.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/20/production-shifting-from-iphone-12-mini-to-pro/">Morgan Stanley believed</a> that Apple chose to cut production of the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; by two million units to create more manufacturing capacity for the more popular &zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; Pro. This was mirrored by a Taiwanese report, citing supply chain sources, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/01/22/poor-iphone-12-mini-sales-supply-chain/">said</a> that strong demand for ‌&zwnj;iPhone 12&zwnj; Pro‌ models in China led Apple to increase its supply of the more expensive devices.<br/>
<br/>
Most strikingly, JP Morgan Chase <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/09/iphone-12-mini-low-january-sales/">claimed</a> that Apple outright halted &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; production in the second quarter of 2021. While the sales reports for the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; did not bode well for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> mini, Apple plans its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; production and supply chain operations well in advance of launch, meaning that the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini was already well on the way to production by the time the issues with the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj;'s sales were clear.<br/>
<br/>
In April 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/21/iphone-13-mini-unpopular-march-quarter/">CIRP released more data</a> suggesting that the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini accounted for just 3 percent of &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; sales – half that of the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj;. These continued poor sales were likely the main reason behind the demise of the "mini" form factor &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
With the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; lineup, Apple opted to replace the "mini" device with an all-new "Plus" device that matched the 6.7-inch display size of its high-end "Pro Max" models. In some respects, the "Plus" mirrors the "mini," offering the latest &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s features in a different display size. Instead of offering a lightweight small-screen option, customers can now choose an even bigger battery and 6.7-inch display – the same size that "Pro Max" customers have been used to for over five years, now at a price of &#36;1,199 – but at a much more accessible &#36;899 price point.<br/>
<br/>
Less than a week after the launch of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/12/kuo-iphone-14-plus-worse-than-iphone-13-mini/">demand for the two devices was "lackluster,"</a> with worse pre-order results than the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> and the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini. He went as far as to claim that "Apple's product segmentation strategy for standard models fails this year" and Apple was believed to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/28/apple-reverses-iphone-14-plan-boost-production/">shelved plans</a> to increase production of the two devices. Display analyst Ross Young said panel orders for the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/30/more-signs-of-low-iphone-14-demand-emerge/">were down 38 percent</a> versus the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj;‌ at the same time last year, while in the resale market, the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/30/more-signs-of-low-iphone-14-demand-emerge/">lost their value twice as fast</a> as the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini and &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; from the previous year.<br/>
<br/>
Other reports from the likes of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/13/iphone-14-plus-sales-lower-than-expected/"><em>DigiTimes</em></a> overwhelmingly presented the same picture of low &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus sales, to the extent that Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/20/apple-slashes-iphone-14-plus-orders/">forced to slash production</a>, suggesting that the low sales of the &zwnj;iPhone 12 mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; mini may not have been caused by the device's size after all. Whether the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus will fare better is yet to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
There are no plans to revive the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s "mini" form factor in Apple's pipeline, according to rumors. The smallest iPhones in the works, such as next year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and the fourth-generation &zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj;, are expected to feature 6.1-inch displays. On the contrary, some future devices, such as the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max, are expected to grow even larger, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/12/larger-displays-exclusive-iphone-16-pro/">increasing to 6.3- and 6.9-inches</a>, respectively.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/there-is-no-iphone-15-mini/">There Is No iPhone 15 Mini: Here&#039;s Why</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/there-is-no-iphone-15-mini-heres-why.2402241/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Developers Working With Apple to Bring iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Console Games to the iPad and Mac</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/devs-working-to-bring-console-games-to-ipad-mac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-working-with-apple-to-bring-iphone-15-pros-console-games-to-the-ipad-and-mac.2402227/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 03:31:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/devs-working-to-bring-console-games-to-ipad-mac/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Developers are working with Apple to bring the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>'s console games to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and Mac, Apple executives told <em>IGN</em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Mac-Gaming.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-899793" /><br/>
In a new <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/apple-iphone-15-pro-gaming-interview">interview</a>, Jeremy Sandmel, Apple's Senior Director of GPU Software, and Tim Millet, Apple's VP of Platform Architecture, discussed the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;'s more advanced gaming capabilities. During the announcement of the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, Apple highlighted how the A17 Pro chip features a brand new GPU with hardware-accelerated ray tracing, enabling console games like "Resident Evil 4" and "Assassin's Creed: Mirage" to be played on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Asked if these new games will be compatible with Apple silicon iPads and Macs, Millet said that "The developers are going to work with us to do it." Sandmel added:<blockquote>...one of the things that fundamentally enabled that is this unification of the architecture of Apple Silicon and the iPhone Silicon and the iPad Silicon. And so you can see that they're able to do exactly what you just suggested, which is bring a game to iPhone and Mac that is the same game. It's the same rendering, it's the same rendering quality and it's the same game they had on a gaming PC and a console.<br/>
<br/>
So we really look at these many generations of SoC architecture across the phone, across the iPad, across now, Apple Silicon Macs. And we'd see that as part of one big unified platform, a graphics and gaming platform in particular.</blockquote>Since these console games are purportedly enabled by the hardware advancements of the A17 Pro, Apple's first chip fabricated with TSMC's 3-nanometer process, it seems possible that Apple is alluding to next-generation iPads and Macs with M3 chips here.<br/>
<br/>
DisplayPort support is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/">built into the USB-C port</a> on all <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, meaning that the devices can output video at up to 4K/60Hz natively to a DisplayPort-equipped external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable. On previous iPhones with a Lightning port, video mirroring is limited to 1080p with Apple's Lightning-to-HDMI or Lightning-to-VGA adapters.<br/>
<br/>
Asked if, given the device's DisplayPort capabilities, &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; owners would be be able to play the likes of Resident Evil 4 on an external display, Sandmel replied:<blockquote>As you probably know, there's the display resolution and then there's the gaming resolution, and then the frame rates, the game rendering. With technologies like MetalFX's upscaling, we can sort of separate those two things. The game can run at really high frame rates, get really great quality results, and then upscale whatever resolution the display, whether that's the iPhone display, whether that's an external display. So yes, the iPhone can connect to these 4K displays, and it can drive them externally doing whatever you do on the phone, including gaming to these other displays. The resolution and frame rate are going to highly depend on what the game's actually doing.</blockquote>The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; does not yet offer a dedicated extended display mode, but it is possible to mirror an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to an external display via a wired connection, as well as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a>. See <em>IGN</em>'s <a href="https://www.ign.com/articles/apple-iphone-15-pro-gaming-interview">full interview</a> for more information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/devs-working-to-bring-console-games-to-ipad-mac/">Developers Working With Apple to Bring iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Console Games to the iPad and Mac</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/developers-working-with-apple-to-bring-iphone-15-pros-console-games-to-the-ipad-and-mac.2402227/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Cameras to Support Spatial Video Later This Year, But Key Questions Remain</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/apple-iphone-15-pro-spatial-video-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-cameras-to-support-spatial-video-later-this-year-but-key-questions-remain.2402182/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 02:18:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/apple-iphone-15-pro-spatial-video-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>September 2023 Apple Event</category>
		<category>spatial video</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[During Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">"Wonderlust" event</a> earlier this week, Apple claimed that the ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌ camera system "pushes the limits of what you can capture with a smartphone." It was a reference to the device's support for "spatial computing video," but the mention was brief and lacking detail.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-iphone-15-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911686" /><br/>
For those who missed it, spatial video is Apple's name for what is essentially 3D video. The iPhone 15 Pro is able to record spatial videos natively by combining video captured by the sensors of the Main and Ultra Wide cameras, which results in something akin to stereoscopic video.<br/>
<br/>
This 3D video can then be played back using Apple's "spatial computing" Vision Pro headset when it's released early next year, allowing users to relive these memories in a fully immersive way. Apple didn't say, but presumably the iPhone 15 Pro can also capture spatial photo stills using similar camera processing.<br/>
<br/>
Other questions remain that Apple's senior VP of worldwide marketing Greg "Joz" Joswiak didn't answer during his whirlwind tour of the iPhone 15 Pro's new camera capabilities, which include the ability to record 4K ProRes video at 60 frames per second, as well as 5x optical zoom on the iPhone 15 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
It's not clear for example what kind of unique file format these spatial videos will use, nor did Apple mention how large they will be. Presumably, iPhone 15 Pro users will need to select a special new mode in the Camera app to capture spatial video. How these videos will be saved in the Photos app, and whether they will be playable on the iPhone in any way, is also unknown.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will undoubtedly reveal the answers to these questions soon enough. The ability to shoot spatial video using an iPhone 15 Pro isn't available yet, but it's "coming later this year," according to the company.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2023-apple-event/">September 2023 Apple Event</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spatial-video/">spatial video</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/16/apple-iphone-15-pro-spatial-video-vision-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro Cameras to Support Spatial Video Later This Year, But Key Questions Remain</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-cameras-to-support-spatial-video-later-this-year-but-key-questions-remain.2402182/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Goldman Sachs Overhauls Apple Savings Procedures to Cut Down on Withdrawal Delays</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/goldman-sachs-apple-savings-overhaul/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/goldman-sachs-overhauls-apple-savings-procedures-to-cut-down-on-withdrawal-delays.2402045/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 14:38:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/goldman-sachs-apple-savings-overhaul/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple Savings account partner Goldman Sachs has changed its system to prevent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> customers from running into extended delays when attempting to withdraw money, reports <em><a href="https://www.theinformation.com/articles/goldman-makes-adjustments-to-fix-apple-savings-account-problems">The Information</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/apple-card-savings-account-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-892213" /><br/>
When the Apple Savings account launched earlier this year, there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/01/apple-savings-money-withdrawal-issues/">were complaints from customers</a> who had long wait times when trying to withdraw money from their accounts. Some people had to wait weeks for money transfers, and in some cases, money disappeared between banks. Goldman Sachs at the time said that the transfers were delayed because of security flags that were meant to help protect user accounts.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs has since adjusted its system to make it less likely to flag legitimate customer withdrawal requests as problematic. According to <em>The Information</em>, when a customer with a large amount of money attempts to move a small portion of their cash to an outside account, Goldman Sachs will be less likely to flag the transaction.<br/>
<br/>
There is also now a cap on the number of days that a withdrawal should take, and Goldman Sachs is prioritizing communication with customers who have flagged transactions to ensure the communication issues that occurred earlier this year do not repeat.<br/>
<br/>
Goldman Sachs in July provided <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/17/apple-goldman-sachs-savings-customer-credit/">one-time &#36;100 credits</a> to customers who had experienced poor customer service as a gesture of good will.<br/>
<br/>
The Apple Savings account has been offered since April, and it is available solely to &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; holders. The account has a 4.15 percent interest rate on Daily Cash and other deposits.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/goldman-sachs-apple-savings-overhaul/">Goldman Sachs Overhauls Apple Savings Procedures to Cut Down on Withdrawal Delays</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/goldman-sachs-overhauls-apple-savings-procedures-to-cut-down-on-withdrawal-delays.2402045/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Card Promo Offers 10% Daily Cash Back on Gas and Electric Vehicle Charging</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-card-gas-promo/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-promo-offers-10-daily-cash-back-on-gas-and-electric-vehicle-charging.2402039/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:57:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-card-gas-promo/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> promotion provides select &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; users with 10 percent total Daily Cash on gas and electric vehicle charging. The bonus can be collected on up to &#36;6,000 worth of gas or charging, for a total reward of &#36;600.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/apple-daily-cash-back.jpg" alt="" width="1177" height="662" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911651" /><br/>
&zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; holders can pay for gas and charging with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-pay/">Apple Pay</a>, a virtual card number in apps, or the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; in person to get the extra cash back reward. <br/>
<br/>
Apple is offering the promotion through October 5. Details can be found in the Daily Cash hub in the Wallet app for those who are eligible.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-card-gas-promo/">Apple Card Promo Offers 10% Daily Cash Back on Gas and Electric Vehicle Charging</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-card-promo-offers-10-daily-cash-back-on-gas-and-electric-vehicle-charging.2402039/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Pre-Orders Now &#039;Preparing to Ship&#039; Ahead of September 22 Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-15-preorders-preparing-to-ship/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-now-preparing-to-ship-ahead-of-september-22-launch.2402035/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:36:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-15-preorders-preparing-to-ship/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this morning began accepting pre-orders for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max, and now just hours later, the first orders have moved into the "preparing to ship" phase as Apple prepares to send the new iPhones out to customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-preparing-to-ship.jpg" alt="" width="1901" height="1069" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911633" /><br/>
Customers in the United States should soon be able to begin tracking their orders through <a href="https://www.ups.com/us/en/track/ups-my-choice.page">the UPS My Choice feature</a>, or through the UPS website <a href="https://www.ups.com/track?loc=en_US&amp;requester=ST/">using a reference number</a> like a phone number or the Apple order number. Orders typically ship from China and Apple does not change the shipping status until they are scanned into a central distribution hub in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> shipments will begin arriving to customers on Friday, September 22. As with every new product release, Apple users in Australia and New Zealand will be the first to get their orders due to time zone differences.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-pro-shipping-estimates-october/">began selling out</a> within an hour after pre-orders went live this morning, and orders for some colors and capacities are now delayed until October or November. Some locations may still have pre-order stock available for in-store pickup, and those who were not able to place a pre-order in time may be able to just go to the store on launch day to pick up a new device, as Apple often has extra stock for in-store purchases.<br/>
<br/>
Cases and accessories are expected to arrive before the new iPhones and have already begun shipping out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15-Pro">iPhone 15 Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-iphone-15-preorders-preparing-to-ship/">Some iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro Pre-Orders Now &#039;Preparing to Ship&#039; Ahead of September 22 Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-iphone-15-and-iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-now-preparing-to-ship-ahead-of-september-22-launch.2402035/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Latest Transparency Report Includes Geofence Requests From U.S. Government</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-transparency-report-geofence-requests/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-latest-transparency-report-includes-geofence-requests-from-u-s-government.2402030/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:20:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-transparency-report-geofence-requests/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared a new <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/transparency/pdf/requests-2022-H1-en.pdf">Transparency Report</a> providing information on customer data requests that the company received from the U.S. government in the first half of 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/01/apple-logo-us-flag-smooth.jpg" alt="" width="940" height="552" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-833045" /><br/>
For the first time ever, Apple has reported the total number of "geofence requests" that it received from the U.S. government. These requests are meant to include specific latitude and longitudes coordinates for a specified time period, but Apple does not collect this information as part of its commitment to customer privacy, and therefore does not provide it to law enforcement, while fully respecting the legal process.<br/>
<br/>
From the Transparency Report:<blockquote>Apple may also receive requests from government agencies seeking customer data related to specific latitude and longitudes coordinates (geofence) for a specified time period. Apple does not have any data to provide in response to geofence requests.</blockquote>For additional information, the Transparency Report is <a href="https://www.apple.com/legal/transparency/pdf/requests-2022-H1-en.pdf">available on Apple's website</a> as a PDF.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-transparency-report-geofence-requests/">Apple&#039;s Latest Transparency Report Includes Geofence Requests From U.S. Government</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-latest-transparency-report-includes-geofence-requests-from-u-s-government.2402030/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Advertised With 72-Hour Battery Life in Low Power Mode, But There&#039;s a Catch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-advertised-with-72-hour-battery-life-in-low-power-mode-but-theres-a-catch.2402020/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 12:30:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the Apple Watch Ultra 2 is <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/09/apple-unveils-apple-watch-ultra-2/">advertised</a> with up to 72 hours of battery life in Low Power Mode, compared to 60 hours for the original Ultra model, there is a catch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-230912.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910333" /><br/>
According to fine print on Apple's website, the testing parameters for the Ultra 2 in Low Power Mode were different than those for the original Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
The fine print for the original Apple Watch Ultra said:<blockquote>Multi-day adventure battery life is based on the following use while in Low Power Mode and with workout settings enabled for fewer GPS and heart rate readings: 15 hours of hiking workout, over 600 time checks, 35 minutes of app use, 3 minutes of talk, and 15 hours of sleep tracking, over the course of 60 hours.</blockquote>The fine print for the Apple Watch Ultra 2 says:<blockquote>Battery life in Low Power Mode is based on the following use: 360 time checks, 360 notifications, 180 minutes of app use, and two 60-minute workouts with music playback from Apple Watch via Bluetooth, over the course of 72 hours.</blockquote>Given these very different testing parameters, customers should keep in mind that the Ultra 2 does not simply offer 12 hours more battery life than the original Ultra in Low Power Mode, which is something that could be easily misconstrued.<br/>
<br/>
It's possible the original Ultra would also get around 72 hours of battery life in Low Power Mode based on the new testing parameters, but this is not proven yet.<br/>
<br/>
We've reached out to Apple with a request for comment, and we'll update this story if the company provides a response.<div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-ultra-2-low-power-mode/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Advertised With 72-Hour Battery Life in Low Power Mode, But There&#039;s a Catch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-advertised-with-72-hour-battery-life-in-low-power-mode-but-theres-a-catch.2402020/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2402003/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 11:07:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple does not list battery capacities for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-watch-series-9-unveiled/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-apple-watch-ultra-2/">Ultra 2</a> models, but <em>MacRumors</em> has discovered this information in a Chinese regulatory database today, and we have outlined our findings below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910331" /><br/>
According to the database, which only provides Apple model numbers instead of product names, the 41mm and 45mm Apple Watch Series 9 models appear to be equipped with 282 mAh and 308 mAh batteries, respectively. These capacities are unchanged compared to the equivalent Apple Watch Series 8 models, which makes sense given that Apple says the Series 9 models have the same 18-hour battery life as Series 8 models.<br/>
<br/>
As for the Apple Watch Ultra 2, it appears to be equipped with a 564 mAh battery, which is approximately 4% larger than the 542 mAh battery in the original Apple Watch Ultra. However, Apple says the Ultra 2 has the same 36-hour battery life as the original Ultra, likely due to it having a brighter display and other new features.<br/>
<br/>
A recap of the Apple Watch battery capacities listed in the database:<p><table class="comparison"><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch</th><br/>
 <th>Battery Capacity</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">282 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 8 (41mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">282 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">308 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Series 8 (45mm)</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">308 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra 2</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">564 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">Apple Watch Ultra</div></td><br/>
 <td><div class="center-wrap">542 mAh</div></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><p><br/>
New features for both the Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 include brighter displays, a faster S9 chip, a new "Double Tap" gesture for interacting with the watches without touching the screen, and more. Both new models have been available to order since Tuesday and will begin arriving to customers and launch in stores on Friday, September 22.<br/>
<br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> also found the same battery capacities for what appears to be the iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/iphone-15-battery-capacities-revealed/">were reported earlier today</a>. We were unable to find a listing for the regular iPhone 15 battery.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/apple-watch-series-9-ultra-2-battery-capacities/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Ultra 2 Battery Capacities Revealed in Regulatory Database</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-ultra-2-battery-capacities-revealed-in-regulatory-database.2402003/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 and Accessory Prize Pack From Speck and Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-and-accessory-prize-pack-from-speck-and-best-buy.2401989/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 09:51:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>No AMP</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with accessory maker <a href="https://speckproducts.com">Speck</a> and <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com">Best Buy</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and a set of cases and accessories from <a href="https://speckproducts.com">Speck</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-iphone-15-clicklock-family.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="785" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911299" /><br/>
Speck is well-known for its range of case options for Apple's iPhones, and though the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models have just been announced this week, Speck is ready with a <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">whole iPhone 15 case lineup</a> and a selection of <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/clicklock-no-slip-interlock-for-magsafe">ClickLock MagSafe grips and mounts</a> that work with the cases.<br/>
<br/>
If you're not a fan of Apple's new FineWoven cases or don't care for the color options that Apple has available, Speck has debuted <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">169 new cases</a> that are available in 17 different designs and 20 colors for all four of the new &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models. The cases are available for purchase now <a href="https://speckproducts.com/pages/search?q=iphone%2015">from Speck's website</a> and from BestBuy retail locations and <a href="https://www.bestbuy.com/">the BestBuy website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Speck has three types of cases that users can choose from, including standard (with no <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe-battery-pack/">MagSafe</a>), &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, and ClickLock for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, which works with ClickLock accessories. Prices range from &#36;25 to &#36;50, and there are options for every aesthetic. The <a href="https://speckproducts.com/products/presidio2-pro-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-pro-cases">Presido2 Pro</a>, for example, has Speck's Armor Cloud technology and protects the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> from drops as high as 13 feet while still looking stylish, plus it works with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-clicklock-clear.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1400" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911302" /><br/>
The <a href="https://speckproducts.com/products/presidio2-grip-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio2 Grip</a>, one of Speck's most popular options, has the same 13-foot drop protection while also offering no-slip inverted grips. This version is 20 percent slimmer than previous versions of the Grip case, it has &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;, and it comes in a range of color options that look great with Apple's new iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-presidio-grip-2.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1212" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911303" /><br/>
If you want protection but don't want to cover up the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s design, Speck has the <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-cases-for-2023/products/presidio-perfect-clear-grip-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio Perfect-Clear Grip MagSafe case</a> with no-slip grips, 13-foot drop protection, and stylish grooves at the sides. If you're not a fan of that no-slip look, there's also a <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-cases-for-2023/products/presidio-perfect-clear-magsafe-with-clicklock-iphone-15-cases">Presidio Perfect-Clear case</a> that has a smoother finish.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-perfect-clear-grip.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1209" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911304" /><br/>
These cases all work with ClickLock, a technology Speck has designed to prevent accidental separation of iPhones and &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; accessories by adding a magnetic interlock mechanism. Speck this week came out with three new ClickLock options that work with its cases and the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models, including the Car Vent Mount, the <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/wallet-for-magsafe-with-clicklock?variant=43285595455619">Wallet</a>, and the StandyGrip.<br/>
<br/>
Priced at &#36;30, <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/wallet-for-magsafe-with-clicklock?variant=43285595455619">Speck's MagSafe Wallet</a> is definitely a product where you want ClickLock because a wallet is the last thing you want to slip off of your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;. Available in several colors, the Wallet holds 1-3 credit, debit, or ID cards.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-iphone-15-wallet.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="1037" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911305" /><br/>
The &#36;30 <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/standygrip-for-magsafe-stand-and-grip-combo-with-clicklock">StandyGrip with MagSafe and ClickLock</a> holds the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; upright in a horizontal or vertical viewing position and it can be used to attach the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to a MacBook so it can serve as a webcam, and that's also a situation where a secure attachment is crucial.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-steadygrip.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="895" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911306" /><br/>
Speck also has the &#36;40 <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/magsafe-accessories/products/car-vent-mount-for-magsafe-with-clicklock">Car Vent Mount for MagSafe with ClickLock</a> that attaches to a car vent and has a built-in cable holder. It uses ClickLock to ensure that your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; isn't going to go flying off of the mount when you hit a bump. To see all of Speck's &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; cases and accessories, make sure to <a href="https://speckproducts.com/collections/iphone-15-iphone-15-plus-iphone-15-pro-and-iphone-15-pro-max-cases-for-2023">visit the Speck website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-car-vent-mount.jpg" alt="" width="1400" height="916" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911307" /><br/>
Speck and Best Buy, the giveaway's sponsors, are providing a 128GB &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and a selection of accessories to go with it, including a Presidio2 Grip Case, a Presidio Perfect Clear Grip Case, and a Presidio Perfect Clear Case, all of which have both &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; and ClickLock. Speck is also adding in its Wallet for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; with ClickLock, its StandyGrip for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; Stand, and its Car Vent Mount for &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; with ClickLock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/speck-bestbuy-logos.jpg" alt="" width="784" height="197" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911527" /><br/>
To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/fcVMe/speck-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Speck Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (September 15) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on September 22. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after September 22 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/macrumors-giveaway-iphone-15-speck/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win an iPhone 15 and Accessory Prize Pack From Speck and Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-an-iphone-15-and-accessory-prize-pack-from-speck-and-best-buy.2401989/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
