<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 09:00:14 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 vs. Series 10 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 10 Rumored Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-10/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-vs-series-10-buyers-guide-10-rumored-upgrades-compared.2434825/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-10&#038;post_date=1725127200/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of rumors, the Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch Ultra 3 are set to launch in just a matter of weeks. There are now 10 changes and improvements rumored to be offered by the new models, so here's everything we're expecting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Apple-Watch-Series-9-vs-Series-10-Buyers-Guide-2-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-963174" /><br/>
All of the changes the Apple Watch Series 10 are expected to feature compared to last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a> are listed below, using information from a wide range of reliable sources that we have previously covered here on <em>MacRumors</em>. We will continue to update this article as more reports emerge prior to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">"It's Glowtime" event</a> on Monday, September 9.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch Series 10</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>41mm and 45mm casing size options</td><br/>
 <td>46mm and 49mm casing size options (+11.1% and +8.9%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1.69-inch and 1.9-inch display size options</td><br/>
 <td>1.89-inch and 2.04-inch display size options (+11.8% and +7.4%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>45mm model</strong>: 38mm width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>46mm model</strong>: 39.7mm width (+4.5%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>10.7mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>11.6mm depth (+8.4%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>3D printed casing (some models only)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>S9 chip</td><br/>
 <td>S10 chip with AI enhancements</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thinner logic board</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Hypertension detection</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Sleep apnea detection</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
According to a report from <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, both the Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch Ultra 3 will apparently feature a new processor that succeeds last year's S9 chip. While this could "lay the groundwork for some AI enhancements down the road," it will not run Apple Intelligence and there are currently said to be no plans to bring "the full initiative" to the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been developing hypertension and sleep apnea detection features for the Apple Watch that were originally slated for release in 2024, but Gurman now says that the "effort hasn't gone smoothly" and "Apple has run into some serious snags." The hypertension detection feature has been insufficiently reliable during testing and there are concerns about integrating it into the refreshed design, which could force Apple to postpone this feature until next year. Likewise, while the Apple Watch Series 10 was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/17/kuo-apple-watch-series-10-larger-screen-thinner/">widely rumored</a> to tout a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">thinner design</a>, that too is now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/">in question</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Likewise, the sleep apnea detection feature is now in trouble because it relies on blood oxygen saturation, which Apple Watches in the United States cannot currently measure due to an ongoing legal dispute with Masimo. Gurman postulates that the dispute with Masimo could be resolved soon, or Apple could find a way around it by arguing that the blood oxygen sensor could be used for purposes that are not directly related to blood oxygen levels. The company could also announce the sleep apnea detection feature and hold off releasing it until a later date.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="release_date">Release Date</h3><br/>
The Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch Ultra 3 are expected to be announced at Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">"It's glowtime" event</a> on Monday, September 9. Pre-orders are likely to open on Friday, September 13, with launch following one week later on Friday, September 20.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Series 9&zwnj; was a very minor upgrade over the Series 8, with the S9 chip, Double Tap, and Precision Finding for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models being the most significant changes. The Apple Watch Series 10 could build on these with new health features and larger display size options, but it looks like current Series 9 users will have little reason to upgrade.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-9-vs-10/">Apple Watch Series 9 vs. Series 10 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 10 Rumored Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-vs-series-10-buyers-guide-10-rumored-upgrades-compared.2434825/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: September 9 iPhone Event, iOS 18.1 Photos Clean Up Tool, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/31/top-stories-september-9-glowtime-iphone-event/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-september-9-iphone-event-ios-18-1-photos-clean-up-tool-and-more.2434818/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/31/top-stories-september-9-glowtime-iphone-event/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's a day earlier than rumors had suggested, but Apple's big iPhone 16 event now has an official date: Monday, September 9. The "It's Glowtime" tagline and glowing Apple logo theme are clear nods to the revamped Siri and new Apple Intelligence features that will undoubtedly be a major point of emphasis for the upcoming devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/top-stories-31aug2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963251" /><br/>
Much of the news this week focused on what announcements we will and won't see at Apple's upcoming event, with the usual focus on iPhone and Apple Watch perhaps being supplemented by a few other hardware announcements but a number of other updates like Macs not coming until later. This week also saw fresh rounds of operating system beta releases, including some new Apple Intelligence features for those on the iOS 18.1 beta, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Event Announced for September 9: 'It's Glowtime'</h2><br/>
Apple has announced plans to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">hold its annual iPhone-centric event on Monday, September 9,</a> at the Apple Park campus in Cupertino, California. The event is set to start at 10:00 a.m., and select members of the media have been invited to attend.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Its-Glowtime-Announcement-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963249" /><br/>
This year's event will see Apple unveil the iPhone 16 lineup, new Apple Watch models, and the AirPods 4, plus we'll get official launch dates for iOS 18, macOS Sequoia, and Apple's other software updates.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16 Likely to Launch on September 20 With These New Features</h2><br/>
With Apple's "It's Glowtime" event taking place on Monday, September 9, pre-orders for the new iPhone 16 lineup are likely to begin on Friday, September 13, with a launch to follow on Friday, September 20.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Mock-Header-Updated-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922680" /><br/>
We've <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-likely-iphone-16-launch-date/">recapped many of the rumors</a> we've heard about the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro lineups, so read up for a refresher on what we can expect to see for Apple's latest flagship phones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple's September 9 'It's Glowtime' Event: What to Expect Beyond the iPhone 16</h2><br/>
While the iPhone 16 lineup will be the headliner for Apple's September 9 event, we're <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/apple-september-2024-event-new-products-expected/">expecting a number of other product introductions</a> to fill out the day's presentation.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/its-glowtime-event-youtube.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962411" /><br/>
We're expecting new Apple Watch Series 10, Apple Watch Ultra 3, and Apple Watch SE 3 models, plus two variants of fourth-generation AirPods, and perhaps a seventh-generation iPad mini and other announcements.<br/>
<br/>
We should also be getting new colors of iPhone and iPad cases and Apple Watch bands, while we'll get final details and release dates for iOS 18 and related operating system updates.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>When to Expect the iPhone SE 4 to Launch</h2><br/>
The iPhone 16 lineup is right around the corner, but Apple's cheapest iPhone is also in need of an update so <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/when-to-expect-iphone-se-4/">when can we expect to see a fourth-generation iPhone SE</a>?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-SE-4-Thumb-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951978" /><br/>
Rumors are currently pointing to an iPhone SE update in the spring of 2025, which makes sense considering all three previous generations have been introduced in March over the years. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/when-to-expect-iphone-se-4/">Check out our coverage</a> for details on what we're expecting to see in what should be a major update for the budget iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>See the Apple Intelligence Photos App 'Clean Up' Tool in Action</h2><br/>
AI-driven Apple Intelligence features won't make the cut for the initial iOS 18 release next month, but Apple has been gradually rolling them out in betas of iOS 18.1, which should see a public release in October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-Photos-Clean-Up-Thumb.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962940" /><br/>
In this week's iOS 18.1 beta, the most notable Apple Intelligence addition is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-clean-up-hands-on/">Clean Up, a tool in the Photos app that lets you remove unwanted objects from your photos</a> and use generative AI to fill in missing pieces of the photo behind the removed objects.<br/>
<br/>
It's a bit hit-or-miss right now, but it's still a work in progress in beta so check out our hands-on video to see what it's capable of at the moment.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pros With M4 Pro and M4 Max Chips Reportedly Being Mass Produced This Month</h2><br/>
Based on past history, next month's event will not include any Mac hardware announcements, but Mac updates based around the M4 chip family should arrive before the end of the year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/m3-mbp-space-black.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="810" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919466" /><br/>
We're expecting a number of Macs with the base M4 chip similar to the one that debuted in the iPad Pro earlier this year, but there are also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/macbook-pro-m4-pro-m4-max-production-report/">more powerful M4 Pro and M4 Max variants in the works</a>, and a new report claims that Apple's supply chain is already gearing up to mass produce updated MacBook Pro models with these more powerful chips.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/aug-29-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/31/top-stories-september-9-glowtime-iphone-event/">Top Stories: September 9 iPhone Event, iOS 18.1 Photos Clean Up Tool, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-september-9-iphone-event-ios-18-1-photos-clean-up-tool-and-more.2434818/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s Rumored Gold Titanium Color Revealed by This Mockup</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/iphone-16-pro-gold-color-mockup/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-rumored-gold-titanium-color-revealed-by-this-mockup.2434785/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:09:54 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/iphone-16-pro-gold-color-mockup/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>9to5Mac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a few weeks ahead of Apple unveiling the iPhone 16 series, we potentially have an early look at a new color option for the Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-16-pro-gold-9to5mac.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1000" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963282" /><br/>
<a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/08/30/iphone-16-pro-gold-titanium/"><em>9to5Mac</em> today</a> shared a mockup image of the rumored gold finish for the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max, based on information provided by a <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/08/24/titan-gray-iphone-15-pro/">previously-accurate</a> source. The publication believes this image is "likely" accurate.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 Pro models were the first highest-end iPhones to not be available in gold since the iPhone X. The devices are offered in four finishes, including Natural Titanium, Blue Titanium, White Titanium, and Black Titanium. The addition of a gold color option for iPhone 16 Pro models would mark a return to the norm.<br/>
<br/>
There have been <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/13/iphone-16-pro-rose-gold-titanium-replace-blue/">many rumors</a> about the iPhone 16 Pro models being offered in a gold or bronze option, which is expected to replace Blue Titanium. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">Apple's event on September 9</a> is fast approaching, so we'll find out for sure soon.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/9to5mac-com/">9to5Mac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/iphone-16-pro-gold-color-mockup/">iPhone 16 Pro&#039;s Rumored Gold Titanium Color Revealed by This Mockup</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pros-rumored-gold-titanium-color-revealed-by-this-mockup.2434785/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: Labor Day Sales Arrive for the Holiday Weekend With Record Lows on iPad, iPhone, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-30-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-labor-day-sales-arrive-for-the-holiday-weekend-with-record-lows-on-ipad-iphone-and-more.2434784/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:47:43 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-30-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Labor Day deals have kicked off this week, and as we head into the long weekend you can still find great discounts on AirPods Max, MacBook Air, Sonos speakers, and more. We're also tracking fresh markdowns on iPhone 15, the 10th gen iPad, M3 MacBook Pro, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0013.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848004" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Labor Day Deals</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/Labor-Day-Deals-Feature0011.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-860632" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on AirPods, MacBook Air, and more this weekend</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> Amazon, Best Buy, Sonos, and more</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton">Labor Day Apple Deals</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Labor Day is coming up on September 2, and many retailers have kicked off sales that you can shop over the long weekend. You can find the full list of the sales in our original article, but we've collected a few of the best sales below as well.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">9th Gen iPad</a> - &#36;199.00, down from &#36;329.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods Max</a> - &#36;399.00, down from &#36;549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a> - Get up to 20% off select devices</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-15268034?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.sony.com%2Fc%2F1%3Fquery%3D%253Arelevance%253AsnaAllCategories%253A1%253AoffersAndSales%253AOn%2BSale%253AoffersAndSales%253AFree%2Bwith%2BPurchase%26currentPage%3D1">Sony</a> - Save on headphones and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1724942100511">Eufy Security SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iphone-15-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963190" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;1,000 off iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fbrowse%2Fapple%2F">AT&T</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/att-1000-off-iphone-15-models/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fbrowse%2Fapple%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 Deals at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
AT&T is offering up to &#36;1,000 off iPhone 15 models ahead of the launch of the next generation devices in September. You'll find offers on the iPhone 15 Pro Max, iPhone 15 Pro, iPhone 15, and iPhone 15 Plus for new and existing AT&T customers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ipad-10th-gen-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963189" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;50 off 10th gen iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cmZpnYMcH4b">Best Buy</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
We're tracking one of the first notable discounts in weeks on the 10th generation iPad at both Amazon and Best Buy. Prices start at &#36;299.00 for the 64GB Wi-Fi model, and include both cellular devices as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/m3-macbook-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963188" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;700 off M3 MacBook Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmUNLtwB0NL">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmUNLtwB0NL"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (512GB M3 Pro) for &#36;1,499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmUNRokDLUg"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (512GB M3 Pro) for &#36;1,799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy and Amazon have a match of the all-time low price on the 512GB M3 Pro 14-inch MacBook Pro right now, available for &#36;1,499.00, down from &#36;1,999.00. This beats the previous low price by &#36;100, and is available to all Best Buy shoppers without the need of a membership. You can find multiple 14-inch and 16-inch models on sale right now at both retailers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung Monitor</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/viewfinity-samsung-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963187" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take &#36;800 off 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2F%3Fth%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/27/samsungs-27-inch-viewfinity-deal/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CB71BY87%2F%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;800 OFF</div>Samsung 27-Inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor for &#36;800.60</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Earlier in the week, we began tracking a low price on Samsung's 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Monitor. This deal has gotten even better today, now available for &#36;800.60, down from &#36;1,599.99, marking a new all-time low price on the monitor.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-8-30-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: Labor Day Sales Arrive for the Holiday Weekend With Record Lows on iPad, iPhone, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-labor-day-sales-arrive-for-the-holiday-weekend-with-record-lows-on-ipad-iphone-and-more.2434784/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: &#039;Glowtime&#039; Event Invites and M4 Macs</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/the-macrumors-show-event-invites-and-m4-macs/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-glowtime-event-invites-and-m4-macs.2434771/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 08:01:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/the-macrumors-show-event-invites-and-m4-macs/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/glowtime-invites-m4-mac-rumors/id1602394741?i=1000667438013">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">recently announced</a> "It's Glowtime" event for September 9 and what we're expecting from this year's M4 Mac models.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-Nb9HCBXmYs?si=4UCSNNghXRw-FAcW" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
Apple this week sent out invitations for the "It's Glowtime" event that it is set to host on Monday, September 9. It is highly likely to unveil the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, Apple Watch Series 10, Apple Watch Ultra 3, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> 3, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a>. We take a look at the event invite that clearly hints at Apple Intelligence's prominent presence at the event and weigh up what sort of role it could play in each of the devices that are set to be revealed.<br/>
<br/>
We also look at the upcoming M4 Mac models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/these-new-macs-are-coming-in-2024/">expected to launch this year</a>: an entry-level 14-inch MacBook Pro with the M4 chip, new 14- and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with the M4 Pro and M4 Max chips, a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> with the M4 chip, and a completely <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">redesigned Mac mini</a> with the M4 and M4 Pro chips. With the exception of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a>, these devices are expected to be minor refreshes that focus on chip upgrades, but they could come with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-new-macs-16gb-ram-standard/">16GB of memory as standard</a> across the board for the first time. Some of these machines are now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/macbook-pro-m4-pro-m4-max-production-report/">believed to be in mass production</a>, so while they probably won't be announced at Apple's "Glowtime" event, launch is likely to take place soon.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/23/the-macrumors-show-latest-rumors-iphone-mac/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about all of the latest Apple rumors for the remainder of 2024, including the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s rumored <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/iphone-16-pro-color-desert-titanium/">"Desert Titanium" color option</a> that's expected to replace Blue Titanium, the two <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">fourth-generation AirPods variants</a> coming later this year both with and without active noise cancellation, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/mac-mini-to-become-smallest-ever-apple-computer/">Mac mini complete redesign</a> with the M4 and M4 Pro chips, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/m4-macbook-pro-panels-shipping/">M4 MacBook Pro</a> refresh. We also took a look at rumors surrounding the third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, the fourth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, and the likelihood of Apple Intelligence <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/08/apple-intelligence-subscription-price/">moving to a subscription model</a> to boost Apple's services revenue. <br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/the-macrumors-show-event-invites-and-m4-macs/">The MacRumors Show: &#039;Glowtime&#039; Event Invites and M4 Macs</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-glowtime-event-invites-and-m4-macs.2434771/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Labor Day Sale Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off M3 MacBook Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-buy-labor-day-sale-macbook-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-labor-day-sale-takes-up-to-1-000-off-m3-macbook-pro.2434768/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:51:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-buy-labor-day-sale-macbook-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy and Amazon have introduced major discounts on the M3 MacBook Pro today, offering up to &#36;1,000 off select models. This includes an all-time low price on the entry-level M3 512GB 14-inch MacBook Pro at <a href="https://howl.me/cmRrRHevBas"><strong>&#36;1,299.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.00, and a <a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">massive &#36;1,000 discount</a> on the high-end 16-inch model exclusively for <a href="https://howl.me/cmRsmSGd2jO">Best Buy members</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/macbook-pro-m3-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-959391" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy and Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Across the 14-inch M3 MacBook Pro lineup you'll find &#36;300-&#36;500 off every model on Best Buy and Amazon. In regards to the Best Buy discounts, most of these do not require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership and are available to all customers. The only exceptions are the higher-end M3 Pro 1TB and M3 Max 1TB models, which have an extra &#36;100 discount exclusively for Best Buy members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're shopping for the 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro, you'll find the steepest discounts at Best Buy. The biggest savings will be found on the M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB SSD model at Best Buy, which is being discounted by &#36;500 for all shoppers, and an extra &#36;500 exclusively for My Best Buy members. This adds up to a massive &#36;1,000 discount on the high-end 16-inch MacBook Pro, at the new record low price of <a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw"><strong>&#36;2,999.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>14-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmRrRHevBas">M3 512GB</a> - &#36;1,299.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JV268%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmRrTeQt8ZE">M3, 8GB, 1TB</a> - &#36;1,499.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KC8X7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmRrUOQzqC0">M3, 16GB, 1TB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off) [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23Q2SV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,499.00 (&#36;500 off) [<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matched at Amazon</a>]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;1,999.00 (&#36;400 off) [Best Buy members only]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 (&#36;400 off) [Best Buy members only]</li></ul><br/>
<h3>16-inch MacBook Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTdxwhum3">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,799.00 (&#36;700 off) [Best Buy members only]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmGLHQWPmNW">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,199.00 (&#36;700 off) [Best Buy members only]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTef4hr6X">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 (&#36;700 off) [Best Buy members only]</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFTeyXwYzw">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,999.00 (&#36;1,000 off) [Best Buy members only]</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/best-buy-labor-day-sale-macbook-pro/">Best Buy Labor Day Sale Takes Up to &#36;1,000 Off M3 MacBook Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-labor-day-sale-takes-up-to-1-000-off-m3-macbook-pro.2434768/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>LG to Offer 3-Month Free Trial of Apple TV+ on Select Smart TV Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/lg-3-month-apple-tv-plus-trial-offer/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lg-to-offer-3-month-free-trial-of-apple-tv-on-select-smart-tv-models.2434766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 07:41:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/lg-3-month-apple-tv-plus-trial-offer/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV Plus</category>
		<category>LG</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[LG today <a href="https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lg-streaming-week-marks-the-celebration-of-a-decade-of-webos-302234488.html">announced</a> that it will be offering a three-month free trial of Apple TV+ on select smart TV models from September 9 through November 17.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/LG-Streaming-Week-Apple-TV-Plus.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963219" /><br/>
The offer will be available to new and "qualified" returning subscribers in both the Apple TV app and LG Streaming app in over 90 countries on 2018-2024 models of LG's 4K and 8K smart TVs, including StanbyME and StanbyME Go models.<br/>
<br/>
The offer is part of LG Streaming Week.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ typically offers a free one-week trial, or a one-month trial with an Apple One package.<br/>
<br/>
Apple TV+ is priced at &#36;9.99 per month or &#36;99 per year in the U.S. as an individual subscription. The streaming service provides access to Apple's library of original series and films, including hits such as <em>The Morning Show</em>, <em>Ted Lasso</em>, <em>Silo</em>, and <em>Severance</em>.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV Plus</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lg/">LG</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/lg-3-month-apple-tv-plus-trial-offer/">LG to Offer 3-Month Free Trial of Apple TV+ on Select Smart TV Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lg-to-offer-3-month-free-trial-of-apple-tv-on-select-smart-tv-models.2434766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16: 20 Rumored Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-20-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419705/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 06:49:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16&#038;post_date=1725036540/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After over a year of rumors, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are set to launch next month. There are now 20 changes and improvements expected to be offered by the new standard models, so here's everything we're expecting.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-vs-16-Feature-Yellow-Pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936647" /></div><br/>
All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their direct forerunners are listed below, using information from a wide range of reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">previously covered</a> here on <em>MacRumors</em>. We will continue to update this article as more rumors emerge prior to Apple's "It's glowtime" event on Monday, September 9.<br/>
<br/>
This guide focuses on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, but to learn about how we are expecting the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> to improve on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">see our other comparison article</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="design">Design</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to largely carry over the design of their predecessors, meaning that they will have the same dimensions. The most noticeable alteration that will denote the new models is said to be a vertical rear camera arrangement to facilitate spatial video capture, but the removal of the mute switch in favor of the Action button introduced on last year's Pro models.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Diagonally arranged rear camera array</td><br/>
 <td>Vertically arranged rear camera array</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action Button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thermal design with copper heatsink</td><br/>
 <td>New thermal design with graphene heatsink</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15</strong>: 171g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong>: 201g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 173g weight (+1%)<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 203g weight (+1%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="cameras">Cameras</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are slated to receive a small number of camera enhancements, such as an improved ultra wide camera, macro photography support, and a dedicated hardware button for photography and videography on the side of the device. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Capacitive "Capture Button" with force-sensitive half-press and sliding gestures to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ultra wide camera with f/2.4 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>Ultra wide camera with f/2.2 aperture for improved-low light performance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Macro photography support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Spatial video capture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="chip_memory_and_connectivity">Chip, Memory, and Connectivity</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models are rumored to benefit from a moderate improvement in processing power thanks to an all-new A18 chip with a more powerful Neural Engine to support exclusive generative AI capabilities. We are also expecting an 33% more memory and Wi-Fi 6E support.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N4P" enhanced 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced Neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support Apple Intelligence</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory (+33%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting denser batteries and faster charging capabilities. It is worth noting that the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus is rumored to feature a smaller battery than its predecessor, but it is not clear how this will affect actual battery life. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 15</strong>: 3,349 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 15 Plus</strong>: 4,383 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16</strong>: 3,561 mAh battery (+6%)<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Plus</strong>: 4,006 mAh battery (-9%)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 27W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging (48% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; (33% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h3><br/>
Support for Apple Intelligence is expected to be one of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s most important features, bringing the new array of AI tools to Apple's standard line of iPhones for the first time. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Apple Intelligence support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance, designed to support new AI features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Blue, Pink, Green, Yellow, and Black</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Blue, Pink, Green, Yellow, Black, White, and Purple</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="release_date">Release Date</h3><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to be announced at Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">"It's glowtime" event</a> on Monday, September 9. Pre-orders are likely to open on Friday, September 13, with launch following one week later on Friday, September 20. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; was a significant upgrade over 2023's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, introducing a new design with a the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, a 48-megapixel camera, a USB-C port, and more. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;'s upgrades will likely not be as substantial as those offered by its predecessor. As a result, most &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; users will have little reason to upgrade, but Apple Intelligence and the new Action and Capture buttons are likely to be among the main motivations to get the latest device.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-15">iPhone 15 (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16/">iPhone 15 vs. iPhone 16: 20 Rumored Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-vs-iphone-16-20-rumored-upgrades-compared.2419705/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Spatial Apps, Games, and Video Coming to Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/new-spatial-content-coming-to-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-spatial-apps-games-and-video-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2434753/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 04:27:29 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/new-spatial-content-coming-to-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Arcade</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expanding its selection of spatial and immersive experiences for the Vision Pro headset with a series of new games, apps, and video content.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/visionos-home-screen-mt-hood.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-900011" /><br/>
Among the newly introduced experiences is a spatial version of "<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/castle-crumble/id1616814625">Castle Crumble</a>," a physics-based puzzle game that lets players interact in a 3D environment. Players can use their hands to precisely target the castles' weak points with a variety of powerful explosives, mystical spells, and unlockable boosts. Castle Crumble is <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/castle-crumble/id1616814625">available now on the App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
"<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/puzzle-sculpt/id6479268606">Puzzle Sculpt</a>," another spatial game, is set to release on September 5. Developed by Schell Games, an award-winning studio known for pioneering gameplay with emerging technologies, "Puzzle Sculpt" offers a relaxing, 3D puzzle-solving experience. The game invites players to interact with a variety of puzzles in a fully immersive spatial environment.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, "<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/immersion-golf/id6480462436?platform=vision">Immersion Golf</a>" from Tag Heuer takes golf enthusiasts to the next level with detailed 3D maps of nearly 40,000 courses worldwide. The app allows players to preview course layouts and obstacles, providing a comprehensive tool for planning their game strategy.<br/>
<br/>
"<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/sandblox-the-marble-game/id6478234307">Sandblox: The Marble Game</a>" allows players to create and share physics-based puzzles and marble runs using intuitive hand tracking. The game encourages both solo and collaborative play, with users able to build complex structures and share their creations online. "<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pinball-nation/id6503935998">Pinball Nation</a>" transforms living spaces into a virtual 1980s pinball arcade, complete with life-sized virtual tables and realistic gameplay, while "<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/beat-slash-mixed/id6612030233">Beat Slash - Mixed</a>" offers a high-energy rhythm game where players use swords to slash beats in time with the music.<br/>
<br/>
Starting September 6, Vision Pro users will also have access to new films and series captured in Apple Immersive Video. This includes the premiere of "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/show/elevated/umc.cmc.5klf6wzriakqz7lcarzyp5bp1">Elevated</a>," an aerial travel series that provides viewers with breathtaking views from staggering heights. Available exclusively to U.S. users, "Elevated" aims to transport audiences to iconic vistas around the world. Another notable addition is "4 Minutes Inside Super Bowl LVIII," a short film that offers an immersive glimpse into the intense atmosphere of the Super Bowl LVIII, where the Kansas City Chiefs faced off against the San Francisco 49ers. This film will be available to a global audience.<br/>
<br/>
On the same day, Vision Pro users worldwide will also be able to watch the first episode of "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/show/boundless/umc.cmc.2y2ypiwhg8dp8027p47jfhlf1">Boundless</a>," titled "Hot Air Balloons," and the second episode of "<a href="https://tv.apple.com/us/show/wild-life/umc.cmc.63jzn7b2c5w488vb72cabapqa">Wild Life</a>," focusing on elephants.<br/>
<br/>
Popular Vision Pro apps are also receiving significant updates. The <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pga-tour-vision/id6471858717?platform=vision">PGA TOUR app</a> now features SharePlay support, enabling users to watch every hole, follow the leaderboard, and examine every shot in 3D. Meanwhile, "<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/synth-riders/id6473729300">Synth Riders</a>," available on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>, has been enhanced with a new Adrenaline Pack, adding high-energy punk and ska music to its existing eclectic mix.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/new-spatial-content-coming-to-vision-pro/">New Spatial Apps, Games, and Video Coming to Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-spatial-apps-games-and-video-coming-to-apple-vision-pro.2434753/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon to Launch New AI-Powered Alexa Using Anthropic&#039;s Claude</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/amazon-launching-new-alexa-claude-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-to-launch-new-ai-powered-alexa-using-anthropics-claude.2434751/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 03:32:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/amazon-launching-new-alexa-claude-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Alexa</category>
		<category>Amazon</category>
		<category>Anthropic</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is set to release a revamped version of its Alexa voice assistant this October that will be powered by AI models from Anthropic's Claude, rather than Amazon's in-house AI technology, reports <em><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/amazon-turns-anthropics-claude-alexa-ai-revamp-2024-08-30/">Reuters</a></em>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/amazon-echo-dot.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956668" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Amazon's Echo device with Alexa</em></div><br/>
The decision to use Claude's AI models comes after Amazon's internal software reportedly struggled with performance issues during initial testing. Sources who spoke to <em>Reuters</em> claim that early versions using Amazon's own AI had difficulty responding promptly, sometimes taking up to 6-7 seconds to acknowledge and reply to prompts.<br/>
<br/>
This new AI-enhanced "Remarkable" Alexa is expected to offer more advanced capabilities compared to the current version. Users will reportedly be able to engage in more complex, context-aware conversations with the assistant. <br/>
<br/>
Some potential features include providing shopping advice for specific scenarios like vacation clothing recommendations, aggregating news stories, executing multi-step tasks from a single prompt such as ordering food or drafting emails, and enhanced home automation with improved ability to remember and apply user preferences.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon plans to offer this upgraded "Remarkable" Alexa as a paid subscription service, with pricing anticipated to be between &#36;5 to &#36;10 per month. In other words, it won't be included in existing Prime memberships. The existing "Classic" Alexa service will remain available for free.<br/>
<br/>
The move to partner with Anthropic for AI technology contrasts with Amazon's typical strategy of relying on in-house developments, but similar partnerships such as Microsoft and Apple's collaborations with OpenAI for ChatGPT integration indicate a broader shift in the tech industry.<br/>
<br/>
Amazon has invested &#36;4 billion in Anthropic, which may have influenced this decision, but the full details of the agreement between the two companies regarding the use of Claude in Alexa have not been disclosed.<br/>
<br/>
Industry analysts estimate that there are approximately 100 million active Alexa users. If 10% of these users opt for the paid version, it could potentially generate at least &#36;600 million in annual revenue for Amazon, assuming the lower end of the expected price range.<br/>
<br/>
The launch of this new Alexa comes at a critical time for Amazon's voice assistant division. Despite Alexa's widespread adoption, with Amazon claiming 500 million Alexa-enabled devices sold, it has struggled to generate significant revenue. Amazon's leadership has reportedly emphasized that 2024 is a crucial year for Alexa to demonstrate its ability to drive meaningful sales.<br/>
<br/>
While Amazon has confirmed its use of various AI models, including its own Titan model and those from partners, it has not specifically commented on the use of Claude for the new Alexa. The official unveiling of the new AI-powered Alexa is expected to take place at Amazon's annual devices and services event, typically held in September. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/alexa/">Alexa</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/amazon/">Amazon</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/anthropic/">Anthropic</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/amazon-launching-new-alexa-claude-ai/">Amazon to Launch New AI-Powered Alexa Using Anthropic&#039;s Claude</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-to-launch-new-ai-powered-alexa-using-anthropics-claude.2434751/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Blames Apple for Loss of iPhone Volume Button Control of Connected Devices</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-blames-apple-for-loss-of-iphone-volume-button-control-of-connected-devices.2434749/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 02:58:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify says users on iPhone will no longer be able to control the volume of connected devices using their physical volume buttons after Apple "<a href="https://support.spotify.com/us/article/spotify-connect/?ref=related">discontinued</a>" the technology that enables the functionality. The change impacts Spotify Connect, a feature that allows users to control Spotify playback on various devices like speakers, game consoles, and smart TVs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/06/Apple-vs-Spotify-feature2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801789" /><br/>
The streaming giant claims that the previous method had become unstable, leading to issues such as volume spikes during playback. As a result, iPhone users will now have to resort to an in-app slider to adjust volume, a change that Spotify is calling a "workaround," reports <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/8/29/24231516/spotify-apple-physical-iphone-volume-controls">The Verge</a></em>.  <br/>
<br/>
To use the new volume control, iPhone owners will need to tap a notification that appears when they press the physical volume buttons. This notification will prompt them to use the in-app slider. Spotify claims that the new solution will provide "persistent, high-quality" volume control, despite the extra steps involved for users. The change is set to take effect on September 3, but some users are <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/alexa/comments/1d7whh9/no_more_volume_control_via_iphone_buttons_when/">reportedly already seeing it</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Spotify claims that Apple is refusing to grant access to the same technology that allows Apple Music to play on third-party devices. In a continuation of long-held tensions between the two companies, the streaming service has gone as far as suggesting that this could violate the EU's Digital Markets Act, which requires major platforms to open up to third-party services.<br/>
<br/>
"We've made requests to Apple to introduce a similar solution to what they offer users on HomePod and Apple TV for app developers who control non-Apple media devices," Spotify said in its update. "Apple has told us that they require apps to integrate into HomePod in order to access the technology that controls volume on iPhones."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/spotify_connected_devices_volume.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1093" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963142" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>Spotify's volume control workaround for Spotify Connect</em></div><br/>
Apple actually offers an API for third-party music services to stream directly to HomePods, but for whatever reason Spotify has chosen not to implement it. Fortunately, iPhone users running iOS 17 can still start an AirPlay session on HomePod using a Siri command (e.g. "Siri, play Fleetwood Mac on Spotify"). It's worth noting that this change only affects Spotify Connect on iOS. Spotify users controlling volume via Bluetooth or AirPlay will not be impacted.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/spotify-loses-iphone-volume-buttons-control/">Spotify Blames Apple for Loss of iPhone Volume Button Control of Connected Devices</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-blames-apple-for-loss-of-iphone-volume-button-control-of-connected-devices.2434749/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Are Apple&#039;s Oldest Products Still Sold Today</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-apples-oldest-products-still-sold-today.2434708/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:49:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For over two decades, the <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/">MacRumors Buyer's Guide</a> has served as a valuable resource for keeping track of when Apple products were last updated.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/AirPods-Max-1360-Days-Old-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963047" /><br/>
Below, we have highlighted five current-generation Apple products that have not received hardware upgrades in several years. We also provide some purchasing recommendations based on both rumors and our own opinions.<br/>
<br/>
This list excludes previous-generation Apple products still sold, such as the iPhone 13, along with various accessories and cables.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Pro Display XDR</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/05/Pro-Display-XDR-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-740290" /><br/>
Apple released the Pro Display XDR <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/12/07/apple-releasing-mac-pro-december-10/">in December 2019</a>, so it will be five years old later this year. The high-end monitor starts at &#36;4,999 and features a 32-inch screen size with 6K resolution, but it lacks a built-in camera and speakers.<br/>
<br/>
In December 2022, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said Apple was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/18/updated-pro-display-xdr-gurman/">working on multiple new external monitors</a>, including an updated version of the Pro Display XDR that will be equipped with an Apple silicon chip, just like the Studio Display with the A13 chip. However, it's unclear when the new Pro Display XDR will be released or what other new features it will have.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 4 years and 8 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Given how expensive the Pro Display XDR is, it is worth waiting for the next model at this point. Also consider the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/studio-display/">Studio Display</a>, which is over two years newer, more affordable, and has a built-in camera and speakers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>HomePod mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/11/homepod-mini-thumb-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-770560" /><br/>
Released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/apple-announces-homepod-mini/">in November 2020</a>, the HomePod mini is also nearly four years old. The smaller Siri-enabled smart speaker has not received any hardware updates since launching, although it did get Blue, Orange, and Yellow color options in November 2021, and Space Gray was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/">replaced with a virtually-identical Midnight finish</a> a few months ago.<br/>
<br/>
In February 2023, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said mass shipments of a second-generation HomePod mini would begin <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/03/homepod-mini-2-shipping-next-year/">in the second half of 2024</a>, but it is unclear if that info is still accurate, as there have not been any recent HomePod mini rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 3 years and 9 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Given there was a rumor that a new HomePod mini might be released later this year, it might be best to hold off for three to four more months to see if that happens. However, given the HomePod mini is a modest &#36;99, there is not too much harm in purchasing one now if you don't want to wait.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/AirPods-Max-Gen-2-Feature-Black-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877635" /><br/>
Released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/12/08/airpods-max/">in December 2020</a>, the AirPods Max will turn four years old later this year. Apple's over-ear headphones have not received any hardware updates since, and remain priced at &#36;549 on Apple's online store, with five color options available. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 3 years and 8 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> We recommend waiting for the AirPods Max with a USB-C port to launch later this year, but the headphones will still more or less be four years old beyond that change, so you may wish to consider newer competing options, such as the Sony XM5, Bose QuietComfort Ultra, and Sonos Ace. Amazon does have the AirPods Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/airpods-max-hit-399/">on sale for &#36;399</a> if you are interested in purchasing them now at a discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/iPad-mini-6-orange-BG.jpg" alt="" width="1881" height="1058" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816576" /><br/>
Apple released the current iPad mini in September 2021, with new features at the time including a larger 8.3-inch display, a USB-C port, a Touch ID power button, the A15 Bionic chip, 5G support on cellular models, a 12-megapixel rear camera with Center Stage support, compatibility with the second-generation Apple Pencil, and more.<br/>
<br/>
In November 2023, Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">said</a> mass production of the next iPad mini would begin in the second half of 2024. More recently, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman said inventory of the current iPad mini was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/ipad-mini-stock-dwindling/">starting to dwindle at Apple Stores</a>, which could be a sign that the device will be updated in the near future.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/16/ipad-mini-7-rumored-to-feature-these-four-upgrades/">Rumored features</a> for the next iPad mini include a newer chip, upgraded cameras, Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support, new color options, and a fix for the so-called "jelly scrolling" effect on the current model's display. <br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 2 years and 11 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> At this point, we suggest waiting for the new iPad mini that is rumored to launch later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods 3</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airpods-3-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953897" /><br/>
Released in October 2021, the third-generation AirPods are nearly three years old.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">Two new fourth-generation AirPods models</a> are expected to be unveiled at <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">Apple's special event on September 9</a>, with both options rumored to feature a tweaked design with better fit in the ear, improved sound quality, and an updated charging case with a USB-C port. The higher-end AirPods 4 are also said to feature active noise cancellation, and a speaker in the charging case that can play a sound for Find My location tracking.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Age:</strong> 2 years and 10 months<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Recommendation:</strong> Do not buy! Apple is expected to announce the fourth-generation AirPods in less than two weeks.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/oldest-apple-products-still-sold-in-2024/">These Are Apple&#039;s Oldest Products Still Sold Today</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-are-apples-oldest-products-still-sold-today.2434708/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reportedly in Talks to Invest in ChatGPT Maker OpenAI</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-chatgpt-maker-openai.2434707/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 10:52:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		<category>The Wall Street Journal</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is in talks to invest in artificial intelligence company OpenAI, according to sources cited by <a href="https://www.wsj.com/tech/ai/openai-apple-funding-chatgpt-50754cd6"><em>The Wall Street Journal</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/iOS-18-ChatGPT.jpg" alt="" width="1825" height="1027" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960667" /><br/>
The report did not indicate how much money Apple would be investing in OpenAI, or provide any additional details about the discussions, but it said this latest fundraising round would value the ChatGPT maker above &#36;100 billion. <br/>
<br/>
Apple previously announced that ChatGPT integration is coming to Siri on iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/02/ios-18-chatgpt-later-this-year/">before the end of the year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
With user permission, Siri will be able to show ChatGPT answers directly in response to questions and other prompts. ChatGPT will also be an option for Apple's system-wide Writing Tools feature, allowing users to generate text and images. Apple said ChatGPT will be powered by OpenAI's latest GPT-4o model on its platforms.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone, iPad, and Mac users will be able to use ChatGPT for free, without creating an account, and ChatGPT Plus subscribers will be able to connect their accounts to access paid features on these devices. Apple said OpenAI will not store ChatGPT requests made from its devices, and it said users' IP addresses will be obscured.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features started rolling out to developers for testing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/29/apple-releases-ios-18-1-apple-intelligence/">in the iOS 18.1 beta last month</a>, but ChatGPT integration is not available yet.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features require an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max, or a Mac or iPad equipped with an M1 chip or newer. The device's language must be set to U.S. English, with support for additional languages to roll out over the next year.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft is also planning to further invest in OpenAI, the report said.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-wall-street-journal/">The Wall Street Journal</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-openai/">Apple Reportedly in Talks to Invest in ChatGPT Maker OpenAI</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reportedly-in-talks-to-invest-in-chatgpt-maker-openai.2434707/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Labor Day Sales Include Year&#039;s Best Prices on iPads, MacBooks, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-labor-day-sales-include-years-best-prices-on-ipads-macbooks-and-more.2434700/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:47:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As we head into the long weekend ending with Labor Day on Monday, a number of retailers have introduced deals that should be advantageous for anyone shopping around for Apple products and related accessories. In this article we've rounded up some of the best Labor Day deals for Apple devices, also including discounts on charging accessories, headphones, speakers, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/Labor-Day-Deals-Feature0011.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-860632" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>AirPods Max</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/airpods-max-blue-image.png" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-857001" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the AirPods Max for &#36;399.00 in every color this week, down from &#36;549.00. This is nearly a match of the all-time low price on the headphones, just &#36;5 higher than that Prime Day deal we saw in July.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZDSP2Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>AirPods Max for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/08/ipad-blue-image.png" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-857000" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon recently introduced a new all-time low price on Apple's 9th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad, available for just &#36;199.00, down from &#36;329.00. This sale beats the previous low price by about &#36;30, and it's available in both colors right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><h2>iPad Mini</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/ipad-mini-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888416" /><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 64GB Wi-Fi iPad mini 6 for &#36;379.99 this week on Amazon, down from &#36;499.00. This is a match for the record low price on the tablet, and right now we're only tracking it on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G91LXFP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;119 OFF</div>iPad mini (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;379.99</div></a></div><h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/macbook-air-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905733" /><br/>
<br/>
If you want a cheaper MacBook model, Best Buy has Apple's 2022 M2 MacBook Air starting at just &#36;799.00 this week. This is a match for the all-time low price on the notebook, and you'll find <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">matching deals at Amazon</a> too.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmYZCN2uvXB"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmYZD1hiHc0"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (512GB) for &#36;999.00</div></a></div><h2>M3 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/macbook-air-new-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939665" /><br/>
<br/>
For newer models, Amazon has every 15-inch M3 MacBook Air on sale right now, available from &#36;1,049.00 and reaching &#36;250 off.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,049.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (8GB/512GB) for &#36;1,249.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX243WQ3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>15-inch M3 MacBook Air (16GB/512GB) for &#36;1,449.00</div></a></div><h2>Studio Display</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/studio-display-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963033" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon has the Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99, down from &#36;1,599.00, which is a match of the all-time low price on the monitor. This is the standard glass version of the Studio Display with the tilt adjustable stand, and Amazon also has a few other models on sale as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09V3GZD32%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;299 OFF</div>Standard Glass Apple Studio Display for &#36;1,299.99</div></a></div><h2>iMac</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/imac-blue-image.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-883127" /><br/>
<br/>
Record low prices hit Apple's newest iMacs this week, starting at &#36;1,099.99 for the 8-core/256GB model, down from &#36;1,299.00. You'll also find the 10-core/256GB and 10-core/512GB model on sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5BFRND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;199 OFF</div>M3 iMac (8-core/256GB) for &#36;1,099.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5GQSPV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/256GB) for &#36;1,299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KBG3M%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;199 OFF</div>M3 iMac (10-core/512GB) for &#36;1,499.99</div></a></div><h2>Accessories</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a> - Get up to 20% off select devices</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-15268034?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.sony.com%2Fc%2F1%3Fquery%3D%253Arelevance%253AsnaAllCategories%253A1%253AoffersAndSales%253AOn%2BSale%253AoffersAndSales%253AFree%2Bwith%2BPurchase%26currentPage%3D1">Sony</a> - Save on headphones and more</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1724942100511">Eufy Security SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;19.99, down from &#36;29.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1592498&u=63177&m=100061">Casely</a> - BOGO everything sitewide with code BOGO-WEEKEND</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/fs-bin/click?id=J2shFQg6J/U&offerid=592602.5&type=3&subid=0">Hyper</a> - Get 20% off select chargers with code POWERUP20</li><br/>
<li><a href="http://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11803854">OWC</a> - Save on computer accessories sitewide</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://shareasale.com/r.cfm?b=1554062&u=63177&m=98197&urllink=&afftrack=">Satechi</a> - Get 25% off sitewide with code SUMMER25</li></ul> Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/labor-day-apple-deals-2024/">Best Apple Labor Day Sales Include Year&#039;s Best Prices on iPads, MacBooks, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-labor-day-sales-include-years-best-prices-on-ipads-macbooks-and-more.2434700/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Sports App to Offer Live Scores and Play-by-Play for More Leagues on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-to-offer-live-scores-and-play-by-play-for-more-leagues-on-iphones-lock-screen.2434699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 08:28:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Sports</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/08/apple-sports-is-ready-for-football-season/">announced</a> several new features and changes coming to its Sports app on the iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Apple-Sports-to-Offer-Live-Activities-for-All-Leagues-Available-Within-App-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2322" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-963060" /><br/>
Starting with iOS 18 and watchOS 11, the Apple Sports app will offer Live Activities for all teams and leagues available in the app, according to Apple. Live Activities provides live scores and play-by-play information at a glance on the iPhone's Lock Screen and in the Dynamic Island on newer models, and on the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added that Live Activities will no longer be available in the Apple TV app with iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Apple said the Sports app has also been optimized for the latest NFL and college football seasons. The app now offers "quick access to scoring drives presented alongside the view of every game play," along with a new dynamic drive tracker that "lets fans visualize where the ball is on the field at any time," the press release said. <br/>
<br/>
In addition, Apple said the app will be updated later this year with a new drop-down navigation and enhanced search functionality.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports provides scores and more for the following leagues:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>NFL</li><br/>
<li>NCAAF</li><br/>
<li>MLS</li><br/>
<li>MLB</li><br/>
<li>NBA</li><br/>
<li>WNBA</li><br/>
<li>NCAA basketball (men's and women's)</li><br/>
<li>NHL</li><br/>
<li>NWSL</li><br/>
<li>Premier League</li><br/>
<li>Bundesliga</li><br/>
<li>LaLiga</li><br/>
<li>Liga MX</li><br/>
<li>Ligue 1</li><br/>
<li>Serie A</li></ul>Apple said additional leagues will become available in the app over time, including Champions League and Europa League.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Sports is a free app <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/apple-sports/id6446788829">available in the App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-sports/">Apple Sports</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-sports-live-activities-and-more/">Apple Sports App to Offer Live Scores and Play-by-Play for More Leagues on iPhone&#039;s Lock Screen</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-sports-app-to-offer-live-scores-and-play-by-play-for-more-leagues-on-iphones-lock-screen.2434699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Will a New Apple TV Still Launch This Year?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-a-new-apple-tv-still-launch-this-year.2434693/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 07:41:41 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It has been nearly two years since the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> last received a hardware upgrade, so you may be wondering when a new model will be released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/apple-tv-4k-yellow-bg-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870258" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about the next-generation Apple TV.<br/>
<br/>
In January 2023, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman reported that a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">new Apple TV was on track for release in the first half of 2024</a>:<blockquote>Beyond the future smart displays and new speaker, Apple is working on revamping its TV box. A new version with the current design is in the works for the first half of next year with a faster processor, the people said.</blockquote>The first half of 2024 passed by without a new Apple TV, so that rumor has expired, and there have been no credible rumors about the device since. As such, it is currently unclear when the next Apple TV will be released.<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently announced that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">holding a special event on September 9</a>, but the only products firmly rumored to be unveiled then include new iPhones, Apple Watches, and AirPods, with no expectation of a new Apple TV so far.<br/>
<br/>
Here is when the previous five Apple TV models were announced:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> October 2022</li><br/>
<li><strong>Second-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> April 2021</li><br/>
<li><strong>First-generation Apple TV 4K:</strong> September 2017</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple TV HD:</strong> September 2015</li><br/>
<li><strong>Third-generation Apple TV:</strong> March 2012</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
Whenever it comes out, the next Apple TV is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">faster processor</a> than the current A15 Bionic chip, and even lower pricing. Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo suggested that the next Apple TV <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">could have a sub-&#36;100 starting price</a>. The current Apple TV starts at &#36;129 in the U.S. with 64GB of storage, and a 128GB model is available for &#36;149.<br/>
<br/>
Both the second-generation (2010) and third-generation (2012) models of the Apple TV were priced at &#36;99 in the U.S. at launch, and Apple eventually lowered the price of the third-generation model to &#36;69, so there is precedent for a sub-&#36;100 Apple TV that would better compete with low-priced streaming devices sold by the likes of Amazon and Roku.<br/>
<br/>
No major design changes have been rumored for the next Apple TV specifically, but Gurman said Apple has considered <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/apple-tv-with-camera-again-rumored/">adding a built-in camera</a> to a future model. tvOS 17 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/use-iphone-facetime-camera-apple-tv/">added a FaceTime app to the Apple TV</a>, allowing for users to have video calls by using the rear camera on a connected iPhone or iPad. If the Apple TV gained a built-in camera, users would no longer need to rely on an external device for video calls on the TV.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/when-is-a-new-apple-tv-coming-out/">Will a New Apple TV Still Launch This Year?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/will-a-new-apple-tv-still-launch-this-year.2434693/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Intelligence Not Device Region Locked to US in Latest Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-device-region-locked-to-us-in-latest-betas.2434676/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 03:20:18 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Intelligence</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple in the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-seeds-ios-18-1-beta-3/">iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia 15.1 betas</a> no longer requires users to set their device region to the United States, so now it's just the US English language requirement that remains.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/apple-intelligence-symbol.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962975" /><br/>
In previous betas, users not only had to change Siri's language to the US to access Apple Intelligence, but they also had to change both their device region and language to the US as well.<br/>
<br/>
However, as per the latest release notes and spotted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/08/28/apple-intelligence-no-longer-requires-setting-the-device-region-to-the-us/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the requirement to change device region to US appears to have been dropped, which means things like measurement system, temperature, and calendar formatting can remain unchanged with Apple Intelligence enabled.<br/>
<br/>
In other words, users running the third betas of iOS 18.1, iPadOS 18.1, and macOS Sequoia 15.1 only have to ensure that English is their preferred language in Settings  General  Language & Region, and that English (United States) is the set Siri language in Settings  Apple Intelligence & Siri.<br/>
<br/>
With those two settings in place, users outside of the US can opt to join the Apple Intelligence waitlist, which in most cases gets accepted in just a few minutes. Note that Apple Intelligence remains unavailable in China, while users in the EU must still have a device signed in with a US App Store ID.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence encompasses a range of capabilities, including composing text and emails, automating actions across various apps, generating images, summarizing documents and texts, and more. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-apple-intelligence-outside-us/">How to Enable Apple Intelligence If You're Outside the US</a></li></ul><br/>
These features require a lot of on-device computing power, so before you do anything, it's worth checking if your device is compatible. iPhone users need either an iPhone 15 Pro or iPhone 15 Pro Max to run Apple Intelligence, while only iPads and Macs powered by M1 or later Apple silicon processors are compatible.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-intelligence/">Apple Intelligence</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/apple-intelligence-not-region-locked-betas/">Apple Intelligence Not Device Region Locked to US in Latest Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-intelligence-not-device-region-locked-to-us-in-latest-betas.2434676/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Next Year&#039;s Upgrade to 12GB RAM Will Be Limited to iPhone 17 Pro Max</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-next-years-upgrade-to-12gb-ram-will-be-limited-to-iphone-17-pro-max.2434654/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 19:51:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Eric Slivka</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Just a day after a noted leaker on Chinese microblogging site Weibo suggested the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a> lineup in 2025 could see an upgrade to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/iphone-17-feature-12gb-ram-up-from-8gb/">12GB of RAM across the board</a>, analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has claimed that the upgrade <a href="https://twitter.com/mingchikuo/status/1828959136421425493/">will be limited to the iPhone 17 Pro Max</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-17-Pro-Max-Smaller-Dynamic-Island-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949323" /><br/>
If Kuo is correct, it means the smaller &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro, the base &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj;, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/15/iphone-17-slim-everything-we-know/">all-new iPhone 17 "Slim"</a> will stick with the 8GB figure rumored for the entire <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup this year. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/when-to-expect-iphone-se-4/">fourth-generation iPhone SE</a> expected in early 2025 will reportedly also carry 8GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
The amount of RAM in Apple's devices is currently of increased importance, as Apple has judged that 8GB is the minimum required for the Apple Intelligence features coming in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, which means only the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and Pro Max of Apple's current phones will support them. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and 15 Plus carry only 6GB of RAM.<br/>
<br/>
While a move to 8GB across the board starting with next month's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup will enable all new iPhones to support Apple Intelligence going forward, a further bump to 12GB would likely allow for even more powerful AI capabilities, but it now appears that may be limited to Apple's highest-end model in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Aside from the increased 12GB of RAM, Kuo says the &zwnj;iPhone 17&zwnj; Pro Max will also have an exclusive cooling system combining vapor chamber technology with graphite sheets. The other new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models launching in 2025 will rely solely on graphite sheets for cooling.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/kuo-12gb-ram-iphone-17-pro-max-exclusive/">Kuo: Next Year&#039;s Upgrade to 12GB RAM Will Be Limited to iPhone 17 Pro Max</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-next-years-upgrade-to-12gb-ram-will-be-limited-to-iphone-17-pro-max.2434654/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Mac OS X Snow Leopard Launched 15 Years Ago Today With &#039;0 New Features&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-launched-15-years-ago-today-with-0-new-features.2434641/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today marks the 15th anniversary of Apple releasing Mac OS X Snow Leopard, which became available to purchase for &#36;29 <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2009/08/24Apple-to-Ship-Mac-OS-X-Snow-Leopard-on-August-28/">on August 28, 2009</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/Mac-OS-X-Snow-Leopard-Web-Banner-Large.jpeg" alt="" width="895" height="503" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962904" /><br/>
After advertising Mac OS X Leopard as having "over 300 new features" in 2007, Apple previewed Snow Leopard at WWDC 2008. Notably, during that year's "State of the Union" session, Apple showed a presentation slide that said the update had "0 new features," as Apple opted to focus on under-the-hood performance and stability improvements.<br/>
<br/>
"We've built on the success of Leopard and created an even better experience for our users from installation to shutdown," said Apple's former software engineering chief Bertrand Serlet. "Apple engineers have made hundreds of improvements so with Snow Leopard your system is going to feel faster, more responsive and even more reliable than before."<br/>
<br/>
With Snow Leopard, Apple said it refined 90% of the foundational "projects" that were built into Mac OS X. Apple pitched the update as offering a more responsive Finder app, an improved Mail app that loads emails up to twice as fast as before, up to 80% faster Time Machine backups, and a 64-bit version of Safari that was up to 50% faster than the previous version. Snow Leopard also took up around half as much disk space as Leopard.<br/>
<br/>
You can watch Serlet speak more about Snow Leopard at WWDC 2009 below.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FTfChHwGFf0?si=W8T4DNbdZse49D_N" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-15-years/">Mac OS X Snow Leopard Launched 15 Years Ago Today With &#039;0 New Features&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/mac-os-x-snow-leopard-launched-15-years-ago-today-with-0-new-features.2434641/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 202 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2434638/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 14:41:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Blurb</category>
		<category>Safari Technology Preview</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">released a new update</a> for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a>, the experimental browser that was <a href="http://www.macrumors.com/2016/03/30/apple-safari-technology-preview-browser/">first introduced</a> in March 2016. Apple designed &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; to allow users to test features that are planned for future release versions of the Safari browser.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/Safari-Technology-Preview-Updated-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960117" /><br/>
&zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; 202 includes fixes and updates for Accessibility, CSS, Editing, JavaScript, Media, Rendering, SVG, Web Animations, Web API, Web Assembly, and WebDriver. <br/>
<br/>
The current &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; release is compatible with machines running <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta. Set to launch this fall, &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; is the newest version of macOS that Apple is working on.  <br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; update is available through the Software Update mechanism in System Preferences or System Settings to anyone who has <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/download/">downloaded the browser</a> from Apple's website. Complete release notes for the update are available <a href="https://developer.apple.com/safari/technology-preview/release-notes/">on the Safari Technology Preview website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's aim with &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; is to gather feedback from developers and users on its browser development process. &zwnj;Safari Technology Preview&zwnj; can run side-by-side with the existing Safari browser and while it is designed for developers, it does not require a developer account to download and use. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/safari-technology-preview/">Safari Technology Preview</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/28/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202/">Apple Releases Safari Technology Preview 202 With Bug Fixes and Performance Improvements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-safari-technology-preview-202-with-bug-fixes-and-performance-improvements.2434638/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
