<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 03:00:29 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Next Year&#039;s iPhone 17 Unlikely to Feature TSMC&#039;s First 2nm Chip</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-17-unlikely-to-get-2nm-chip/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-years-iphone-17-unlikely-to-feature-tsmcs-first-2nm-chip.2431471/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 02:13:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-17-unlikely-to-get-2nm-chip/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		<category>Phone Chip Expert</category>
		<category>2nm</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Reports that next year's iPhone 17 will adopt TSMC's next-generation 2nm process are "fake news," a reputable source of accurate predictions about Apple's plans claimed on Monday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
According to a post by Weibo user "Phone Chip Expert," the 2nm process won't go into mass production until the end of 2025. The account holder, who claims to have 25 years of experience in the integrated circuit industry, including work on Intel's Pentium processors, suggests the iPhone 17 will therefore still use TSMC's 3nm process. <br/>
<br/>
"The 2nm process won't be mass-produced until the end of 2025, so the iPhone 17 definitely can't catch up," read a machine translation of Phone Chip Expert's <a href="https://weibo.com/1833340431/OnJ3ojmDk">post</a>. "It won't be until the iPhone 18 that a 2nm processor will be used." <br/>
<br/>
"Anyone who has seen the capacity planning chart will know that this is yet another report from an unscrupulous media outlet," added the user, commenting on an article by <em><a href="https://new.qq.com/rain/a/20240715A05A7900">Zhitong Finance</a></em> that repeated claims recently made by Taiwanese newspapers based on "industry sources." <br/>
<br/>
TSMC plans to begin volume production of 2nm chips next year, but multiple reports out of Taiwan suggested that the company had been accelerating the process ahead of schedule to secure a stable yield for mass production. Apple is TSMC's main client, and it is typically the first to get TSMC's new chips. Apple acquired all of TSMC's 3nm chips in 2023 for iPhones, iPads, and Macs, for example.<br/>
<br/>
The 2nm fabrication process, also known simply as "N2," is expected to offer a 10 to 15 percent speed improvement at the same power or a 25 to 30 percent power reduction at the same speed compared to chips made with the supplier's ‌3nm‌ technology. The A17 Pro chip in Apple's iPhone 15 Pro models is manufactured with TSMC's first-generation 3nm process, known as N3B. Apple's M4 chip, which recently debuted in the new iPad Pro, uses an enhanced version of this ‌3nm‌ technology.<br/>
<br/>
Code in iOS 18 has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/02/iphone-16-models-a18-chip/">confirmed</a> that all four iPhone 16 models are set to use Apple's next-generation A18 chip, based on TSMC's N3E process. N3E is TSMC's second-generation 3nm chip fabrication process, which is less expensive and has improved yield compared to TSMC's first-generation 3nm process. <br/>
<br/>
The Weibo user contesting claims that 2nm will be ready for the iPhone 17 has a track record of accurate predictions. Phone Chip Expert was the first to reveal that the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2015/09/28/iphone-7-already-rumored-to-be-waterproof/">iPhone 7 would be water-resistant</a> and that the standard iPhone 14 models would continue to use the A15 Bionic chip, while the more advanced A16 chip would be exclusive to the ‌iPhone 14‌ Pro models. These forecasts were later confirmed by multiple credible sources and were proven correct when the products were released.<br/>
<br/>
More recently, Phone Chip Expert was the first source of information about Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-developing-its-own-ai-server-processor/">developing its own AI server processor using TSMC's 3nm process</a>, targeting mass production by the second half of 2025.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/phone-chip-expert/">Phone Chip Expert</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2nm/">2nm</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/16/iphone-17-unlikely-to-get-2nm-chip/">Next Year&#039;s iPhone 17 Unlikely to Feature TSMC&#039;s First 2nm Chip</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/next-years-iphone-17-unlikely-to-feature-tsmcs-first-2nm-chip.2431471/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Adds &#039;Recovered&#039; Album in Photos to Restore Lost or Damaged Photos and Videos</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-recovered-album-photos/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-adds-recovered-album-in-photos-to-restore-lost-or-damaged-photos-and-videos.2431439/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 15:26:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-recovered-album-photos/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> include a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app feature designed to help users recover images and videos that are lost or damaged, providing a way to get missing content back.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/icloud-photos.jpg" alt="" width="836" height="470" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-897381" /><br/>
There is a "Recovered" album in the Utilities section of &zwnj;Photos&zwnj;, and it shows up if there are pictures or videos on a user's device that are not part of their &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; Library. If you see the Recovered album in your &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app, tapping into it will provide an option to permanently delete or restore any pictures or video stored in the album.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;Photos&zwnj; and videos can be lost due to database corruption issues, images taken with a camera app that did not properly get saved to the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; library, or third-party apps that are provided with access to manage a Photo Library. Here's how to recover a lost image or video:<br/>
<ol><br/>
 	<li>Open the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app and tap into Albums.</li><br/>
 	<li>Scroll down to Utilities, and choose the Recovered album.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on a photo or video in the album, or use Select to select multiple items.</li><br/>
 	<li>Tap on Permanently Delete or Restore to Library.</li><br/>
</ol><br/>
When upgrading to &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, or &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, or Mac will automatically scan for photos and videos that are able to be recovered, providing immediate access to any missing content.<br/>
<br/>
Note that the Recovered album only shows up in the Utilities section of the &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; app if lost photos or videos are located on a device. If there are none, you will not see the album.<br/>
<br/>
With iOS 17.5.1 and iPadOS 17.5.1, there was a fix for an unusual bug related to a database corruption issue. After installing iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5, some users saw long-deleted images reappearing in their Photo Library. Apple later said this was due to a database corruption issue that had caused the photos to reappear even after being deleted.<br/>
<br/>
The Recovered album feature in the latest software updates should prevent something like this from happening again, while also giving users access to photos and videos that are in limbo.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;, and &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; betas are available to developers and public beta testers at this time. The software updates will see a public launch this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-recovered-album-photos/">iOS 18 Adds &#039;Recovered&#039; Album in Photos to Restore Lost or Damaged Photos and Videos</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-adds-recovered-album-in-photos-to-restore-lost-or-damaged-photos-and-videos.2431439/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-ios-18-and-ipados-18-public-betas.2431427/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:16:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today provided the first betas of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> to public beta testers, bringing the new software to the general public for the first time since the Worldwide Developers Conference in June. Apple has seeded three developer betas so far, and the first public beta includes the same content that's in the third developer beta.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PixQ3st8R7I" title="iOS 18 Public Beta Out Now! (So Many NEW Features)" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Public beta testers who have <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signed up for Apple's beta testing program</a> can download the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; updates by opening up the Settings app, going to General, tapping into the Software Update section and selecting the &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; Public Beta option.<br/>
<br/>
Note that betas can have bugs, battery issues, and other complications, so it is wise to install the software on a secondary device or make a backup in case you need to downgrade back to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, which are AI features deeply integrated into the operating system. Not all functionality is available at this time, but it brings Writing Tools for rewriting, polishing, proofreading, and summarizing text across apps, and you can generate custom images with Image Playground. There are custom emoji available through the Genmoji feature, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting entirely overhauled. Note that Apple Intelligence isn't yet live in the betas. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/ipaos-18-image-playground.jpg" alt="" width="2150" height="1210" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957173" /><br/>
Along with the AI features (which will be limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and M-series iPads), &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; brings a redesigned <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> with the option to rearrange app icons and widgets with open spaces, plus there's a tint option and new darker colors for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-dark-mode/">Dark Mode</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Home-Screen-Feature-1.5.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957459" /><br/>
Control Center has been revamped and you can pick and choose what you want to have front and center from the new Controls Gallery. There are multiple pages so you can group related controls, and you can customize sizes. As part of this update, the Flashlight and Camera icons on the Lock Screen can be swapped out, and you can also choose Control Center options for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Action Button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/control-center-ios-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954460" /><br/>
The Messages app supports scheduling texts, you can use any emoji for the Tapback feature, and you can send messages via satellite. There are text effects you can use for any word, phrase, or emoji, plus formatting like bold and italic is an option. For texts with Android users, Apple now supports <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/rcs/">RCS</a>, which basically means you won't run into issues with sending images and files, plus you can see typing indicators and read receipts and send texts over Wi-Fi.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iMessage-Send-Later-iOS-18.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955789" /><br/>
Safari is able to summarize webpages and show you important info at a glance, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app has been overhauled to focus more on surfacing your best photos. A dedicated Passwords app makes it easier to get to your saved passwords and logins, and you can now lock any app with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-18-safari-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957055" /><br/>
There are a ton of new features in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj; that aren't mentioned here, so for a more in-depth look make sure to check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a> and our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-public-beta-1/">Apple Releases First iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 Public Betas</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-ios-18-and-ipados-18-public-betas.2431427/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2431426/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:15:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> update to its public beta testing group, giving the general public a chance to try out the new operating system's features ahead of its fall launch. The first public beta includes the same content as the third developer beta.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macos-sequoia-iphone-mirroring.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956750" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; from the Software Update section of the System Settings app after <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">signing up on Apple's beta testing website</a> and opting into the public beta under the Beta Updates section.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;'s biggest feature is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which is designed to let you control your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac using your keyboard and mouse. You can see notifications and use your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps even when your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is tucked away and locked, and later this year, you'll be able to use the feature to drag and drop apps from your Mac to your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
Window tiling has been improved to make it easier to get multiple windows on your Mac in a way that works for you, Safari can summarize websites and show you highlights, and the Messages app supports scheduling messages and using the Tapback feature with any emoji.<br/>
<br/>
There's a new Passwords app for managing your passwords, logins, and passkeys, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app has a new design, the Notes app supports audio transcription and summarization, and you can also type in any equation and get it solved automatically.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; supports all of the new Apple Intelligence features that are also coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, offering all kinds of quality of life improvements. Writing tools help you proofread and polish your writing across apps, you can create unique images with Image Playground, and make up your own emoji with Genmoji. &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; includes a Clean Up tool for removing unwanted images, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> will use AI for better language understanding and contextual relevance. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will even be able to consult ChatGPT for complicated queries.<br/>
<br/>
There are a long list of additional features coming to &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">more information available in our dedicated roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-macos-sequoia-public-beta/">Apple Releases First macOS Sequoia Public Beta With iPhone Mirroring and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-macos-sequoia-public-beta-with-iphone-mirroring-and-more.2431426/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases First watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/watchos-11-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2431428/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:14:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/watchos-11-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a> to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to give the new features a try ahead of when the software launches this fall.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/watchos-11-vitals.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957264" /><br/>
&zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; can be downloaded after signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's beta software website</a> and upgrading your <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the public beta version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>. You'll need to open up the Watch app on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, go to General, select Software Update, and choose the &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj; Public Beta option under Beta Updates.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;watchOS 11&zwnj;, Apple added a new Vitals app that can be used to give you a daily overview of your health metrics, letting you know if anything is out of the ordinary. It compares information collected at night like heart rate, sleep, respiratory rate, and oxygen level to your levels over the previous weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Smart Stack has new widgets like Translate and Shazam, plus it's smarter because it is able to suggest widgets based on time, date, location, and daily routine. Interactive widgets let you access app features from the Smart Stack, and it also supports Live Activities.<br/>
<br/>
Training Load is a new way of measuring how the intensity and duration of workouts impact the body over time, with Apple providing an effort level for cardio-based workouts to help you know when to rest and when to push harder.<br/>
<br/>
You can now customize your Activity Ring requirements for different days of the week, and Apple added support for rest days. Taking a break from activity will no longer ruin a streak because you can pause for a day, a week, a month, or more.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features include more workout types, Check In for Messages, a revamped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> watch face, improvements to Double Tap, and more, with additional information <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">available in our watchOS 11 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/watchos-11-public-beta/">Apple Releases First watchOS 11 Public Beta With Vitals App and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-first-watchos-11-public-beta-with-vitals-app-and-more.2431428/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds First tvOS 18 Public Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta.2431430/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:13:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first public beta of tvOS 18, giving the general public a chance to try out the new features ahead of the software's fall launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-796083" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/04/apple-tv-4k-design-triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can download the tvOS 18 beta by opening up the Settings app on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, choosing the Software Updates section under System, and then toggling on the Get Public Beta Updates option. Signing up on <a href="https://beta.apple.com/sp/betaprogram/">Apple's public beta website</a> is required to get the option to show up.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 isn't as feature rich as some of Apple's other updates, but it brings a new InSight feature to the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. InSight is similar to Amazon X-Ray, providing real-time information about actors, music, and more in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a> shows and movies.<br/>
<br/>
The Enhanced Dialogue feature uses computational audio and machine learning to better boost vocal clarity over background noise and music, plus it works with built-in TV speakers, AirPods, and other Bluetooth devices. Subtitles have been tweaked to show up automatically when relevant, such as when the TV is muted.<br/>
<br/>
Apple added new screen savers and made it easier to swap between them, plus there's 21:9 aspect ratio support for projectors and an option for Live Captions during <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS 18 is limited to public beta testers and developers right now, but it will see a public launch this fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta/">Apple Seeds First tvOS 18 Public Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-first-tvos-18-public-beta.2431430/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Revised iOS 18 Beta 3 Reverts Emoji Changes</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-beta-3-emoji-changes-reverted/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revised-ios-18-beta-3-reverts-emoji-changes.2431423/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 12:33:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-beta-3-emoji-changes-reverted/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The revised third beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> that Apple released today eliminates the emoji and sticker changes that Apple introduced with the initial third beta release.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ios-18-emoji-stickers-memoji.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-957882" /><br/>
In the prior beta, stickers behaved like emoji and could be added right inline with your messages, rather than only being available as large, stand alone message additions or drag and drop add-ons to texts. You could type a message and add a little sticker or Memoji to the end of it rather than an emoji, but Apple has pulled back this change, along with the interface changes that were introduced.<br/>
<br/>
Emoji, Memoji, and stickers were all combined, and could be navigated using small icons at the bottom of the emoji picker, plus emoji were displayed larger than before, with fewer on a single screen. Apple added dedicated sections for stickers and Memoji rather than showing stickers only in the Recents section, and both stickers and Memoji could be created from the emoji window. It was a design that made both Memoji and stickers quicker to access and use.<br/>
<br/>
With the revised version of beta 3, the emoji picker has been reverted to the beta 2 design. It's not clear why Apple made the change, but it's likely temporary. Sometimes Apple adds features in the beta and then pulls them to implement further refinements before reintroducing them at a later time, so we could see the emoji picker changes re-added in a later beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/ios-18-beta-3-emoji-changes-reverted/">Revised iOS 18 Beta 3 Reverts Emoji Changes</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/revised-ios-18-beta-3-reverts-emoji-changes.2431423/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy&#039;s Black Friday in July Sale Takes Up to &#36;700 Off M3 MacBook Pro for Members</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buys-m3-macbook-pro-discounts/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-black-friday-in-july-sale-takes-up-to-700-off-m3-macbook-pro-for-members.2431410/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:05:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buys-m3-macbook-pro-discounts/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy's "<a href="https://howl.me/cmFVZNJq4IC">Black Friday in July</a>" sale is in full swing today, and in addition to a few <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buy-low-prices-m1-ipad-air/">iPad Air discounts</a> we shared earlier, there are also some steep markdowns on the M3 MacBook Pro. You will need a <a href="https://howl.me/cmFVLw9QMH4">My Best Buy Plus or Total membership</a> in order to get some of these deals.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/macbook-pro-january.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-931746" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's deals include all-time low prices on the 14-inch and 16-inch models, and the best discounts will be found on the larger screen computers. The 16-inch M3 MacBook Pro is currently discounted by &#36;500 for all customers on Best Buy, but if you have a My Best Buy Plus/Total membership, you can <a href="https://howl.me/cmFVSBa773D">add up to an extra &#36;200 off select models</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVQGyVHqc"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;700 OFF</div>M3 MacBook Pro at Best Buy</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also find &#36;300 off 14-inch models on Best Buy this week, and these deals do not require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership. We've collected all of the M3 MacBook Pro discounts in the list below, and remember that the Black Friday in July sale ends Wednesday, so be sure to place any orders before that day.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>14-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS5KrLaL8">M3 Pro 512GB</a> - &#36;1,699.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS546rWne">M3 Pro 1TB</a> - &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFS6pLDH28">M3 Max 1TB</a> - &#36;2,899.00 (&#36;300 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h2>16-inch MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVRzZBpRY">M3 Pro, 18GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;1,899.00 for members (&#36;600 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVR8jvMLx">M3 Pro, 36GB RAM, 512GB</a> - &#36;2,299.00 for members (&#36;600 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVSBa773D">M3 Max, 36GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;2,799.00 for members (&#36;700 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmFVTandF8t">M3 Max, 48GB RAM, 1TB</a> - &#36;3,299.00 for members (&#36;700 off)</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buys-m3-macbook-pro-discounts/">Best Buy&#039;s Black Friday in July Sale Takes Up to &#36;700 Off M3 MacBook Pro for Members</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buys-black-friday-in-july-sale-takes-up-to-700-off-m3-macbook-pro-for-members.2431410/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock for Mac Hits Record Low &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-for-mac-hits-record-low-99-99-price-180-off.2431403/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:31:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC this week has knocked the price of the popular <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock</a> down to &#36;99.99, from its original price of &#36;279.99. This is a match of the all-time low price on the accessory, which we last tracked way back in April. You'll see this price once you add the accessory to your cart and head to the checkout screen, where an automatic coupon will be applied.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/owc-docks-white-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944277" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Besides this dock, you'll find a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">large collection of accessories on sale</a> at this time on OWC, including USB-C hubs, external drives and enclosures, and internal memory upgrade kits for Mac.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;180 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock, this accessory features two Thunderbolt 3 ports, five USB Type-A ports, one USB Type-C port, one Mini DisplayPort port, one gigabit Ethernet port, one S/PDIF digital audio output port, and one 3.5mm stereo audio input/output port. There are also two memory card slots for microSD and SD cards.<br/>
<br/>
All of the devices listed below are in new condition at OWC, although the retailer does provide various item condition options for anyone who might want to save money by purchasing open box items. Be sure to visit <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">OWC's sale landing page</a> to browse the full sale, which also features deals on cables, Mac accessories, keyboards, and headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDSDRDR%2F">Atlas Dual SD Card Reader</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;99.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T04C%2F">4TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;124.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T08C%2F">8TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;217.76, down from &#36;394.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;74.74, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;147.74, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;2.99, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock/">OWC&#039;s 14-Port Thunderbolt Dock for Mac Hits Record Low &#36;99.99 Price (&#36;180 Off)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/owcs-14-port-thunderbolt-dock-for-mac-hits-record-low-99-99-price-180-off.2431403/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Revised Third Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/macos-sequoia-revised-third-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-revised-third-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers.2431401/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:11:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/macos-sequoia-revised-third-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sequoia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded a revised third beta of macOS 15 Sequoia to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after the initial <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/apple-seeds-macos-sequoia-beta-3/">release of the third beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955370" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/macOS-Sequoia-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a> beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; includes <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> Mirroring, which allows you to control your locked &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; from your Mac. You can open and use &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps, interact with notifications, and drag and drop files between your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and Mac and vice versa.<br/>
<br/>
There are new options for window tiling, and dragging a window to the edge of the display will suggest a tiled location to make it easier to use multiple apps at once. Apple is adding a Passwords app for managing passwords, Safari can summarize websites and surface key information, and Notes has support for live audio transcription and math equations.<br/>
<br/>
All of the Apple Intelligence features coming to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> will also be available in &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;, but Apple does not plan to add these until later in the beta testing process. Apple Intelligence includes Writing Tools for editing, proofreading, and summarizing text in apps, and an Image Playground allows for AI images to be created from prompts.<br/>
<br/>
Custom emoji or "Genmoji" can be created for any situation and used just like emoji, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> is getting much smarter. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; will be able to do more in apps and will better understand requests, especially those made in regard to on-screen content.<br/>
<br/>
The updated third beta comes as we await the launch of a public beta for &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj;. Apple said that a version of &zwnj;macOS Sequoia&zwnj; would be available for public beta testers at some point in July.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sequoia.246">macOS Sequoia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/macos-sequoia-revised-third-beta/">Apple Seeds Revised Third Beta of macOS Sequoia to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-revised-third-beta-of-macos-sequoia-to-developers.2431401/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Revised Third Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-revised-third-beta/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-revised-third-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers.2431400/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 10:09:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-revised-third-beta/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded updated third betas <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a> to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-3/">Apple initially released the third betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Generic-iOS-18-Feature-Real-Mock.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954594" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;/&zwnj;iPadOS 18&zwnj;‌ Developer Beta setting. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; introduces Apple Intelligence, a set of AI features that are built deeply into the operating system. Apple Intelligence won't be coming until later in the beta testing process, but it includes features for refining and editing writing, generating images and emoji, and most notably, improving <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> and search. &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; is gaining a better understanding of natural language, improved contextual awareness, and the personal assistant will integrate with ChatGPT to answer more complex queries.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Intelligence features are limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models and iPads with an M-series chip, but there are a number of other features that are coming. Apple is allowing users to rearrange Home screen apps to have open spaces, plus there's a dark mode for app icons and tinting options.<br/>
<br/>
The Control Center is customizable and third-party developers can add controls for their apps, with the Lock Screen Flashlight and Camera icons able to be replaced or removed. Messages is gaining Rich Communication Services support to improve conversations with Android users, the option to schedule texts to be sent later, new text effects, messages over satellite when there's no cellular, and the option to use any emoji for Tapback responses.<br/>
<br/>
There's a dedicated Passwords app for logins, passkeys, Wi-Fi passwords, and verification codes, and there's now an option to lock and hide apps, which means they can't be opened without secondary <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mask-face-id/">Face ID</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> authentication even when your phone is unlocked.<br/>
<br/>
Safari has a highlights feature that summarizes articles and surfaces key information on websites, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app interface has been overhauled, and there's a new Tap to Cash feature for privately and securely transferring money using Apple Cash. Other features include equation solving and voice memo transcription in Notes, a game mode for improving game performance, and an option to respond to &zwnj;Siri&zwnj; on AirPods with head gestures.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is only available to registered developers at the current time, but this revised third beta comes as we are expecting a public beta. Apple said in June that a public beta would be made available sometime in July. <div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-18.244">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-18.245">iPadOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-releases-ios-18-revised-third-beta/">Apple Seeds Revised Third Betas of iOS 18 and iPadOS 18 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-revised-third-betas-of-ios-18-and-ipados-18-to-developers.2431400/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Buy Kicks Off &#039;Black Friday in July&#039; With Record Low Prices on M1 iPad Air</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buy-low-prices-m1-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-kicks-off-black-friday-in-july-with-record-low-prices-on-m1-ipad-air.2431385/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 07:35:11 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buy-low-prices-m1-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking deals on Apple's <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYtvdOtL2">fifth-generation iPad Air</a>, which are only available on Best Buy. This sale includes nearly every model of the M1 iPad Air on sale at an all-time low price, with as much as &#36;250 off select models. The deals are part of Best Buy's Prime Day-like "<a href="https://howl.me/cmFRZqv6lnW">Black Friday in July</a>" sale, which lasts through Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/m1-ipad-air-fathers-day.jpg" alt="" width="3840" height="2160" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-954135" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Starting with the 64GB Wi-Fi M1 iPad Air, Best Buy has this model for <a href="https://howl.me/cmtYtvdOtL2"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.99. This is an all-time low price on this model of the 2022 iPad Air, and it's available in three colors. You'll also find the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air on sale for &#36;499.99, down from &#36;749.99, which is about &#36;50 cheaper than the previous record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmtYtvdOtL2"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFRRhzMOZI"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;250 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad Air for &#36;499.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmFRR6RSPCN"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad Air for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple introduced new M2 iPad Air models in May, which is why we're seeing steep discounts on the previous generation models more often. You can still <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/early-prime-day-m2-ipad-air/">save a bit of money on the 2024 models</a> if you're interested in owning the latest version.<br/>
<br/>
Best Buy's <a href="https://howl.me/cmFRZqv6lnW">Black Friday in July</a> event has much more on sale than just the iPad Air, including <a href="https://howl.me/cmFR5CIOn2i">other Apple products</a> like MacBooks and Apple Watches. You can also find great deals on TVs, video games, appliances, headphones, smartphones, sound bars, streaming devices, computers, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/best-buy-low-prices-m1-ipad-air/">Best Buy Kicks Off &#039;Black Friday in July&#039; With Record Low Prices on M1 iPad Air</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-buy-kicks-off-black-friday-in-july-with-record-low-prices-on-m1-ipad-air.2431385/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Amazon Prime Day: M3 MacBook Air Sees New Record Low Prices With &#36;200 Off Every Model</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/prime-day-m3-macbook-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-m3-macbook-air-sees-new-record-low-prices-with-200-off-every-model.2431379/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:28:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/prime-day-m3-macbook-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon today has kicked off <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">early Prime Day deals</a> on Apple's 2024 M3 MacBook Air, with new record low prices on both the 13-inch and 15-inch models. This is the first time we've tracked discounts on these computers in a few weeks, and they're reaching up to &#36;200 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m3-macbook-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958729" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;898.99</strong></a> for the 8GB RAM/256GB SSD 13-inch MacBook Air, which is down from &#36;1,099.00. For the bigger model, prices start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,099.00</strong></a> for the 8GB RAM/256GB SSD 15-inch MacBook Air, down from &#36;1,299.00.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;898.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>15-inch MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;1,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Shoppers should note that Best Buy is offering an extra &#36;50 in savings on these computers, but you'll need to have a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership in order to see the discounts. Otherwise, if you don't have a membership, you can find matching prices on every M3 MacBook Air at Best Buy.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23V2ZK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;898.99, down from &#36;1,099.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX22NCHQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQBNsFbNk">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX246FNZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,299.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQCCPC5E3">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>15-inch M3 MacBook Air</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23GFMJ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 256GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,099.00, down from &#36;1,299.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDrLzdh5">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX23P9S7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">8GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,299.00, down from &#36;1,499.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQDI1Z9Ul">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX24BN3L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">16GB RAM 512GB SSD</a> - &#36;1,499.00, down from &#36;1,699.00 (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQD4AX4A0">matched at Best Buy</a>)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking to spend a little less, and are fine with investing in a previous generation model, Amazon also has great deals on the 2022 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. You can get the 256GB model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;799.00</strong></a> (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQA1aRSRo">matched at Best Buy</a>) and the 512GB model for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3C5H787%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;999.00</strong></a> (<a href="https://howl.me/cmFQBiXyWV2">also matched at Best Buy</a>), and they're both &#36;200 off and all-time low prices.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/prime-day-m3-macbook-air/">Amazon Prime Day: M3 MacBook Air Sees New Record Low Prices With &#36;200 Off Every Model</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/amazon-prime-day-m3-macbook-air-sees-new-record-low-prices-with-200-off-every-model.2431379/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color.2431376/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 06:09:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>New Banner (Featured)</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/07/apple-introduces-homepod-mini-in-midnight/">announced</a> that the existing HomePod mini is now available in a Midnight color option, which replaces the nearly-identical Space Gray color previously offered. The speaker remains available in Blue, Orange, White, and Yellow as well.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/HomePod-Mini-Midnight-1.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958753" /><br/>
Apple now offers both the full-sized second-generation HomePod and the HomePod mini in Midnight, so this minor change brings some consistency to the lineup. Apple did not mention any other changes to the HomePod mini today, and the speaker remains priced at &#36;99 in the U.S. for all of the color options.<br/>
<br/>
The new Midnight color option <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-homepod/homepod-mini">can be ordered on Apple.com</a> starting today, and it will be available at Apple Store locations in the U.S., Canada, China, Singapore, and 28 other countries and regions starting July 17.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first released the HomePod mini in November 2020, and it has yet to release a second-generation model of the speaker.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/homepod-mini-midnight-color/">Apple Releases HomePod Mini in New Midnight Color</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-homepod-mini-in-new-midnight-color.2431376/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Series Is Just Two Months Away: Everything We Know</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-is-just-two-months-away-everything-we-know.2431371/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 04:44:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple typically releases its new iPhone series around mid-September, which means we are about two months out from the launch of the iPhone 16. Like the iPhone 15 series, this year's lineup is expected to stick with four models – iPhone 16, iPhone 16 Plus, iPhone 16 Pro, and iPhone 16 Pro Max – although there are plenty of design differences and new features to take into account.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/12/iPhone-16-Pro-Sizes-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-927877" /><br/>
To bring you up to speed, we've summarized below the biggest iPhone 16 rumors we've covered so far here on <em>MacRumors</em>. For more details, follow the links, or dive into our dedicated roundups for both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    1. Larger Displays</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Biggest Ever iPhones</span><br><br/>
This year's iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are rumored to be getting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">bigger display sizes</a>, increasing to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. For comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively. The new display sizes would be the largest ever for the iPhone.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
    2. Vertical Camera Layout</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
Apple's iPhone 16 base models will feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-iphone-16-slim-camera-bump/">vertical camera arrangement</a> with a pill-shaped raised surface, instead of a diagonal camera arrangement like the iPhone 15. The new camera bump features two separate camera rings for the Wide and Ultra Wide cameras. The vertical camera layout is expected to enable Spatial Video recording, which is currently limited to the iPhone 15 Pro models.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
3. Battery Changes</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">All iPhone 16 Models</span><br><br/>
One rumor suggests the ‌iPhone 16‌ and iPhone 16 Pro Max will feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/07/some-iphone-16s-to-feature-bigger-batteries/">larger batteries</a> than their predecessors, but the ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus may have reduced capacity. The iPhone 16 is said to have a 6% increase over the iPhone 15, with the iPhone 16 Pro Max gaining a 5% increase. In contrast, the iPhone 16 Plus is rumored to have a 9% reduction in capacity. On the other hand, Apple could also potentially use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/25/iphone-15-hybrid-lens-rumor/">stacked battery technology</a> to increase energy density and prolong lifespan across the lineup. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
4. Capture Button</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">New Camera Capabilities</span><br><br/>
All iPhone 16 models will have a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/18/iphone-16-capture-button-touch-pressure/">Capture Button</a>" dedicated to triggering image or video capture. The button will add features like the ability to zoom in and out by swiping left and right on the button, focus on a subject with a light press, and activate a recording with a more forceful press. The Capture Button will be located on the bottom right side of the ‌iPhone 16, and will take the place of the mmWave antenna on U.S. ‌iPhone‌ models, with the antenna relocating to the left side of the device below the volume and Action buttons.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
5. Ultra Wide Lens Upgrade</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro & iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro models are expected to feature an upgraded <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">48-megapixel Ultra Wide camera lens</a>, which should allow it to capture more light, resulting in improved photos when shooting in 0.5× mode, especially in low-light environments. This also means that iPhone 16 Pro models should be able to shoot 48-megapixel ProRAW photos in Ultra Wide mode. These photos retain more detail in the image file for more editing flexibility, and can be printed at large sizes. The iPhone 16 Pro Max is also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/iphone-16-pro-dual-48mp-cameras/">rumored</a> to boast a bigger main camera thanks to an advanced custom 48-megapixel Sony IMX903 sensor.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
6. Super Telephoto Camera</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro Max could be the first to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/18/iphone-16-pro-max-super-telephoto-camera/">super telephoto periscope camera</a> for dramatically increased optical zoom. "Super" or "ultra" telephoto usually describes cameras with a focal length of over 300mm. The current telephoto lens is equivalent to a 77mm lens, so if accurate, there could be a notable increase in zoom capabilities. Super telephoto cameras are often used for sports and wild animal photography, but the extremely soft backgrounds they create also make them useful for portrait photography, providing there is enough distance between the subject and the photographer.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
7. Faster Wi-Fi Support</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Wi-Fi 6E & Wi-Fi 7</span><br><br/>
Apple's 2024 iPhone Pro models are expected to get <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/15/iphone-16-pro-wifi-7-48mp-ultra-wide-rumors/">Wi-Fi 7 in the Pro models</a>, enabling data transfer over the 2.4GHz, 5GHz, and 6GHz bands simultaneously. This should result in faster Wi-Fi speeds, lower latency, and more reliable connectivity. With technologies such as 4K QAM, Wi-Fi 7 is  also expected to offer peak data transfer speeds of over 40 Gbps, a 4× increase over Wi-Fi 6E. Meanwhile, the iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">rumored to support Wi-Fi 6E</a>, which works with the 6 GHz band, enabling faster wireless speeds and reduced signal interference.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
8. New A18 Series Chips</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">All iPhone 16 Models</span><br><br/>
Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/27/iphone-16-lineup-a18-a18-pro-chips-analyst-says/">next-generation A18 Pro chip</a> is expected to be manufactured with TSMC's second-generation 3nm process, known as N3E. All four iPhone 16 models will be equipped with A18-branded chips, according to rumors, but Apple could still differentiate between the standard models and the Pro models, even giving the chips separate A18 and A18 Pro names. It makes sense for all four ‌iPhone 16‌ models to have the same A18 chip because of the Apple Intelligence features set to debut in iOS 18. Apple Intelligence requires a high-powered chip for the AI features to run on-device. At this time, only the ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌ and Pro Max are able to use Apple Intelligence.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
9. 5G Qualcomm Modem</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro & iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
Apple is expected to use <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/12/iphone-16-pro-5g-advanced-rumor/">Qualcomm's latest Snapdragon X75 modem</a> in this year's Pro and Pro Max models. The Snapdragon X75 includes improved carrier aggregation and other technology advancements for faster 5G download and upload speeds compared to the X70, which is used in iPhone 15 models. The modem's combined mmWave and sub-6GHz 5G transceiver also takes up 25% less circuit board space, and is said to use up to 20% less power. The standard iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus are expected to retain the Snapdragon X70 modem.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
10. Tetraprism Lens</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro</span><br><br/>
Both iPhone 16 Pro models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">expected to feature 5x optical zoom</a>, which is currently exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro Max. Apple's tetraprism lens system has a "folded" design that allows it to fit inside the smartphone, enabling up to 5x optical zoom and up to 25x digital zoom. In contrast, the current smaller iPhone 15 Pro is limited to up to 3x optical zoom, which is in line with the iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
11. Micro-Lens Technology</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">More Efficient OLED</span><br><br/>
Apple is said to be weighing up the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">use of micro-lens technology</a> to maintain or increase the brightness of OLED displays on next year's iPhone 16 models while potentially reducing their power consumption. MLA works by using a uniform pattern of billions of lenses inside the panel that reduces internal reflections. These lenses turn the path of light reflected backwards from the inside of the panel towards the screen, which can serve either to increase perceived brightness while maintaining the same level of power consumption, or maintain brightness levels while consuming less power compared to conventional OLED panels at the same luminance.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
12. Action Button</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 15 Pro models include an Action Button, and in 2024, the Action Button is expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/30/iphone-16-action-button-all-models/">expanded to the standard iPhone 16 models</a>. The Action Button used across the iPhone 16 lineup will be identical to the iPhone 15 Pro Action Button. The Action button, which replaces the traditional mute switch, can perform multiple functions such as activating the Flashlight, turning on the Camera, launching a Shortcut, enabling or disabling a Focus mode, using Translate, turning on/off Silent Mode, and more.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
13. 40W Fast Charging and 20W MagSafe</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Both iPhone 16 Pro Models</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will support 40W wired fast charging and 20W MagSafe charging, according to a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/iphone-16-pro-40w-fast-charging-20w-magsafe/">recurring rumor</a>. Right now, iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro models are capable of up to 27W peak charging speeds with an appropriate USB-C power adapter, while official MagSafe chargers from Apple and authorized third parties can wirelessly charge the iPhone 15 models at up to 15W. The charging boost is expected to balance and improve the problem of increasing charging time caused by the increase in battery capacity. <br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
14. Upgraded Microphone</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Enhanced Siri</span><br><br/>
Apple is said to be planning a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/12/07/apple-iphone-16-microphone-upgrade-siri-ai/">significant upgrade</a> to the iPhone 16 microphone to improve the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-4-apple-intelligence-powered-siri/">Apple Intelligence-enhanced Siri experience</a>, which will include contextual awareness, semantic indexing, app control, and on-screen awareness. Apple's Siri AI ambitions will heavily rely on improved voice input processing, and the new mic is expected to offer significantly enhanced signal-to-noise ratio.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
15. New Thermal Design</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Reduced Heat</span><br><br/>
Apple is rumored to be working on a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/iphone-16-new-thermal-design/">graphene thermal system</a> for the ‌iPhone 16‌ lineup, while the ‌iPhone 16‌ Pro models could add metal battery casings to reduce overheating. Graphene has high thermal conductivity, surpassing that of copper, which is currently used in iPhone heat-sinks. Apple has been filing patents related to using graphene for thermal management for some time. The move could be in response to widely encountered overheating issues experienced with the iPhone 15 Pro, which Apple addressed through a software update.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
16. Expanded Storage</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Both iPhone 16 Pro Models</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max will be available with double the maximum storage capacity as the iPhone 15 Pro models, increasing from 1TB to 2TB, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/19/iphone-16-pro-2tb-option-rumor/">according to one rumor</a>. The move is said to be a result of Apple's switch to higher-density Quad-Level Cell (QLC) NAND flash for higher storage models. Apple's use of QLC NAND could allow Apple to fit more storage into a smaller space and it is less expensive than Triple-Level Cell (TLC) NAND, which current iPhones use. On the downside, QLC has comparatively slower read and write speeds.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
17. Increased Memory</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 & iPhone 16 Plus</span><br><br/>
Apple's iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus models have been rumored to both <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/14/iphone-16-and-16-plus-8gb-ram-rumor/">feature 8GB of RAM</a>, an increase over the 6GB of RAM in the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus. More working memory should equate to improved performance for multitasking on the iPhone. Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/19/apple-iphone-15-pro-requirement-apple-intelligence/">hinted</a> that plenty of RAM is required for Apple Intelligence features, so it is perhaps no coincidence that all devices in the iPhone 16 lineup will have at least 8GB of RAM.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
18. Upgraded Neural Engine</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Enhanced Machine Learning</span><br><br/>
Apple's next-generation A18 chips will feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> with "significantly" more cores, according to one Taiwanese report. An upgraded Neural Engine should improve the performance of Apple Intelligence features and machine learning tasks. Apple's iPhone 12 through iPhone 15 models all include a 16-core Neural Engine. Despite no difference in core counts across generations, Apple has still managed to improve their performance in successive models.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
19. Ultra-Thin Bezel Technology</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Maximized Display Size</span><br><br/>
Apple plans to maximize the display size on the iPhone 16 series by using a new ultra-thin bezel technology, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/20/iphone-16-ultra-thin-bezels-rumor/">according to one rumor</a>. Apple will use Border Reduction Structure (BRS) technology to minimize the bezel at the bottom of the display. BRS achieves this by rolling up the internal copper wiring into a more compact package. Apple reportedly plans to apply the borderless display technology to all four iPhone 16 models, but the Pro models will have the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/iphone-16-pro-thinnest-bezels-smartphone/">thinnest bezels of any smartphone</a>, beating the screen border thinness of even its latest iPhone 15 Pro devices.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
20. New Polished Titanium Finish</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">iPhone 16 Pro & iPhone 16 Pro Max</span><br><br/>
Apple will use an improved finishing process for the titanium chassis on the iPhone 16 Pro models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/29/iphone-16-pro-new-polished-titanium-finish/">according to one rumor</a>. The new process will allegedly make the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max look more polished than the iPhone 15 Pro models, which have a brushed finish. The improved manufacturing process will result in a glossy appearance that is more akin to the heavily polished stainless steel material used in previous Pro iPhones. However, the new titanium finish will be less prone to scratches compared to stainless steel.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
21. Reduced Lens Flare</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">Less Photo Artifacts</span><br><br/>
Apple is said to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/iphone-16-pro-camera-reduced-lens-flare/">testing</a> a new anti-reflective optical coating technology for its iPhone cameras that could improve the quality of photos by reducing artifacts like lens flare and ghosting. Apple plans to bring new atomic layer deposition (ALD) equipment into the iPhone camera lens manufacturing process to apply the coating. ALD-applied materials can also protect against environmental damage to the camera lens system without affecting the sensor's ability to capture light effectively.<br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 18px; color: #4A90E2; margin-top: 2px;"><br/>
22. New Colors</span><br><br/>
<span style="font-weight: bold; font-size: 14px; color: #FFFFFF; background-color: #4A90E2; padding: 3px 6px; border-radius: 4px; margin-bottom: 2px;">All iPhone 16 Models</span><br><br/>
The iPhone 16 Pro and ‌iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/iphone-16-lineup-to-come-in-these-two-new-colors/">expected</a> to be available in black, white or silver, gray or "Natural Titanium," and rose. This suggests that the iPhone 15 Pro's Blue Titanium option will be discontinued and replaced with a new rose color. Meanwhile, the ‌iPhone 16‌ and ‌iPhone 16‌ Plus is said to be coming in black, green, pink, blue, and white. Compared to the iPhone 15, this means that white will replace yellow, with the other colors remaining the same.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/iphone-16-series-all-the-latest-rumors/">iPhone 16 Series Is Just Two Months Away: Everything We Know</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-series-is-just-two-months-away-everything-we-know.2431371/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Approves First Retro PC Emulator for iPhone, iPad, and Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-for-iphone-ipad-and-vision-pro.2431363/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 02:50:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-ios/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple this weekend approved free PC emulator "UTM SE" for the App Store on iPhone, iPad, and Vision Pro. The app allows users to emulate old versions of Windows OS, macOS, Linux, and more to fire up classic software and games on Apple devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/utm-se-pc-emulator-ios.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958701" /><br/>
As the first of its kind to be allowed on the App Store, UTM SE offers several unique features like VGA mode support for graphics and terminal mode for text-only OSes, emulation of x86, PPC, and RISC-V architectures, support for pre-built machines, and the ability to create custom bootable machines.<br/>
<br/>
Apple initially rejected the app in June, despite changing its global App Store policy in April regarding <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">retro game emulators</a>. According to the developers, Apple <a href="https://x.com/UTMapp/status/1799647652134654045">said</a> the app violated rule 4.7 of its App Review Guidelines because "PC is not a console," regardless of the fact that there are retro Windows/DOS games for the PC that UTM SE can be useful in running. <br/>
<br/>
Apple also deemed UTM SE unsuitable for third-party marketplaces in the European Union, because it violated rule 2.5.2 of its Notarization Review Guidelines. That rule states that apps have to be self-contained and can't execute code "which introduces or changes features or functionality of the app, including other apps."<br/>
<br/>
After Apple's rejection, UTM's developer said they would not keep going back and forth because the app would become "a subpar experience." However, after help from the AltStore team and <a href="https://x.com/UTMapp/status/1812241740172263663">another developer</a> to work on some changes, UTM SE was finally approved by Apple on Saturday.<br/>
<br/>
As with other emulators, UTM SE requires that users supply the operating systems they want to emulate, but the <a href="https://mac.getutm.app/gallery/">UTM site includes guides</a> for Windows XP through Windows 11 emulation, as well as downloads of pre-built virtual Linux machines. UTM SE can be downloaded from the App Store [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/utm-se-retro-pc-emulator/id1564628856">Direct Link</a>].<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/15/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-ios/">Apple Approves First Retro PC Emulator for iPhone, iPad, and Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-approves-first-retro-pc-emulator-for-iphone-ipad-and-vision-pro.2431363/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Popular Delta Retro Game Emulator Officially Comes to iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/14/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-officially-comes-to-ipad.2431316/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 01:21:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/14/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Game emulator <a href="https://deltaemulatorapp.com/ipad/">Delta</a>, which has been a hit among retro gaming enthusiasts on iPhone, is now officially available for iPad, following an app update to version 1.6.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/delta-emulator-ipad.jpg" alt="" width="1536" height="866" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958693" /><br/>
Delta has been hugely popular since its debut on the App Store and the emulator has been a constant presence in the Top Charts, with users flocking to play retro games that originally appeared on NES, SNES, N64, Nintendo DS, Game Boy, and Game Boy Advance.<br/>
<br/>
With iPad support in v1.6, users can now take full advantage of the device's larger display and play in fullscreen. There are new controller skins designed specifically for iPad, and the app supports multiple windows in Stage Manager and Split View, with games able to optionally pause when switching windows. The iPad version also supports external game controllers, and the developer Riley Testut says emulated games "hand off" seamlessly between iPhone and iPad, allowing gamers to continue playing where they left off. <br/>
<br/>
Testut says the need for BIOS files has now been eliminated, streamlining the setup process. Users should also notice a considerable improvement in the performance of DS games. The update introduces various menu button gestures, providing more intuitive navigation options. An experimental feature, "Reverse Controller Skin Screens," has also been added, allowing users to switch controller skin screens at runtime, offering greater customization and flexibility during gameplay.<br/>
<br/>
Testut previously explained that Delta for iPad had not originally been a development priority because the plan was to limit the emulator's launch to the EU via alternative app marketplace AltStore PAL, which doesn't support iPad.<br/>
<br/>
However, in a reversal of a years-old policy, Apple in April decided to allow retro game emulators on the ‌App Store‌. Delta was therefore made available on the App Store as a free download in the United States and other countries, with users supporting the developer via <a href="https://www.patreon.com/rileyshane?utm_source=search">Patreon</a>. Official download links for the latest version can be found on the <a href="https://deltaemulatorapp.com/ipad/">Delta website</a>.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/14/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-ipad/">Popular Delta Retro Game Emulator Officially Comes to iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-officially-comes-to-ipad.2431316/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s AirPods Pro 2 vs. Samsung&#039;s Galaxy Buds3 Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-pro-2-vs-samsungs-galaxy-buds3-pro.2431266/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 08:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/10/samsung-galaxy-z-fold6-flip6/">this week introduced</a> its latest earbuds, the <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN6mU8k">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a>, which look quite a bit like Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2. Given the similarities, we thought we'd compare Samsung's new earbuds to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Galaxy Buds3 Pro vs AirPods Pro" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/I_aTHWKmo9c" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
Design wise, you could potentially mistake Samsung's Galaxy Buds3 Pro for the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;. The Buds3 Pro have the same general shape and a silicone tip, though it's worth noting that the Buds3 Pro come in both white and gray, so you're not limited to white as you are with the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2. The charging case is similar to the AirPods Charging Case too, but there's a transparent upper portion.<br/>
<br/>
The Buds3 Pro sound great out of the box, but there is an option to adjust the sound using the equalizer, which isn't possible with the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2. The Active Noise Cancellation and the "Ambient Mode" or transparency on the Buds3 Pro work as well as those features on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;, and it's tough to tell the difference between them.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's Buds3 Pro do not perform as well as the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; when it comes to ambient noise detection to adjust sound, however. The &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; can adjust sound when someone is speaking to you so you can hear them, but the Buds3 Pro struggled to do the same.<br/>
<br/>
The Buds3 Pro have a built-in LED light for aesthetics, and there are controls on the stem for adjusting volume. Samsung also added an interpreter mode for translating foreign languages when connected to the most recent Galaxy phones, but the feature wasn't super accurate.<br/>
<br/>
Though the Buds3 Pro are similar to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2, it's hard to see the two as competitors because you're only going to want to use the Buds3 Pro with Android devices, while the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 work best with Apple devices. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users should stick with the AirPods, while Samsung users will want to check out the Buds3 Pro.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung's Galaxy Buds3 Pro <a href="https://howl.me/cmDIUN6mU8k">are priced at &#36;250</a>, which is the same price as the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2. Pre-orders are available now ahead of a July 24 launch date.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/airpods-pro-2-vs-galaxy-buds3-pro/">Apple&#039;s AirPods Pro 2 vs. Samsung&#039;s Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-airpods-pro-2-vs-samsungs-galaxy-buds3-pro.2431266/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Early Prime Day Deals on Apple Products</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/amazon-prime-day-2024-best-apple-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-prime-day-deals-on-apple-products.2431260/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:23:45 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/amazon-prime-day-2024-best-apple-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Prime Day</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is soon to be back with its annual <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime">summertime Prime Day event</a>, lasting for just two days from July 16-17. As it does every year, Prime Day offers shoppers a huge selection of deals across Amazon's storefront, and there are already many deals you can get on sale ahead of the event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/10/primeday2020_feature3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-763521" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For our coverage, we're focusing entirely on early discounts for Apple and Apple-related products that can be purchased right now on Amazon. As of today, this includes deals on AirPods, Apple Watch, iPad, MacBook Air, and more. We're also sharing deals being matched at retailers like Best Buy in some cases.<br/>
<br/>
As is typical for Prime Day deals, these markdowns are very time sensitive, so sales listed below may disappear fast, and new ones may appear even faster. With this in mind, we'll keep this article updated over the next few days, and keep an eye on the MacRumors front page as we'll be posting particularly great deals in separate articles next week.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, and perhaps most importantly, Amazon Prime Day requires you to have an <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Famazonprime"><strong>Amazon Prime membership</strong></a> to take advantage of the discounts. Amazon Prime costs &#36;14.99 per month or &#36;139.00 per year, and it comes with a 30-day free trial for new subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/prime-day-series-9.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958519" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Series 9</h3><br/>
You can get up to &#36;100 off most Apple Watch Series 9 models right now on Amazon, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FApple-Smartwatch-Aluminum-Fitness-Resistant%2Fdp%2FB0CSVB8BP1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.00</strong></a> for the 41mm GPS watches. We've rounded up all of the deals below, focusing on the aluminum devices, but you can also find &#36;100 discounts on a few stainless steel models as well.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5F%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Fth%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm GPS) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTFHP3W%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us1%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm GPS) for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSV7172L%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (41mm Cellular) for &#36;399.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CSTJ2Y5N%2Fref%3Dfs_a_wt2_us2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Apple Watch Series 9 (45mm Cellular) for &#36;429.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3>SE</h3><br/>
Apple's 40mm GPS Apple Watch SE is available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> today on Amazon, down from &#36;249.00. This is just &#36;10 higher compared to the all-time low price on the wearable. This deal is available in all three aluminum color options, and only Amazon has the discount.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the 44mm GPS Apple Watch SE on sale right now, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWYCT6C%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;219.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;279.00. This is another near all-time low price that's just &#36;10 away from the lowest price on the Apple Watch SE, and it's only available in Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-ipad-pro-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958610" /><br/>
<br/>
Over at Best Buy, today you can find some of the biggest discounts on the M2 11-inch and 12.9-inch iPad Pro that we've seen in months, including both Wi-Fi and cellular tablets. A My Best Buy Plus/Total membership is not required to see these discounts.<br/>
<br/>
With such steep savings, these previous generation iPad Pros are worth looking into purchasing for anyone who wants to prioritize saving money over owning the newest M4 iPad Pro. There are some major differences between the two generations, like the M4's support for Apple Pencil Pro and a new nano-texture display option, so be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-pro-2022-vs-2024/">read about which one works best for you</a> in our Buyer's Guide.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
<strong>Wi-Fi</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/clM5Y6X7yBI">512GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;899.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM5ZY2SiSP">1TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,199.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM50J6paxv">2TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,599.00 (&#36;300 off)</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Cellular</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSae5mICO">128GB Cellular</a> for &#36;799.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSaLdSe0X">256GB Cellular</a> for &#36;899.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCScfQIIAB">512GB Cellular</a> for &#36;949.00 (&#36;350 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSc22N2b9">1TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,249.00 (&#36;450 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSdKc6izG">2TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,649.00 (&#36;450 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>12.9-Inch</h3><br/>
<strong>Wi-Fi</strong><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEAPmsBXFB">128GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;899.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM54mrLxFi">256GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;999.00 (&#36;200 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM547Ht1nE">512GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,099.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM55UKUlgu">1TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;400 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/clM56AO1pl6">2TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,799.00 (&#36;400 off)</li></ul><br/>
<strong>Cellular</strong><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSfouMhNS">128GB Cellular</a> for &#36;999.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSf0DN24w">256GB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,099.00 (&#36;300 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSgI7LBgp">512GB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,149.00 (&#36;450 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCShFBt2of">1TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,449.00 (&#36;550 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmCSiepS0Mp">2TB Cellular</a> for &#36;1,849.00 (&#36;550 off)</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m4-ipad-pro-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958609" /><br/>
<br/>
For the newest M4 iPad Pros, Amazon is offering up to &#36;200 off select models of both the 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Pro. Deals are primarily focused on Wi-Fi models, but you can find a few cellular tablets on sale at this time as well.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;928.00 (&#36;71 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9G6SP%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,114.00 (85 off)</li></ul><br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9SMLK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">256GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,199.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3JB95VD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">512GB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,399.00 (&#36;100 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J82K45%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;1,754.00 (&#36;145 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J7T414%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">1TB Wi-Fi (Nano-Texture Glass)</a> for &#36;1,844.00 (&#36;155 off)</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8S6S5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">2TB Wi-Fi</a> for &#36;2,099.00 (&#36;200 off)</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>M2 iPad Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/ipad-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958546" /><br/>
<br/>
<h3>11-Inch</h3><br/>
The cheapest model is the 128GB Wi-Fi 11-inch iPad Air for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WGD6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;559.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;599.00. You'll also find deals on the 256GB, 512GB, and 1TB models below, all of which are in stock on Amazon with delivery dates as soon as the middle of next week for Prime members.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J5WGD6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;559.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6FSV3%2Fref%3Dtwister_B0D3KGR4NB%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26_encoding%3DUTF8%26geniuslink%3Dtrue%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;45 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;654.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J53DNX%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;55 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;844.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6VB4J%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;75 OFF</div>M2 11-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,024.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3>13-Inch</h3><br/>
The 13-inch M2 iPad Air models start at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J59856%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"><strong>&#36;729.00</strong></a> for the 128GB Wi-Fi tablet, down from &#36;799.00. Similar to the 11-inch devices, all Wi-Fi models are on sale this week, and for the larger display iPad Airs these discounts reach up to &#36;90 off original prices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J59856%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;70 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (128GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;729.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8W54H%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;839.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J8BD6L%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;75 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (512GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,024.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J75PYR%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;90 OFF</div>M2 13-inch iPad Air (1TB Wi-Fi) for &#36;1,209.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The iPad Air is Apple's middle-tier iPad model, equipped with an LCD Liquid Retina display, True Tone support, four unique color options, Touch ID, relocated front-facing camera, and two new size options with the 11-inch and 13-inch sizes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/2022-ipad-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958608" /><br/>
<br/>
Amazon is taking &#36;30 off the Wi-Fi models of the 2022 iPad, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;319.00</strong></a> for 64GB Wi-Fi. You'll also find both cellular devices on sale this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;319.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;469.00</div></a></div><h2>M3 MacBook Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m3-macbook-pro-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958607" /><br/>
<br/>
The best M3 MacBook Pro deal you'll find right now is on the 14-inch M3 Pro 512GB model, priced at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;1,699.00</strong></a>. That's a &#36;300 discount and the best price we've ever tracked, but you can also find a few other solid markdowns on more 14-inch MacBook Pros and 16-inch MacBook Pros at Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5LN355%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro 512GB) for &#36;1,699.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KB9M3%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro 1TB) for &#36;2,099.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5JCMQ5%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;300 OFF</div>14-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Max 1TB) for &#36;2,899.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CM5KXTND%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;500 OFF</div>16-inch MacBook Pro (M3 Pro 512GB) for &#36;1,999.00</div></a></div><h2>M2 MacBook Air</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/m2-macbook-air-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958554" /><br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX">Best Buy</a> and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B3BVWJ6Y%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> today have Apple's 256GB 13-inch M2 MacBook Air for <a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"><strong>&#36;799.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;999.00. You'll find all four colors on sale at this price, including Midnight, Silver, Space Gray, and Starlight.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmDI58LD6XX"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>13-inch M2 MacBook Air (256GB) for &#36;799.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Compared to previous sales, this is a match of the all-time low price on the 13-inch M2 MacBook Air. Right now, both Best Buy and Amazon have this steep discount, and we aren't tracking any notable deals on the 512GB model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/pencil-prime-day.jpg" alt="" width="2002" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958605" /><br/>
<br/>
Apple Pencil deals include all-time low prices on the Apple Pencil 2 at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;79.00</strong></a> and Apple Pencil Pro at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;119.00</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CL7J12YK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil USB-C for &#36;69.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;79.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J71RM7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;10 OFF</div>Apple Pencil Pro for &#36;119.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prime-day/">Prime Day</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/amazon-prime-day-2024-best-apple-deals/">The Best Early Prime Day Deals on Apple Products</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-early-prime-day-deals-on-apple-products.2431260/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 3, HomePod With Screen Rumor, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/top-stories-everything-new-ios-18-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-3-homepod-with-screen-rumor-and-more.2431259/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/top-stories-everything-new-ios-18-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is moving right along with development and testing on iOS 18 and related software updates, with the third developer betas arriving this past week and public beta versions of most of them expected very shortly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/top-stories-13jul2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958642" /><br/>
Not all of the new features Apple showed off at WWDC last month will be available right away, however, with some rolling out in later iOS 18 updates over the next year. In particular, significant Siri enhancements with Apple Intelligence are reportedly slated for iOS 18.4 in the spring of 2025. Other news this week included hints of a touchscreen-equipped HomePod and rumors about the next-generation Apple Watch SE, so read on below for all the details!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 3</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/apple-seeds-ios-18-beta-3/">seeded the third beta of iOS 18</a> to developers for testing, and there are a handful of new features and changes. Check out our list of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/08/everything-new-ios-18-beta-3/">everything new in iOS 18 beta 3</a>, including Dark Mode for additional app icons, tweaks to the Photos app, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-on-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955605" /><br/>
Apple also seeded the third betas of iPadOS 18, macOS Sequoia, watchOS 11, tvOS 18, visionOS 2, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 Public Beta Coming Soon: How to Get Your iPhone Ready</h2><br/>
Apple last month announced that the first public beta of iOS 18 would be released in July, so it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon/">should be available to try out soon</a>. The first public betas of iOS 17 and iOS 16 were both released in the first half of July over the past two years, so it is possible that the iOS 18 public beta will be available next week.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Public-Beta-Thumb-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958425" /><br/>
Ahead of time, read our story outlining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/ios-18-public-beta-coming-soon/">how to get your iPhone ready for the iOS 18 public beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>New Siri Experience With Apple Intelligence Likely to Debut in Spring 2025</h2><br/>
While some Apple Intelligence features will be available when iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS Sequoia are first released to the public later this year, Apple last month said that some of the remaining features will be rolled out "over the course of the next year." <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Apple-Intelligence-General-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-956491" /><br/>
According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman, a smarter version of Siri powered by Apple Intelligence <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/new-siri-experience-to-debut-spring-2025/">will likely launch as part of iOS 18.4 in the spring of 2025</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>tvOS 18 Hints at HomePod With Touchscreen Display</h2><br/>
A reference to an unreleased HomePod with a built-in screen has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/09/tvos18-homepod-touchscreen-display/">allegedly been uncovered in the tvOS 18 beta</a>, following earlier reports that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/the-macrumors-show-apples-next-big-thing-robots/">Apple plans to release such a device</a> in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/HomePod-With-Screen-and-Arm-FaceTime-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801481" /><em>MacRumors concept mockups based on early rumors</em></div><br/>
Apple is rumored to have been prototyping <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/04/leak-confirms-apples-work-on-home-accessory/">several different smart home accessories</a>, including a HomePod with a screen, a smart home hub with a robotic arm, a device that combines a HomePod and Apple TV, and more, but it is unclear if or when all of them will be released to the public.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Reportedly Developing Apple Watch SE With Plastic Casing</h2><br/>
Apple is developing a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/apple-watch-se-with-plastic-casing/">next-generation version of the low-end Apple Watch SE with a plastic casing</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-866330" /><br/>
A third-generation Apple Watch SE is expected to be released in September, but it is unclear if Apple will move forward with the plastic casing, which would replace the aluminum casing on previous models. The current Apple Watch SE starts at &#36;249 in the U.S., and the move to plastic could allow for the next model to have an even lower starting price.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10+ Changes to Control Center in iOS 18</h2><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-control-center/">significantly overhauling Control Center on iOS 18</a> for the first time since iOS 11, with greater customization, multiple pages, additional controls, and more. Apple also now allows users to customize the Flashlight and Camera shortcuts on the Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iOS-18-Control-Center-Guide-1.jpg" alt="" width="2100" height="1180" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958438" /><br/>
Check out our list outlining <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-18-control-center/">more than 10 new features and changes in Control Center on iOS 18</a>, which will be widely released later this year for the iPhone XS and newer.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/jul-11-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/13/top-stories-everything-new-ios-18-beta-3/">Top Stories: Everything New in iOS 18 Beta 3, HomePod With Screen Rumor, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-everything-new-in-ios-18-beta-3-homepod-with-screen-rumor-and-more.2431259/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
