<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 01:02:59 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Epic Games to Bring Fortnite to iPad in EU After iPadOS &#039;Gatekeeper&#039; Decision</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fortnite-coming-to-ipad-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-to-bring-fortnite-to-ipad-in-eu-after-ipados-gatekeeper-decision.2425163/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 15:24:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fortnite-coming-to-ipad-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>Epic Games</category>
		<category>Fortnite</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With Apple soon to be required to bring the same EU changes that it made on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a> today confirmed that it will release Fortnite for the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2020/08/fortnite_apple_featured.jpg" alt="" width="2140" height="1204" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-754674" /><br/>
&zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; is already working to release an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; version of Fortnite in the EU, with the game set to be available from the forthcoming &zwnj;Epic Games&zwnj; Store, an alternative app marketplace. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; version of Fortnite is coming "soon," and an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; version will follow "this year."<br/>
<br/>
The European Commission <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/">said this morning</a> that iPadOS, the operating system designed to run on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, is considered a digital gatekeeper under the EU's Digital Markets Act (DMA). As a result, Apple has six months to comply with the requirements set by the DMA, and we've already seen those requirements implemented on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Today, the European Commission said that iPads will also need to comply with the Digital Markets Act &#x1f64c;<br><br>We’re moving full steam ahead to bring Fortnite and the <a href="https://twitter.com/EpicGames?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@EpicGames</a> Store to iPhones in the EU soon and iPads this year! &#x1f389; <a href="https://t.co/MHh6EGVinC">https://t.co/MHh6EGVinC</a></p>&mdash; Epic Games Newsroom (@EpicNewsroom) <a href="https://twitter.com/EpicNewsroom/status/1784978618344456484?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 29, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
As of iOS 17.4, &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users in the European Union can download apps from alternative app marketplaces rather than the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, and starting in iOS 17.5, apps are available directly from developer websites. Right now, only &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; apps can be downloaded outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but Apple will need to expand this functionality to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; as well.<br/>
<br/>
Within six months, EU users will be able to download &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; apps from alternative app marketplaces and from websites. As with the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; updates, the upcoming changes are limited to the European Union, and the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; app ecosystem will function as is in the rest of the world.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/epic-games/">Epic Games</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fortnite/">Fortnite</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fortnite-coming-to-ipad-eu/">Epic Games to Bring Fortnite to iPad in EU After iPadOS &#039;Gatekeeper&#039; Decision</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/epic-games-to-bring-fortnite-to-ipad-in-eu-after-ipados-gatekeeper-decision.2425163/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>FCC Fines AT&amp;T, T-Mobile and Verizon Almost &#36;200 Million for Illegally Sharing Customer Location Data</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fcc-fines-carriers-customer-data-sharing/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fcc-fines-at-t-t-mobile-and-verizon-almost-200-million-for-illegally-sharing-customer-location-data.2425162/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:42:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fcc-fines-carriers-customer-data-sharing/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		<category>FCC</category>
		<category>AT&amp;amp;T</category>
		<category>Verizon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The United States Federal Communications Commission (FCC) today announced [<a href="https://docs.fcc.gov/public/attachments/DOC-402213A1.pdf">PDF</a>] that it has fined AT&T, Verizon, and Sprint/T-Mobile &#36;196 million collectively for illegally selling access to customer location information without consent.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/3-4-24-iPhone-Case-Refresh-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-939420" /><br/>
Sprint and T-Mobile (now merged into T-Mobile) have been fined &#36;12 million and &#36;80 million, respectively. Verizon has been fined almost &#36;47 million, and AT&T has been fined more than &#36;57 million.<br/>
<br/>
The FCC <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/05/01/fcc-questions-us-carriers-location-data/">first began investigating</a> the four major U.S. carriers in 2019 after they were found <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/01/09/us-cell-carriers-still-selling-your-location-data/">selling real-time location information</a> from customer devices to third-party data aggregators, which led to that location data being sold a second time to private investigators, bounty hunters, law enforcement agencies, credit card companies, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Following the investigation, the FCC confirmed that wireless carriers had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/01/31/fcc-carriers-illegal-location-data-sharing/">violated federal law</a> by sharing consumer location data. Fines were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/02/28/fcc-us-carriers-customer-location-data-fines/">proposed back in 2020</a>, but carriers were given an opportunity to provide evidence and legal arguments against the decision before the fines were formally imposed.<br/>
<br/>
The fines vary based on the length of time that each carrier sold access to customer location information without safeguards, and the number of entities that were provided access. The FCC determined that carriers were obligated to protect the personal information of their customers, which they did not do.<br/>
<blockquote>"Our communications providers have access to some of the most sensitive information about us. These carriers failed to protect the information entrusted to them. Here, we are talking about some of the most sensitive data in their possession: customers' real-time location information, revealing where they go and who they are," said FCC Chairwoman Jessica Rosenworcel. "As we resolve these cases - which were first proposed by the last Administration - the Commission remains committed to holding all carriers accountable and making sure they fulfill their obligations to their customers as stewards of this most private data."</blockquote><br/>
The four carriers had different practices, but each carrier relied on contract-based assurances that the data aggregators purchasing the real-time location information would get consent from customers before accessing their location, which did not happen. Even after learning that data was being misused in this way, the FCC says the carriers "continued to sell access to location information without taking reasonable measures to protect it from unauthorized access."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/fcc/">FCC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/att/">AT&amp;T</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/verizon/">Verizon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/fcc-fines-carriers-customer-data-sharing/">FCC Fines AT&amp;T, T-Mobile and Verizon Almost &#36;200 Million for Illegally Sharing Customer Location Data</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/fcc-fines-at-t-t-mobile-and-verizon-almost-200-million-for-illegally-sharing-customer-location-data.2425162/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>First Physical Apple Cards Expiring Soon, Apple Shipping Out Replacements</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/first-physical-apple-cards-expiring-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-physical-apple-cards-expiring-soon-apple-shipping-out-replacements.2425155/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:38:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/first-physical-apple-cards-expiring-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Card</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today began informing early <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a> customers that their physical titanium cards are set to expire this summer, with replacements to be sent in the near future. Customers who signed up for the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; in August 2019, when the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; launched, will be receiving the notice.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-card-expiration.jpg" alt="" width="1403" height="789" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948571" /><br/>
It appears that the physical &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; is designed to last for five years before a replacement is sent out. Most of the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj;'s functionality is digital, with options for rotating security codes and credit card numbers for online purchases, but there is a number associated with the physical card that's used for in-person transactions. Credit card companies add expiration dates to physical cards for fraud prevention purposes, to introduce new technology, and more.<br/>
<br/>
From Apple's email:<br/>
<blockquote>We're sending a replacement titanium card to your billing address so you can continue to use it at physical locations. Remember, even without a physical card you can always use your Apple Card at any location that accepts Apple Pay. Your new titanium card will be shipped within 2 weeks from the date of this communication.<br/>
<br/>
You can continue to use your titanium card until it expires or you activate the new one. You can still use Apple Card with Apple Pay and your virtual card number to shop at merchants that don't yet accept Apple Pay by typing in your number from Wallet or using Safari AutoFill.</blockquote><br/>
Replacement cards will include a prepaid shipping label so that customers can send in their old &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; to be recycled. Apple recommends that &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; users who receive a new card activate it when it arrives, as the current card is scheduled to stop working at its expiration date.<br/>
<br/>
Customers who signed up for &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; at some point after it first launched will likely receive emails at the five year mark. Note that some customers have been receiving emails for the last month or so, but these may be customers who were able to sign up for the &zwnj;Apple Card&zwnj; early as part of a beta test.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-card/">Apple Card</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/first-physical-apple-cards-expiring-soon/">First Physical Apple Cards Expiring Soon, Apple Shipping Out Replacements</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/first-physical-apple-cards-expiring-soon-apple-shipping-out-replacements.2425155/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple to Use &#039;Best OLED Panels on the Market&#039; for Upcoming iPad Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/ipad-pro-best-oled-panels/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-use-best-oled-panels-on-the-market-for-upcoming-ipad-pro.2425145/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 10:04:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/ipad-pro-best-oled-panels/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models will feature "by far the best OLED tablet panels on the market," <a href="https://www.displaysupplychain.com/blog/apple-to-announce-oled-ipads-on-may-7th-lgd-and-12-9-dominating-on-sdcs-challenges">according to Display Supply Chain Consultants</a>. Set to be announced on May 7, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled-ipad-pro/">OLED iPad Pro</a> models will feature LTPO (a more power efficient form of OLED), a 120Hz ProMotion refresh rate, and a tandem stack and glass thinning that will bring "ultra-thin and light displays" that support high brightness, extended battery life, and a long lifetime.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/07/iPad-Pro-OLED-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-853666" /><br/>
As has been previously rumored, today's report suggests that the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models will be available in 12.9-inch and 11.1-inch sizes, with both options to feature slimmed down bezels and a much thinner design. The 12.9-inch version, for example, will be over 1mm thinner than the current model.<br/>
<br/>
There is a possibility that the 11.1-inch &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; will be in short supply at launch because Apple has been dealing with light leakage issues that are not impacting the 12.9-inch model.<br/>
<br/>
Along with the best OLED display on the market, the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models could get Apple's next-generation AI-optimized M4 chip, and they are expected to ship alongside a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> and an updated version of the Magic Keyboard. Apple will also introduce new 10.9-inch and 12.9-inch LCD <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple plans to unveil the updated iPads on Tuesday, May 7 at 7:00 a.m. Pacific Time.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/ipad-pro-best-oled-panels/">Apple to Use &#039;Best OLED Panels on the Market&#039; for Upcoming iPad Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-to-use-best-oled-panels-on-the-market-for-upcoming-ipad-pro.2425145/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Faces New Cybersecurity Law in UK</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/apple-faces-new-uk-cybersecurity-law/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-new-cybersecurity-law-in-uk.2425138/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 08:10:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/apple-faces-new-uk-cybersecurity-law/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A new British cybersecurity law mandates smart device manufacturers like Apple to enhance protections or face hefty penalties.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series-store.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913490" /><br/>
The legislation, known as the <a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/new-laws-to-protect-consumers-from-cyber-criminals-come-into-force-in-the-uk">Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure (PSTI) Act</a>, introduces robust requirements aimed at securing devices connected to the internet to make it harder for cybercriminals to get access to private networks.<br/>
<br/>
The law specifically targets the inadequacies in current security measures by mandating three major changes: the elimination of default passwords, a clear protocol for reporting security vulnerabilities, and detailed consumer information on the length of product support and software updates. These stipulations apply to all companies manufacturing or selling smart devices in the UK.<br/>
<br/>
For Apple, the law will necessitate a review of how its products comply with these enhanced standards. While Apple devices do not use default passwords, the company will need to ensure that all of its connected devices sold in the UK clearly communicate the duration of security support to customers. In addition, affected companies are expected to establish or refine their contact points for security issue reporting. <br/>
<br/>
Retailers such as Apple stores are also required to provide customers with point-of-sale information about the cybersecurity practices relevant to the devices they purchase. The PSTI Act also includes strict penalties for non-compliance, with fines that can reach up to £10 million (&#36;12.5 million USD) or 4% of the offending company's global turnover. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/apple-faces-new-uk-cybersecurity-law/">Apple Faces New Cybersecurity Law in UK</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-faces-new-cybersecurity-law-in-uk.2425138/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Lineup Dummies Show How Four Model Sizes Compare</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/iphone-16-lineup-dummies/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-dummies-show-how-four-model-sizes-compare.2425133/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:38:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/iphone-16-lineup-dummies/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Sonny Dickson</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the best looks yet at the rear design and increased size of Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models was today shared online. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iphone-16-lineup-dummy-models.jpeg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-948550" /><br/>
The images, <a href="https://x.com/SonnyDickson/status/1784540264872423518">posted on X</a> by <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a>, show four dummy models representing the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max. These units are designed to take the place of real devices for display or testing purposes.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="zxx" dir="ltr"><a href="https://t.co/dlxXgpXV8U">pic.twitter.com/dlxXgpXV8U</a></p>&mdash; Sonny Dickson (@SonnyDickson) <a href="https://twitter.com/SonnyDickson/status/1784928575386468633?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 29, 2024</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
<br/>
The dummy models provide a clear look at the slightly larger size of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max, which are expected increase from 6.1- to 6.3-inches and 6.7- to 6.9-inches, and how they compare to the other models in the lineup.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are expected to stay at 6.1- and 6.7-inches like their predecessors, but they are rumored to receive a redesigned vertical camera array designed to accommodate spatial video capture. Starting with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, Apple's two non-Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models have had diagonally arranged dual rear cameras. The entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to launch as usual in the fall.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/sonny-dickson/">Sonny Dickson</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/iphone-16-lineup-dummies/">iPhone 16 Lineup Dummies Show How Four Model Sizes Compare</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-lineup-dummies-show-how-four-model-sizes-compare.2425133/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M1 iPad Air Drops to New Low Price of &#36;399.99 at Best Buy</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/m1-ipad-air-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-ipad-air-drops-to-new-low-price-of-399-99-at-best-buy.2425127/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 07:12:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/m1-ipad-air-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Best Buy today has discounted Apple's M1 iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) to a new all-time low price of <a href="https://howl.me/cl89ff8kl2A"><strong>&#36;399.99</strong></a> in the Starlight color option, down from &#36;599.99. Best Buy says this deal will last through the end of the day, and it's only available in one color at this record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iPad-Air-5-Colors-16x9.jpg" alt="" width="1494" height="840" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-941843" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Best Buy. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This is &#36;50 cheaper than the previous all-time low price on the M1 iPad Air. Prices on the 2022 tablet continue to get discounted as we get closer to next week's Apple event, which is expected to include the announcement of an updated iPad Air lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl89ff8kl2A"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;200 OFF</div>M1 iPad Air (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;399.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for an even cheaper entry-level Apple tablet, Best Buy also has record low prices on the 10th gen iPad. The 64GB Wi-Fi iPad is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/cl89hFDxEyf"><strong>&#36;349.00</strong></a> and the 256GB Wi-Fi model is on sale for <a href="https://howl.me/cl89iaLKtNR"><strong>&#36;499.00</strong></a>, both of which are &#36;100 discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl89hFDxEyf"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;349.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cl89iaLKtNR"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;499.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/m1-ipad-air-new-low-price/">Apple&#039;s M1 iPad Air Drops to New Low Price of &#36;399.99 at Best Buy</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m1-ipad-air-drops-to-new-low-price-of-399-99-at-best-buy.2425127/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Popular Delta Retro Game Emulator Coming to iPad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/delta-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad.2425122/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 06:03:08 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/delta-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Game emulator <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Delta</a> has made a splash on iPhone following Apple's recently announced App Store support for retro game emulators, and now the developer Riley Testut has confirmed that Delta is almost ready for its iPad debut.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DV9QFZltxDI?si=tfliOh7JKOmD1Jyc" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
In a <a href="https://www.threads.net/@rileytestut/post/C6RxU_rOLeP">post</a> shared on Threads over the weekend, Testut said the iPad version is "near completion," with just controller skins to finish and some bug fixes to iron out.<br/>
<br/>
Testut explained that Delta for iPad had not originally been a development priority because the plan was to limit the emulator's launch to the EU via alternative app marketplace AltStore PAL, which doesn't support iPad.<br/>
<br/>
However, in a reversal of a years-old policy, Apple earlier this month <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">announced</a> that it would allow retro game emulators on the ‌App Store‌. Delta was therefore made available on the App Store as a <a href="http://<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">free download</a> in the United States and other countries on April 17, with users supporting the developer via <a href="https://www.patreon.com/rileyshane">Patreon</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Delta has been hugely popular since its debut on the App Store and the emulator has been a constant presence in the Top Charts, with users flocking to play retro games that originally appeared on NES, SNES, N64, Nintendo DS, Game Boy, and Game Boy Advance.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="text-post-media" data-text-post-permalink="https://www.threads.net/@rileytestut/post/C6RxU_rOLeP" data-text-post-version="0" id="ig-tp-C6RxU_rOLeP" style=" background:#FFF; border-width: 1px; border-style: solid; border-color: #00000026; border-radius: 16px; max-width:540px; margin: 1px; min-width:270px; padding:0; width:99.375%; width:-webkit-calc(100% - 2px); width:calc(100% - 2px);"> <a href="https://www.threads.net/@rileytestut/post/C6RxU_rOLeP" style=" background:#FFFFFF; line-height:0; padding:0 0; text-align:center; text-decoration:none; width:100%; font-family: -apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, sans-serif;" target="_blank"> <div style=" padding: 40px; display: flex; flex-direction: column; align-items: center;"><div style=" display:block; height:32px; width:32px; padding-bottom:20px;"> <svg aria-label="Threads" height="32px" role="img" viewBox="0 0 192 192" width="32px" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"> <path d="M141.537 88.9883C140.71 88.5919 139.87 88.2104 139.019 87.8451C137.537 60.5382 122.616 44.905 97.5619 44.745C97.4484 44.7443 97.3355 44.7443 97.222 44.7443C82.2364 44.7443 69.7731 51.1409 62.102 62.7807L75.881 72.2328C81.6116 63.5383 90.6052 61.6848 97.2286 61.6848C97.3051 61.6848 97.3819 61.6848 97.4576 61.6855C105.707 61.7381 111.932 64.1366 115.961 68.814C118.893 72.2193 120.854 76.925 121.825 82.8638C114.511 81.6207 106.601 81.2385 98.145 81.7233C74.3247 83.0954 59.0111 96.9879 60.0396 116.292C60.5615 126.084 65.4397 134.508 73.775 140.011C80.8224 144.663 89.899 146.938 99.3323 146.423C111.79 145.74 121.563 140.987 128.381 132.296C133.559 125.696 136.834 117.143 138.28 106.366C144.217 109.949 148.617 114.664 151.047 120.332C155.179 129.967 155.42 145.8 142.501 158.708C131.182 170.016 117.576 174.908 97.0135 175.059C74.2042 174.89 56.9538 167.575 45.7381 153.317C35.2355 139.966 29.8077 120.682 29.6052 96C29.8077 71.3178 35.2355 52.0336 45.7381 38.6827C56.9538 24.4249 74.2039 17.11 97.0132 16.9405C119.988 17.1113 137.539 24.4614 149.184 38.788C154.894 45.8136 159.199 54.6488 162.037 64.9503L178.184 60.6422C174.744 47.9622 169.331 37.0357 161.965 27.974C147.036 9.60668 125.202 0.195148 97.0695 0H96.9569C68.8816 0.19447 47.2921 9.6418 32.7883 28.0793C19.8819 44.4864 13.2244 67.3157 13.0007 95.9325L13 96L13.0007 96.0675C13.2244 124.684 19.8819 147.514 32.7883 163.921C47.2921 182.358 68.8816 191.806 96.9569 192H97.0695C122.03 191.827 139.624 185.292 154.118 170.811C173.081 151.866 172.51 128.119 166.26 113.541C161.776 103.087 153.227 94.5962 141.537 88.9883ZM98.4405 129.507C88.0005 130.095 77.1544 125.409 76.6196 115.372C76.2232 107.93 81.9158 99.626 99.0812 98.6368C101.047 98.5234 102.976 98.468 104.871 98.468C111.106 98.468 116.939 99.0737 122.242 100.233C120.264 124.935 108.662 128.946 98.4405 129.507Z" /></svg></div> <div style=" font-size: 15px; line-height: 21px; color: #999999; font-weight: 400; padding-bottom: 4px; "> Post by @rileytestut</div> <div style=" font-size: 15px; line-height: 21px; color: #000000; font-weight: 600; "> View on Threads</div></div></a></blockquote><br/>
<script async src="https://www.threads.net/embed.js"></script></div><br/>
Delta works with popular game controllers, and supports cheats, save states, backups, syncing, and more. Other features include an option to fast forward, a "hold" button for games where a button needs to be consistently held, support for Haptic Touch, and box art for imported games. Local multiplayer gaming is available on iPhone, and up to four players can participate. A future version of Delta will also include SEGA Genesis support, according to Testut. <br/>
<br/>
iPad support will arrive when Delta 1.6 hits the App Store, but <a href="https://www.patreon.com/rileyshane?utm_source=search">Patreon supporters</a> don't have to wait and can grab Delta 1.6 now. <br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/delta-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad/">Popular Delta Retro Game Emulator Coming to iPad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/popular-delta-retro-game-emulator-coming-to-ipad.2425122/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPadOS Identified as Digital &#039;Gatekeeper&#039; Under New EU Tech Rules</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-identified-as-digital-gatekeeper-under-new-eu-tech-rules.2425116/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 03:15:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		<category>European Commission</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[EU antitrust officials on Monday identified iPadOS, Apple's operating system for iPads, as a <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/IP_24_2363">significant digital gatekeeper</a> under the EU's new tech regulations, which carry strict requirements that aim to promote fair competition and expand options for consumers. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2016/01/European-Commisssion.jpg" alt="" width="1080" height="719" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-484620" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/app-store-safari-and-ios-designated-gatekeepers/">Last September</a>, the Commission designated Apple as a gatekeeper for its iOS <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> operating system, its web browser Safari, and its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. On the same day, the Commission opened a market investigation to assess whether iPadOS constitutes an important gateway for business users to reach end users in order to assess whether should be designated as a gatekeeper.  <br/>
<br/>
That investigation has now ended. According to an <a href="https://ec.europa.eu/commission/presscorner/detail/en/IP_24_2363">EC press release</a> shared on Monday, the Commission's investigation found that Apple "presents the features of a gatekeeper in relation to iPadOS," for the following reasons:<br/>
<blockquote><ul><li>Apple's business user numbers exceeded the quantitative threshold elevenfold, while its end user numbers were close to the threshold and are predicted to rise in the near future.</li><br/>
<li>End users are locked-in to iPadOS. Apple leverages its large ecosystem to disincentivise end users from switching to other operating systems for tablets.</li><br/>
<li>Business users are locked-in to iPadOS because of its large and commercially attractive user base, and its importance for certain use cases, such as gaming apps.</li></ul></blockquote>The Commission has now given Apple a six-month deadline to fully comply with the obligations set by the Digital Markets Act (DMA), which means we should expect enforced changes in iOS like alternative app marketplaces, web distribution, and alternative browsers to come to iPadOS as well in a forthcoming update.<br/>
<blockquote>"The Digital Markets Act is a dynamic tool which allows us to tackle the realities of digital markets," said Margrethe Vestager, Executive Vice-President in charge of competition policy. "Today, we have brought Apple's iPadOS within the scope of the DMA obligations. Our market investigation showed that despite not meeting the thresholds, iPadOS constitutes an important gateway on which many companies rely to reach their customers. Today's decision will ensure that fairness and contestability are preserved also on this platform, in addition to the 22 other services we designated last September. Apple has six months to make iPadOS compliant with the DMA."</blockquote>To be classified as a "gatekeeper" under the DMA, a company must fulfill certain criteria, including having sales across the EU of at least €7.5 billion, or a market capitalization of €75 billion or above. The designation also requires platforms or services to have more than 45 million monthly active users and over 10,000 active business users annually within the EU.<br/>
<br/>
Alphabet, Amazon, Apple, ByteDance, Meta and Microsoft were all designated gatekeepers by the Commission, and had to fully comply with all DMA obligations by March 7. <br/>
<br/>
Companies that do not adhere to the new regulations risk facing EU investigations, substantial fines, and the imposition of "behavioral or structural remedies." The fines can amount to 10 percent of a company's global revenue, with a 20 percent penalty for repeat violations.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-commission/">European Commission</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/eu-says-ipados-digital-gatekeeper-dma/">iPadOS Identified as Digital &#039;Gatekeeper&#039; Under New EU Tech Rules</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipados-identified-as-digital-gatekeeper-under-new-eu-tech-rules.2425116/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: No Apple Vision Pro 2 Launch Planned Before End of 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/no-apple-vision-pro-2-before-end-of-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-no-apple-vision-pro-2-launch-planned-before-end-of-2026.2425113/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 02:36:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/no-apple-vision-pro-2-before-end-of-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple does not plan to launch a second-generation version of its Vision Pro headset until the end of 2026, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/apple-vision-pro-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944159" /><br/>
Writing in the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-28/apple-rivals-retool-to-compete-with-iphone-and-vision-pro-ios-18-and-ai-details-lvjhucsv">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman said Apple's latest Vision Pro roadmap "doesn't currently call for a second-generation model until the end of 2026." In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/19/gurman-apple-vision-pro-2-at-least-18-months-away/">February 2024</a>, he said that the device was "at least 18 months away."<br/>
<br/>
According to Gurman's sources, Apple is still trying to figure out a way to bring a cheaper version to market before then, although the company remains "flummoxed" by how exactly to bring down the cost.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-vision-pro-major-upgrades-unlikely-until-2027/">February</a> said he believes new Vision Pro models with significant changes to the specification may not enter mass production until 2027.<br/>
<br/>
At the time, Kuo said he did expect a modified Vision Pro to enter mass production in late 2025 to early 2026, with Apple focused on improving costs and production. However, this leads him to believe that the "user experience will not differ from the current model." Indeed, it is even possible that these changes will not be announced to the public, beyond a potential price cut.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to release the Vision Pro in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">additional countries</a> before WWDC in June, with reports that the device could be coming to China <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-vision-pro-launch-china-may/">as soon as next month</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/no-apple-vision-pro-2-before-end-of-2026/">Gurman: No Apple Vision Pro 2 Launch Planned Before End of 2026</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-no-apple-vision-pro-2-launch-planned-before-end-of-2026.2425113/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>HomePod and HomePod Mini Launch in Malaysia, Thailand, and Turkey on May 10</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/homepod-lineup-launching-malaysia-thailand-may-10/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-and-homepod-mini-launch-in-malaysia-thailand-and-turkey-on-may-10.2425112/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 01:50:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/homepod-lineup-launching-malaysia-thailand-may-10/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>HomePod</category>
		<category>HomePod mini</category>
		<category>Thailand</category>
		<category>Malaysia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today announced that its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a> and second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> will go on sale in <a href="https://www.apple.com/my/newsroom/2024/04/apple-introduces-homepod-and-homepod-mini-in-malaysia/">Malaysia</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/th/newsroom/2024/04/apple-introduces-homepod-and-homepod-mini-in-thailand/">Thailand</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/tr/">Turkey</a> from next week. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/01/HomePod-2-and-Mini-feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-882635" /><br/>
Apple is accepting pre-orders through its online stores in the three countries from today, with the speakers shipping and going on sale in Apple's regional retail stores on May 10.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; was initially released by Apple in October 2020 across the U.S. and a handful of other countries. Since launch, the speaker has not seen significant hardware revisions, though Apple did introduce new colors in November 2021 and activated the devices' temperature and humidity sensors via software updates last year. The introduction of the &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; in two more countries makes the prospect of a second-generation model being released anytime soon pretty unlikely.<br/>
<br/>
In 2021, Apple phased out the original full-size &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, but it launched a second-generation version in January. This new &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; retains a design similar to its predecessor but includes an enlarged backlit touch interface and several other enhancements. Both the new &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj; and &zwnj;HomePod mini&zwnj; are Siri-based smart speakers, and come with Matter compatibility and support for stereo pairing.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod-mini/">HomePod mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/thailand/">Thailand</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/malaysia/">Malaysia</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#HomePod">HomePod (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Homepod-Mini">HomePod Mini (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/homepod-homekit-carplay-home-auto-technology.193">HomePod, HomeKit, CarPlay, Home & Auto Technology</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/29/homepod-lineup-launching-malaysia-thailand-may-10/">HomePod and HomePod Mini Launch in Malaysia, Thailand, and Turkey on May 10</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/homepod-and-homepod-mini-launch-in-malaysia-thailand-and-turkey-on-may-10.2425112/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Weekend Deals Include Up to &#36;59 Off Select Models at Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/airpods-weekend-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-weekend-deals-include-up-to-59-off-select-models-at-amazon.2425072/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 07:19:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/airpods-weekend-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This weekend we're tracking a pair of AirPods deals at Amazon, including savings on the AirPods 2 and AirPods Pro 2. The cheapest model starts at just <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;89.00</strong></a> for the AirPods 2, down from their original price of &#36;129.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-2-Discount-Feature-Red-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895365" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Secondly, the AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C are available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. Although this is another second-best price on the earbuds, it's one of the most consistent deals we've tracked in 2024 and just a &#36;9 difference compared to that record low price. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;59 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Both of these earbuds have an estimated delivery date around May 3, and they represent solid second-best prices on each model. There are a few minor changes to the AirPods Pro 2 besides the addition of USB-C, including additional dust resistance and support for lossless audio with the Vision Pro headset.  <br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/airpods-weekend-deals/">AirPods Weekend Deals Include Up to &#36;59 Off Select Models at Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-weekend-deals-include-up-to-59-off-select-models-at-amazon.2425072/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumored to &#039;Overhaul&#039; Notes, Mail, Photos, and Fitness Apps</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-overhaul-notes-mail-photos-and-fitness-apps.2425069/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 06:44:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-28/apple-rivals-retool-to-compete-with-iphone-and-vision-pro-ios-18-and-ai-details-lvjhucsv"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman today said</a> that iOS 18 will "overhaul" many of Apple's built-in apps, including Notes, Mail, Photos, and Fitness.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-General-Notes-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946875" /><br/>
Gurman did not reveal any specific new features planned for these apps. It was previously rumored that the Notes app will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">gain support for  displaying more math equations, and a built-in option to record voice memos</a>, but this is the first time we have heard about updates planned for the Mail, Photos, and Fitness apps.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also corroborated our exclusive <em>MacRumors</em> report last week about <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">Apple finally planning a Calculator app for iPadOS 18</a>.<br/>
<br/>
A recap of iOS 18 rumors:<br/>
<br/>
<ol><li><strong>Smarter Siri:</strong> iOS 18 is rumored to include <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/16/ios-18-slew-of-new-ai-features/">new generative AI features</a> for Siri, Spotlight, Shortcuts, Apple Music, Messages, Health, Keynote, Numbers, Pages, and more. These features are expected to be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-working-on-on-device-llm/">powered by Apple's on-device large language model (LLM)</a>, but Apple has reportedly also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/22/apple-generative-ai-google-openai-baidu/">discussed partnerships with companies like Google, OpenAI, and Baidu</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>More Customizable Home Screen:</strong> One of the design changes rumored for iOS 18 is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-more-customizable-home-screen-rumor/">more customizable Home Screen</a>, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/">ability to place app icons anywhere on the Home Screen grid</a>. This change will allow for blank spaces, rows, and columns between app icons.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Improved Texting With Android Users:</strong> Apple announced that it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/16/apple-to-adopt-rcs-messaging-standard/">will support the cross-platform messaging standard RCS in the Messages app</a> on the iPhone starting "later" in 2024, so it will likely be an iOS 18 feature. Compared to SMS, RCS support will improve the texting experience between iOS and Android devices by allowing for higher-resolution photos and videos, audio messages, typing indicators, read receipts, Wi-Fi messaging, and more.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calculator Revamp:</strong> iOS 18, iPadOS 18, and macOS 15 are expected to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">revamped Calculator app with several new features</a>, including a sidebar that lists recent calculations, an improved interface for converting units, integration with the Notes app, and more. Yes, this means that Apple will finally be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">making its Calculator app available on the iPad</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Math in Notes App:</strong> With iOS 18, the Notes app is expected to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">gain support for displaying mathematical notation</a>, allowing users to include more types of algebraic equations and formulas in notes.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Custom Routes in Apple Maps:</strong> At least two new Apple Maps features are expected on iOS 18, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/">custom routes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/27/ios-18-topographic-maps/">topographic maps</a>. Custom routes would allow users to choose specific roads to travel on while navigating, while topographic maps include details such as trails, contour lines, elevation, and points of interest for hiking and other outdoor uses. Apple already introduced topographic maps on the Apple Watch with watchOS 10.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Safari Browsing Assistant:</strong> Another new generative AI feature potentially coming with iOS 18 is a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-18-safari-browsing-assistant-rumor/">browsing assistant in Safari</a>, but no specific details are known yet. There are already multiple iPhone web browsers with AI tools, such as Microsoft Edge and its GPT-4-powered Copilot, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/29/arc-search-iphone-app-ai/">Arc Search</a>, which can summarize web pages to provide concise information.</li><br/>
<li><strong>AirPods Pro as Hearing Aid:</strong> iOS 18 will reportedly include a so-called <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/airpods-pro-to-gain-hearing-aid-mode-ios-18/">"hearing aid mode" for AirPods Pro</a>, but it is unclear how it would differ from Apple's existing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-conversation-boost-airpods-pro/">Conversation Boost feature</a> that launched in 2021.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Next-Generation CarPlay:</strong> Apple's website says the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/25/ios-17-4-next-generation-carplay/">first vehicles with next-generation CarPlay will arrive in 2024</a>, so the platform might debut alongside iOS 18 later this year. However, it is possible that next-generation CarPlay will also be compatible with some iOS 17 versions.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Freeform Scenes:</strong> iOS 18 is rumored to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/ios-18-macos-15-freeform-app-scenes/">add a new "Scenes" option to Apple's drawing app Freeform</a>. This feature would allow users to select specific sections or "scenes" on the canvas for easier navigation.</li></ol>For additional rumors and expectations, read our comprehensive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>, which we routinely update with the latest information.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will announce iOS 18 during its WWDC keynote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">on June 10</a>, and the update should be widely released in September.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/">iOS 18 Rumored to &#039;Overhaul&#039; Notes, Mail, Photos, and Fitness Apps</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumored-to-overhaul-notes-mail-photos-and-fitness-apps.2425069/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Event Rumors: iPad Pro With M4 Chip and New Apple Pencil With Haptic Feedback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-rumors-ipad-pro-with-m4-chip-and-new-apple-pencil-with-haptic-feedback.2425067/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 06:19:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 11&quot;</category>
		<category>iPad Pro 12.9&quot;</category>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>May 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-28/apple-rivals-retool-to-compete-with-iphone-and-vision-pro-ios-18-and-ai-details-lvjhucsv"><em>Power On</em> newsletter</a> today, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-04-28/apple-rivals-retool-to-compete-with-iphone-and-vision-pro-ios-18-and-ai-details-lvjhucsv"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> outlined some of the new products he expects Apple to announce at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">"Let Loose" event on May 7</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2018/11/ipad-pro-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870798" /><br/>
First, Gurman now believes there is a "strong possibility" that the upcoming iPad Pro models will be equipped with Apple's next-generation M4 chip, rather than the M3 chip that debuted in the MacBook Pro and iMac six months ago. He said a key new feature of the M4 chip will be an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/14/iphone-16-upgraded-neural-engine-rumor/">upgraded Neural Engine</a> that boosts performance for AI tasks, and he believes Apple will market the next iPad Pro as an AI-powered device.<br/>
<br/>
Second, he said that the new Apple Pencil that is expected to be announced at the event will feature haptic feedback for the first time. While he did not provide any details about how this will work, perhaps the Apple Pencil will have a small Taptic Engine that vibrates when switching between drawing tools, and using the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-apple-pencil-4-rumor/">rumored "squeeze" gesture</a> that <em>MacRumors</em> previously discovered within the iPadOS 17.5 beta's code.<br/>
<br/>
Third, he reiterated that Apple will introduce a first-ever <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">12.9-inch version of the iPad Air</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/03/gurman-new-ipad-magic-keyboard-to-feature-aluminum/">redesigned Magic Keyboard</a> for iPads.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's event begins on May 7 at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time), with a video stream to be available on Apple.com and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1J38FlDKxo">on YouTube</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/may-2024-apple-event/">May 2024 Apple Event</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#11-iPad-Pro">11" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#12-9-iPad-Pro">12.9" iPad Pro (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ipad-pro-m4-chip-and-apple-pencil-haptic-rumors/">Apple Event Rumors: iPad Pro With M4 Chip and New Apple Pencil With Haptic Feedback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-rumors-ipad-pro-with-m4-chip-and-new-apple-pencil-with-haptic-feedback.2425067/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Deep Discounts on OWC&#039;s Best Thunderbolt Docks, USB-C Hubs, Memory, and More Mac Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-deep-discounts-on-owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks-usb-c-hubs-memory-and-more-mac-accessories.2425017/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 07:54:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[OWC is hosting a <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">big Mac accessory sale</a> that includes a number of discounts on Thunderbolt docks, USB-C hubs, external drives and enclosures, internal memory upgrade kits for Mac, and more. Most products are in stock and ready to ship out today, and OWC offers free shipping on orders &#36;149.00 and over.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/owc-docks.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940659" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with OWC. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of the sale include a collection of Thunderbolt docks for up to &#36;150 off. These docks allow you to easily connect a wide array of peripherals to your Mac, including two 4K displays or one 5K display with the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock</a>, which is available for &#36;129.99. This isn't quite as steep of a discount as we've previously seen on the accessory, but at &#36;150 off it's still a great second-best price for anyone who missed previous sales.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>OWC 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In regards to the 14-Port Thunderbolt 3 Dock, this accessory features two Thunderbolt 3 ports, five USB Type-A ports, one USB Type-C port, one Mini DisplayPort port, one gigabit Ethernet port, one S/PDIF digital audio output port, and one 3.5mm stereo audio input/output port. There are also two memory card slots for microSD and SD cards.<br/>
<br/>
All of the devices listed below are in new condition at OWC, although the retailer does provide various item condition options for anyone who might want to save money by purchasing open box items. Be sure to visit <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2F">OWC's sale landing page</a> to browse the full sale, which also features deals on cables, Mac accessories, keyboards, and headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Docks and Hubs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTCDSDRDR%2F">Atlas Dual SD Card Reader</a> - &#36;79.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3MDK5P%2F">Thunderbolt Mini Dock</a> - &#36;109.99, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4HUB5P%2F">Thunderbolt Hub</a> - &#36;139.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB3DK14PSG%2F">14-Port Thunderbolt Dock</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FTB4DKG11P%2F">Thunderbolt Go Dock</a> - &#36;299.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>External Drives and Enclosures</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T04C%2F">4TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;124.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FME3NH7T16C%2F">16TB Mercury Elite Pro External Storage</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;379.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FMED3ER7T08C%2F">8TB Mercury Elite Pro RAID External Storage</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;394.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Memory</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S32P%2F">32GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;78.99, down from &#36;89.98</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2F2666DDR4S64S%2F">64GB Memory Upgrade Kit</a> - &#36;154.99, down from &#36;179.96</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Miscellaneous</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FOWC%2FCBLUSCC2M1%2F">2M USB-C to USB-C Charging Cable</a> - &#36;2.99, down from &#36;14.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11911660?url=https%3A%2F%2Feshop.macsales.com%2Fitem%2FMatias%2FFK416BT%2F">Matias Wireless Multi-Pairing Keyboard</a> - &#36;49.99, down from &#36;69.00</li></ul> Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks/">Get Deep Discounts on OWC&#039;s Best Thunderbolt Docks, USB-C Hubs, Memory, and More Mac Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-deep-discounts-on-owcs-best-thunderbolt-docks-usb-c-hubs-memory-and-more-mac-accessories.2425017/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: Apple Announces &#039;Let Loose&#039; Event With New iPads and More Expected</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/top-stories-let-loose-ipad-event-announcement/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-announces-let-loose-event-with-new-ipads-and-more-expected.2425013/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/top-stories-let-loose-ipad-event-announcement/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[New iPads are coming, and Apple is holding a virtual event to introduce them! While it appears likely to be a relatively short video event, we should be seeing new iPad Pro and iPad Air models, some new accessories, and perhaps some additional surprises.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/top-stories-27apr2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948317" /><br/>
Other Apple news and rumors this week included word that Apple is FINALLY planning to introduce a native Calculator app for the iPad later this year, the release of a fresh round of betas for iOS 17.5 and related operating system updates, and perhaps the end of the road coming for Apple's FineWoven accessories, so read on below for details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Announces 'Let Loose' Event on May 7</h2><br/>
Apple this week <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">announced that it will be holding its first event of the year on Tuesday, May 7,</a> at 7 a.m. Pacific Time (10 a.m. Eastern Time). During the event, Apple is expected to unveil <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/07/gurman-new-ipads-first-week-of-may/">new iPad Pro and iPad Air models</a>, along with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-apple-pencil-4-rumor/">updated Apple Pencil</a> and Magic Keyboard accessories. As always, there could be other surprises in store too.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Event-Let-Loose-Pastel-Blellow.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947822" /><br/>
The event invitation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">has a tagline of "Let Loose"</a> and includes an artistic render of an Apple Pencil. The event will be streamed on Apple.com and on YouTube, and we will have full coverage of everything announced.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Tim Cook Hints at New Apple Pencil</h2><br/>
Just moments after Apple announced its "Let Loose" event taking place on May 7, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-has-six-artistic-logos/">Apple CEO Tim Cook hinted at a new Apple Pencil</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/5.7.24-Logos-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2925" height="1646" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947814" /><br/>
"Pencil us in for May 7," said Cook, in a post shared on social media platform X.<br/>
<br/>
The next-generation Apple Pencil is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-apple-pencil-4-rumor/">rumored to feature a new "squeeze" gesture</a> for certain actions, and it <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/25/apple-pencil-visionon-support-in-testing/">may support Apple's Vision Pro headset starting with visionOS 2</a> later this year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Finally Plans to Release a Calculator App for iPad Later This Year</h2><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">finally planning a Calculator app for the iPad</a>, over 14 years after launching the device, according to a source familiar with the matter.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPad-And-Calculator-App-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947832" /><br/>
iPadOS 18 will include a built-in Calculator app for all iPad models that are compatible with the update, which should be widely released in September.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">revamped Calculator app for macOS 15</a> will likely be based on the iPad app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Seeds Third Beta of iOS 17.5 to Developers</h2><br/>
Apple this week made the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-3-to-developers/">third betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5</a> available to developers and members of its public beta program for testing.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943813" /><br/>
iOS 17.5 introduces the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">ability to download select iPhone apps via the web in the EU</a>, adds a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-17-5-apple-news-quartiles-game/">new Quartiles game for Apple News+ subscribers</a> in select countries, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/new-ipad-and-apple-pencil-features-ipados-17-5/">hints at new iPad and Apple Pencil features</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>FineWoven Accessories May Get One Last Outing Before Apple Pulls Plug</h2><br/>
A leaker this week claimed that Apple had <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/21/apple-reportedly-stops-finewoven-production/">stopped production of FineWoven accessories</a> following poor reviews from customers, but they later said that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/finewoven-accessories-may-get-one-last-season/">may offer the accessories in one final set of new colors</a> before discontinuing them for good.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iPhone-15-Pro-FineWoven-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947658" /><br/>
FineWoven is a fabric material that Apple introduced after it announced that it would no longer make leather accessories for the iPhone and other devices. Customers have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/21/apples-finewoven-iphone-cases-poor-reviews/">complained about FineWoven accessories</a> being prone to scratches and stains.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Vision Pro Customer Interest Dying Down at Some Retail Stores</h2><br/>
Apple launched its Vision Pro headset in the U.S. in early February, but a recent report claims that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/">customer interest in the device has dramatically slowed</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Blue-Magenta.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898550" /><br/>
Apple said it will release the Vision Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">in additional countries later this year</a>, and that will likely include the UK, Canada, Australia, Germany, France, Japan, China, Singapore, and South Korea.<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro starts at &#36;3,499, limiting customer demand for the device, but a less-expensive model will likely be released in the future.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/apr-25-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/top-stories-let-loose-ipad-event-announcement/">Top Stories: Apple Announces &#039;Let Loose&#039; Event With New iPads and More Expected</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-apple-announces-let-loose-event-with-new-ipads-and-more-expected.2425013/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple ID Accounts Logging Out Users and Requiring Password Reset</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/apple-id-accounts-logging-out-users/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-accounts-logging-out-users-and-requiring-password-reset.2425001/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:41:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/apple-id-accounts-logging-out-users/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There are widespread reports of Apple users being locked out of their Apple ID overnight for no apparent reason, requiring a password reset before they can log in again.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-id-account.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948406" /><br/>
Users say the sudden inexplicable Apple ID sign-out is occurring across multiple devices. When they attempt to sign in again they are locked out of their account and asked to reset their password in order to regain access.<br/>
<br/>
This has led to additional Apple ID issues for users with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/enable-stolen-device-protection/">Stolen Device Protection</a> enabled who are away from a trusted location, as well as any app-specific passwords previously set up in iCloud also being reset.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/04/26/signed-out-of-apple-id-account-problem-password/">9to5Mac</a></em>, user reports about the problem <a href="https://www.threads.net/@nichagan/post/C6Pzb8jLrvx">began appearing on social media</a> at around 8 p.m. Eastern Time and became <a href="https://www.threads.net/@singletary/post/C6P9jfJt1VH">increasingly prevalent</a> into the <a href="https://www.threads.net/@ngorby/post/C6PvqnArUpZ">early hours</a> of the <a href="https://mastodon.social/@ChrisLawley/112340853972099137">morning</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe src="https://theinternet.social/@tbridge/112340463598872085/embed" class="mastodon-embed" style="max-width: 100%; border: 0" width="400" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><script src="https://theinternet.social/embed.js" async="async"></script><iframe src="https://cosocial.ca/@shayman/112340605964569939/embed" class="mastodon-embed" style="max-width: 100%; border: 0" width="400" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><script src="https://cosocial.ca/embed.js" async="async"></script><iframe src="https://theinternet.social/@tbridge/112340684990421148/embed" class="mastodon-embed" style="max-width: 100%; border: 0" width="400" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><script src="https://theinternet.social/embed.js" async="async"></script></div><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> staff members have also been affected by the service outage, which does not appear to have been picked up by Apple's own <a href="https://www.apple.com/support/systemstatus/">System Status webpage</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We have contacted Apple for comment and will update readers if we hear back. Have you been affected by the Apple ID issue? Let us know in the comments.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/27/apple-id-accounts-logging-out-users/">Apple ID Accounts Logging Out Users and Requiring Password Reset</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-id-accounts-logging-out-users-and-requiring-password-reset.2425001/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Asks Customers for Vision Pro Feedback</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-asks-customers-for-vision-pro-feedback/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-customers-for-vision-pro-feedback.2424990/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:59:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-asks-customers-for-vision-pro-feedback/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has been soliciting Vision Pro feedback since the device launched, but this week, the company has picked up on sending out surveys. We've had several reports from Vision Pro customers who have been asked to share their thoughts about the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-WWCD23-Vision-Pro-EyeSight-230605.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922614" /><br/>
Apple asks about Vision Pro satisfaction, environment usage, favorite features, what it's being used for, how often it's used, and how long usage sessions last. Apple also asks about guest mode and who else uses the Vision Pro, which is a curious question because it's not at all set up for multi-person usage. Some of the questions:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Overall, how satisfied are you with your Vision Pro?</li><br/>
 	<li>What is your favorite feature or aspect of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> so far?</li><br/>
 	<li>How often do you use your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;?</li><br/>
 	<li>For how long do you typically wear your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; before you decide to take it off?</li><br/>
 	<li>Who else uses your Vision Pro?</li><br/>
 	<li>Before taking the survey, did you know that you can let others use your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; with the Guest User feature?</li><br/>
 	<li>Which of these activities do you do regularly on your Vision Pro? (with a long list of options)</li><br/>
 	<li>What types of video content are you most interested in watching on &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;?</li><br/>
 	<li>When using your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;, how often are you immersed in an Environment?</li><br/>
 	<li>Whenever you're using apps on &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;, how often do you multitask?</li><br/>
 	<li>Have you set up your Persona to use in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>?</li><br/>
 	<li>How satisfied are you with how your Persona looks on &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;?</li><br/>
 	<li>Where is your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; used most?</li><br/>
 	<li>Which of these accessories do you use with your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;? (with a list that includes mice, cases, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, and more).</li><br/>
 	<li>What head band do you use most often with your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj;?</li><br/>
 	<li>How often do you use your &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; while the battery is connected to a power source?</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
The survey is long and in-depth, and also goes into the other devices that each respondent owns.<br/>
<br/>
The uptick in Vision Pro survey distribution comes as there have been reports about waning interest in the headset. Over the weekend, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that customers aren't as curious about the Vision Pro, with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/22/apple-vision-pro-customer-interest-dying-down/">demand for demos</a> in retail stores "way down." At some locations, demos and sales have dropped from a "couple of units a day to just a handful in a whole week."<br/>
<br/>
Vision Pro headset owners have also reported a decrease in usage, picking it up just once or twice a week rather than on a daily basis.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> said on Tuesday that Apple is dropping the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-cuts-vision-pro-shipments/">number of Apple Vision Pro units</a> that it plans to ship, and he said it is a sign that demand in the U.S. has "fallen sharply beyond expectations."<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes that Apple needs to address the lack of key applications, price, and comfort without impacting user experience in order for the Vision Pro to ultimately see success in the future.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AppleVisionPro">Vision Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-asks-customers-for-vision-pro-feedback/">Apple Asks Customers for Vision Pro Feedback</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-asks-customers-for-vision-pro-feedback.2424990/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Reignites Talks With OpenAI About Generative AI for iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-open-ai-ios-18-talks/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reignites-talks-with-openai-about-generative-ai-for-ios-18.2424987/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:04:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-open-ai-ios-18-talks/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Apple GPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is once again talking with OpenAI about using OpenAI technology to power artificial intelligence features in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-04-26/apple-intensifies-talks-with-openai-for-iphone-generative-ai-features">reports <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
Apple held talks with OpenAI <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/21/apple-iphone-ai-talks-google-openai-ongoing/">earlier in the year</a>, but nothing had come of the discussion. Apple and OpenAI are now said to be speaking about the terms of a possible agreement and how Apple might utilize OpenAI features.<br/>
<br/>
Along with OpenAI, Apple is still having discussions with Google about licensing Google's Gemini AI. Apple has not come to a final decision, and Gurman suggests that the company could partner with both Google and OpenAI or pick another provider entirely.<br/>
<br/>
Rumors suggest that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/13/apple-says-ios-18-ambitious-compelling/">have a major focus on AI</a>, with Apple set to introduce AI functionality across the operating system. Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/tim-cook-apple-generative-ai-break-new-ground/">confirmed in February</a> that Apple plans to "break new ground" in AI.<br/>
<br/>
We'll get a first look at the AI features that Apple has planned in just over a month, with &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; set to debut at the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/wwdc/">Worldwide Developers Conference</a> that kicks off on June 10.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-gpt/">Apple GPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-open-ai-ios-18-talks/">Apple Reignites Talks With OpenAI About Generative AI for iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-reignites-talks-with-openai-about-generative-ai-for-ios-18.2424987/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Event Next Month Said to Be &#039;Accompanied By an Event in London&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-let-loose-event-london/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-next-month-said-to-be-accompanied-by-an-event-in-london.2424983/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:37:22 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-let-loose-event-london/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>May 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/apple-event-let-loose-may-7/">"Let Loose" event</a> "will be accompanied by an event in London," according to <a href="https://www.independent.co.uk/tech/apple-event-ipad-iphone-vision-pro-b2533340.html"><em>The Independent</em>'s Andrew Griffin</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/5.7.24-Let-Loose-Event-and-iPad-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948297" /><br/>
The report does not provide any additional details about what will be happening in London, but it might simply be a briefing that allows journalists in the UK to receive hands-on time with the new iPads and other products that Apple is expected to announce next month. Apple has frequently invited the media to hands-on briefings <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1782792088310206713">in New York City</a>, and it also held a briefing <a href="https://twitter.com/rsgnl/status/1765006539981484402">in Toronto, Canada</a> for the new MacBook Air models last month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's "Let Loose" event begins on Tuesday, May 7 at 7 a.m. Pacific Time, which will be 3 p.m. local time in London. New devices and accessories expected to be announced at the event include two new iPad Pro models, two new iPad Air models, an updated Apple Pencil, and a redesigned Magic Keyboard for iPads, and there is always a chance of a surprise or two. A video stream of the event will be available <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">on Apple.com</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f1J38FlDKxo">on YouTube</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst Ming-Chi Kuo has repeatedly said that he expects Apple to launch its Vision Pro headset in additional countries <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/28/kuo-on-apple-vision-pro-wider-launch/">before its developers conference WWDC</a>, which <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">begins June 10</a>. Could the accompanying "event" in London allow journalists in the UK to receive hands-on time with the Vision Pro too? It could make sense for Apple to launch the Vision Pro internationally before it announces visionOS 2 at WWDC, and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/13/vision-pro-keyboard-new-languages/">UK is one of nine countries</a> where the headset is expected to become available next.<br/>
<br/>
Of course, this is all just some pre-event speculation for fun based on a single sentence in a British newspaper. Apple's actual plans remain to be seen.<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> We have confirmed that Apple has invited journalists and well-known social media content creators from Europe and abroad to an in-person gathering at its Battersea campus in London. This will be a multi-day function that begins on the same day as the "Let Loose" event, and the media will receive product briefings.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/may-2024-apple-event/">May 2024 Apple Event</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/26/apple-let-loose-event-london/">Apple Event Next Month Said to Be &#039;Accompanied By an Event in London&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-event-next-month-said-to-be-accompanied-by-an-event-in-london.2424983/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
