<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:11:35 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 17 Plus Rumored to Feature Smaller Screen Than iPhone 15 Plus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/iphone-17-plus-smaller-screen-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-plus-rumored-to-feature-smaller-screen-than-iphone-15-plus.2424402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:35:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/iphone-17-plus-smaller-screen-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Ross Young</category>
		<category>iPhone 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the iPhone 16 series is still months away from launching, another rumor has already surfaced about the two-generations-away iPhone 17 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-General-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-912515" /><br/>
In a <a href="https://twitter.com/DSCCRoss/status/1780646505164239364">post shared today</a> on social media platform X, oft-accurate display industry expert Ross Young said he heard that the "iPhone 17 Plus" will be equipped with a smaller screen than the current-generation iPhone 15 Plus, which has a 6.7-inch display. However, he did not reveal the exact screen size planned for the iPhone 17 Plus.<br/>
<br/>
Currently, the iPhone 15 Plus has the same screen size as the iPhone 15 Pro Max. If this rumor is accurate, a smaller screen would further differentiate the Plus model from the Pro Max model, starting with the iPhone 17 lineup.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, it has been rumored that the iPhone 16 Pro and Pro Max will have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">larger 6.3-inch and 6.9-inch displays</a>, which would be a 0.2-inch increase over each of the 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro and the 6.7-inch iPhone 15 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
A summary of what to expect follows, but given the iPhone 17 lineup is still a year and a half away, keep in mind that details could change.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 15</h2><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 15: 6.1-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus: 6.7-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro: 6.1-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Pro Max: 6.7-inch display</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 16</h2><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 16: 6.1-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Plus: 6.7-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Pro: 6.3-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 16 Pro Max: 6.9-inch display</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17</h2><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 17: 6.1-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 17 Plus: A smaller-than-6.7-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 17 Pro: 6.3-inch display</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 17 Pro Max: 6.9-inch display</li></ul><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-17/">iPhone 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/iphone-17-plus-smaller-screen-rumor/">iPhone 17 Plus Rumored to Feature Smaller Screen Than iPhone 15 Plus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-17-plus-rumored-to-feature-smaller-screen-than-iphone-15-plus.2424402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Hands-On With the New App Store Delta Game Emulator</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-emulator-hands-on/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-app-store-delta-game-emulator.2424397/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 12:19:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-emulator-hands-on/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[A decade ago, developer Riley Testut released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2014/02/19/gba4ios-game-boy-emulator/">the GBA4iOS emulator for iOS</a>, and since it was against the rules at the time, Apple put a stop to downloads. Emulators have been a violation of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> rules for years, but that changed on April 5 when Apple suddenly reversed course and said that it was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allowing retro game emulators</a> on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/DV9QFZltxDI" title="Delta Emulator" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
With official support available for emulators, Testut this morning <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">released his latest emulator</a>, Delta, on the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;. Unlike the other two emulators that have been released in the last week, Delta is incredibly polished and provides an all-around pleasant gameplay experience.<br/>
<br/>
Delta supports game systems that include the NES, SNES, Nintendo 64, Game Boy Color, Game Boy Advance, and Nintendo DS. Skins for the different systems load automatically depending on what's being played, and the app does an excellent job making you feel like you're playing on a retro Nintendo device.<br/>
<br/>
It is worth noting that Delta is such a great emulator because it is not, in fact, new. It has been able to be installed on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> using alternate installation means, but the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is a much more streamlined way to get it. Delta is <strong>the</strong> must have emulator, at least for NES content.<br/>
<br/>
Delta's on-screen controls work flawlessly for games, but it is also compatible with a wide range of retro and modern game controllers. It supports save and load states, and content can be synced between devices. There are also advanced features like support for Game Genie and GameShark cheat codes, a hold button, and fast forward for speeding through slow parts of games.<br/>
<br/>
When you import a game, Delta automatically detects the appropriate box art, and there is support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3d-touch/">3D Touch</a> and app icon shortcuts for accessing recent and favorite games.<br/>
<br/>
There are no games included with Delta when you install it, but it can open zipped files that are uploaded to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud-drive/">iCloud Drive</a>, Dropbox, or Google Drive. Apple's &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules permit "retro game console emulator apps" and Apple says that developers are required to ensure that their software complies with "all applicable laws."<br/>
<br/>
If you haven't downloaded Delta already, it's well worth going to pick it up. We're not expecting Delta to get pulled from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj;, but there's always the possibility that Nintendo could protest now that it's more widely available, so download it sooner rather than later.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-emulator-hands-on/">Hands-On With the New App Store Delta Game Emulator</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hands-on-with-the-new-app-store-delta-game-emulator.2424397/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>What to Know About Apple Allowing Game Emulators in the App Store</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/what-to-know-about-iphone-app-store-emulators/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-know-about-apple-allowing-game-emulators-in-the-app-store.2424395/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:46:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/what-to-know-about-iphone-app-store-emulators/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple updated its App Review Guidelines this month to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">allow "retro game console emulator apps"</a> on the App Store for the iPhone and other devices. Below, we outline everything to know about these emulators and available options so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Emulators-in-the-App-Store-What-to-Know-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947035" /><br/>
This information is up to date as of April 2024, but Apple's policies could change over time.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>What is Allowed</h2><br/>
Apple told us that emulators that can load games (ROMs) are permitted on the App Store, so long as the apps are emulating "retro console games" only.<br/>
<br/>
Apple would not tell us which consoles it classifies as retro, but developer Riley Testut's popular emulator Delta is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">now available on the App Store</a>, and it can emulate games for the Game Boy, Game Boy Color, Game Boy Advance, Nintendo Entertainment System (NES), Super Nintendo Entertainment System (SNES), Nintendo 64, and Nintendo DS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Emulators-in-the-App-Store-What-to-Know-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947034" /><br/>
There is also a Commodore 64 emulator on the App Store called <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/emu64-xl/id6483251916">Emu64 XL</a>.<br/>
<br/>
We have not come across any other fully-functioning emulators on the App Store released after the rule change, but more will likely be available in the future. Apple recently <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/">removed an emulator called iGBA</a> from the App Store for ripping off Testut's code for Delta and its predecessor GBA4iOS, while the developer of NES emulator Bimmy <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/nes-emulator-bimmy-for-iphone-in-app-store/">decided to remove the app</a> from the App Store to avoid the risk of legal action from Nintendo.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Legality</h2><br/>
While a U.S. court <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sony_Computer_Entertainment,_Inc._v._Connectix_Corp.">ruled</a> that emulators are legal, downloading copyrighted ROMs is typically against the law in the country. On its <a href="https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/55888/~/intellectual-property-%26-piracy-faq">customer support website</a> in the U.S., Nintendo says that downloading pirated copies of its games is illegal:<blockquote>Pirate copies of game files are often referred to as "ROMs".<br/>
<br/>
The uploading and downloading of pirate copies of Nintendo games is illegal.</blockquote>Nintendo recently sued the developers of Nintendo Switch emulator Yuzu for "facilitating piracy at a colossal scale," leading to a <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090357/nintendo-yuzu-emulator-lawsuit-settlement">reported &#36;2.4 million settlement</a>. Nintendo has yet to comment on the availability of emulators in the App Store, but Delta and its predecessor GBA4iOS have been available on the iPhone outside of the App Store for over a decade now without being shut down. Nintendo did <a href="https://www.idownloadblog.com/2014/05/14/nintendo-strikes-gba4ios-with-dmca-takedown-notice/">issue a DMCA takedown notice</a> against the GBA4iOS website in 2014, but the emulators have continued to remain available.<br/>
<br/>
For those who want to abide by the letter of the law, it is generally legal to download and play <a href="https://hh.gbdev.io/">"homebrew" games</a> available in the public domain.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/what-to-know-about-iphone-app-store-emulators/">What to Know About Apple Allowing Game Emulators in the App Store</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/what-to-know-about-apple-allowing-game-emulators-in-the-app-store.2424395/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AltStore PAL Alternative App Marketplace Launches on iPhone in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/altstore-eu-alternative-app-marketplace/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/altstore-pal-alternative-app-marketplace-launches-on-iphone-in-eu.2424392/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 10:30:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/altstore-eu-alternative-app-marketplace/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[One of the first alternative app marketplaces went live in the European Union today, with developer Riley Testut <a href="http://rileytestut.com/blog/2024/04/17/introducing-altstore-pal/">introducing AltStore PAL</a>, a version of his AltStore that can be accessed in EU countries.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/altstore-pal-eu.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947008" /><br/>
<a href="https://altstore.io">AltStore PAL</a> is an open-source app that is designed to distribute apps from independent developers. At launch, it features two apps, including Testut's Delta game emulator and clipboard manager app Clip. Delta is also being <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">simultaneously released in the App Store</a> outside of the European Union, but it looks like EU customers will need to download it from AltStore.<br/>
<br/>
Testut says that once AltStore PAL is "running smoothly," third-party app developers will be able to submit their apps for distribution outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. The app marketplace is designed to be decentralized with no directory, so developers will need to self-promote their apps and direct users to their websites to install an app through AltStore.<br/>
<br/>
Distributing apps through AltStore is free of charge, but it is worth noting that apps that see more than one million first annual installs will need to pay Apple an 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee. App marketplaces have to pay the fee for every install with no free allowance, so AltStore is charged 0.50 euros each time it is installed. To afford the fee, Testut is charging 1.50 euros per year for AltStore PAL access.<br/>
<br/>
Testut has been working on AltStore PAL since Apple announced plans to support <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/08/app-store-connect-alternative-app-marketplaces/">alternative app marketplaces</a> in iOS 17.4. It is open to all apps, but Testut says that it makes the most sense for "smaller, indie apps that otherwise couldn't exist due to &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; rules."<br/>
<br/>
AltStore PAL is equipped with Patreon integration to allow developers to monetize their apps. Developers can offer their apps to just their patrons, and this method of distribution also allows for a sub-1 million cap on those who can subscribe to use an app.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users in the European Union can download AltStore PAL <a href="https://altstore.io">from the AltStore website</a>. Alternative app marketplaces are not available outside of the European Union.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/altstore-eu-alternative-app-marketplace/">AltStore PAL Alternative App Marketplace Launches on iPhone in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/altstore-pal-alternative-app-marketplace-launches-on-iphone-in-eu.2424392/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS 14.5</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-14-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-14-5.2424391/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 10:27:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-14-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.5 update to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its launch. The public beta comes two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-seeds-first-public-beta-of-macos-14-5/">released the first public beta</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900182" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/macos-sonoma-4.jpg" alt="" width="2336" height="1314" /><br/>
Beta testers can opt-in through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, simply toggle on the Sonoma Public Beta. Note that you must sign up to participate on Apple's <a href="https://beta.apple.com">beta testing website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There have been no new features found in the &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.5 developer betas so far, and Apple listed no additions in its release notes. It is likely that the update focuses on bug fixes and other small under-the-hood improvements. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-14-5/">Apple Seeds Second Public Beta of macOS 14.5</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-public-beta-of-macos-14-5.2424391/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases Second Public Beta of iOS 17.5</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5.2424390/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 10:25:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 updates to public beta testers, allowing non-developers to test the software ahead of its release. The second public iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 betas come two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/apple-releases-ios-17-5-public-beta-1/">released the first betas</a> for public beta testers.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943813" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Public beta testers can get the beta by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Public Beta. Signing up on Apple's beta testing website is required.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.5 is limited on new outward-facing features, focusing primarily on changes in the European Union. App developers in the EU are now able to add their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> apps to their website, so that users can download them directly without having to use the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<br/>
<br/>
To offer an app for download from a website in the European Union, developers need to meet specific criteria. Developers need to be a member of the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more and must have an app with more than one million first installs on iOS in the European Union in the prior year. Other requirements include submitting to Apple's notarization process and publishing transparent data collection policies.<br/>
<br/>
This feature is limited to the European Union due to the Digital Markets Act and is not available to all users.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/everything-new-in-ios-17-5-beta-1/">also have updates</a> to mobile device management and there are code changes suggesting Battery Health functionality could come to the new iPads and that Apple will soon add alerts for third-party item trackers.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5/">Apple Releases Second Public Beta of iOS 17.5</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-second-public-beta-of-ios-17-5.2424390/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Delta Game Emulator Now Available From App Store on iPhone</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delta-game-emulator-now-available-from-app-store-on-iphone.2424388/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 09:58:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Game emulator apps have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/">come and gone</a> since <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">Apple announced App Store support</a> for them on April 5, but now popular game emulator Delta from developer Riley Testut is available for download.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Delta-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946979" /><br/>
Testut is known as the developer behind GBA4iOS, an open-source emulator that was available for a brief time more than a decade ago. GBA4iOS led to Delta, an emulator that has been available outside of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, but is now sanctioned by Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Delta is an all-in-one emulator that supports game systems including NES, SNES, N64, Nintendo DS, Game Boy, and Game Boy Advance. It works with popular game controllers, and supports cheats, save states, backups, syncing, and more. As this is Testut's longtime project, it is more polished and feature rich than other emulators that have popped up.<br/>
<br/>
Other features include custom controller skins, an option to fast forward, a "hold" button for games where a button needs to be consistently held, support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/haptic-touch-vs-3d-touch-whats-the-difference/">Haptic Touch</a>, and appropriate box art for imported games. Local multiplayer gaming is available, and up to four players can participate.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this week, Apple approved iGBA, a direct copy of Testut's original GBA4iOS app. iGBA made it to the top of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; charges, but Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-removes-igba-from-app-store/">pulled it</a> after learning that it was a knockoff. <br/>
<br/>
Delta can be downloaded from the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; for free, and it does not collect information or include ads. The app is available in the United States and other countries, but it is not available in the European Union where it is instead being offered through an alternative app marketplace. [<a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/delta-game-emulator/id1048524688">Direct Link</a>]<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">Delta Game Emulator Now Available From App Store on iPhone</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delta-game-emulator-now-available-from-app-store-on-iphone.2424388/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>AirPods Pro 2 Available for &#36;189 Plus More Deals on Headphones and Earbuds</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/airpods-pro-2-earbuds-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-available-for-189-plus-more-deals-on-headphones-and-earbuds.2424380/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 07:39:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/airpods-pro-2-earbuds-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a> and <a href="https://howl.me/cl3CWR0qA3a">Best Buy</a> today are discounting a variety of audio devices, including products from Apple, JBL, Samsung, Beats, Sony, Google, and more. The headliner of the sale is Apple's AirPods Pro 2 with USB-C for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;189.00</strong></a> at Amazon, down from &#36;249.00.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Airpods-Pro-2-Discount-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895403" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
In addition to the AirPods Pro deal, we've collected a few notable deals on other headphones and earbuds at Best Buy. Another highlight is the Beats Studio Pro headphones for <a href="https://howl.me/cl3CX4WdW0Q"><strong>&#36;199.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;349.99, as well as Sony's WH1000XM4 Over-the-Ear headphones for <a href="https://howl.me/cl3CR9qZNf6"><strong>&#36;279.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;349.99.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>AirPods 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHWRXH8B%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>AirPods Pro 2 (USB-C) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
All of the deals shared below do not require a My Best Buy Plus or Total membership, and are available to all shoppers. For a wider look at Best Buy's current deals, be sure to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/13/best-buys-sale-macbook-air-ipad/">check out our post from over the weekend</a>, which includes all-time low prices on iPads and MacBooks.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3COlSasGV">JBL Endurance Peak 3 Earbuds</a> - &#36;79.95, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CPAd6VAa">Samsung Galaxy Buds FE</a> - &#36;89.99, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CSSu7lPY">Sony WHCH720N Headphones</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CMK02TuT">Samsung Galaxy Buds2 Pro</a> - &#36;189.99, down from &#36;229.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CX4WdW0Q">Beats Studio Pro</a> - &#36;199.99, down from &#36;349.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CQUCRrFG">Sony WF1000XM5 Earbuds</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cl3CR9qZNf6">Sony WH1000XM4 Over-the-Ear Headphones</a> - &#36;279.99, down from &#36;349.99</li></ul> Our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> has more information on the latest Apple-related sales and bargains.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/airpods-pro-2-earbuds-deals/">AirPods Pro 2 Available for &#36;189 Plus More Deals on Headphones and Earbuds</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/airpods-pro-2-available-for-189-plus-more-deals-on-headphones-and-earbuds.2424380/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Rumor: Notes App to Offer New Voice Memos and Math Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-notes-app-to-offer-new-voice-memos-and-math-features.2424379/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 07:26:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 will add a few new features to the Notes app related to voice memos and mathematics, according to information obtained <a href="https://appleinsider.com/articles/24/04/17/apple-notes-in-ios-18-looks-to-up-the-ante-with-microsoft-onenote">by <em>AppleInsider</em></a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-General-Notes-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946875" /><br/>
First, the report claims that iOS 18 will allow iPhone users to record voice memos directly within the Notes app, and these recordings could then be embedded in notes. Audio recordings can already be copy and pasted from the Voice Memos app into the Notes app for playback, but this step would no longer be necessary starting with iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
Second, the report claims that the Notes app will likely gain support for displaying mathematical notation on iOS 18, meaning that users would be able to add more types of mathematical equations to notes. This feature will allegedly have some kind of integration with the Calculator app, but the exact implementation is unclear.<br/>
<br/>
The report also says macOS 15 will feature a redesigned Calculator app.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will unveil iOS 18 at its annual developers conference WWDC, which runs from June 10 through June 14, and the update should be widely released in September. We recently recapped <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/ios-18-new-features/">other new features and changes expected with iOS 18</a>, including a more customizable Home Screen, Siri enhancements, and more.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">iOS 18 Rumor: Notes App to Offer New Voice Memos and Math Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-rumor-notes-app-to-offer-new-voice-memos-and-math-features.2424379/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Considers Expanding Manufacturing Base to Indonesia</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-considers-manufacturing-base-indonesia/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-considers-expanding-manufacturing-base-to-indonesia.2424371/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 05:06:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-considers-manufacturing-base-indonesia/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Indonesia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple CEO <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tim-cook/">Tim Cook</a> said the company is "looking at" potential manufacturing opportunities in Indonesia following his recent meeting with the country's president. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/indonesia-tim-cook-president.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946822" /><div class="center-wrap"><em>&zwnj;Tim Cook&zwnj; with Indonesian ministers (photo: AP Photo)</em></div><br/>
During the meeting with Joko Widodo, Cook highlighted the mutual interest in boosting local manufacturing to support Indonesia's economic growth. "We talked about the president's desire to see manufacturing in the country, and it's something that we will look out," Cook later told reporters.<br/>
<br/>
Indonesia has been actively seeking to attract foreign manufacturing to power its economic development, with the Widodo administration pushing to become a new hub for international business. This offers new openings for Apple as it pursues its strategy to reduce reliance on Chinese manufacturing, which is mainly operated by its assembly partner Foxconn. <br/>
<br/>
Apple seeks to diversify its supply chain in the face of geopolitical tensions, economic slowdown, and other risks such as production disruptions caused by China's COVID lockdowns. With production shifts already opened in Vietnam and India, Apple is exploring further expansion in Southeast Asia. <br/>
<br/>
"I think the investment ability in Indonesia is endless. There are many great places to invest, and we're investing. We believe in the country," Cook added.<br/>
<br/>
The meeting came shortly after Cook's visit to Vietnam, where he met with Prime Minister Pham Minh Chinh. In Hanoi, Cook outlined plans to deepen Apple's investment and increase expenditures with local suppliers, reinforcing the company's commitment to enhancing its presence in the region.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/indonesia/">Indonesia</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-considers-manufacturing-base-indonesia/">Apple Considers Expanding Manufacturing Base to Indonesia</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-considers-expanding-manufacturing-base-to-indonesia.2424371/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Boosts Efforts in Renewable Energy and Water Sustainability</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-renewable-energy-water-sustainability/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-efforts-in-renewable-energy-and-water-sustainability.2424369/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 04:47:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-renewable-energy-water-sustainability/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Environmental Responsibility</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is intensifying its global investment in clean energy and water sustainability, advancing towards its "Apple 2030" goal of achieving carbon neutrality across its entire value chain by the decade's end, the company has <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/04/apple-ramps-up-investment-in-clean-energy-and-water-around-the-world/">announced</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-global-clean-energy-and-water-Spain-solar-power-project_big.jpg.large_.jpg" alt="" width="980" height="551" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946813" /><br/>
<blockquote>"Clean energy and water are foundational to healthy communities and essential building blocks for a responsible business," said Lisa Jackson, Apple's vice president of Environment, Policy, and Social Initiatives. "We're racing toward our ambitious Apple 2030 climate goal while taking on the long-term work to transform electrical grids and restore watersheds to build a cleaner future for all."</blockquote>Apple says it has successfully increased its clean electricity capacity to over 18 gigawatts — a threefold increase since 2020 — largely powered by solar energy projects in the U.S. and Europe. The initiatives support Apple's operational and manufacturing needs as well as cater to the electricity used by customers to power their devices.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also set a target to replenish 100% of the freshwater used in its corporate operations in high-stress areas. The company has established partnerships aimed at restoring aquifers and rivers and has provided nearly 7 billion gallons of water benefits slated for the next 20 years. Apple says that, with the help of suppliers, the company conserved over 76 billion gallons of water through the Supplier Clean Water Program.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/environmental-responsibility/">Environmental Responsibility</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/apple-renewable-energy-water-sustainability/">Apple Boosts Efforts in Renewable Energy and Water Sustainability</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-boosts-efforts-in-renewable-energy-and-water-sustainability.2424369/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>WhatsApp Rolls Out Chat Filters to Help Find Conversations Faster</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/whatsapp-rolls-out-chat-filters/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-chat-filters-to-help-find-conversations-faster.2424358/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 00:09:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/whatsapp-rolls-out-chat-filters/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>WhatsApp</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[WhatsApp is rolling out new Chat Filters to make it easier to find the messages you are looking for and reduce the need to scroll through your inbox. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/whatsapp-chat-filters.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946801" /><br/>
The following three new filters appear at the top of the app's main conversation list: All, Unread, and Groups. In a <a href="https://blog.whatsapp.com/find-messages-faster-with-chat-filters">blog post</a>, WhatsApp describes them like so:<br/>
<blockquote><ul><li><strong>All</strong>: The default view of all your messages.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Unread</strong>: Perfect for when you want to see which conversations you need to catch up on or respond to. It shows messages that are either marked by you as unread or haven’t been opened yet, so you can prioritize your responses.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Groups</strong>: A highly requested feature, now all your group chats will be organized in one place, making it easier to find your favorite ones whether it's your weekly family dinner discussion or planning your next vacation. This will also show subgroups of Communities.</li></ul></blockquote>WhatsApp says the Chat Filters feature is rolling out now and will be available to everyone on both iOS and Android in the coming weeks.<br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://wabetainfo.com/whatsapp-beta-for-ios-24-8-10-75-whats-new/">WABetaInfo</a>, WhatsApp is also developing a feature that lets users pin their favorite channels to the top of the Channels list in the Updates screen, similar to how you can pin chats in the chats list. Initially, users will be able to pin up to a maximum of three channels, but WhatsApp has also tested up to five. The feature remains limited to WhatsApp beta users for now. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/whatsapp/">WhatsApp</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/whatsapp-rolls-out-chat-filters/">WhatsApp Rolls Out Chat Filters to Help Find Conversations Faster</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/whatsapp-rolls-out-chat-filters-to-help-find-conversations-faster.2424358/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Native Microsoft OneNote App Now Available for Apple Vision Pro</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/microsoft-onenote-vision-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/native-microsoft-onenote-app-now-available-for-apple-vision-pro.2424348/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:23:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/microsoft-onenote-vision-pro/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Microsoft <a href="https://techcommunity.microsoft.com/t5/microsoft-365-blog/microsoft-onenote-now-available-on-apple-vision-pro/ba-p/4115959">today introduced</a> a version of OneNote that is designed to run on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset. OneNote for Vision Pro was created for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, and it includes many of the features that are available on OneNote for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/microsoft-onenote-vision-pro.jpg" alt="" width="999" height="562" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946785" /><br/>
The app can be used to write memos, notes, and digital notebooks, and there are options to sync content to OneDrive for access across multiple platforms. There is support for tags like Important and To Do, and notes can be protected with a password.<br/>
<br/>
OneNote on Vision Pro works hands-free or with a connected keyboard and mouse. In the future, Microsoft plans to add support for Copilot, two-factor authentication, and inserting images from the camera or the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app.<br/>
<br/>
OneNote <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/microsoft-onenote/id410395246">can be downloaded</a> from the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> as of today. It works with personal and work accounts that are not managed by an organization.<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft has made many of its apps available on the Vision Pro, including Teams, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/microsoft-onenote-vision-pro/">Native Microsoft OneNote App Now Available for Apple Vision Pro</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/native-microsoft-onenote-app-now-available-for-apple-vision-pro.2424348/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in the iOS 17.5 Beta</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-5-beta-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-the-ios-17-5-beta.2424343/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:08:39 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-5-beta-features&#038;post_date=1713316119/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is currently testing iOS 17.5, the fifth major update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system that came out last September. Like iOS 17.4, iOS 17.5 primarily focuses on regulatory changes in the European Union, but there are a few other features worth noting.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Green-and-Purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-940351" /><br/>
This guide aggregates everything that's been found during the iOS 17.5 beta testing period so far.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="app_downloads_from_websites_eu_only">App Downloads From Websites (EU Only)</h2><br/>
iOS 17.5 introduces support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/02/ios-17-5-app-website-downloads-eu/">web-based app distribution</a> in the European Union, allowing developers to offer their apps for download directly on their websites. Apps can be downloaded from websites in the EU <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">as of the second beta</a>. <br/>
<br/>
As with the iOS 17.4 changes that added alternative app marketplaces, this functionality is limited to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> and can only be used in the EU. Developers need to be a member of the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more and must have more than one million first installs on iOS in the prior year to offer an app for download.<br/>
<br/>
All apps downloaded from websites onto iPhones must submit to Apple's notarization process, and while there is no commission to pay to Apple, Apple does charge a 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="podcast_widget">Podcast Widget</h2><br/>
The Podcasts widget that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or the Lock screen now features a background that changes depending on the art of the podcast that's being played.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="mobile_device_management">Mobile Device Management</h2><br/>
MDM solutions are able to enforce a beta version during automated device enrollment. Automated device enrollment is designed to simplify initial device setup.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_news+">Apple News+</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-news-plus/">Apple News</a>+ includes a new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-17-5-apple-news-quartiles-game/">daily word game</a> called Quartiles. The game requires players to combine tiles to form words and earn points. Quartiles is limited to customers who have a paid &zwnj;Apple News&zwnj;+ subscription.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-17.5-Quartiles-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945719" /><br/>
<h2 id="code_changes">Code Changes</h2><br/>
There are several changes to the code in iOS 17.5, and these hint at features that could come later in the beta or when the update launches.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="third-party_item_tracker_alerts">Third-Party Item Tracker Alerts</h3><br/>
iOS 17.5 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/ios-17-5-third-party-item-tracker-alerts/">references support</a> for third-party item trackers, a feature that Apple has been working on since last year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple and Google developed a cross-platform solution for unwanted tracking alerts, and it looks like iOS 17.5 will let &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users know when a third-party tracker is nearby. "You can disable this item and stop it from sharing its location with the owner. To do this, follow the instructions provided on a website by the manufacturer of this item," reads some of the code in the update.<br/>
<br/>
Google launched its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/08/google-android-find-my-device-network-2/">Android-based Find My Device network</a> earlier this month.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="facetime">FaceTime</h3><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> may gain a "Block All Participants" option for group &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; calls, possibly for blocking spam. This feature does not appear to be functional as of yet.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="ipad_battery_health">iPad Battery Health</h3><br/>
There are references to a Battery Health menu on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, a feature that is not currently available. This is not an option in the beta as of now, and it may be limited to the new iPads that Apple is rumored to be introducing in May.<br/>
<br/>
The Battery Health menu would likely show maximum remaining capacity and charge cycle count, similar to the Battery Health menu on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="new_apple_pencil">New Apple Pencil</h3><br/>
There are references to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> "V4" in the iOS 17.5 code, and there are also mentions of a "squeeze" feature that could perhaps add support for completing actions with a squeeze on the new &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
Apple is likely to release iOS 17.5 in early May. New iPads are planned for May, so the update could come out right around when Apple debuts the new &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; models.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-5-beta-features/">Everything New in the iOS 17.5 Beta</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-the-ios-17-5-beta.2424343/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>NES Emulator for iPhone and iPad Now Available on App Store [Removed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/nes-emulator-bimmy-for-iphone-in-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nes-emulator-for-iphone-and-ipad-now-available-on-app-store-removed.2424326/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:33:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/nes-emulator-bimmy-for-iphone-in-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first approved Nintendo Entertainment System (NES) emulator for the iPhone and iPad was made <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bimmy-nes-emulator/id1528825236">available on the App Store</a> today following Apple's rule change. The emulator is called <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/bimmy-nes-emulator/id1528825236">Bimmy</a>, and it was <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nes-emulator-bimmy.2424312/">developed by Tom Salvo</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-NES-Emulator-Bimmy-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946735" /><br/>
On the App Store, Bimmy is described as a tool for testing and playing public domain/"homebrew" games created for the NES, but the app allows you to load ROMs for any NES games available for download online, such as Super Mario Bros. and Donkey Kong. Nintendo released the NES game console in 1985, so some of these games are nearly 40 years old. On its <a href="https://en-americas-support.nintendo.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/55888/~/intellectual-property-%26-piracy-faq">website</a>, Nintendo says "downloading of pirate copies of Nintendo games is illegal."<br/>
<br/>
The release of Bimmy comes after <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/15/apple-further-explains-igba-removal/">Apple removed Game Boy emulator iGBA from the App Store</a> for ripping off another emulator known as GBA4iOS, which was distributed outside the App Store. Apple said it had approved of iGBA's functionality prior to learning that the app was a knockoff, suggesting that emulators for older Nintendo game consoles are permitted on the App Store, and Bimmy seems to be the first proof of that.<br/>
<br/>
Apple updated its App Review Guidelines to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/05/app-store-guidelines-emulators-music-app-links/">permit retro game console emulators</a> earlier this month. Apple says developers of emulators are "responsible for all such software" offered in the app, including compliance with "all applicable laws."<br/>
<br/>
<strong>Update:</strong> In a post on the MacRumors Forums, the developer of Bimmy <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nes-emulator-for-iphone-and-ipad-now-available-on-app-store.2424326/post-33074585">said</a> they decided to remove the app from the App Store. "No one reached out to me pressuring me to remove it," he said. "But I'd rather not have the risk."<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/nes-emulator-bimmy-for-iphone-in-app-store/">NES Emulator for iPhone and iPad Now Available on App Store [Removed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nes-emulator-for-iphone-and-ipad-now-available-on-app-store-removed.2424326/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Celebrating Earth Day and International Dance Day With New Apple Watch Activity Challenges</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-watch-earth-day-activity-challenge-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-and-international-dance-day-with-new-apple-watch-activity-challenges.2424325/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:23:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-watch-earth-day-activity-challenge-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Activity Challenge</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will launch its next Apple Watch activity challenge on Saturday, April 22 in celebration of Earth Day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-earth-day-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1036" height="583" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946748" /><br/>
To complete the challenge, Apple Watch owners will need to complete a workout that lasts for 30 minutes or longer, with the activity recorded through the Workout app or an app that adds information to the Health app.<blockquote>Let's get moving for the planet. On April 22, do any workout for 30 minutes or more to earn this award. Record it with the Workout app or any app that adds to Health.</blockquote>Apple Watch owners who earn the award will unlock a dedicated in the Fitness app, plus they will get a series of animated stickers that can be used in the Messages and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> apps.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/earth_day_2024_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946749" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/earth_day_2024_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946750" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/earth_day_2024_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946751" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/earth_day_2024_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946752" /><br/>
After the Earth Day challenge, Apple will also launch another challenge for International Dance Day, which takes place on April 29. The Dance Day award can be earned by completing a dance workout that lasts 20 minutes or longer, and it too will unlock a badge and animated stickers. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/dance_day_2024_4.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946765" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/dance_day_2024_3.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946766" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/dance_day_2024_2.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946767" /><br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/dance_day_2024_1.png?noresize" alt="" width="300" height="300" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946768" /><br/>
The April Earth Day challenge and Dance Day challenge follow the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/06/apple-watch-heart-month-activity/">the February heart month challenge</a>, and for those curious, it does appear that Apple has trimmed down the number of activity challenges that it is offering in 2024.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/activity-challenge/">Activity Challenge</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-watch-earth-day-activity-challenge-2024/">Apple Celebrating Earth Day and International Dance Day With New Apple Watch Activity Challenges</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-celebrating-earth-day-and-international-dance-day-with-new-apple-watch-activity-challenges.2424325/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iOS 17.5 Beta Lets EU iPhone Users Download Apps Directly From Websites</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-17-5-beta-lets-eu-iphone-users-download-apps-directly-from-websites.2424313/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the second beta of iOS 17.5 that's available today, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users located in the European Union are able to download apps directly from the websites of Apple app developers without going through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> or an alternative app marketplace.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-EU-iOS-Changes-Orange-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946723" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-announces-app-downloads-from-websites/">Since March</a>, Apple has been working on support for downloading apps from websites, and the feature is finally ready for testing. Apple started letting developers offer their apps through alternative app marketplaces in the EU in iOS 17.4, but the website option adds a new method for acquiring apps.<br/>
<br/>
App developers that want to offer iOS apps from their websites in the European Union <a href="https://developer.apple.com/support/web-distribution-eu/">need to meet specific criteria</a> to ensure the safety of &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users. Apps must undergo Apple's Notarization process, and developers need to be a member of the Apple Developer Program for two continuous years or more.<br/>
<br/>
Only apps that have had one million annual first installs or more on iOS in the EU in the prior year are eligible for download from a website. Developers that meet these terms will be able to use an API for web-based app downloads. Apps downloaded through the web using the API can be backed up, restored, and updated as standard apps can.<br/>
<br/>
When an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; user in the EU visits a website to install an app, users will need to grant express permission for that developer to install apps to Settings. A system sheet will display the app name, developer name, app description, screenshots, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Developers are only able to offer apps from their developer account, and are required to publish transparent data collection policies so users are aware of how data is collected and used. Apps distributed outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; need to provide customer support, refunds, and offer a way to manage apps.<br/>
<br/>
While developers do not have to pay a cut of app sales to Apple for apps distributed through websites, there is a 0.50 euro Core Technology Fee for each annual install over one million in the past 12 months. The fee is waived for nonprofit organizations, accredited educational institutions, and government entities.<br/>
<br/>
Downloading apps outside of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; is limited to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users who are located in the European Union, and Apple has implemented these options to comply with the EU's Digital Markets Act. The functionality is not available on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, nor is it open to &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; users in other countries.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/ios-17-5-app-web-downloads-eu/">New iOS 17.5 Beta Lets EU iPhone Users Download Apps Directly From Websites</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-ios-17-5-beta-lets-eu-iphone-users-download-apps-directly-from-websites.2424313/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers.2424315/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:59:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second betas of upcoming iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/02/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-1-to-developers/">released the first betas</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-17.5-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-943813" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a> Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
Most of the features that Apple promised would be coming in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; have now been released, but iOS 17.5 adds additional app ecosystem changes in the European Union. App developers can offer apps for download on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/12/apple-announces-app-downloads-from-websites/">directly from their websites</a>, in addition to through app marketplaces.<br/>
<br/>
There are also code changes that hint at new Apple Pencils and a Battery Health feature for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, with more information on what's new available in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/03/everything-new-in-ios-17-5-beta-1/">iOS 17.5 beta features post</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-ios-17-5-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Betas of iOS 17.5 and iPadOS 17.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-betas-of-ios-17-5-and-ipados-17-5-to-developers.2424315/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers.2424316/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:58:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-2/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.5 update to developers, with the software coming two weeks after Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/02/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-1/">released the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
We don't yet know what might be included in &zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.5, and no new features were found in the first developer beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-5-beta-2/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.5 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-5-to-developers.2424316/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Second Beta of visionOS 1.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-2-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-visionos-1-2-to-developers.2424318/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 09:57:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-2-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the second beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> 1.2 update to developers, allowing them to test new features ahead of the software seeing a public launch. The second &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2 beta comes two weeks after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/02/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-1-to-developers/">release the first beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-934088" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/visionOS-Home-Screen.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
The &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta can be downloaded by going to the Settings app on the device and toggling on developer betas. A registered developer account is required, and Apple recommends making a backup before installing new software.<br/>
<br/>
Apple may make further improvements to Personas, EyeSight, and other features with &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; 1.2, but no major new additions were found in the first beta.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/16/apple-seeds-visionos-1-2-beta-2-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Second Beta of visionOS 1.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-second-beta-of-visionos-1-2-to-developers.2424318/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
