<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:03:03 PST</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Urges FTC to Establish Stronger Right to Repair Rules</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ifixit-ftc-right-to-repair-rules/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-urges-ftc-to-establish-stronger-right-to-repair-rules.2410982/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 16:51:28 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ifixit-ftc-right-to-repair-rules/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Right to Repair</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular repair site iFixit <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/86420/were-calling-on-the-ftc-to-restore-our-right-to-repair">today sent a petition</a> to the United States Federal Trade Commission calling for new Right to Repair rules that would protect consumer interests.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/Apple-Self-Service-Repair-Program-iPhone.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-895789" /><br/>
iFixit's petition calls attention to some of the "blocks" that manufacturers have put in place that prevent customers and independent repair shops from repairing their electronics, such as proprietary screws or repairs that require software authentication, which is a method that Apple employs. iFixit wants the FTC to consider the following rules:<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Consumable components should be replaceable and readily available throughout a product's usable lifespan.</li><br/>
 	<li>Components that commonly break should be replaceable and readily available as repair parts.</li><br/>
 	<li>Consumers should be able to choose to take damaged products to a repair shop of their choice, or perform a repair themselves.</li><br/>
 	<li>When a manufacturer discontinues support for a product, its key functions should remain intact, and an independent repair shop should be able to continue to perform repairs.</li><br/>
 	<li>Identical components from two identical devices should be interchangeable without manufacturer intervention. (This is not the case with Apple devices).</li><br/>
 	<li>Independent repair shops should not be required to report customers' personally identifiable information to the manufacturer.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
In France, Right to Repair laws require manufacturers to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2021/02/26/apple-rolls-out-device-repairability-scores-france/">provide a device repairability score</a> that gives context on how difficult or easy it is to repair, and iFixit says that the FTC should adopt a similar policy in the United States.<br/>
<br/>
"Consider this a request for the FTC to stretch its arm out," reads <a href="https://www.ifixit.com/News/86420/were-calling-on-the-ftc-to-restore-our-right-to-repair">iFixit's blog post on the petition</a>. The site acknowledges that developing and enforcing any kind of rule could take years, but it is hopeful that the FTC will consider the request.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in August supported <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/11/california-right-to-repair-law/">California's Right to Repair law</a>, drawing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/23/apple-supports-right-to-repair-in-california/">praise from iFixit</a>, but there is no equivalent federal right to repair mandate at this time. Apple in October endorsed a push for nationwide <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/24/apple-expanding-device-repair-programs/">Right to Repair law</a> that "balances repairability with product integrity, usability, and physical safety."<br/>
<br/>
Apple was supportive of California's law in particular because it requires parts to be sourced from the manufacturer, and it does not allow for parts from third-party sources. Notably, California's law does not have some of the specific provisions that iFixit is proposing, such the option to swap components from two identical devices or the option to conduct repairs without tying components to a device's IMEI.<br/>
<br/>
While iFixit has lauded Apple for backing California's Right to Repair law, the site in September <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/19/ifixit-lowers-iphone-14-repairability-score/">lowered the iPhone 14's repairability score</a> from a 7/10 to a 4/10 because of the way that Apple ties repair components to a specific device by requiring validation.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/right-to-repair/">Right to Repair</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ifixit-ftc-right-to-repair-rules/">iFixit Urges FTC to Establish Stronger Right to Repair Rules</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-urges-ftc-to-establish-stronger-right-to-repair-rules.2410982/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Withings Launches Smart Scale That Helps With Diabetes Management</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/withings-smart-scale-diabetes-management/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/withings-launches-smart-scale-that-helps-with-diabetes-management.2410978/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:53:59 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/withings-smart-scale-diabetes-management/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Withings</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Withings today announced the launch of the Body Pro 2, a cellular-connected smart scale that is able to detect early signs of diabetes and assess the risk of diabetes complications.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/withings-diabetes-management-scale.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922562" /><br/>
Using add-on health modules that are available by prescription, the scale is able to track biomarkers that are usually only available in a clinical setting. The diabetes module monitors Electrochemical Skin Conductance, which allows it to detect signs of Diabetic Peripheral Neuropathies that can lead to diabetic foot ulcers. Peripheral neuropathies are one of the most common diabetic complications, according to Withings, and as of now, are checked for only at annual doctor visits.<br/>
<br/>
The scale works out of the box and requires no setup thanks to its cellular connection, which is able to transmit data securely to care teams. In addition to diabetes management, it has a number of other features, including support for tailored messages that can show up on the display, an eyes-closed mode that hides weight readings and instead provides motivational messages, and tools for measuring body composition.<br/>
<br/>
The scale is able to recognize patients using a ProgramMemberID feature that ensures that care teams are getting readings from the right person, plus there is an "engagement score" to allow for tailored coaching.<br/>
<br/>
More information about the Body Pro 2 can be <a href="https://withingshealthsolutions.com/devices/body-pro-2-2/">found on the Withings website</a>. As this is designed to be provided through a medical facility, pricing is not available.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/withings/">Withings</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/withings-smart-scale-diabetes-management/">Withings Launches Smart Scale That Helps With Diabetes Management</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/withings-launches-smart-scale-that-helps-with-diabetes-management.2410978/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.1, Preventing Downgrading</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-1/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-1-preventing-downgrading.2410975/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:17:42 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-1/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today stopped signing iOS 17.1, a move that will prevent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> users from downgrading to that version of iOS. Apple is no longer signing iOS 17.1 following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/07/apple-releases-ios-17-1-1/">release of iOS 17.1.1</a>, which came out on November 7.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.1-Feature-Fall-Muted.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-915266" /><br/>
It is not unusual that iOS 17.1 is no longer being signed. Apple routinely stops signing older versions of iOS after new releases in order to encourage customers to keep their operating systems up to date and to prevent users from downgrading to older, less secure versions of the software.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17.1.1 is the current version of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> that is available to the public. It introduced several bug fixes, addressing a weather widget bug and fixing issue that could cause NFC not to work in &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models charged with a BMW wireless charger.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ios-17-2-beta-3-new-features/">also testing iOS 17.2</a>, an update that is expected to come out in December.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-1/">Apple Stops Signing iOS 17.1, Preventing Downgrading</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-stops-signing-ios-17-1-preventing-downgrading.2410975/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Announces 8TB T5 EVO Portable SSD</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/samsung-announces-8tb-t5-evo-portable-ssd/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-announces-8tb-t5-evo-portable-ssd.2410973/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 15:00:48 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/samsung-announces-8tb-t5-evo-portable-ssd/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Samsung</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today <a href="https://news.samsung.com/global/samsung-unveils-new-portable-ssd-t5-evo-that-offers-8tb-capacity-in-a-compact-design">announced the launch</a> of its latest portable SSD, <a href="https://howl.me/ck0j1XGvcAW">the T5 EVO</a> with up to 8TB of storage space available. 8TB is the largest capacity size offered by portable SSDs on the market.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/samsung-t5-ssd.jpg" alt="" width="1440" height="800" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922565" /><br/>
The T5 Evo supports USB 3.2 Gen 1 speeds for transferring data at up to 460MB/s. That's much faster than standard hard drives, but slower than NVME SSDs like Samsung's T7 and T9 series.<br/>
<br/>
Samsung designed the T5 with a rectangular body that has a clip able to be attached to luggage and backpacks, and it features drop protection up to six feet thanks to a rubberized surface. Samsung has also included Dynamic Thermal Guard technology to protect against overheating.<br/>
<br/>
The SSD measures in at 3.74 inches in length and 1.57 inches in width, and it weighs 3.6 ounces, so it is portable and ideal for travel.<br/>
<br/>
The 8TB version of the T5 EVO SSD is priced at &#36;650, and it can be <a href="https://howl.me/ck0j1XGvcAW">purchased from the Samsung website</a>. Samsung is also offering 2TB and 4TB versions, priced at &#36;190 and &#36;350, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
<em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/samsung/">Samsung</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/samsung-announces-8tb-t5-evo-portable-ssd/">Samsung Announces 8TB T5 EVO Portable SSD</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-announces-8tb-t5-evo-portable-ssd.2410973/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Telegram Demos visionOS App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/telegram-demos-visionos-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/telegram-demos-visionos-app.2410969/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 14:09:16 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/telegram-demos-visionos-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Telegram founder Pavel Durov today showed off a brief glimpse at Telegram's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> app, which is one of the first third-party &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; app concepts that we've seen so far.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/telegram.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922553" /><br/>
In the video, which is <a href="https://t.me/durov/239">available on Telegram</a> and was first noticed by <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2023/11/14/telegram-visionos-app/">9to5Mac</a></em>, the Telegram app has a translucent design that blends into the area surrounding it, which is the design language that Apple is using for &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
The app has a sidebar that lists all of the available conversations that a user has going. Videos that are played pop out of the interface and become more immersive, while emoji characters take over the display and animate in unique ways when shared. Messages can be sent using a virtual keyboard or through dictation via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>.<br/>
<br/>
As with all &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; icons on the Home interface, the Telegram icon animates and pops out a bit when it is visually selected, with the animation serving as a visual cue that the app is highlighted. A tap of the fingers launches the app, as the Vision Pro headset uses eye and gesture navigation.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to launch the Vision Pro in early 2024, which likely translates to during or before the month of April. We should soon be seeing many other third-party app &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; experiences as the debut date approaches.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/telegram-demos-visionos-app/">Telegram Demos visionOS App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/telegram-demos-visionos-app.2410969/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything New in iOS 17.2 Beta 3</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ios-17-2-beta-3-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-2-beta-3.2410962/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 12:12:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ios-17-2-beta-3-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is continuing on with the beta testing of a new iOS 17.2 update, and the third beta includes new features and refinements for existing features. We are still early in the beta testing process, which means there are new discoveries to make.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iOS-17.2-Beta-3-Whats-New-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922574" /><br/>
iOS 17.2 beta 3 is available to developers right now, but Apple should be making the update available to public beta testers later this week.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Music Favorite Songs</h2><br/>
In the Music section of the Settings app, there is now an option to add songs to your Music Library when they are favorited. The feature is toggled on by default, but it can be turned off if desired.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-17-2-music-add-favorite-songs.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922545" /><br/>
The option to "Favorite" songs was added in iOS 17.1.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Keyboard</h2><br/>
Apple has added an option to disable inline predictions when typing. It can be accessed by opening up the Settings app, choosing General, going to Keyboard, and scrolling down to the "Show Predictions Inline" option.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/keyboard-inline-predictions.jpg" alt="" width="1808" height="1017" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922546" /><br/>
<h2>Phone and FaceTime</h2><br/>
In the Phone and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> settings, there is a Share Name and Photo option that uses the Contact Poster. Name and Photo Sharing can be toggled off, set to Contacts Only, or set to Always Ask, which prompts you before sharing that information with others.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/phone-share-photo.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922547" /><br/>
This setting was previously available for the Messages app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>FaceTime</h2><br/>
If you join a &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; call that includes a contact you have blocked, you will now get a warning. Apple provides warnings when joining a call with a blocked contact, or when a blocked contact is joining a call you're already on.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Photos</h2><br/>
When opening the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app after updating to iOS 17.2 beta 3, there is a prompt to allow &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; to access the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> library. &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; is then able to use &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; to curate songs for Memories.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/ios-17-photos-permission.jpg" alt="" width="1761" height="991" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922548" /><br/>
&zwnj;Photos&zwnj; is listed as an app accessing &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; under Settings &gt; Privacy and Security after enabling access. Note that &zwnj;Photos&zwnj; already had this capability, but Apple now offers an option to turn off access.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>More iOS 17.2 Beta 3 Features</h2><br/>
Know of a feature that we left out in this list? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/ios-17-2-beta-3-new-features/">Everything New in iOS 17.2 Beta 3</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-new-in-ios-17-2-beta-3.2410962/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Releases New Firmware for USB-C Apple Pencil</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/usb-c-apple-pencil-new-firmware/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-usb-c-apple-pencil.2410960/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:54:30 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/usb-c-apple-pencil-new-firmware/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Pencil</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the first firmware update for the USB-C <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> that came out last week. The new firmware has a version number of 10M5164.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Apple-Pencil-USB-C-sliding-cap-feature.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-917176" /><br/>
There is no word on what features, fixes, or updates might be included in the updated firmware, and Apple does not provide release notes for &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; software releases.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="New Apple Pencil (USB-C) - Unboxing &amp; Hands-On!" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MbuXDZ_VKRA" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to the MacRumors YouTube channel</a> for more videos.</em></div><br/>
The USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; is almost identical in design to the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2, but it is shorter and has a hidden USB-C port for charging and pairing. It is not able to wirelessly charge, and it lacks some of the features available with the more expensive &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; models such as pressure sensitivity.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The first update for the USB-C Apple Pencil is out!<br><br>Interestingly, it&#39;s labeled as &quot;Apple Pencil Gen 3&quot;<br><br>Version: 35347.35347.16<br>Build: 10M5164</p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1724514768571019574?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 14, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple does not have an established procedure for updating &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hardware, but in the case of the USB-C &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;, connecting it to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> with a USB-C cable and powering on the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; should be enough to spur the new software to download.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad-accessories.139">iPad Accessories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/usb-c-apple-pencil-new-firmware/">Apple Releases New Firmware for USB-C Apple Pencil</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-releases-new-firmware-for-usb-c-apple-pencil.2410960/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2410951/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:17:27 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today released the third betas of upcoming iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 updates to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">second betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Warm.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918854" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to opt into the betas by opening up the Settings app, going to the Software Update section, tapping on the "Beta Updates" option, and toggling on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with a developer account is required to download and install the beta.<br/>
<br/>
The biggest new feature in iOS 17.2 is the Journal app, which can be used to record daily activities and thoughts. You can write about your day to day life, but Apple also provides topic suggestions based on the music you listen to, the places you visit, and the people you see. Journal entries support pictures, voice recordings, and location information, with the app organized by entry date.<br/>
<br/>
In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, there's a Favorites playlist that houses everything you've favorited, plus Apple added support for collaborative playlists. You can now share a playlist with multiple people, and each participant can add songs.<br/>
<br/>
Stickers can now be used to reply to iMessages when you long press on a chat bubble in the Messages app, and there's also now support for the extra-secure iMessage Contact Key Verification option. If you have an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, the Action Button supports Translate in iOS 17.2, and there are new Weather and Clock widgets.<br/>
<br/>
More on what's new in iOS 17.2 can be found in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-beta-1-features/">iOS 17.2 beta features list</a>.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-ios-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Betas of iOS 17.2 and iPadOS 17.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-betas-of-ios-17-2-and-ipados-17-2-to-developers.2410951/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-3/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2-to-developers.2410950/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:16:21 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-3/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a> 14.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the software coming a week after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-2/">second beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900001" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/sonoma-desktop-wwdc.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><br/>
Registered developers can opt-in to the beta through the Software Update section of the System Settings app. Under Beta updates, toggle on the Sonoma Developer Beta. Note that an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> associated with an Apple Developer account is required to get the beta.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;macOS Sonoma&zwnj; 14.2 adds an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> Favorites playlist that houses everything you've favorited, plus Apple added support for collaborative playlists. You can now share a playlist with multiple people, and each participant can add songs. <br/>
<br/>
Shazam can also be added to the Control Center or menu bar on the Mac. <br/>
<br/>
Stickers can be used to reply to iMessages when you long press on a chat bubble in the Messages app, and there's also now support for the extra-secure iMessage Contact Key Verification option.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-macos-sonoma-14-2-beta-3/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of macOS Sonoma 14.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-macos-sonoma-14-2-to-developers.2410950/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Continues Development on visionOS With Beta 6 Release</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-releases-visionos-beta-6/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-development-on-visionos-with-beta-6-release.2410948/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:11:04 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-releases-visionos-beta-6/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>visionOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the fifth beta of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a>, the software that runs on the Vision Pro headset. The fifth beta <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/31/apple-releases-visionos-beta-5/">came out in late October</a>, so it has two weeks since Apple last released a &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; update.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-898552" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Vision-Pro-with-battery-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Only a limited number of developers have access to Vision Pro at this time, with the headsets used for app testing purposes. Most people do not have access to the &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; beta, and it is not entirely clear what Apple is adding in each &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; update.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is letting developers attend Vision Pro labs around the world, and developers who visit these locations are able to test the Vision Pro in person and get help from Apple engineers on their &zwnj;visionOS&zwnj; apps.<br/>
<br/>
The Vision Pro headset is not expected until early 2024, so Apple still has several months to refine the hardware and software.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-releases-visionos-beta-6/">Apple Continues Development on visionOS With Beta 6 Release</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-continues-development-on-visionos-with-beta-6-release.2410948/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-2-to-developers.2410946/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:07:29 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>watchOS</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming watchOS 10.2 update to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after Apple seeded the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-2-to-developers/">first watchOS 10.2 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901009" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" /><br/>
To install the ‌watchOS 10.2‌ update, developers will need to open the Apple Watch app, go to the Software Update section under "General" in Settings, and toggle on the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a>‌ Developer Beta. An <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a> linked to a developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
Once beta updates have been activated, ‌&zwnj;watchOS 10&zwnj;‌ can be downloaded under the same Software Update section. To install software, an Apple Watch needs to have 50 percent battery life and it must be placed on an Apple Watch charger.<br/>
<br/>
watchOS 10.2 adds support for iMessage Contact Key Verification, a feature designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials.<br/>
<br/>
Users can ensure that there is no "man in the middle" snooping on iMessage conversations, and there is a Contact Verification Code so that iMessage users can verify that they're speaking to the correct individual during in-person meetings or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-10/">watchOS 10</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-programming.135">Apple Programming</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-watchos-10-2-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of watchOS 10.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-watchos-10-2-to-developers.2410946/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.2 to Developers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-2-to-developers.2410949/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 10:06:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today seeded the third beta of an upcoming tvOS 17.2 to developers for testing purposes, with the beta coming a week after the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-2-to-developers/">release of the second tvOS 17.2 beta</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-869857" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/Apple-TV-2022-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" /><br/>
Registered developers are able to download the tvOS 17.2 update by opting in to the beta through the Settings app on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>. A registered developer account is required.<br/>
<br/>
tvOS updates are often minor in scale compared to other operating system updates, focusing primarily on bug fixes and smaller improvements rather than notable outward-facing changes, but tvOS 17.2 introduces an overhauled &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; app. <br/>
<br/>
The app now includes a sidebar that houses content from both Apple's services and streaming services that integrate with the tvOS Watch Now feature. There are dedicated sections for Search, Watch Now, ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-tv-plus/">Apple TV+</a>‌, MLS Season Pass, Sports, the Store, and the Library at the top of the sidebar, along with dedicated sections for streaming services like ABC, CBS, Comedy Central, Hulu, ESPN, Discovery, Peacock, Prime Video, and more.<br/>
<br/>
You can click into each streaming service to see content that's available specifically on that service, and there's also a new My TV section that replaces "My Channels."<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-seeds-tvos-17-2-beta-3-to-developers/">Apple Seeds Third Beta of tvOS 17.2 to Developers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-seeds-third-beta-of-tvos-17-2-to-developers.2410949/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Announces 2023 App Store Award Finalists</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-announces-app-store-award-finalists-2023/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-2023-app-store-award-finalists.2410931/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 08:00:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-announces-app-store-award-finalists-2023/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today shared its <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/11/meet-the-2023-app-store-award-finalists/">2023 App Store award finalists</a>, highlighting standout apps chosen by the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> editorial team. Apple has picked almost 40 apps and games to showcase across 10 different categories.<br/>
<br/>
<img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876046" src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/app-store-awards-2022.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" /><blockquote>"We are excited about the achievements of these App Store Award finalists who are helping users around the world to explore their interests in drawing, design, video editing, education, music, time management, working out, hiking, playing games, and so much more," said Phil Schiller, Apple Fellow. "These finalists are all incredibly talented and have put enormous effort into creating these great apps and games. We are inspired by their accomplishments and look forward to announcing the winners of the App Store Awards later this month."</blockquote><br/>
Apple has selected <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, and Mac apps and games finalists, along with top Apple Watch apps, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> apps, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a> games.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>App of the Year Finalists</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone App of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/alltrails-hike-bike-run/id405075943">AllTrails</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/duolingo-language-lessons/id570060128">Duolingo</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/flighty-live-flight-tracker/id1358823008">Flighty</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPad App of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/concepts/id560586497">Concepts</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/davinci-resolve-for-ipad/id1581363826">DaVinci Resolve</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/ai/app/pr%C3%AAt-%C3%A0-makeup/id1434594204">Prêt-à-Makeup</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac App of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/linearity-curve-graphic-design/id1219074514">Linearity Curve</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/photomator-photo-editor/id1444636541">Photomator</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/portal-immersive-escapes/id1436994560">Portal</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Apple TV App of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/in/app/bugsnax/id1449161497">Bugsnax</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/fiton-workouts-fitness-plans/id1442473191">FitOn</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/mubi-stream-great-cinema/id626148774">MUBI</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Apple Watch App of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/planny-daily-planner/id1515324201">Planny</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/gb/app/smartgym-gym-home-workouts/id922744883">SmartGym</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/tide-guide-charts-tables/id1406371071">Tide Guide</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Game of the Year Finalists</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPhone Game of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/afterplace/id1539778232">Afterplace</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/honkai-star-rail/id1599719154">Honkai: Star Rail</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/vampire-survivors/id6444525702">Vampire Survivors</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>iPad Game of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/my/app/eggy-party/id1555408463">Eggy Party</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lost-in-play/id6449434958">Lost in Play</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pocket-city-2/id1533709428">Pocket City 2</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Mac Game of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/elex-ii/id6443519981?mt=12">ELEX II</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lies-of-p/id6459738231?mt=12">Lies of P</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/return-to-monkey-island/id1658628321">Return to Monkey Island</a></li><br/>
 	<li><strong>Apple Arcade Game of the Year</strong> - <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/cityscapes-sim-builder/id1631153096">Cityscapes</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/hello-kitty-island-adventure/id1553505132">Hello Kitty Island Adventure</a>, <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/stitch/id1581052096">stitch.</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<h2>Cultural Impact Finalists</h2><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/balance-menopause-support/id1503345959">balance</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/copilot-track-budget-money/id1447330651">Copilot</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/endling/id1625083646">Endling</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/finding-hannah/id1617252957">Finding Hannah</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/how-to-say-goodbye/id1590322079">How to Say Goodbye</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/pok-pok-montessori-preschool/id1550204730">Pok Pok</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/proloquo/id1521978238">Proloquo</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/rebel-girls/id1555126110">Rebel Girls</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/too-good-to-go-end-food-waste/id1060683933">Too Good To Go</a></li><br/>
<li><a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/unpacking/id6450058135">Unpacking</a></li><br/>
</ul><br/>
According to Apple, the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; award finalists were picked for "excellence, inventiveness, and technical achievement." They have helped Apple users "flex their creativity, challenge themselves, and have fun with family and friends."<br/>
<br/>
Apple will pick a winner from each category (and several from the cultural category), with the winners to be announced in a few weeks. Winners receive a physical &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; award modeled after the design of the &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; logo.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-announces-app-store-award-finalists-2023/">Apple Announces 2023 App Store Award Finalists</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-announces-2023-app-store-award-finalists.2410931/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TikTok Launches Support for Adding Songs to Apple Music Library</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/tiktok-launches-add-to-apple-music/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-launches-support-for-adding-songs-to-apple-music-library.2410930/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:56:32 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/tiktok-launches-add-to-apple-music/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		<category>Apple Music</category>
		<category>TikTok</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[TikTok <a href="https://newsroom.tiktok.com/en-us/add-to-music-app-launches-in-partnership-with-major-music-streaming-services">today launched</a> its new "Add to Music App" feature with support for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, Spotify, and Amazon Music.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/tiktok-add-to-apple-music.jpeg" alt="" width="5760" height="3240" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922510" /><br/>
The feature allows users to directly save songs they find on TikTok to their preferred music streaming service library via an Add Song button located beside the track name at the bottom of a TikTok video. Users can also use the Add to Music App feature from an artist's Sound Detail page.<br/>
<br/>
The first time a user presses the button, they will be asked to choose their preferred music streaming service and it will default to that service from then onwards. Any added songs will also be saved to a new playlist in the music app and users can select other playlists to add to if they wish. The Add to Music App feature is now available in the U.S. and UK, with more countries to follow.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tiktok/">TikTok</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/tiktok-launches-add-to-apple-music/">TikTok Launches Support for Adding Songs to Apple Music Library</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/tiktok-launches-support-for-adding-songs-to-apple-music-library.2410930/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nothing Announces iMessage Compatibility via New App</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility-via-new-app.2410928/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:32:00 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Nothing</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Phone brand Nothing today <a href="https://us.nothing.tech/pages/nothing-chats">announced</a> plans to introduce a new "Nothing Chats" app that features iMessage compatibility later this month.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/nothing-imessage.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-922498" /><br/>
The app is powered by Sunbird, an unofficial iMessage client that debuted last year with over 10,000 downloads on the Google Play Store. To use the Nothing Chats app with iMessage, users will need to log in with their <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a>. The app touts end-to-end encryption in line with Sunbird's privacy policy.<br/>
<br/>
In a new video, Nothing CEO Carl Pei explained that the app will support individual and group chats, typing indicators, full-size media sharing, and voice notes. Features like read receipts, message reactions, and replies will be added later.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/A9PP8AeSbbo?si=5o-emFtogqMnGgag" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
<br/>
Nothing Chats will also support RCS messaging on the Phone (2). The app will be available in the U.S., UK, and EU from Friday, November 17.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nothing/">Nothing</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility/">Nothing Announces iMessage Compatibility via New App</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nothing-announces-imessage-compatibility-via-new-app.2410928/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>4 Best Black Friday Deals on iPad and iPhone Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/4-best-black-friday-ipad-iphone-accessories/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/4-best-black-friday-deals-on-ipad-and-iphone-accessories.2410927/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 07:14:44 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/4-best-black-friday-ipad-iphone-accessories/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Black Friday</category>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Today we're tracking a series of discounts on popular iPad and iPhone accessories, most of which have hit all-time low prices ahead of Black Friday. This includes the Magic Keyboard Folio, 11-inch Magic Keyboard, Apple Pencil 2, and MagSafe Duo Charger.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/accessories-snow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922499" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For a deep dive into all of the current best Black Friday deals, you can visit our guide on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>The Best Early Black Friday Apple Deals</strong></a>.<br/>
<br/>
Starting with the Apple Pencil 2, Amazon has the stylus for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;89.00</strong></a> right now, down from &#36;129.00. This is about &#36;5 higher than the previous Amazon all-time low price, so it's still a solid deal.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Apple Pencil 2 for &#36;89.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Moving to the iPad keyboards, Amazon is discounting the Magic Keyboard Folio to <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;169.00</strong></a>, down from &#36;249.00. This keyboard works with the 10th generation iPad, and Amazon's new sale price is now the steepest discount we've ever tracked for this accessory.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLFH8RC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;80 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard Folio for &#36;169.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
If you have an 11-inch iPad Pro, you can match it with the 11-inch iPad Pro Magic Keyboard for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;199.00</strong></a> on Amazon, down from &#36;299.00. This one is available in both White and Black colors, and it's another best-ever price.<br/>
<br/>
The only downside is Amazon's current shipping estimate, which has a generous one to four week estimate for shipping. This still guarantees a delivery by Christmas, so if you're looking to buy it as a present and want to take advantage of this solid discount, now is definitely the time to buy.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0931V9M9D%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;100 OFF</div>Magic Keyboard (11-Inch iPad Pro) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Amazon has the MagSafe Duo Charger for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08MWR2NXZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"><strong>&#36;98.50</strong></a> this week, down from &#36;129.00. Woot had this accessory for around &#36;94 last week, but that sale has now expired and Amazon's is now a solid second-best price for anyone who missed Woot's discount.<br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for just the MagSafe Charger, that Woot sale is still available. You can get it for <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13142092?url=https%3A%2F%2Felectronics.woot.com%2Foffers%2Fapple-magsafe-charger-21%3Fref%3Dw_cnt_wp_0_21"><strong>&#36;29.99</strong></a> in new condition (with bulk packaging) over there, which beats Amazon's current sale by about &#36;5.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08MWR2NXZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>MagSafe Duo Charger for &#36;98.50</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can find <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/02/best-early-black-friday-apple-deals/"><strong>all the Apple Black Friday Deals currently available</strong></a> in our dedicated post. For everything else, we're keeping track of all of the season's best Apple-related deals in our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/"><strong>Black Friday roundup</strong></a>, so be sure to check back throughout the month for an updated list of all the most notable discounts you'll find for Black Friday 2023.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/black-friday/">Apple Black Friday</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/community-discussion.20">Community Discussion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/4-best-black-friday-ipad-iphone-accessories/">4 Best Black Friday Deals on iPad and iPhone Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/4-best-black-friday-deals-on-ipad-and-iphone-accessories.2410927/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 May Feature More Power-Efficient Samsung OLED Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-may-feature-more-power-efficient-samsung-oled-display.2410919/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 05:23:33 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Next year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> could feature a more power-efficient display thanks to a new OLED material set that is reportedly being developed by Samsung specifically for Apple.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-16-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="3532" height="1986" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913689" /><br/>
A material set includes a variety of components for OLED screens, such as capping layers (CPL), which adjust the optical characteristics of the screen. Each component is produced by a specialist manufacturer and supplied to Samsung, which then uses them to construct the final OLED panel. <br/>
<br/>
A different composition of materials in the set can alter attributes of the OLED panel, such as lifespan, brightness, color accuracy, or manufacturing efficiency.<br/>
<br/>
Back in April, <em>The Elec</em> <a href="https://thelec.net/news/articleView.html?idxno=4489">reported</a> that Samsung was using its "M12" material set for this year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, while also developing a new OLED material set, dubbed "M14," specifically for Apple's 2024 iPhones. The precise reason for the development was not known at the time, but a new report from the Korean-language outlet suggests it could be related to making the OLED panel more energy efficient. <br/>
<br/>
Citing Korean Ubi Research analyst Daejeong Yoon, <em>The Elec</em> now reports that Samsung's OLED development roadmap has been focused on replacing blue fluorescent materials with a blue phosphorescence that could reduce the overall power consumption of an OLED panel. <br/>
<br/>
According to Yoon, Samsung originally intended to use the more power-efficient material in OLED panels developed for a variety of foldable phones in 2024, but it is not easy to develop, and Samsung could instead reserve it for Apple's M14 material set. <br/>
<br/>
"Following the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; next year, M14 will be applied to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 in 2025, and the application period for the Apple &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; OLED material set will increase to two years," Yoon was quoted as saying.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max are expected to have larger display sizes, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/16/iphone-16-display-sizes/">according to multiple sources</a>. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro will have a display that's 6.27 inches in size (rounded to 6.3), while the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro Max is expected to have a display that's 6.85 inches in size (rounded to 6.9). <br/>
<br/>
A previous report in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/01/iphone-16-oled-displays-micro-lens-efficiency/">September</a> suggested &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; OLED panels could use micro-lens technology to maintain or increase the brightness of the displays while potentially reducing their power consumption. <br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile an earlier report in May <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/18/apple-mass-produce-microled-iphone/">claimed</a> that Apple intends to mass produce more advanced microLED displays in order to lessen its reliance on Samsung and increase its own control over supply, laying the groundwork to realize its ultimate goal of bringing the next-generation technology to iPhones.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/theelec-kr/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/iphone-16-more-efficient-oled-display/">iPhone 16 May Feature More Power-Efficient Samsung OLED Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-may-feature-more-power-efficient-samsung-oled-display.2410919/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Delete Your Threads Profile and Stay on Instagram - Here&#039;s How</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delete-your-threads-profile-and-stay-on-instagram-heres-how.2410911/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 03:15:57 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Instagram</category>
		<category>Threads</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[When Meta launched Threads in July, one of the complaints users had about the platform was that it was impossible to delete your Threads profile <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/06/deleting-threads-profile-also-deletes-instagram/">without also deleting your Instagram account</a>.  <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/instagram-threads-app.jpg" alt="" width="1079" height="607" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-902359" /><br/>
Up until now, the only alternative was to "temporarily" deactivate your Threads profile. This option makes your posts and interactions with others invisible on the platform, but it leaves your posts on Meta's servers unless you go through them and manually delete them one by one.<br/>
<br/>
Thankfully, Instagram head Adam Mosseri on Monday <a href="https://www.threads.net/@mosseri/post/Czmfy17SDfl">posted</a> that the company was finally doing something to resolve the issue – it's in the process of rolling out a way to delete or deactivate a Threads profile separately while leaving the associated Instagram account intact. <br/>
<br/>
The following steps show you how to delete your Threads profile, as per Mosseri's instructions.<br/>
<ol><li>In the Threads app, tap the profile icon in the bottom-right corner of the screen.</li><br/>
<li>Tap the two-line menu icon in the top right of your profile.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Account</strong>, then tap <strong>Delete or Deactivate Profile</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Tap <strong>Delete</strong> profile, then confirm your choice.</li></ol>If you don't see the option, the rollout hasn't reached you just yet, but it shouldn't be long before it pops up, so check back in a day or two.<br/>
<br/>
According to Mosseri, Threads is also rolling out a way for users to prevent their Threads posts from appearing on Facebook and Instagram. When the rollout is complete, users can find two options in the Privacy section of the app's settings, under "Suggesting posts on other apps." Tapping this will reveal separate switches to turn off suggestions on Instagram and Facebook.<br/>
<br/>
Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg said on a company <a href="https://s21.q4cdn.com/399680738/files/doc_earnings/2023/q3/transcript/META-Q3-2023-Earnings-Call-Transcript.pdf">earnings call</a> last month that Threads now has "just under" 100 million monthly users. Since its launch earlier this year it has gained a web app, an ability to search for posts, and a post editing feature. However, the app still isn't available in the EU because Meta hasn't yet worked out how to comply with the bloc's <a href="https://www.independent.ie/business/technology/no-instagram-threads-app-in-the-eu-irish-dpc-says-metas-new-twitter-rival-wont-be-launched-here/a1927220337.html">Digital Markets Act regulations</a>.  <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/instagram/">Instagram</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/threads/">Threads</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/delete-threads-profile-keep-instagram-account/">Delete Your Threads Profile and Stay on Instagram - Here&#039;s How</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/delete-your-threads-profile-and-stay-on-instagram-heres-how.2410911/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Launches Tap to Pay on iPhone in France</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france.2410905/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 02:08:13 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>France</category>
		<category>Tap to Pay on iPhone</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has <a href="https://www.apple.com/fr/newsroom/2023/11/apple-introduces-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france/">announced</a> Tap to Pay on iPhone in France, allowing independent sellers, small merchants, and large retailers in the country to use ‌iPhones‌ as a payment terminal.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Apple-Tap-to-Pay-on-iPhone-avail-FR-transaction.jpg" alt="" width="1960" height="1306" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922462" /><br/>
Tap to Pay first arrived in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/02/08/apple-announces-tap-to-pay-iphone-feature/">February 2022</a> in the US, and allows  iPhones to accept payments via Apple Pay, contactless credit and debit cards, and other digital wallets‌‌‌.  All transactions are encrypted, and Apple has no information about what is purchased or the person who made the purchase.<br/>
<br/>
No additional hardware or credit card machine is required‌ to use Tap to Pay on iPhone. The feature uses NFC technology to securely authenticate the contactless payments, plus the feature also supports PIN entry, which includes accessibility options.<br/>
<blockquote>"We are very excited to offer Tap to Pay on iPhone to merchants throughout France, so that they have a simple, secure and confidential way to accept contactless payments while benefiting from the power, security and usability of the iPhone," said Jennifer Bailey, Apple Vice President of Apple Pay and Apple Wallet. "With more than 90% of bank cards in France equipped with contactless technology, and the increasing adoption of contactless payments, merchants will be able to accept payments from their customers with a simple gesture on their iPhone."</blockquote>The banking group BPCE (Banques Populaires, Caisses d'Epargne and Payplug) and along with Adyen, myPOS, Revolut, SumUp, Viva Wallet, and Worldline now offer Tap to Pay on iPhone to French customers. They will soon be joined by BNP Paribas, Crédit Coopératif, Market Pay, Stancer and Stripe, according to Apple.<br/>
<br/>
Tap to Pay on ‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌ requires ‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌ XS or newer models, and works for customers as any normal ‌‌‌‌Apple Pay‌‌‌‌ transaction would. Sellers just need to open up the app, register the sale, and present their ‌‌‌‌iPhone‌‌‌‌ to the buyer, who can then use an appropriate contactless payment method.<br/>
<br/>
France becomes the <a href="https://developer.apple.com/tap-to-pay/#regions">eighth region</a> to support Tap to Pay, following similar rollouts in the U.K., Australia, Taiwan, Brazil, Ukraine, and the Netherlands earlier in the year.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/france/">France</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tap-to-pay-on-iphone/">Tap to Pay on iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/14/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france/">Apple Launches Tap to Pay on iPhone in France</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-launches-tap-to-pay-on-iphone-in-france.2410905/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17.2 Beta: All the New Features So Far</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2410880/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 14:32:51 PST</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features&#038;post_date=1699925571/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is beta testing iOS 17.2, the second major update to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> operating system that came out in September. We are expecting to see a public launch in December, so there are still several betas to go before the software debuts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iOS-17.2-Feature-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918853" /><br/>
This guide includes everything new in the iOS 17.2 beta, and we'll be updating it throughout the beta testing period. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="journal_app">Journal App</h2><br/>
iOS 17.2 includes the Journal app that Apple announced as part of &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;. With the Journal app, users can record their daily activities and thoughts, with Apple providing optional prompts that can be used as inspiration.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/Journal-App-iOS-17-Feature-Green.jpg" alt="" width="2612" height="1469" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918878" /><br/>
A Journal entry can be added by tapping on the "+" button in the Journal app, and from there, users can choose a suggestion as the basis for their writing or just opt for "New Entry" to write anything at all.<br/>
<br/>
Entries are automatically tagged with a date for organizational purposes, but there are options for bookmarking, too. Journal entries can include images, voice recordings, and location tags.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_app_sticker_reactions">Messages App Sticker Reactions</h2><br/>
You can now long press on any chat bubble in the Messages app to add a sticker response that serves as an alternative to a tapback reaction. Tapping on "Add Sticker" lets you choose either a sticker or an emoji to apply to the corner of an iMessage.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tapback-reply-sticker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918892" /><br/>
There was already an option to drag a sticker or an emoji onto any message bubble, but this is a much quicker method of quickly responding to an incoming message with a quick graphic that is more expressive than a tapback reaction.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="spatial_video_recording">Spatial Video Recording</h2><br/>
With iOS 17.2, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max can be used to record spatial video that will be viewable in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/photos/">Photos</a> app on the Vision Pro headset. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/spatial-video-apple-visioin-pro.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911687" /><br/>
Spatial video recording can be enabled by going to the Settings app, tapping into the Camera section, selecting Formats, and toggling on "Spatial Video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a>." Apple says that for best results when recording spatial video, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> should be held stable in landscape orientation while capturing video. Video is recorded at 30 frames per second at 1080p, and one minute of video takes up 130MB of storage space.<br/>
<br/>
When spatial videos captured with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; are viewed on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, they appear as normal videos. Viewing the video in 3D requires the Vision Pro headset. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="collaborative_apple_music_playlists">Collaborative Apple Music Playlists</h2><br/>
There is now an option to create a playlist in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> that multiple people can add to. In a playlist you have made, tap on the three-dot icon in top right of the app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-collaborative-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="5484" height="3085" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918890" /><br/>
From there, select the Collaborate option and choose "Start Collaboration." You'll be able to create a link to the playlist, and anyone who has access to that link can add to it. You can also invite people to join via QR code, and if you want, you can approve each person that asks to join.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="favorites_apple_music_playlist">Favorites Apple Music Playlist</h2><br/>
Songs that you have favorited in the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; app are now aggregated into a Favorites playlist.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/apple-music-favorite-playlists.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918891" /><br/>
<h2 id="apple_music_listening_history_focus_filter">Apple Music Listening History Focus Filter</h2><br/>
There is a Focus Filter for the &zwnj;Apple Music&zwnj; Listening History feature, so if you want to let someone else use your device to listen to music, you can activate this to turn off the Listening History so their song choices won't affect your recommendations.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-focus-filters.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918906" /><br/>
<h2 id="action_button_translate">Action Button Translate</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max users can now <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-translate-action-button/">choose a new Translate option</a> for the Action button.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-translate.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918874" /><br/>
When the Action button is set as Translate, pressing to hold causes the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; to pop up a Translate window that listens for spoken text. It is able to translate from one set language to another, using the languages that you have previously set up in the Translate app.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="imessage_contact_key_verification">iMessage Contact Key Verification</h2><br/>
First previewed in December 2022, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/ios-17-2-imessage-contact-key-verification/">iMessage Contact Key Verification</a> is a feature designed for those who face "extraordinary digital threats," such as journalists, human rights activists, and government officials.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/Apple-advanced-security-iMessage-Contact-Key-Verification_screen-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-876653" /><br/>
Users can ensure that there is no "man in the middle" snooping on iMessage conversations, and there is an option to display a Contact Verification Code so that iMessage users can verify that they're speaking to the correct individual during in-person meetings or on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a> calls.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="messages_in_icloud_syncing">Messages in iCloud Syncing</h2><br/>
The "Messages" section in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/icloud/">iCloud</a> in the Settings app has been renamed to "Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;." It shows the total amount of storage that messages are taking up, the number of messages synced to &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj;, and the time of the last sync. There's also a "Sync Now" option to force an update.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-messages-in-icloud.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918896" /><br/>
Apple previously said that additional settings would be synced through Messages in &zwnj;iCloud&zwnj; in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, like Text Message Forwarding, Send & Receive accounts, and SMS filters across devices, so this may see those additional settings syncing.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_tv_app">Apple TV App</h2><br/>
Apple has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/26/apple-tv-app-redesign-tvos-17-2/">removed the separate tabs</a> for Movies and TV shows in the Store section of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> has said that Apple also plans to remove the option to purchase TV shows and movies from the iTunes app as part of a TV app redesign, but that has not yet happened.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-tv-app.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918905" /><br/>
<h2 id="emergency_alerts_local_awareness">Emergency Alerts Local Awareness</h2><br/>
Under Notifications & Emergency Alerts in the Settings app, there is a new "Local Awareness" option that can be turned on. Apple says that Local Awareness uses your approximate location to improve the timeliness, accuracy, and reliability of emergency alerts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-emergency-local-awareness.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918902" /><br/>
<h2 id="weather_widgets">Weather Widgets</h2><br/>
There are new Details, Daily Forecast, and Sunrise/Sunset widgets for the Weather app. Details shows information like precipitation chance, UV index, wind speed, and air quality, while Daily Forecast offers the weather for the next few days in a small widget size. Sunrise/Sunset shows the sunrise and sunset times for each day.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/weather-app-widgets.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918889" /><br/>
<h2 id="digital_clock_widget">Digital Clock Widget</h2><br/>
There is a new Digital Clock widget that can be added to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/home-screen/">Home Screen</a> or Lock Screen.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-clock-widget.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918894" /><br/>
<h2 id="contact_posters">Contact Posters</h2><br/>
You can now select rainbow-colored text for your name when setting up a Contact Poster in the Contacts app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-contact-poster-rainbow.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918893" /><br/>
<h2 id="books_page-turning_animation">Books Page-Turning Animation</h2><br/>
There's a new "Fast Fade" option for the page-turning animation in the Books app. Apple has also removed the icon that you could turn on to scroll through content quickly.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-page-turn-animation.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918897" /><br/>
<h2 id="airplay">AirPlay</h2><br/>
There's a new "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airplay/">AirPlay</a> Receiver" setting that will allow the upcoming &zwnj;Apple Vision Pro&zwnj; headset to stream or share content to an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-airplay-handoff.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918898" /><br/>
It also looks like the &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; feature for hotels that Apple announced earlier this year is live or will be live soon. It is designed to let you &zwnj;AirPlay&zwnj; content from your &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; to an AirPlay-equipped smart TV.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="memoji">Memoji</h2><br/>
Apple added a "Body" section for Memoji where users can customize waist, bust, shoulders, and arms.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-memoji-body.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918895" /><br/>
<h2 id="news_app">News App</h2><br/>
The News app now supports Live Activities for following news-related events such as elections.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/ios-17-2-apple-news-live-activities.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-918899" /><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="expanded_sensitive_content_warnings">Expanded Sensitive Content Warnings</h2><br/>
Apple's opt-in Sensitive Content Warning feature <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-expands-sensitive-content-warnings/">is expanding</a> to Contact Posters in the Contacts and Phone apps, as well as in stickers in the Messages app. Sensitive Content Warnings use on-device machine learning to blur out photos or videos with any nudity detected before users view them.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/Sensitive-Content-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922023" /><br/>
<h2 id="app_store_categories">App Store Categories</h2><br/>
The "Apps" and "Games" sections of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/09/ios-17-2-beta-app-store/">new top bar navigation</a> that allows users to scroll through various app categories, exploring apps in that category with a tap.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/app-store-categories.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-922085" /><br/>
The categories mirror the categories that can be found at the bottom of each &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; section, and it is a layout that Apple has previously used for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-arcade/">Apple Arcade</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="applecare+_coverage_menu">AppleCare+ Coverage Menu</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ "Coverage" menu is now in Settings > General rather than Settings > General > About, making it more visible than before. The Coverage interface lists &zwnj;AppleCare&zwnj;+ on your device and any paired AirPods. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="siri">Siri</h2><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> in iOS 17.2 can provide details on an estimated time of arrival when there are active turn-by-turn directions in the Maps app, and the personal assistant can provide altitude data. <br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="more_ios_17.2_beta_features">More iOS 17.2 Beta Features</h2><br/>
Know of a feature that we've missed on this list? Let us know in the comments below.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ios-17-2-beta-features/">iOS 17.2 Beta: All the New Features So Far</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-2-beta-all-the-new-features-so-far.2410880/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
