<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 03:02:54 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Everything to Expect From the &#039;It&#039;s Glowtime&#039; Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-september-2024-event-what-to-expect/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-to-expect-from-the-its-glowtime-apple-event.2435249/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 12:30:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-september-2024-event-what-to-expect&#038;post_date=1725661858/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will hold its annual fall iPhone-centric event on Monday, September 9 at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time. There are multiple new devices on the horizon, including new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, refreshes for all of the Apple Watches, new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a>, and perhaps some other surprises.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/d5BA0CZLhlw" title="Apple&#39;s &quot;It&#39;s Glowtime&quot; Event: What to Expect for iPhone 16, Apple Watch, &amp; More!" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
This guide highlights everything that we might see at Apple's "It's Glowtime" event based on current rumors.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_16_and_iphone_16_plus">iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Plus</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus will look almost identical to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus, with few design changes planned, but there are new capabilities to look forward to.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-16-Camera-Lozenge-2-Perspective.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-935161" /><br/>
Apple plans to bring the Action Button to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus, so it won't be a Pro-exclusive feature anymore and will be available on all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models. The Action Button can be set to turn on a Focus mode, activate a Shortcut, open the Camera, activate the Flashlight, and more. With <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a>, it can do even more because you can also assign Control Center controls to the Action Button, and third-party developers can now make Control Center options.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/iphone-16-colors-dummies.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-960310" /><em>Dummy models featuring the rumored &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; colors</em></div><br/>
Along with the Action Button, all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models could have a Capture Button, located on the right side of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> below the Power Button. On U.S. iPhones, it will be located where the mmWave antenna is on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models, with the antenna moving to the left with the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup. While most rumors have suggested it's coming to all models, there is a chance that it could be limited to the Pro models. <br/>
<br/>
The Capture Button will be used to take images and video, and it will respond to pressure and touch for extra gesture support. A light press will autofocus, while a harder press will take the shot. Swiping left and right will zoom in or out, and there may also be an option for swapping between photo and video modes.<br/>
<br/>
Rather than the diagonal camera that Apple has used for the last several &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and 16 Plus will have a vertical camera arrangement for the dual-lens camera system. The vertical arrangement could allow for the iPhones to capture spatial video for the Vision Pro.<br/>
<br/>
The Main camera isn't expected to get an upgrade, but Apple might boost the aperture of the Ultra Wide camera to improve low-light performance and add support for macro mode for the first time.<br/>
<br/>
There will be new colors for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, with some rumors suggesting we'll see black, green, light pink, blue, and white for five total color options, and other rumors pointing toward green, white, pink, and blue. In both of these scenarios, the white replaces the yellow Apple used for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models. Apple is rumored to be using the color-infused back glass that it used for the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, but with a frosted effect for the glass that contrasts with the frame color.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could opt for a more power efficient OLED display that might improve battery life while also increasing overall brightness.<br/>
<br/>
A18 chips will be in all the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, which means the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will support the Apple Intelligence features that are coming in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. There could also be some iPhone-specific Apple Intelligence functionality that hasn't yet been announced.<br/>
<br/>
The A18 chips will be built on TSMC's 3-nanometer process, with Apple expected to include Neural Engine improvements for Apple Intelligence. Both &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will get 8GB RAM, up from 6GB in the prior-generation models in order to support AI. Apple may also be planning for a new thermal design that will combat overheating and improve performance.<br/>
<br/>
There could be some minor increases to battery life for the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model, as it is rumored to be getting a minor capacity boost. Depending on the chip efficiency, we could see some small improvements for both models, but that will depend on how much battery the new features eat up.<br/>
<br/>
We have more on the features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">coming to the iPhone 16 in our roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="iphone_16_pro_and_iphone_16_pro_max">iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max</h2><br/>
Like the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and Pro Max will get the all-new Capture Button, and in these devices, it will be accompanied by some camera improvements.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is planning for a 48-megapixel Ultra Wide lens that uses pixel binning down to 12-megapixels, and the end result is basically much better performance in low-light for your wide-angle shots and your macro photos. The 5x Telephoto lens that was limited to the 15 Pro Max will be coming to the 16 Pro, so both Pro models will have it this time around.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Left-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928696" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models may be able to record 4K video at up to 120 frames per second, an increase over the current 60 frames per second limit when filming in 4K. Apple has also tested 8K recording, but it is not clear if that made it into the launch version of the device. Apple also plans to add a feature for pausing and resuming a video recording. <br/>
<br/>
Display size is getting bigger, and it's the first time we've seen an increase in display size since the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12. The &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; display will measure in at 6.3 inches, up from 6.1, while the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will have a 6.9-inch display, up from 6.7 inches. The change is not drastic, but it will be noticeable if you have an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; next to an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There could be some improvements to the Main camera, and there's a chance the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will have a new Sony sensor that offers higher-quality images with better dynamic range and noise control.<br/>
<br/>
We're also expecting the bezels around the edge of the display to be slimmed down, and Apple is rumored to be adopting more efficient OLED display technology, so we could see some improvements to brightness and contrast. According to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, the bezels could be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/">about a third smaller</a>. <br/>
<br/>
All of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models will get an A18 chip, but there could be variants. Apple could use a higher-end A18 chip with an extra GPU core in the Pro models, which would let all &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; devices run Apple Intelligence, but would still provide for some differentiation between the Pro and non-Pro models. A new thermal architecture with a graphene heatsink and metal battery casing is expected, and while the heatsink is also coming to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj;, the other thermal changes could be Pro only.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to adopt Qualcomm's X75 5G modem in the Pro models for faster 5G speeds through carrier aggregation. The X75 has a combined mmWave and sub-6GHz transceiver rather than using separate hardware, so it's smaller and uses up less power.<br/>
<br/>
We could see improvements in battery life with the X75 chip and the A18 processor, plus Apple is using slightly bigger batteries with a 5 to 9 percent jump in capacity. There have been rumors that the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models will support Wi-Fi 7, but that's also a feature Apple might hold until next year. As for storage, both Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/both-iphone-16-pro-models-256gb-base-storage/">could start with 256GB</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Early on, there were a few rumors about 20W <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a> charging speeds and 40W wired charging speeds, but that's sounding like a long shot now. The microphone will have better water resistance and better sound thanks to AI. There may also be some &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Pro-specific Apple Intelligence features that we don't know about yet.<br/>
<br/>
As with every new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; launch, there are updated colors. We're expecting the standard black, white, and natural titanium options, but this year's special color is a shade of gold. Some rumors have described it as a bronze shade, and some dummy leaks have suggested that it's a darker brown color than Apple's prior gold selections, but color is so dependent on lighting that it's hard to say for sure. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s &zwnj;Mark Gurman&zwnj; says the shade "looks impressive and not terrible like the early renders."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/sonny-iphone-16-pro-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961824" /><em>Early &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; dummy models via <a href="https://x.com/sonnydickson/status/1824381930579824739?s=46">Sonny Dickson</a></em></div><br/>
<br/>
More detail on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;'s expected features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">can be found in the iPhone 16 Pro roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch_series_10">Apple Watch Series 10</h2><br/>
Apple is refreshing the Apple Watch this year, but there are some ambiguities and questions about just what we'll see. 2024 marks the 10th anniversary of when the Apple Watch was introduced in September 2014, and it will be the "Series 10," but the Apple Watch <em>launched</em> in 2015. While there have been rumors of a major anniversary refresh, it's been unclear if that will happen this year or next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-watch-series-9-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953899" /><br/>
The Apple Watch is expected to be slimmer than prior versions, and Apple is increasing the size. Rather than 41mm and 45mm models, it's looking like we'll get 45mm and 49mm options. Size could increase through a decrease in bezels and by making the casing itself larger. A 4mm jump will be a noticeable but not enormous size increase.<br/>
<br/>
There <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/26/alleged-first-look-at-apple-watch-x-series-10/">were CAD renders</a> of a next-generation Apple Watch with a 2-inch display, which is just slightly bigger than the 49mm Apple Watch Ultra display. That screen could be destined for the 49mm Series 10. Apple could boost water resistance with the design change, certifying the device for high-speed water sports up to 20 meters deep. The new Series 10 models may get the Depth app, which was first introduced for the Apple Watch Ultra. <br/>
<br/>
Aside from the increase in size and the thinner design, the updated models are said to look like the current Apple Watch models with no radical changes. Early on, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s &zwnj;Mark Gurman&zwnj; said that Apple was working on a new magnetic band attachment system, but it's no longer sounding like that's a feature we're going to get this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will update the OLED display to be more energy efficient, and with a bigger casing, battery size may increase too, leading to better battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is reportedly planning to include an updated heart rate and ECG sensor in the Apple Watch Series 10 that will enable new features like sleep apnea detection. Sleep apnea detection has been long rumored for the Series 10, but it was unclear if it would be implemented at launch because of an ongoing patent dispute that has seen Apple disable blood oxygen detection in the current-generation Apple watch models in the U.S. <br/>
<br/>
Sleep apnea causes a person to stop breathing while asleep, which can lead to excessive tiredness. It is usually diagnosed through a sleep study, and fixing it requires a breathing apparatus like a CPAP machine. The Apple Watch Series 10 and Ultra 2 will reportedly be able to detect sleep apnea using Apple Watch sleep tracking, providing a reading after collecting sleep data for several days.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also wanted to include blood pressure monitoring, but that feature was not ready for launch and will not be included in the Series 10.<br/>
<br/>
For the last several years, the Apple Watch has used an S-series chip that's changed little, but this year's S10 is expected to bring a notable upgrade in performance. While the Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/">will not get</a> "major" Apple Intelligence capabilities, there could perhaps be AI features tied to a future health coach service, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s &zwnj;Mark Gurman&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
We have additional details on what to expect for the Apple Watch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">in our roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch_ultra_3">Apple Watch Ultra 3</h2><br/>
If there are new health features in the Apple Watch Series 10, Apple will also add them to the next-generation Apple Watch Ultra that's coming this fall. We aren't expecting a new design or any other physical changes to the device, but it will get the same chip and health features that Apple plans to add to the Apple Watch Series 10.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ultra-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952114" /><br/>
<h2 id="apple_watch_se_3">Apple Watch SE 3</h2><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> 3 could get a refresh this fall, and there are rumors that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/05/apple-watch-se-plastic/">will use a plastic casing</a> rather than an aluminum casing for the device.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/apple-watch-se-gen-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-865510" /><br/>
A rigid plastic material would keep costs down, while also being more durable than aluminum in terms of scratches and drops. Such an Apple Watch could also be made in an array of bright colors, which would appeal to children.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has been promoting the Apple Watch as an option for parents who want to give their kids a device for communication and safety, and a lower-cost &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; could help and also differentiate the device from the aluminum Apple Watch models.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not used plastic for the casing of a device since the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 5c, a phone that came in vibrant blue, yellow, pink, and green colors. Aside from a new material, the &zwnj;Apple Watch SE&zwnj; is expected to have the same general design with no updates and no other feature changes except for an improved chip.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="airpods_4">AirPods 4</h2><br/>
There are two versions of the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; in the works, both of which feature a new design. The updated AirPods will look like a cross between the current AirPods and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, with Apple adopting a shorter stem. <em>Bloomberg</em>'s &zwnj;Mark Gurman&zwnj; says there <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/gurman-airpods-4-this-year/">will be an updated fit</a>, but it's not yet clear what that means.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/airpods-3-orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953897" /><br/>
The higher-priced &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; will have Active Noise Cancellation, a feature that has previously been limited to the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. The lower-end model will be a direct upgrade to the current <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Pricing on these new models isn't known yet. The &zwnj;AirPods 3&zwnj; cost &#36;179 (with &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; case), the AirPods 2 are &#36;129, and the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 are &#36;249, so Apple needs to price the new model somewhere in the middle. The lower-cost &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; could get a price drop to put it closer in line with the AirPods 2, which will be discontinued, and the ANC model could be priced between &#36;180 and &#36;200, well below the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is going to update the &zwnj;AirPods 4&zwnj; case, and it could have a new look. It will get a speaker for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a>, allowing it to play a sound when lost, and it'll have a USB-C port for charging instead of a Lightning port. &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj; charging will also still be a feature.<br/>
<br/>
Depending on design, the ANC probably won't be on par with the ANC in the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; as those have silicone ear tips, but there are rumors of improvements to sound quality.<br/>
<br/>
Eventually, Apple plans to announce hearing aid replacement functionality for the AirPods, plus it will add an option for conducting hearing tests with the earbuds. These features may not be available when the AirPods launch, instead coming at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_unlikely_possibilities">Other Unlikely Possibilities</h2><br/>
<h3 id="airpods_max">AirPods Max</h3><br/>
Apple plans to refresh the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; in 2024, but don't get excited. We aren't expecting any new features except for a USB-C port instead of a Lightning port, and possibly new color options. It's more likely that the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; refresh will come later in the year than at the September event.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Green-Triad.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936393" /><br/>
<h3 id="ipad_mini_7">iPad mini 7</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-7/">iPad mini 7</a> could see an update in 2024, but it likely won't be coming at Apple's September event. Apple is said to be planning to hold a second event in October 2024, and it would make more sense for the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> to come out then alongside new M4 Macs. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/09/ipad-mini-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-862965" /><br/>
Few changes are expected for the next-generation &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;, and it will continue to have an 8.3-inch display size with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> power button. There could be a small change to the display to cut down on the "jelly scrolling" effect that some people complained about with the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; 6. Jelly scrolling refers to the sometimes noticeable lag when scrolling vertically through text-based content like a webpage.<br/>
<br/>
We are expecting the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; to have a variant of the A17 or A18 chip that is compatible with Apple Intelligence, and we could get new colors, an upgraded front-facing camera, and support for Wi-Fi 6E.<br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="ipad_11">iPad 11</h3><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> hasn't been refreshed since 2022, and it is overdue for an update. There are rumors suggesting we could get a new model in 2024, but it too will likely come out later in the year. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/ipad-blue-green.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-962224" /><br/>
There are no rumors about new features for the next-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, but it is expected to get a better A-series chip.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="software_updates">Software Updates</h2><br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-18/">iPadOS 18</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sequoia/">macOS Sequoia</a>, tvOS 18, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/watchos-11/">watchOS 11</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos-2/">visionOS 2</a> are in beta testing, and at the fall event, Apple will give us a heads up on when the new operating system updates will be released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iOS-18-on-iPhone-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-955605" /><br/>
Typically &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; and its sister updates come out just a few days ahead of when new iPhones launch, so if the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models launch on Friday, September 20 after their September 9 debut date, we could see the software come out earlier in the week of September 20.<br/>
<br/>
There may also be Apple Intelligence features that are exclusive to the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models that Apple has been keeping under wraps, so there may be some software-based surprises coming.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="how_to_watch">How to Watch</h2><br/>
Apple's "It's Glowtime" event will start at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time on Monday, September 9. Apple will <a href="https://www.apple.com/apple-events/">livestream the event on its website</a> and <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uarNiSl_uh4">on YouTube</a>, plus the livestream will be available through the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> app on supported devices.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Apple Event - September 9" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/uarNiSl_uh4" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
For those unable to watch the livestream, MacRumors will be providing full event coverage on MacRumors.com and the <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorslive">MacRumorsLive Twitter account</a>, plus we'll do a much deeper dive into all the announcements over the course of the next week.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-september-2024-event-what-to-expect/">Everything to Expect From the &#039;It&#039;s Glowtime&#039; Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/everything-to-expect-from-the-its-glowtime-apple-event.2435249/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 10 Could Have Upgraded Heart Rate Sensor and Better Water Resistance</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-10-upgraded-sensor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-could-have-upgraded-heart-rate-sensor-and-better-water-resistance.2435247/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:54:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-10-upgraded-sensor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming Apple Watch Series 10 and Ultra 3 models that Apple will introduce next week could include an updated heart rate and ECG sensor that will enable new health features like sleep apnea detection, reports <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-10-ecg-water-resistance/">9to5Mac</a></em>. Sleep apnea detection has been long rumored for the Series 10, but it was believed to rely on blood oxygen monitoring, a feature that is disabled in current-generation U.S. Apple Watch models due to patent issues.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-series-9-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-948907" /><br/>
Sleep apnea causes a person to stop breathing while asleep, which can lead to excessive tiredness. It is usually diagnosed through a sleep study, and fixing it requires a breathing apparatus like a CPAP machine. The Apple Watch Series 10 and Ultra 3 will reportedly be able to detect sleep apnea using Apple Watch sleep tracking, providing a reading after collecting sleep data for several days.<br/>
<br/>
Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> has said that the new Apple Watch Series 10 models will have larger 45mm and 49mm display sizes, but <em>9to5Mac</em> claims that the resolutions are lower than current 45mm and 49mm models, and the site believes that the Series 10 will come in 44mm and 48mm sizes. The new watch sizes will be highlighted by a new "Reflections" watch face, as well as a "Regatta" Hermès watch face.<br/>
<br/>
The Hermès watch face will also be available on the Apple Watch Ultra 3, hinting at the first Hermès band for the Ultra. An Hermès band with what could be titanium lugs <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/hermes-edition-owners-thread.1999198/page-536?post=33358773#post-33358773">was recently spotted on eBay</a>, further suggesting that Hermès will design bands for the larger, more rugged Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
With the display size increase and a redesign that will see the new model offering reduced thickness, Apple could also boost water resistance, certifying the device for high-speed water sports up to 20 meters deep. The new Series 10 models may get the Depth app, which was first introduced for the Apple Watch Ultra.<br/>
<br/>
Other new features coming to the Series 10 include an upgraded S10 chip and new OLED display technology that is more power efficient. More information on rumors we've heard about the Series 10 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-x/">can be found in our guide</a>.<br/>
<br/>
There are no other features planned for the Apple Watch Ultra, and though not mentioned in the report, Apple also plans to refresh the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-10-upgraded-sensor/">Apple Watch Series 10 Could Have Upgraded Heart Rate Sensor and Better Water Resistance</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-10-could-have-upgraded-heart-rate-sensor-and-better-water-resistance.2435247/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch SE 2 Stock Running Low Ahead of New Models Next Week</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-9-se-2-stock-running-low/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-apple-watch-se-2-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-models-next-week.2435246/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 11:50:53 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-9-se-2-stock-running-low/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-watch/apple-watch">Apple Watch Series 9</a> and <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/buy-watch/apple-watch-se">Apple Watch SE 2 stock</a> is running low on Apple's online store in the U.S. and some other countries, with various configurations listed as currently unavailable. Some standalone <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/watch/bands">Apple Watch bands</a> are also out of stock.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/Apple-Watch-Faces-watchOS-10-Feature-Iridescent.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901010" /><br/>
Apple Watch inventory routinely dwindles ahead of new models launching. At its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">special event on Monday</a>, Apple is expected to announce Apple Watch Series 10 models with larger displays and a thinner design, an Apple Watch SE 3 that might have a plastic casing, and an Apple Watch Ultra 3 with internal upgrades, including a faster chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch SE 2 configurations selling out supports the expectation of an Apple Watch SE 3. The current Apple Watch SE was released in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
We'll have full coverage of Apple's event next week, ranging from the iPhone 16 series to all of the rumored new Apple Watch and AirPods models, so be sure to follow along to learn more about all of the devices that are announced.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-series-9-se-2-stock-running-low/">Apple Watch Series 9 and Apple Watch SE 2 Stock Running Low Ahead of New Models Next Week</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-series-9-and-apple-watch-se-2-stock-running-low-ahead-of-new-models-next-week.2435246/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: 9th and 10th Gen iPads Get Lowest Prices Ever, Plus First Deals on Anker&#039;s New MagGo Accessories</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-6-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9th-and-10th-gen-ipads-get-lowest-prices-ever-plus-first-deals-on-ankers-new-maggo-accessories.2435239/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:39:36 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-6-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week's best Apple deals focused on iPad models, including the 9th generation and 10th generation tablets, which both hit record low prices in the last few days. You'll also find steep discounts on Anker's latest MagSafe-compatible accessories, Sonos headphones and speakers, and Bluetooth trackers in the deals below. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0010.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848000" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/anker-maggo-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964247" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Buy two Anker MagGo accessories, get 15% off</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dhomepage_masterBanner_1">Anker</a></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dhomepage_masterBanner_1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">BUY TWO GET 15% OFF</div>Anker MagGo Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Anker this week <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger%3Fref%3Dhomepage_masterBanner_1">launched a sale</a> discounting a few of its latest MagSafe-compatible accessories, including the new <a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=J2shFQg6J/U&mid=43469&murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.anker.com%2Fproducts%2Fa25m8-maggo-qi2-wireless-charging-station-magsafe-compatible%3Fvariant%3D44057193316502%26ref%3Dmaggo-magsafe-compatible-wireless-charger_explore_the_latest_lineup">MagGo 3-in-1 Foldable Wireless Charging Station</a>. With this sale, when you buy two MagGo accessories, you'll get 15 percent off your order.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPads</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ipads-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964246" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Take up to &#36;130 off 9th and 10th gen iPads</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/04/every-9th-gen-ipad-deals/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09G9CJM1Z%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;130 OFF</div>9th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;199.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLT98Q7%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;50 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This week we saw notable discounts on both the 9th generation and 10th generation iPad, available for &#36;199.00 (&#36;130 off) and &#36;299.00 (&#36;50 off), respectively. These are both record low prices for each model of the iPad, and they're both available on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Sonos</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/sonos-ace-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964245" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Sonos headphones and other audio accessories</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers">Sonos</a><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/03/sonos-end-of-summer-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.sonos.com/en-us/shop/promotional-offers"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;180 OFF</div>Sonos End of Summer Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Sonos introduced a new set of discounts on headphones, speakers, and more this week during its end of summer sale. The most notable discount this time around is on the Sonos Ace headphones at &#36;50 off, priced at &#36;399.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Bluetooth Trackers</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/airtag-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964244" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on AirTag and Eufy SmartTrack Card</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1725642392301">Amazon</a></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1725642392301"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;13 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;16.95</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D54JZTHY%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;19 OFF</div>AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.98</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Solid deals on Bluetooth trackers reemerged this week, including the AirTag 4-Pack for &#36;79.98 and the Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;16.95. The price on the AirTag is just &#36;6 higher compared to its all-time low price, and you can also get the AirTag 1-Pack for &#36;24.99 right now on Amazon.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Grid Studio</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/grid-studio-iphone-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964258" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get 20% off select Grid Studio products</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://gridstudio.cc/">Grid Studio</a></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://gridstudio.cc/"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">20% OFF</div>Grid Studio Anniversary Sale</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Grid Studio is celebrating its fourth anniversary this week, and you can get 20 percent off select products with the code GRID4 at checkout. Grid Studio is known for its disassembled iPhone art, but you can also find products like Game Boys and N64 controllers.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9-6-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: 9th and 10th Gen iPads Get Lowest Prices Ever, Plus First Deals on Anker&#039;s New MagGo Accessories</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-9th-and-10th-gen-ipads-get-lowest-prices-ever-plus-first-deals-on-ankers-new-maggo-accessories.2435239/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: &#039;It&#039;s Glowtime&#039; iPhone 16 Apple Event Expectations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/the-macrumors-show-iphone-apple-event-expectations/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-its-glowtime-iphone-16-apple-event-expectations.2435233/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 09:01:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/the-macrumors-show-iphone-apple-event-expectations/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Featured (sticky)</category>
		<category>September 2024 Apple Event</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ahead of Apple's "It's Glowtime" <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> event, on this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/what-to-expect-from-apples-huge-iphone-16-event/id1602394741?i=1000668626393">The MacRumors Show</a>, we talk through all of the major announcements we're expecting to see.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_w6USrTUtgU?si=kbqRr42-OXpPVEC-" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus are rumored to feature vertical camera layouts, enabling spatial video recording. The devices are expected to be powered by the A18 chip with support for Apple Intelligence. The Action Button, which is currently exclusive to Pro models, is expected to appear on the standard models for the first time, offering customizable functionality for actions such as launching the camera or enabling silent mode. A new Capture Button is also rumored to be included, allowing for dedicated photo and video controls, with gestures such as swiping to zoom or using a soft press for focus.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will reportedly introduce larger displays, increasing from 6.1- to 6.3-inches and 6.7- to 6.9-inches, while incorporating slimmer bezels for a sleeker design. These models are also rumored to include an upgraded 48-megapixel ultra wide camera to enhance low-light photography. Like the standard models, the Pro variants will feature the A18 chip and the all-new Capture Button.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to unveil the Apple Watch Series 10 and Apple Watch Ultra 3, which will reportedly have sleep apnea detection and the S10 chip, potentially bringing some AI enhancements. The Series 10 is also expected to have larger, thinner casings. Meanwhile, the more affordable <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a> 3 is rumored to feature larger displays, plastic casings to lower manufacturing costs, and a faster chip.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to introduce the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airpods-4/">AirPods 4</a> in two variants. Both versions will reportedly include an improved design, a USB-C port, the H2 chip, and Bluetooth 5.3. The high-end model is expected to feature Active Noise Cancellation (ANC) and a charging case with a built-in speaker for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a>. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's "It's Glowtime" event starts at 10:00 a.m. PDT on Monday, September 9. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/30/the-macrumors-show-event-invites-and-m4-macs/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our discussion about what we're expecting from this year's M4 Mac models.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/05/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-apple-watch-x/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2024-apple-event/">September 2024 Apple Event</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/the-macrumors-show-iphone-apple-event-expectations/">The MacRumors Show: &#039;It&#039;s Glowtime&#039; iPhone 16 Apple Event Expectations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-its-glowtime-iphone-16-apple-event-expectations.2435233/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Kuo: Apple&#039;s 5G Modem to Rapidly Roll Out in iPhones Starting Next Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/kuo-apple-5g-modem-rollout-begins-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apples-5g-modem-to-rapidly-roll-out-in-iphones-starting-next-year.2435231/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 08:49:31 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/kuo-apple-5g-modem-rollout-begins-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple 5G Modem</category>
		<category>Ming-Chi Kuo</category>
		<category>Qualcomm</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is rumored to have been working on its own 5G modem for iPhones since 2018, and it appears the chip will finally debut next year.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/02/5G-Modem-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-886940" /><br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo today <a href="https://x.com/mingchikuo/status/1832075299460399578">estimated</a> that shipments of Apple's in-house 5G chip will reach 35-40 million units in 2025, and "grow rapidly" to 90-110 million units in 2026 and 160-180 million units in 2027.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo previously said <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/24/kuo-iphone-se-4-thin-iphone-17-apple-5g-chip/">two iPhone models with an Apple-designed 5G modem</a> will be released in 2025, including a fourth-generation iPhone SE in the first quarter of the year and an all-new, ultra-thin iPhone 17 model in the third quarter.<br/>
<br/>
All existing iPhones that are currently sold by Apple are equipped with Qualcomm modems for cellular connectivity, but Kuo expects Apple to transition away from Qualcomm over time. Earlier this year, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/01/31/apple-extends-qualcomm-modem-licensing-deal/">extended its 5G modem supply agreement with Qualcomm</a> for iPhone launches through 2026, so Apple still has plenty of time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/07/25/apple-intel-acquisition/">acquired the majority of Intel's smartphone modem business</a> in 2019, as part of its efforts to design its own 5G chip. It is unclear if Apple's chip would have any consumer benefits over Qualcomm's modems, but it would reduce Apple's reliance on Qualcomm. In 2017, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2017/01/20/apple-qualcomm-1-billion-lawsuit/">Apple sued Qualcomm</a> over alleged anticompetitive practices and &#36;1 billion in unpaid royalty rebates. The two companies <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2019/04/16/apple-qualcomm-settlement/">settled the lawsuit</a> in 2019.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-5g-modem/">Apple 5G Modem</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/qualcomm/">Qualcomm</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/kuo-apple-5g-modem-rollout-begins-2025/">Kuo: Apple&#039;s 5G Modem to Rapidly Roll Out in iPhones Starting Next Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/kuo-apples-5g-modem-to-rapidly-roll-out-in-iphones-starting-next-year.2435231/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: Apple Event in October Will Include New iPad Mini</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-ipad-mini-rumored-for-october/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-event-in-october-will-include-new-ipad-mini.2435228/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 08:33:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-ipad-mini-rumored-for-october/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">report today</a> outlining his expectations for Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">upcoming iPhone 16 event</a>, which takes place on Monday, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> briefly mentioned that a new iPad mini is "on deck" for another Apple event in October.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/09/ipad-mini-2021-youtube.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-816317" /><br/>
Gurman expects the new iPad mini to be announced at the October event alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/23/apple-testing-four-m4-macs/">first Macs with the M4 series of chips</a>, including the 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro, Mac mini, and iMac. The M4 chip debuted <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-debuts-m4-chip/">in the iPad Pro</a> earlier this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has yet to confirm an October event this year. In 2023, it held a virtual event on October 30 to unveil MacBook Pro and iMac models with the M3 series of chips.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman did not reveal any new features planned for the seventh-generation iPad mini, but previous rumors have indicated that upgrades will include a faster chip, upgraded front and rear cameras, a fix for "jelly scrolling" screen tearing in portrait orientation, Wi-Fi 6E and Bluetooth 5.3 support, and new color options.<br/>
<br/>
Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo previously said the next iPad mini would enter mass production <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/12/larger-ipad-air-launching-early-2024/">in the second half of 2024</a>, so there is agreement from multiple credible sources about the device being updated later this year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released the current iPad mini in September 2021, with new features at the time including a larger 8.3-inch display, a USB-C port, a Touch ID power button, the A15 Bionic chip, 5G support on cellular models, a 12-megapixel rear camera with Center Stage support, compatibility with the second-generation Apple Pencil, and more.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman said "new iPads" plural would be unveiled at the October event, so the entry-level iPad may be updated then too.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-ipad-mini-rumored-for-october/">Gurman: Apple Event in October Will Include New iPad Mini</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-apple-event-in-october-will-include-new-ipad-mini.2435228/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 65+ Upgrades to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-65-upgrades-to-expect.2430076/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 08:28:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro&#038;post_date=1725647280/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 13 Pro</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> is set to succeed 2023's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, introducing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-15-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro/">over 30 new features</a> and improvements to Apple's high-end smartphones. With many users adopting three-year upgrade cycles, plenty of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> Pro owners will be looking to upgrade to the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, so this guide breaks down every major difference you should be aware of between the two generations based on rumors. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/iPhone-13-Pro-vs-16-Pro-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-956610" /></div><br/>
The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj;‌ Pro debuted in 2021, introducing a brighter display with ProMotion technology for refresh rates up to 120Hz, the A15 Bionic chip, a telephoto camera with 3x optical zoom, macro photography and photographic styles, Cinematic mode for recording videos with shallow depth of field, ProRes video recording, a 1TB storage option, and up to five hours of additional battery life.<br/>
<br/>
Three years later, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to offer over 65 further upgrades. All of the changes the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature compared to their 2021 predecessors are listed below, using information from reliable sources that we have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">previously covered</a> here on <em>MacRumors</em>. We will continue to update this article as more rumors emerge prior to Apple's "It's Glowtime" event on Monday, September 9.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
The design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; is expected to be a relatively significant evolution over the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro, iterating on the titanium frame and slightly rounded edges introduced on the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models last year. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Surgical-grade stainless steel chassis</td><br/>
 <td>Aerospace-grade titanium chassis</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Glossy frame with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Brushed frame with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Ring/Silent switch</td><br/>
 <td>Action button</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Thermal design with copper heatsink and black foil battery casing</td><br/>
 <td>New thermal design with graphene heatsink and metal battery casing</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More repairable design</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Alpine Green, Silver, Gold, Graphite, and Sierra Blue color options</td><br/>
 <td>Black Titanium, White Titanium, Desert Titanium, and Titanium Gray color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h3 id="dimensions">Dimensions</h3><br/>
To accommodate larger displays, both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to grow in height and width. In addition to last year's increase in depth, the devices are due to be considerably larger, but with a notable reduction in weight thanks to the adoption of a titanium frame. <br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7.85mm depth</td><br/>
 <td>8.25mm depth (0.4mm thicker)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 146.7mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 160.8mm height</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 149.6mm height<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 163.0mm height</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 71.5mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 78.1mm width</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 71.45mm width<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 77.58mm width</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 204g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 238g weight</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 194g weight<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 225g weight</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="displays">Displays</h2><br/>
Both &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are expected to feature larger displays than their predecessors, pushing the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max to be the biggest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> ever offered. There are also reportedly improvements to the underlying OLED technology in store, in addition to considerably slimmer bezels, making for a noticeable overall display upgrade.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6.1- or 6.7-inch display</td><br/>
 <td>6.3- or 6.9-inch display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Always-On Display</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Slimmer borders around the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1,000 nits typical max brightness<br/>
Up to 1,200 nits peak HDR brightness</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 1,200 nits typical SDR brightness<br/>
Up to 1,600 nits peak HDR brightness</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>More efficient OLED display with brighter micro-lens technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="performance">Performance</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are rumored to bring notable improvements in processing power, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> Apple silicon chip with support for Apple Intelligence and 33% more memory.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip (TSMC's "N5P" 5nm process)</td><br/>
 <td>A18 chip (TSMC's "N3E" enhanced &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; process)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>16-core Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>Enhanced neural Engine with "significantly" more cores to support Apple Intelligence more effectively</td><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Dedicated AV1 decoder</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6GB memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="connectivity">Connectivity</h2><br/>
Connectivity is also due to get a significant upgrade on the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, bolstering the device's 5G, Wi-Fi, Thread, and Ultra Wideband specifications.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X60 5G modem</td><br/>
 <td>Snapdragon X75 5G modem</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi‑Fi 7 connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Thread networking technology</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="cameras">Cameras</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models are slated to receive a range of substantial camera enhancements, such as a larger main camera sensor, a 48-megapixel sensor on the ultra wide camera, and a dedicated hardware button for photography and videography on the side of the device.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Capacitive "Capture Button" with force-sensitive half-press and sliding gestures to trigger photography and videography features</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Photonic Engine for better low light performance</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1/1.65-inch main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌</strong>: 1/1.28-inch main camera sensor<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro‌ Max</strong>: 1/1.14-inch main camera sensor</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Sony IMX-703 main camera sensor</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: Sony IMX-803 main camera sensor<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: Sony IMX-903 main camera sensor with stacked design for better performance, a 14-bit Analog-to-Digital Converter (ADC) for high-quality image data conversion, and Digital Gain Control (DCG) for better dynamic range and noise control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>7P main camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>8P main camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with sensor-shift optical image stabilization</td><br/>
 <td>Telephoto camera with larger sensor, folded tetraprism design, optical image stabilization, and autofocus 3D sensor-shift module</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>77mm maximum focal length</td><br/>
 <td>120mm maximum focal length</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>5P telephoto camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel ultra wide camera with f/1.8</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel ultra wide camera with f/2.2 aperture, 48-megapixel ProRaw support, and improved low-light performance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 <td>6P ultra wide camera lens</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Anti-reflective coating on camera lenses</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 3x optical zoom</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, 2x, and 5x optical zoom</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>13mm, 24mm, 28mm, 35mm, and 120mm focal length picker</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 3</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Support for new JPEG-XL format</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Shoot and instantly transfer 48-megapixel ProRAW images to Mac via USB 3</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record video directly to an external drive</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 30 fps</td><br/>
 <td>ProRes video recording up to 4K at 60 fps with external recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Log video recording</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Academy Color Encoding System</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Record spatial video for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Action mode for improved video stabilization</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="batteries_and_charging">Batteries and Charging</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models could receive some major improvements in battery technology and charging, sporting bigger, denser batteries and faster charging capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Setting to prevent charging above 80%</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Battery manufacture date, first use, and cycle count information in Settings</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Single-layer battery technology</td><br/>
 <td>Stacked battery technology for increased energy density and prolonged lifespan</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 13 Pro</strong>: 3,095 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 13 Pro Max</strong>: 4,352 mAh battery</td><br/>
 <td><strong>iPhone 16 Pro</strong>: 3,355 mAh battery<br/>
<strong>iPhone 16 Pro Max</strong>: 4,676 mAh battery</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 20W wired charging</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 40W wired charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>15W charging via <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/magsafe/">MagSafe</a></td><br/>
 <td>20W charging via &zwnj;MagSafe&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="other_features_and_changes">Other Features and Changes</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models will also offer support for Apple Intelligence, Apple's new suite of personal AI features, later this year, as well as satellite connectivity, Crash Detection, and more storage.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Apple Intelligence support</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Emergency SOS via Satellite</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Microphone</td><br/>
 <td>Upgraded microphone with improved signal-to-noise ratio and water resistance</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
<tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Crash Detection</td><br/>
</tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning connector with USB 2 transfer speeds (up to 480Mb/s)</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port with USB 3 transfer speeds (up to 10Gb/s, 20x faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>DisplayPort support for up to 4K HDR video output</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Up to 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>Up to 2TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max are expected to be announced at Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">"It's Glowtime" event</a> on Monday, September 9. Pre-orders are likely to open on Friday, September 13, with launch following one week later on Friday, September 20. For more information about the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">see our comprehensive roundup</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="will_it_be_worth_upgrading">Will It Be Worth Upgrading?</h2><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; was a fairly significant upgrade over the &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro, introducing a vast array of significant features including a titanium chassis, much slimmer bezels, the Action button, and a USB-C port. The &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; will build on these upgrades, offering larger displays, the Capture button, improved cameras, and Apple Intelligence support. With a total of over 65 upgrades likely to be in store, many &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; Pro users will find upgrading to an &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; model worthwhile.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-13-pro-vs-16-pro/">iPhone 13 Pro vs. iPhone 16 Pro: 65+ Upgrades to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-13-pro-vs-iphone-16-pro-65-upgrades-to-expect.2430076/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Denies Evidence of Hidden Browser Settings to UK Regulator [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-denies-evidence-of-hidden-settings/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-denies-evidence-of-hidden-browser-settings-to-uk-regulator-updated.2435223/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 08:08:20 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-denies-evidence-of-hidden-settings/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Antitrust</category>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update</strong>: Apple told <em>MacRumors</em> that Open Web Advocacy's allegation that Apple is misleading the Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) is inaccurate. Apple says it told the CMA that the design of the identified browser setting was changed in a recent software update. The design was apparently never intended to discourage users from setting third-party browsers as the default.<br/>
<br/>
<hr></hr><br/>
<br/>
Apple faces allegations of misleading the UK's Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) over a user interface issue in iOS related to changing the default browser, <a href="https://open-web-advocacy.org/blog/apple-appears-to-mislead-uk-regulator-over-deceptive-default-browser-user-interface/">Open Web Advocacy</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/apple-ios-app-store-safari-changes.jpeg" alt="" width="2048" height="1151" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-933983" /><br/>
Earlier this year, reports surfaced accusing Apple of implementing a deceptive design practice in iOS that made it more difficult for users to switch their default browser if Safari was already set as the default. The issue was initially <a href="https://open-web-advocacy.org/blog/apples-one-weird-trick-to-stop-you-changing-your-default-browser/">highlighted in March 2024</a> and was independently verified by multiple sources, including <a href="https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2024/04/report-people-are-bailing-on-safari-after-dma-makes-changing-defaults-easier/2/"><em>Ars Technica</em></a> and the CMA. Specifically, the design hid the option to change the default browser when Safari was set as the default, while other browsers like Chrome and Firefox continued to display the option regardless of whether they were the default or not. This behavior was eventually addressed in an iOS update.<br/>
<br/>
Now, in a formal response to the CMA, Apple has denied that this issue ever existed. The company responded to the regulator's inquiry on August 1, 2024, stating that the allegations regarding the hidden option to change the default browser were incorrect. The response read, "This is not correct. The default browser app setting in the Safari tab is clearly visible when the user has set Safari as the default." The statement effectively denies that the behavior reported by the CMA and others had ever been present in iOS, despite the availability of screenshots, videos, and other forms of evidence supporting the claims from media outlets and industry experts.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has not provided an explanation for how its claim in the August response aligns with these findings, leaving open the question of whether the company's internal processes failed to verify the accuracy of its statements or whether it is actively attempting to minimize the situation. The matter could have legal implications. Under UK law, providing false or misleading information to a regulatory body such as the CMA can be considered a criminal offense. The CMA has the authority to request documentation, internal communications, and other records to verify claims made by companies under investigation. If it is determined that Apple provided false or incomplete information, the company could face penalties, including fines.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/antitrust/">Apple Antitrust</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-denies-evidence-of-hidden-settings/">Apple Denies Evidence of Hidden Browser Settings to UK Regulator [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-denies-evidence-of-hidden-browser-settings-to-uk-regulator-updated.2435223/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Kicks Off New Sale With Major Savings on Monitors, TVs, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/samsung-kicks-off-new-sale/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-kicks-off-new-sale-with-major-savings-on-monitors-tvs-and-more.2435219/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 07:18:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/samsung-kicks-off-new-sale/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung is getting ready to kick off a new <a href="https://howl.me/cm2nRsr0Knk">Discover Samsung</a> sale soon, and today the company has a few early access discounts available to customers. The popular Smart Monitor M80D is being discounted during this sale, but you'll also find sales on storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and wearable tech.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/07/samsung-smart-monitor-m80d-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-958530" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Samsung has its new 32-inch Smart Monitor M80D on sale today for <a href="https://howl.me/cmEbIKKFC8A"><strong>&#36;549.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;699.99, which is a second-best price on the monitor. The display retains key features of the previous model, like USB-C charging connectivity, AirPlay 2 support, an integrated webcam, and several smart TV features that enable it to be used when not connected to a PC. <br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbIKKFC8A"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;150 OFF</div>32-inch Smart Monitor M80D for &#36;549.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In terms of new features, the M80D includes a Multi Control feature that allows images and text to be moved between the display and a Galaxy Book, Tablet, or Phone. You can also pair Galaxy Buds to the monitor for a spatial audio experience with head tracking, as well as guided workouts when paired with a Galaxy Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXY1mXjV0">49-inch Odyssey G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;999.99, down from &#36;1,299.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmh387N2uIj">34-inch OLED Curved Smart Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;799.99, down from &#36;1,199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZtLQWw9">49-inch Odyssey OLED G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmSCTMeMf1L">55-inch Odyssey Ark 2nd Gen Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,799.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cm2n0jDHGtL">57-inch Odyssey Neo G9 Curved Gaming Monitor</a> - &#36;1,599.99, down from &#36;2,499.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>TVs</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cm2nXy3dE71">The Frame TV</a> - Save up to &#36;1,700</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXZZbVCrL">70-inch QLED 4K QE1C TV</a> - &#36;989.99, down from &#36;1,799.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX0OsAHAg">55-inch Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,499.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1gp9dhd">55-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K TV</a> - &#36;1,099.99, down from &#36;1,999.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX1NCbcAf">65-inch OLED S90C TV</a> - &#36;1,499.99, down from &#36;2,599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmcX2c09le2">85-inch Samsung Neo QLED 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;2,599.99, down from &#36;4,799.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Galaxy Products</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbV7Ybcky">Galaxy Z Fold6</a> - Save up to &#36;1,500 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbXJFsJWi">Galaxy Z Flip6</a> - Save up to &#36;800 with trade-in credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbYxetDfM">Galaxy Watch Ultra</a> - Save up to &#36;350</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmEbZknUAIi">Galaxy Buds3 Pro</a> - Save up to &#36;130</li></ul> Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/samsung-kicks-off-new-sale/">Samsung Kicks Off New Sale With Major Savings on Monitors, TVs, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-kicks-off-new-sale-with-major-savings-on-monitors-tvs-and-more.2435219/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>When to Expect an AirTag 2 to Launch</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/when-to-expect-airtag-2-to-launch/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-an-airtag-2-to-launch.2435217/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:52:16 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/when-to-expect-airtag-2-to-launch/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>AirTag</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple released the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> in April 2021, and the item tracking accessory has not received any hardware updates since then.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/07/airtag-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-903337" /><br/>
Below, we recap rumors about when the second-generation AirTag is expected to be released, as well as potential new features and changes.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Timing</h2><br/>
In a <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">report today</a> outlining his <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/">expectations for Apple's upcoming iPhone 16 event</a>, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman briefly mentioned that Apple is developing a new AirTag, but he does not expect the accessory to be released until 2025:<blockquote>A fresh AirTag is also in development, though Apple isn't planning a release until next year either.</blockquote>He did not provide any additional details about the next AirTag in the report.<br/>
<br/>
In October 2023, Apple supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo said mass production of the second-generation AirTag had been postponed from the fourth quarter of 2024 <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/18/airtag-2-postponed-until-2025/">until some point in 2025</a>, but he did not provide a reason for the apparent change in plans. Kuo and Gurman are thus in agreement that a new AirTag is not coming until next year.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Features</h2><br/>
Gurman previously said the new AirTag would feature an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/airtag-with-new-chip-due-next-year/">upgraded chip with improved location tracking</a>. If so, the AirTag could be updated with the second-generation Ultra Wideband chip that debuted in all iPhone 15 models last year.<br/>
<br/>
Kuo believes the new AirTag will have some kind of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/02/kuo-new-airtag-production-late-2024/">integration with Apple's Vision Pro headset</a>, but he has not shared any specific details.<br/>
<br/>
No design changes have been rumored for the AirTag so far. Read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags-2/">AirTag 2 guide</a> for more.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airtag/">AirTag</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/when-to-expect-airtag-2-to-launch/">When to Expect an AirTag 2 to Launch</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/when-to-expect-an-airtag-2-to-launch.2435217/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 16 Pro Models Rumored to Support 4K/120 FPS Video Recording, 8K Video Allegedly Tested</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/iphone-16-pro-4k-at-120fps-video-rumor/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-rumored-to-support-4k-120-fps-video-recording-8k-video-allegedly-tested.2435215/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 06:10:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/iphone-16-pro-4k-at-120fps-video-rumor/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>9to5Mac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iPhone 16 Pro models will be able to record 4K video at up to 120 FPS, according to "reliable sources" cited in a <a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/09/06/iphone-16-pro-4k-120fps-video-camera/"><em>9to5Mac</em> report</a> today. For comparison, all four iPhone 15 models are capable of 4K video recording at up to 60 FPS.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/iPhone-16-Cameras-Feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919420" /><br/>
The report adds that Apple has allegedly tested 8K video recording on the iPhone 16 Pro models, but it is unclear if this capability will be enabled. Since an 8K image is around 33 megapixels, the rumored 48-megapixel Main and Ultra Wide cameras on the iPhone 16 Pro models would be capable of 8K video recording, but the 12-megapixel Telephoto camera would not be. With the iPhone 17 Pro Max <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/25/iphone-17-pro-max-48mp-telephoto/">rumored to gain a 48-megapixel Telephoto camera</a> next year, the report said 8K video recording might debut on that device instead.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, the report said the iPhone's built-in Camera app will finally allow you to pause and resume a singular video recording.<br/>
<br/>
Many other details mentioned in the report have already been rumored by other sources, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/iphone-16-lineup-wave-of-camera-improvements/">support for a new JPEG-XL image format</a>, the Capture/Camera button <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/22/iphone-16-lineup-wave-of-camera-improvements/">supporting third-party apps</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/29/both-iphone-16-pros-5x-optical-zoom-rumor/">both iPhone 16 Pro models supporting the 5x optical zoom</a> functionality that debuted on the iPhone 15 Pro Max last year.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is expected to unveil the iPhone 16 series during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">special event on Monday</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/9to5mac-com/">9to5Mac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/iphone-16-pro-4k-at-120fps-video-rumor/">iPhone 16 Pro Models Rumored to Support 4K/120 FPS Video Recording, 8K Video Allegedly Tested</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-16-pro-models-rumored-to-support-4k-120-fps-video-recording-8k-video-allegedly-tested.2435215/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>How Much Will the iPhone 16 Cost?</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/how-much-will-iphone-16-cost/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-much-will-the-iphone-16-cost.2435213/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 05:43:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/how-much-will-iphone-16-cost/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> series is expected to launch on September 20 and will compete in a quickly evolving smartphone market, and with some notable upgrades rumored, the new models could see price changes compared to previous years.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/iPhone-16-Pro-Mock-Article.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-924441" /><br/>
Successive <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models always come with new features and hardware upgrades, but Apple typically does not increase the retail prices as a result. However, that could change this year due to an increasingly competitive smartphone market, potential supply chain disruptions, and other global economic challenges.<br/>
<br/>
Last year saw a record high for the total cost of an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s components, and could be a harbinger of things to come. According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/record-high-iphone-15-costs/">one report</a>, last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models cost more to produce than the previous <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>. For example, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max is believed to cost Apple &#36;558 to produce, a 12% increase over the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌ Pro Max model released in 2022.  <br/>
<br/>
The other models in the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;‌ lineup were also subject to cost increases. The standard ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;‌'s components totaled &#36;423, a 16% increase compared to the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;‌. The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;‌ Plus is calculated at &#36;442, a 10% increase over its predecessor, while the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;‌ grew by 8% to &#36;523. <br/>
<br/>
Despite the increased costs, Apple did not increase the retail prices of any of its ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;‌ 15 models last year. However, Tokyo-based research company Fomalhaut Techno Solutions believes that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/record-high-iphone-15-costs/">Apple's bottom line will be impacted</a> if the company continues to absorb the impact of increased production costs. That could see Apple choose to hike the retail prices of this year's &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; series.<br/>
<br/>
Speculation about a price hike is also due to a bump in hardware components required to support Apple intelligence. Apple is expected to increase the RAM in the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models to 8GB, up from 6GB in the previous versions.<br/>
<br/>
On the other hand, Apple will be wary of hiking prices in the face of the increased cost of living, as well as recent market challenges in Asia that have seen falling sales. For example, &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; resellers in China have become <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/29/iphone-sales-china-dependent-promotions/">increasingly dependent on promotional discounts</a> to move stock, indicating Apple's latest &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; generation is struggling to achieve the same popularity as previous models in China. Additionally, the design of the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; is not expected to change significantly, making it even harder to justify a price increase.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also mass producing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/20/iphone-16-pro-assembled-india-first-time/">India</a> for the first time as it looks to diversify production beyond China, which could potentially result in cost savings. According to a report by <em>The Economic Times</em>, the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; maker is anticipated to reduce production expenses by 10% through manufacturing Pro models in India. However, despite these savings, consumers may not see lower prices, as taxes and component costs could well keep retail prices steady.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/iPhone-15-vs-16-Feature-Yellow-Pink-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-936648" /><br/>
We don't know with complete certainty what prices Apple will set for its next-generation &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models. But it's worth noting that if the starting price of the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; model remains unchanged (&#36;799), it will have the same starting price as the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 12, which was released in 2020. That said, Apple could remove certain configuration options so that customers are essentially forced to pay more, as it did with the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max last year. <br/>
<br/>
Prior to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; release, speculation circulated that the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max might have a higher starting price of &#36;1,199, up from the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max's &#36;1,099 base price. This prediction proved partially correct, but for a different reason than expected. Apple didn't raise the price outright – instead, it removed the lowest storage option of 128GB for the Pro Max model. As a result, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max now starts at 256GB of storage, priced at &#36;1,199 – the same amount Apple previously charged for the 256GB &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max. So while the price-per-gigabyte remained consistent with the previous generation, the entry price increased.<br/>
<br/>
Apple could adopt the same strategy for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;. According to a new TrendForce report, this time Apple is expected to offer both the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max with a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/both-iphone-16-pro-models-256gb-base-storage/">minimum of 256GB storage</a>, doing away with the 128GB starting option on its smaller Pro model for the first time. <br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/iphone-16-launch-month-is-here-everything-we-know/">iPhone 16 Launch Month Is Here: Here's Everything We Know</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple will debut the new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; series on Monday, September 9 at a special event, dubbed "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">It's Glowtime.</a>" For all the details of what we can expect from the four new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; models, be sure to check out our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> roundups.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/how-much-will-iphone-16-cost/">How Much Will the iPhone 16 Cost?</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/how-much-will-the-iphone-16-cost.2435213/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: New AirPods Max and Apple TV Unlikely to Be Announced at September Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-airpods-max-and-apple-tv-unlikely/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-airpods-max-and-apple-tv-unlikely-to-be-announced-at-september-apple-event.2435209/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 05:09:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-airpods-max-and-apple-tv-unlikely/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Max</category>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>2024 AirPods Max</category>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[New versions of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> may not debut at Apple's upcoming "It's Glowtime" event, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">today suggested</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/Airpods-Max-Feature-Blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-936392" /><br/>
In a report detailing some <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">final expectations</a> for the September 9 Apple event, Gurman said that the company is still working on a new version of the &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; with new color options and a USB-C port instead of Lightning. This product refresh has been rumored for some time, but with plenty of &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; inventory still in stock, Gurman suggested that the new model may not arrive until later.<br/>
<br/>
Likewise, Apple has apparently been working on an updated &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; that was originally supposed to launch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">earlier this year</a>. With no sign of the new model and stable inventory of the current model, Gurman says that "a new version isn't on the immediate horizon."<br/>
<br/>
The new &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj; are <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1762690933659988326">not expected</a> to feature the H2 chip introduced in September 2022 or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/20/airpods-max-2-could-miss-out-on-adaptive-audio/">features like Adaptive Audio</a>. Gurman previously said that the changes are expected to be so minor that the refreshed device will still be considered to be first-generation &zwnj;AirPods Max&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Whenever it comes out, the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; is rumored to feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/18/apple-tv-faster-chip-2024-launch/">faster processor</a> than the current A15 Bionic chip, and even lower pricing. Apple analyst <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ming-chi-kuo/">Ming-Chi Kuo</a> suggested that the next &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/18/kuo-even-cheaper-apple-tv/">could have a sub-&#36;100 starting price</a><div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/2024-airpods-max/">2024 AirPods Max</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Max">AirPods Max (Caution)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/new-airpods-max-and-apple-tv-unlikely/">Gurman: New AirPods Max and Apple TV Unlikely to Be Announced at September Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-new-airpods-max-and-apple-tv-unlikely-to-be-announced-at-september-apple-event.2435209/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed Ahead of Apple Event</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/revealed-all-new-iphone-16-pro-colors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-ahead-of-apple-event.2435207/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 05:01:58 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/revealed-all-new-iphone-16-pro-colors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is "shaking up its color palette" for its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup this year, according to well-connected <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches"><em>Bloomberg</em> reporter Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/sonny-iphone-16-pro-colors.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-961824" /><em>Early <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> dummy models via <a href="https://x.com/sonnydickson/status/1824381930579824739?s=46">Sonny Dickson</a></em></div><br/>
According to Gurman, the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models will come in a Gold Titanium to replace Blue Titanium, while the Black, White, and Natural Titanium options that debuted with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> will remain unchanged.<br/>
<br/>
Previous rumors and leaks were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/19/iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed/">apparently accurate</a> about the Pro model colorways, although the Gold Titanium version was previously described as "bronze-like" with a "Desert Titanium" naming convention. Gurman <a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1831100741160743239">recently said</a> the Gold color "looks impressive and not terrible like the early renders."<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus will reportedly come in these colors: White (replacing yellow) and new shades of green, pink, and blue. Gurman does not mention a black option, but it's possible it could be available in essentially the same shade as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>'s black.<br/>
<br/>
Apple will debut the new &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup at its upcoming "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">It's Glowtime</a>" event, which is scheduled to begin at 10:00 a.m. Pacific Time on Monday, September 9.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/revealed-all-new-iphone-16-pro-colors/">New iPhone 16 and iPhone 16 Pro Colors Revealed Ahead of Apple Event</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-iphone-16-and-iphone-16-pro-colors-revealed-ahead-of-apple-event.2435207/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#039;Noticeably Thinner&#039; Apple Watch Series 10 to Eventually Get Sleep Apnea Detection</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-10-sleep-apnea/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/noticeably-thinner-apple-watch-series-10-to-eventually-get-sleep-apnea-detection.2435205/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 04:42:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-10-sleep-apnea/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The Apple Watch Series 10 will include a new sleep apnea detection feature, but it may not be available as soon as the new model launches, according to <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/apple-watch-series-9-display.jpeg" alt="" width="1960" height="1102" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-913380" /><br/>
Sleep apnea detection, which builds on the watch's existing sleep tracking, will attempt to determine if a wearer has sleep apnea and then suggest further testing with a medical professional.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman had expressed doubt about the feature's inclusion in the 2024 Apple Watch model, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/07/07/series-10-larger-screens-and-faster-chip/">previously reporting</a> that Apple's efforts hadn't gone smoothly and that it had "run into some serious snags." <br/>
<br/>
The sleep apnea detection feature was said to be in trouble because it relies on blood oxygen saturation, which Apple Watches in the United States cannot currently measure due to an ongoing legal dispute with Masimo. <br/>
<br/>
Gurman previously suggested that the dispute with Masimo could be resolved by September, or Apple could find a way around it by arguing that the blood oxygen sensor could be used for purposes that are not directly related to blood oxygen levels. Either way, the Apple Watch Series 10 model will eventually feature sleep apnea detection, perhaps via a later software update.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, the new hypertension detection (high blood pressure) feature Apple appears to have been working on has been insufficiently reliable during testing, suggesting the feature is being delayed and "no longer on the cards for an immediate release," according to Gurman.<br/>
<br/>
The overall design of the Apple Watch Series 10 is said to be similar to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, but Apple has given them slightly larger screen-size options and the watch case itself is said to be noticeably thinner. Apple is expected to unveil the new models alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> at its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">September 9 event</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-watch-10-sleep-apnea/">&#039;Noticeably Thinner&#039; Apple Watch Series 10 to Eventually Get Sleep Apnea Detection</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/noticeably-thinner-apple-watch-series-10-to-eventually-get-sleep-apnea-detection.2435205/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report Details Last-Minute Apple Event Rumors About New iPhones, Apple Watches, and AirPods</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-details-last-minute-apple-event-rumors-about-new-iphones-apple-watches-and-airpods.2435204/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 04:40:15 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods</category>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		<category>Apple Watch SE</category>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		<category>September 2024 Apple Event</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> today shared his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">final expectations</a> for Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2024-apple-event/">"It's Glowtime" event</a>, providing some new tidbits and clarifications about the new devices set to be announced on Monday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/08/its-glowtime-event-youtube.jpeg" alt="" width="1280" height="720" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-962411" /><br/>
<h3>iPhone 16 Pro</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>Along with larger 6.3- and 6.9-inch display sizes, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max will have bezels that are "now about a third slimmer" for a "sleeker overall look."</li><br/>
<li>The new models will feature faster chips with an improved Neural Engine that Apple will say is optimized for artificial intelligence.</li><br/>
	<li>The new "Capture" button coming to both models will be the biggest selling point for the new devices beyond AI features. It will work like a DSLR camera's shutter button, with the ability to press it lightly to focus on a subject and press harder to capture a picture. Swiping across the button will switch between photo and video camera modes, as well as zoom in and out. </li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>AirPods</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>Apple is preparing to announce the ability for AirPods to work as a hearing aid replacement, as well as a device for conducting hearing tests. The company has experienced delays with developing the new functionality and it may not be available until a later date.</li><br/>
	<li>Gurman added that Apple apparently discovered a bug on the upcoming, fourth-generation AirPods that resulted in draining battery life. The issue was software-related and fixed prior to factories shipping the new devices.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
<h3>Apple Watch</h3><br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>Apple's "It's Glowtime" event will be the first time that Apple updates all three Apple Watch lines simultaneously.</li><br/>
	<li>The Apple Watch Ultra 3 will only offer minor improvements that focus on internal upgrades rather than exterior changes.</li><br/>
	<li>The Apple Watch Series 10 will feature the first design update for the device since the Series 7, offering larger display size options and a "noticeably thinner" casing.</li><br/>
	<li>While the Apple Watch is not expected to get "major" Apple Intelligence capabilities, any AI technology debuting on the new devices will likely be tied specifically to a "future health coach service."</li><br/>
	<li>Despite plans to bring hypertension detection to the new Apple Watches this year, Gurman now believes that the feature has been delayed.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
Gurman added that new Mac and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> models are likely to appear at a follow-up event, no earlier than October, rather than at the September event. The next-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> and a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airtags/">AirTag</a> are also scheduled for release next year. See the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-sept-9-event-preview-iphone-16-apple-intelligence-airpods-and-watches">full report</a> for more information.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods/">AirPods 3</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-se/">Apple Watch SE</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/september-2024-apple-event/">September 2024 Apple Event</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods">AirPods (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_SE">Apple Watch SE (Don't Buy)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/last-minute-apple-event-rumors/">Report Details Last-Minute Apple Event Rumors About New iPhones, Apple Watches, and AirPods</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-details-last-minute-apple-event-rumors-about-new-iphones-apple-watches-and-airpods.2435204/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Approves WeChat Update for iPhone 16 Amid Ongoing Revenue-Sharing Negotiations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-approves-iphone-16-wechat-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-approves-wechat-update-for-iphone-16-amid-ongoing-revenue-sharing-negotiations.2435198/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 03:19:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-approves-iphone-16-wechat-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		<category>WeChat</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has approved an update to WeChat for the upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a>, signaling a potential thaw in relations between the tech giant and Tencent, the Chinese company behind the massively popular messaging app. The development, reported by <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-09-06/apple-clears-wechat-for-iphone-16-as-talks-persist-over-app-fees">Bloomberg</a></em>, comes as Tencent and Apple continue negotiations over revenue-sharing agreements for WeChat's mini-games ecosystem.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/wechat-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964045" /><br/>
The approval of the WeChat update for Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> lineup is likely to quell speculation about a deteriorating relationship between the two companies, and suggests Apple is committed to maintaining WeChat's presence on its devices, given the app's critical importance in the Chinese market.<br/>
<br/>
Tencent's chief strategy officer, James Mitchell, revealed during an earnings call that the company is in talks with Apple regarding a revenue-sharing deal. The negotiations center around allowing Tencent to accept payments in WeChat mini-games through Apple's payment system, potentially resolving a long-standing point of contention.<br/>
<br/>
With nearly 1.4 billion users in China, WeChat serves as a ubiquitous platform for various services, including bill payments and ticket bookings. While many of these transactions are exempt from Apple's fees, in-app content and online entertainment, such as mini-games, remain subject to Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a> policies.<br/>
<br/>
The rise of mini-games within WeChat has led to developers seeking ways to monetize their creations by selling in-game items. Some have resorted to "steering" practices, guiding players to make payments outside of Apple's ecosystem to avoid fees and improve their profit margins. Apple has been pushing Tencent to close these loopholes, viewing them as violations of its &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; policies.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also warned ByteDance, the company behind TikTok, about in-app spending policies. However, these aggressive actions reportedly risk alienating content creators in a crucial market at a time when Apple's business practices are under increased global scrutiny.<br/>
<br/>
Unlike in the US, Apple holds a smaller market share in China, failing to make the top five in smartphone sales last quarter. Meanwhile, Chinese companies like Tencent and ByteDance maintain significant control over online content, including games and video platforms. Apple's challenges in the Chinese market were underscored by a 6.5% decline in Greater China revenue for the June quarter.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/wechat/">WeChat</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/apple-approves-iphone-16-wechat-update/">Apple Approves WeChat Update for iPhone 16 Amid Ongoing Revenue-Sharing Negotiations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-approves-wechat-update-for-iphone-16-amid-ongoing-revenue-sharing-negotiations.2435198/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>TrendForce: Both iPhone 16 Pro Models to Feature 256GB Base Storage</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/both-iphone-16-pro-models-256gb-base-storage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trendforce-both-iphone-16-pro-models-to-feature-256gb-base-storage.2435195/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 02:16:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/both-iphone-16-pro-models-256gb-base-storage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>TrendForce</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is expected to offer both the iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max with a minimum of 256GB storage, doing away with the 128GB starting option on its smaller Pro model for the first time, according to a new TrendForce report.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/01/iPhone-16-Pro-Right-Side-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-928697" /><br/>
Currently, Apple's 6.1-inch iPhone 15 Pro starts at &#36;999 and comes with the minimum 128GB of storage, while the 6.7-inch iPhone 15 Pro Max starts at &#36;1,199 with a minimum 256GB of storage. Ahead of the launch of the iPhone 15 models, there were rumors that the ‌iPhone 15 Pro‌ Max could start at &#36;1,199, instead of the &#36;1,099 starting price it charged for the iPhone 14 Pro Max. <br/>
<br/>
That did turn out to be accurate, but only because Apple eliminated the lower priced 128GB storage tier. The iPhone 15 Pro Max now starts at 256GB, and &#36;1,199 is the same price Apple charged for the 256GB iPhone 14 Pro Max. Looking ahead to the upcoming iPhone 16 series, TrendForce believes Apple will follow the same strategy for the iPhone 16 Pro model. <br/>
<br/>
TrendForce bases its prediction on the assumption that the iPhone 16 Pro will include a costly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/18/iphone-16-pro-tetraprism-lens-rumor/">tetraprism periscope lens</a> – a feature that was last year exclusive to the iPhone 15 Pro Max model. In other words, upping the minimum capacity to 256GB will allow Apple to pass over the cost to the consumer while diluting the impression of rising prices. <br/>
<br/>
TrendForce notes that even if the price remains at the same level, consumers' usage habits, such as shooting and storing a large number of high-definition photos and videos, and downloading music and large-scale games, will continue to push up the demand for the average storage capacity.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/is-128gb-enough-iphone-storage/">Is 128GB Enough iPhone Storage?</a></li></ul><br/>
In 2018, Apple's iPhone X came with 64GB, an entry-level storage tier that persisted in successive premium device generations until the iPhone 12 Pro in 2020, when Apple adopted 128GB as the new baseline. The next year saw all iPhone 13 models offered with a minimum 128GB. If Apple makes 256GB the new minimum across its premium devices this year, we could well see it reach all models in 2025.<br/>
<br/>
This year's iPhone 16 Pro and iPhone 16 Pro Max are rumored to be getting <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/08/iphone-16-pro-larger-display-sizes/">bigger display sizes</a>, increasing to 6.27- and 6.86-inches, respectively. For comparison, the iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with 6.1-inch and 6.7-inch displays, respectively. The new display sizes will be the largest ever for the iPhone, and should also increase the physical space for internal components and parts.<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/01/iphone-16-launch-month-is-here-everything-we-know/">iPhone 16 Launch Month Is Here: Here's Everything We Know</a></li></ul><br/>
Apple will unveil the new iPhone 16 lineup next week on Monday, September 9 at an event with the tagline "<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/08/26/apple-september-9-iphone-event/">It's Glowtime,</a>" which is believed to be a reference the new Siri interface that comes with Apple Intelligence.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/trendforce/">TrendForce</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/06/both-iphone-16-pro-models-256gb-base-storage/">TrendForce: Both iPhone 16 Pro Models to Feature 256GB Base Storage</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/trendforce-both-iphone-16-pro-models-to-feature-256gb-base-storage.2435195/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Ugreen Launches Qi2 iPhone Chargers With Emoji Faces</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/05/ugreen-iphone-uno-chargers/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ugreen-launches-qi2-iphone-chargers-with-emoji-faces.2435187/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:49:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/05/ugreen-iphone-uno-chargers/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Ugreen <a href="https://www.ugreen.com/pages/ugreen-uno-release">today announced</a> the launch of several new Apple-specific charging products that have a robot-style design with emoji faces. The Uno series includes a Qi2 charger, a wireless power bank, and a 100W USB-C charger.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ugreen-uno-series.jpg" alt="" width="1491" height="839" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964026" /><br/>
According to Ugreen, the chargers were created with "Fast and Fun Charging" for Apple users in mind. Each one has a TFT screen that can display different emoji faces when charging.<br/>
<br/>
The 10,000 mAh Ugreen Uno Magnetic Wireless Power Bank has a Qi2 wireless charger that can charge a compatible <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> at up to 15W. There's also a 20W two-way USB-C port for charging, and a foldable metal stand.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ugreen-uno-power-bank.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964028" /><br/>
The Ugreen Uno 2-in-1 Magnetic Wireless Charger is also Qi2, and it is able to charge the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; at up to 15W and AirPods at up to 5W. It has an upright magnetic charging puck with an adjustable viewing angle. There's also a 5W USB-C charger that an Apple Watch charger can be plugged into for Apple Watch fast charging.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ugreen-2-in-1-charger.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964027" /><br/>
The Ugreen Uno Charger 100W can be used to charge a 16-inch MacBook Pro to 43 percent in 30 minutes. It has a total of three USB-C ports and a single USB-A port, with power distributed between the different ports when multiple devices are plugged in.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/09/ugreen-uno-usb-c-charger.jpg" alt="" width="1246" height="701" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-964029" /><br/>
Ugreen is also working on a 30W 10,000 mAh power bank and a 6-in-1 USB-C hub for the Uno series. The products will be available later this year.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/09/05/ugreen-iphone-uno-chargers/">Ugreen Launches Qi2 iPhone Chargers With Emoji Faces</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ugreen-launches-qi2-iphone-chargers-with-emoji-faces.2435187/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
