<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:03:44 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>&#36;1,700 &#039;Spacetop&#039; Laptop Uses AR Glasses Instead of a Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/spacetop-ar-glasses-laptop/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1-700-spacetop-laptop-uses-ar-glasses-instead-of-a-display.2428161/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:37:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/spacetop-ar-glasses-laptop/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> can be used as a display for a connected Mac, but it is bulky, heavy, and uncomfortable. The <a href="https://www.sightful.com">Spacetop G1</a>, a new laptop from former Magic Leap employees, promises to solve those problems by pairing a computer with a set of lightweight AR glasses that look more comfortable to wear for long periods of time.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="This is Spacetop G1. The AR laptop for work." src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/eEkhCdkgeyM" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Priced at &#36;1,700, Spacetop is basically a keyboard with an attached set of glasses. There is no display, but there is a top case that the glasses can be stored in when the device is not in use. Videos featuring the device show users typing on the keyboard while viewing a set of AR windows that are placed around them.<br/>
<br/>
The Spacetop runs SpaceOS, which the company says is a spatial operating system built for productivity. It focuses on web tasks, which provides content without the company having to recruit developers to build apps.<br/>
<br/>
The AR glasses weigh in at 85 grams, while the Vision Pro weighs between 600 and 650 grams depending on the attached Light Seal. The keyboard is just under 12 inches wide, and the whole setup weighs three pounds, which is heavier than a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a> or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/spacetop-laptop.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953569" /><br/>
It includes a Qualcomm Snapdragon QCS8550 chip, 128GB storage, 16GB RAM, and two open-ear speakers. There are two USB-C ports on the keyboard component that allow it to be connected to a traditional external display, and the battery lasts for up to eight hours. The glasses are equipped with two OLED display panels with a 1920x1080 resolution and a 90Hz refresh rate, and custom prescription lenses are supported.<br/>
<br/>
The Spacetop G1 will retail for &#36;1,900, but those who reserve it early can get a &#36;200 discount, dropping the price to &#36;1,700. A machine can be reserved for a &#36;100 refundable deposit, and it is expected to start shipping in October 2024.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/spacetop-ar-glasses-laptop/">&#36;1,700 &#039;Spacetop&#039; Laptop Uses AR Glasses Instead of a Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/1-700-spacetop-laptop-uses-ar-glasses-instead-of-a-display.2428161/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>PSA: Bartender Mac App Under New Ownership, But Lack of Transparency Raises Concerns</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/bartender-mac-app-new-owner/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-bartender-mac-app-under-new-ownership-but-lack-of-transparency-raises-concerns.2428159/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:22:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/bartender-mac-app-new-owner/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Popular Mac app Bartender appears to have been quietly sold approximately two months ago, with neither the prior owner nor the current owner providing customers or potential customers with information on the sale.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/bartender-app.jpg" alt="" width="2128" height="1197" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953571" /><br/>
The transaction came to light after some Reddit users saw a <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/macapps/comments/1d7zjv8/bartender_5_not_safe_anymore_warning_from/">warning from MacUpdater</a> letting them know that the company behind Bartender had been silently replaced. MacUpdater warned users that updates to the app from version 5.0.52 could be potentially unsafe due to the lack of transparency surrounding the situation.<br/>
<br/>
Bartender's new owners replied to the Reddit thread and confirmed that Bartender had been acquired, but did not explain why customers had not been notified nor why there had been a certificate change without said explanation.<br/>
<blockquote>Hey everyone, new owners of Bartender here! Our team acquired Bartender from Ben S, the original developer, two months ago. As we prepare to roll out updates for Bartender, we needed to re-sign the app with Apple using our company's information, replacing Ben's. This led to a one-time certificate change.<br/>
<br/>
Truth be told, we should have notated it on the release notes but, since we could not update them retroactively, we included this fact on our blog &amp; shared it with users as they emailed us. We've collaborated closely with Ben to understand his vision for Bartender. Our goal is to implement many of the improvements he had planned and address any reported bugs from the past few months to enhance Bartender's performance.</blockquote><br/>
Reddit users asked Bartender's owners for more information on their identity, but there was no response. The Bartender website was updated with information about the certificate change after users began seeing popups asking for new permissions, and while the blog post calls the new certificate request "expected and valid," no background information is provided on the purchase. In the Reddit thread, the owners claim to have posted information about the sale on the website, but that has turned out to be untrue.<br/>
<br/>
At this point, it does not appear that Bartender's new owners plan to inform customers about the change in ownership, but users should be aware that the app has been sold and is no longer being updated by the original developer. The new owner's intentions are not clear, but as Reddit users have pointed out, the situation raises some red flags.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/bartender-mac-app-new-owner/">PSA: Bartender Mac App Under New Ownership, But Lack of Transparency Raises Concerns</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/psa-bartender-mac-app-under-new-ownership-but-lack-of-transparency-raises-concerns.2428159/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 2024 Back to School Sale Likely Launching Soon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-back-to-school-2024-sale-soon/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-back-to-school-sale-likely-launching-soon.2428156/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:20:59 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-back-to-school-2024-sale-soon/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Back to School Promotion</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple could soon launch its annual Back to School promotion for university students in the United States and Canada, based on ads that have been popping up on social networks.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/2022-back-to-school-apple-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2178" height="1224" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-851334" /><br/>
On Instagram, Apple is promoting Macs to college and university students. The ad in question depicts a Back to School image with the following text: "Buy Mac for university or college with education savings. Plus get a gift card for up to &#36;200." The screenshot of the ad is from a Canadian user, and that price point suggests we will see the same &#36;150 discount in the United States that Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/06/apple-launches-2023-back-to-school-promotion/">provided last year</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-ad-back-to-school.jpg" alt="" width="700" height="1104" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953574" /><br/>
Clicking on the ad redirects to Apple's education website, but there is as of yet no mention of the back to school sale. Last year's back to school sale began on Tuesday, June 4, but <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said in his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-06-02/apple-ipad-pro-m4-chip-review-company-inches-closer-to-laptops-with-new-tablets-lwxjbna0">Power On newsletter</a> that the 2024 sale will not begin until later in the month.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's back to school sales provide students with a free Apple gift card when purchasing a Mac or an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>. Last year, Apple offered U.S. students <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/06/apple-launches-2023-back-to-school-promotion/">up to &#36;150</a> when purchasing a Mac and up to &#36;100 when purchasing an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/back-to-school-promotion/">Back to School Promotion</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-back-to-school-2024-sale-soon/">Apple&#039;s 2024 Back to School Sale Likely Launching Soon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-2024-back-to-school-sale-likely-launching-soon.2428156/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Employees Warn of Advanced AI Dangers</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-employee-letter/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-employees-warn-of-advanced-ai-dangers.2428151/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 12:55:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-employee-letter/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		<category>OpenAI</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Several current and former employees of OpenAI and Google DeepMind today <a href="https://righttowarn.ai">shared an open letter</a> warning of the dangers of advanced AI and the current lack of oversight of companies working on AI technology.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/open-ai-logo.jpg" alt="" width="1093" height="615" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953560" /><br/>
The employees suggest there are a number of risks that we are facing from AI development, including further entrenchment of existing inequalities, manipulation and misinformation, and loss of control of autonomous AI systems, which the letter says could lead to human extinction.<br/>
<br/>
AI companies have "strong financial incentives" to forge ahead with development and to avoid sharing information about their protective measures and risk levels. "We do not think they can all be relied upon to share it voluntarily," reads the letter, which says that it is up to current and former employees to speak out.<br/>
<blockquote>So long as there is no effective government oversight of these corporations, current and former employees are among the few people who can hold them accountable to the public. Yet broad confidentiality agreements block us from voicing our concerns, except to the very companies that may be failing to address these issues. Ordinary whistleblower protections are insufficient because they focus on illegal activity, whereas many of the risks we are concerned about are not yet regulated.</blockquote><br/>
Employees are ultimately calling on AI companies to offer solid whistleblower protections for speaking out about the risks of AI.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>Avoid creating or enforcing agreements that prevent criticism for risk-related concerns.</li><br/>
 	<li>Offer a verifiably anonymous process for employees to raise risk-related concerns to the board, regulators, and independent organizations with relevant expertise.</li><br/>
 	<li>Support a culture of open criticism to allow employees to raise risk-related concerns about technologies to the public, the board, regulators, and more, as long as trade secrets are protected.</li><br/>
 	<li>Avoid retaliating against employees who publicly share risk-related confidential information after other processes have failed.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
A total of 13 employees signed the letter, including seven former OpenAI employees, four current OpenAI employees, one former Google DeepMind employee, and one current Google DeepMind employee. OpenAI <a href="https://www.vox.com/future-perfect/2024/5/17/24158478/openai-departures-sam-altman-employees-chatgpt-release">has threatened</a> employees with loss of vested equity for speaking up, and it makes them sign draconian NDA agreements that muzzle criticism.<br/>
<br/>
The letter comes as Apple prepares to announce multiple AI-powered features for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> and other software updates on Monday. Apple is working on its own AI functionality that will be baked into apps across the operating system, plus it has <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-finalizing-deal-openai-chatgpt-ios-18/">signed a deal</a> with OpenAI to integrate ChatGPT features into &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/openai/">OpenAI</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-employee-letter/">OpenAI Employees Warn of Advanced AI Dangers</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-employees-warn-of-advanced-ai-dangers.2428151/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Some AT&amp;T, T-Mobile and Verizon Customers Report Issues With Calls [Update: Fixed]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/us-carriers-call-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-at-t-t-mobile-and-verizon-customers-report-issues-with-calls-update-fixed.2428138/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:51:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/us-carriers-call-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>T-Mobile</category>
		<category>AT&amp;amp;T</category>
		<category>Verizon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[There appears to be an outage with at least one U.S. cellular carrier, with customers unable to place or receive calls. AT&amp;T, T-Mobile, and Verizon customers have been complaining about the issue on social networks, and there are also reports of outages on the <a href="https://downdetector.com">Down Detector website</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/02/ATT-Banner.jpeg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-937556" /><br/>
According to a statement from AT&T, the outage is affecting calls between carriers in the United States. All of the major carriers are working to restore service.<blockquote>There is a nationwide issue that is affecting the ability of customers to complete calls between carriers.  The carriers are working as quickly as possible to diagnose and resolve the issue.”</blockquote>Customers affected have been reporting dropped calls and an inability to hear the person they're attempting to communicate with.<br/>
<br/>
<b>Update:</b> AT&T says that the interoperability issue has been fixed, and that it worked with other carriers to solve the problem. <div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/t-mobile/">T-Mobile</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/att/">AT&amp;T</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/verizon/">Verizon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/us-carriers-call-outage/">Some AT&amp;T, T-Mobile and Verizon Customers Report Issues With Calls [Update: Fixed]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/some-at-t-t-mobile-and-verizon-customers-report-issues-with-calls-update-fixed.2428138/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18 Beta Available Next Week With These 25 New Features Expected</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-beta-next-week-with-these-new-features/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-beta-available-next-week-with-these-25-new-features-expected.2428134/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 09:57:48 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-beta-next-week-with-these-new-features/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 is just days away, with Apple set to unveil the software update during its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/wwdc-2024-full-schedule/">WWDC keynote on June 10</a>. Many new features and changes are expected for the iPhone, with more details outlined in our rumor recap below.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
The first beta of iOS 18 should be made available to members of the Apple Developer Program immediately after the WWDC keynote, and a <a href="https://beta.apple.com/">public beta</a> will likely follow in July. The update should be widely released to all users in September, and it is rumored that it will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">compatible with the same list of iPhone models as iOS 17</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Here are some of the key new features and changes rumored or previewed for iOS 18 so far:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><strong>Apple Maps:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-maps-custom-routes-ios-18/">Custom routes</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/27/ios-18-topographic-maps/">topographic maps</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple Music:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">Auto-generated playlists</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/ios-18-apple-music-song-transitions/">smarter song transitions</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Apple News:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">AI-generated news article summaries</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calculator:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/19/macos-15-revamped-calculator-app/">Several new features</a>, including a sidebar that lists recent calculations, an improved interface for converting units, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">integration with the Notes app</a>, and more. The app will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/23/calculator-app-for-ipad-rumor/">finally be available on iPads</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Calendar:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/01/ios-18-calendar-reminders-integration-rumor/">Deeper integration with the Reminders app</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>CarPlay:</strong> New accessibility features, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features-for-carplay/">Sound Recognition</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Control Center:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-control-center-updates-rumor/">Updated interface</a>, including a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/ios-18-control-center-rumored-changes/">revamped music widget and improved controls for HomeKit accessories</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Fitness:</strong> The app will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/28/ios-18-notes-mail-photos-fitness-rumors/">"overhauled" on iOS 18</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Freeform:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/11/ios-18-macos-15-freeform-app-scenes/">A new "Scenes" function</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Health:</strong> <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-02-15/apple-s-ai-plans-github-copilot-rival-for-developers-tool-for-testing-apps">New features powered by AI</a>, but no specific details are known yet.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Home Screen:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/">Place app icons anywhere on the grid</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/ios-18-to-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons/">change colors of app icons</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Keynote and Pages:</strong> AI-powered features for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/22/apple-generative-ai-features-and-smarter-siri/">auto-generating slides in Keynote, writing faster in Pages, and more</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Magnifier:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/apple-previews-ios-18-magnifier-app/">A new Reader Mode</a>, and the option to easily launch Detection Mode with the Action button on newer iPhone models.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Mail:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">Suggested replies to emails</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Messages:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/ios-18-rumored-features-for-messages-app/">RCS support, per-word effects, suggested replies, custom emoji, message recaps, and new Tapback icons</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Notes:</strong> A built-in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">audio recording tool</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/ios-18-audio-transcriptions-rumor/">audio transcriptions</a>, and the ability to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/ios-18-notes-app-voice-memos-math-rumors/">display mathematical notation</a>.<br/>
<li><strong>Notifications:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">AI-generated notification summaries</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Photos:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">AI-powered photo retouching</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Safari:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/10/ios-18-safari-browsing-assistant-rumor/">Browsing assistant</a> that can <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">summarize web pages</a>, and a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/safari-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">"Web Eraser" tool</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Settings:</strong> A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/31/ios-18-refreshed-settings-app/">revamped interface with improved search</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-18-accessibility-features/">new accessibility features</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Shortcuts:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">Automate complex tasks more easily</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Siri:</strong> A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/06/ios-18-siri-improvements/">smarter ChatGPT-inspired version of Siri</a> with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/">more per-app controls</a> (<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/">in 2025</a>).</li><br/>
<li><strong>Spotlight:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/03/ios-18-ai-features-for-siri-spotlight-revealed/">More intelligent search results and improved sorting</a>.</li><br/>
<li><strong>Voice Memos:</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/ios-18-audio-transcriptions-rumor/">Audio transcriptions</a>.</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
For even more rumors, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18 roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-beta-next-week-with-these-new-features/">iOS 18 Beta Available Next Week With These 25 New Features Expected</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-beta-available-next-week-with-these-25-new-features-expected.2428134/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Samsung Opens Up Orders for New 2024 Monitors, Including Updated Smart Monitor M8</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/samsung-2024-monitors/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-opens-up-orders-for-new-2024-monitors-including-updated-smart-monitor-m8.2428129/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:54:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/samsung-2024-monitors/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung today launched orders for its <a href="https://howl.me/cmotgisc3SN">new lineup of 2024 monitors</a>, headlined by the updated Smart Monitor M80D. When ordering select monitors, you can get up to &#36;300 in Samsung credit to use on a later purchase with the retailer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/samsung-dog.jpg" alt="" width="961" height="500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953484" /><br/>
Most monitors ordered today will arrive around June 11 for residences in the United States, and Samsung does also offer options to pick up the monitors in local Best Buy stores. You'll find every new Samsung monitor available for order in the lists below, along with the amount of Samsung credit you'll get when you place the order.<br/>
<br/>
In regards to the newly updated <a href="https://howl.me/cmotb3kGPSf">Smart Monitor M80D</a>, this model includes a Multi Control feature that allows images and text to be moved between the display and a Galaxy Book, Tablet, or Phone. <br/>
<br/>
If you own a pair of Galaxy Buds, you can pair the earphones to the monitor for a spatial audio experience with head tracking. Additionally, Samsung added the ability to pair a Galaxy Watch to the monitor, allowing you to perform guided workouts while using the display. <br/>
<br/>
Other than these features, the iMac-style 4K monitor hasn't changed in the hardware department from last year's M8 model, which features 400 nits of brightness, a 60Hz refresh rate (non variable), 99% sRGB, and adaptive picture technology.<br/>
<br/>
The display also retains key features like USB-C charging connectivity, AirPlay 2 support, an integrated webcam, and several smart TV features that enable it to be used when not connected to a PC.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Smart Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmotfdkMwYX">27-inch Smart Monitor M50D</a> - &#36;279.99 with &#36;50 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmoteh0m0jW">32-inch Smart Monitor M50D</a> - &#36;299.99 with &#36;50 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmotds7HhYq">32-inch Smart Monitor M70D</a> - &#36;399.99 with &#36;75 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmotcNcxOkk">43-inch Smart Monitor M70D</a> - &#36;499.99 with &#36;100 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmotb3kGPSf">32-inch Smart Monitor M80D</a> - &#36;699.99 with &#36;150 Samsung credit</li></ul><h2>Gaming Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmos5ynMpvs">27-inch Odyssey OLED G6</a> - &#36;899.99 with &#36;200 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmos4ZWSvFD">32-inch Odyssey OLED G8</a> - &#36;1,299.99 with &#36;300 Samsung credit</li></ul><h2>High Resolution Monitors</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmotaKBh22L">27-inch ViewFinity S7</a> - &#36;349.99 with &#36;75 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmos8FtYeZF">27-inch ViewFinity S8</a> - &#36;399.99 with &#36;75 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmos9jrMJG3">32-inch ViewFinity S7</a> - &#36;399.99 with &#36;75 Samsung credit</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmos72vEWsF">32-inch ViewFinity S8</a> - &#36;449.99 with &#36;100 Samsung credit</li></ul> <em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Samsung. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/samsung-2024-monitors/">Samsung Opens Up Orders for New 2024 Monitors, Including Updated Smart Monitor M8</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/samsung-opens-up-orders-for-new-2024-monitors-including-updated-smart-monitor-m8.2428129/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Save on Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/accessories-from-anker-eufy/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-on-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery-on-amazon.2428128/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:14:02 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/accessories-from-anker-eufy/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Amazon is back today with a large collection of discounts from <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Anker</a>, <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">Eufy</a>, and <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Jackery</a>, including a wide array of wall chargers, Bluetooth trackers, and other USB-C accessories. Some of these deals will require you to clip an on-page coupon then head to the checkout screen before you see the final sale price, and some require a Prime membership.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-purple-may.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949011" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
This week Eufy has a few discounts on its Find My-compatible SmartTrack Bluetooth tracker accessories, including the SmartTrack Card for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654"><strong>&#36;16.98</strong></a>, down from &#36;29.99. You can also get the SmartTrack Link in multiple pack options, starting at <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659794010"><strong>&#36;13.99</strong></a> for the 1-Pack, down from &#36;19.99. Both of these beat the deals we last saw on these trackers in early May.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1717513195769"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;13 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Card for &#36;16.98</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714660094244"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;21 OFF</div>Eufy SmartTrack Link 4-Pack for &#36;48.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Switching to the Anker deals, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3SU6JI04LB2MZ_1713191397056">20,000 mAh Prime Power Bank with Smart Digital Display</a> for &#36;89.98 if you're a Prime member, down from &#36;129.99. If you need a bigger battery, you can get the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> for &#36;129.99 with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99. Additionally, below you'll find more Anker accessories including speakers and USB-C products.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station for &#36;69.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light for &#36;129.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Highlights of Jackery's deals include the <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a>, available for just &#36;99.99, down from &#36;149.00. This is a miniature-sized portable power station that can fit in the palm of your hand and weighs just 2.13 lbs, while featuring a 31,000 mAh capacity and 128W output.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>Jackery Explorer 100 Plus for &#36;99.99</div></a></div><h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659902126">SmartTrack Link 1-Pack</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659917907">SmartTrack Link 2-Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727">SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BKJZ5BVF%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.21TJMGTITJI3Q_1714659979654">SmartTrack Card</a> - &#36;16.98, down from &#36;29.99</li></ul><br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;64.99, down from &#36;79.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1717512554052">MagGo Power Bank 10,000 mAh</a> - &#36;69.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CXDTNJST%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.34INF6WP7XS4L_1717512037932">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;38.24 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;149.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFXLVY1V%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2N2MUC6OP3WR0_1717512364497">MagGo 3-in-1 Wireless Charging Station</a> - &#36;69.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;99.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CF54FWFL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2QZK0WFI9NXZJ_1717513024737">MagGo 3-in-1 Folding Charging Station</a> - &#36;93.49 for Prime members, down from &#36;109.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1ONCDOQGWGFK4_1717511791324">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;129.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;112.46, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;42.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.49 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;9.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;59.99, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CNVMQNDX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1DHAFXF4LOVCC_1710769872160">Explorer 100 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;99.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D2KZY522%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NXT41HEMR2FG%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NXT41HEMR2FG_1717512999884">Explorer 600 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;419.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;499.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.LPIOTAJGGK4P_1713373339383">Solar Generator 300 Plus Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.2HOQ15SVTKP5E_1713373175628">Expansion Battery Pack for 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;509.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;799.00</li> <br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB083KBKJ8Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1KHS8AIX808CW_1713373227768">Explorer 1000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;619.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.231PUR2N7PBPM_1713373287626">Explorer 2000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DL1VPD%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QELY4DYBF6HU_1710770037246">Expansion Battery Pack for 2000 Plus</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,599.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BZ8DZ3HR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.B0BZ8DZ3HR%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3M5389ELMN7TD_1713385917457%26th%3D1">Explorer 3000 Pro Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;2,149.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;2,799.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
If you're on the hunt for more discounts, be sure to visit our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a> roundup where we recap the best Apple-related bargains of the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/accessories-from-anker-eufy/">Save on Popular Accessories From Anker, Eufy, and Jackery on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/save-on-popular-accessories-from-anker-eufy-and-jackery-on-amazon.2428128/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Uber Planning to Add Mini Games to iPhone App to Play During a Ride</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/uber-planning-mini-games-in-iphone-app/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uber-planning-to-add-mini-games-to-iphone-app-to-play-during-a-ride.2428126/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:58:24 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/uber-planning-mini-games-in-iphone-app/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Uber</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Uber appears to be planning to offer mini games that can be played within its <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/uber-request-a-ride/id368677368">iPhone app</a>, according to hidden code in the app.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Uber-App-Icon-Vignette.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="675" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953458" /><br/>
<em>MacRumors</em> contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a> discovered several references to the ability to load games in the latest version of the Uber app, released on Monday. One line of code says that the gaming feature will require an internet connection.<br/>
<br/>
It is unclear when Uber plans to make the mini games available to the public, and there is no guarantee that the feature will launch. No further details are known at this time, beyond the new lines of code added to the app, so we cannot confirm if the games will be available for free or require in-app purchases.<br/>
<br/>
By offering games in its iPhone app, Uber would provide passengers with a convenient way to stay entertained during a ride. Uber would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/youtube-playables/">following in the footsteps of YouTube</a>, which added some lightweight games to its iPhone app last month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/uber/">Uber</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/uber-planning-mini-games-in-iphone-app/">Uber Planning to Add Mini Games to iPhone App to Play During a Ride</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/uber-planning-to-add-mini-games-to-iphone-app-to-play-during-a-ride.2428126/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide.2337402/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:45:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air&#038;post_date=1717523100/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iPad mini</category>
		<category>No Top Comments</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple recently introduced the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>, featuring the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro support, and a larger display size option. In 2021, Apple debuted the sixth-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a>, offering an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> Air-style redesign with a larger display, the A15 Bionic chip, and more. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/03/ipad-mini-vs-air-early-2022.jpg" alt="" width="2498" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-839261" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; effectively shares the design of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, with both devices possessing many of the same features such as an all-screen design with no Home button, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/touch-id/">Touch ID</a> in the top button, and stereo speakers. There are still some important differences between the devices, such as their display sizes and chips, that clearly set the devices apart.<br/>
<br/>
Should you buy the more expensive, larger &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, or opt for the more affordable, smaller &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;? Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two iPads is best for you. All of the key differences between the two devices are listed below:<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>8.3-inch display with 326 ppi</td><br/>
 <td>11-inch or 13-inch display with 264 ppi</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>SDR brightness: 500 nits max</td><br/>
 <td>11-inch model SDR brightness: 500 nits max<br/>
13-inch model SDR brightness: 600 nits max</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smaller, compact design for maximum portability</td><br/>
 <td>Larger design that is better for productivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Weighs 0.66 pounds (297 grams)</td><br/>
 <td>Weighs 1.02 pounds (462 grams) or 1.36 pounds (617 grams)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>6-core CPU</td><br/>
 <td>8-core CPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>9-core GPU</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>4GB of memory</td><br/>
 <td>8GB of memory</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Media Engine<br/>
Hardware-accelerated H.264 and HEVC<br/>
Video decode engine<br/>
Video encode engine</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Rear Quad-LED True Tone flash</td><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 3</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6 connectivity</td><br/>
 <td>Wi-Fi 6E connectivity</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; hover</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Supports &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with USB-C and second-generation &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;</td><br/>
 <td>Supports &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; with USB-C and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Compatible with Bluetooth keyboards only</td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-connector/">Smart Connector</a> to support Apple's Magic Keyboard and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/smart-keyboard/">Smart Keyboard</a> Folio</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>64GB or 256GB of storage</td><br/>
 <td>128GB, 256GB, 512GB, or 1TB of storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Available in Space Gray, Starlight, Purple, and Pink</td><br/>
 <td>Available in Space Gray, Starlight, Purple, and Blue</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;499</td><br/>
 <td>Starts at &#36;599 or &#36;799</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is the best all-around option for the majority of users, providing a large screen for productivity and consuming entertainment in a slim, portable design. The additional &#36;100 needed to buy the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; over the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is more than justified for the benefits that come with its larger display and &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip, not least the ability to practically use it as a laptop replacement with the Magic Keyboard and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/stage-manager/">Stage Manager</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Yet, most customers who choose the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will do so because of its screen size rather than in spite of it. The &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is ideal for comfortably reading books, playing handheld games, and easy transport and storage. Those who buy the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; will likely have a specific use case in mind for how they will use the device, such as for note-taking on the go, throwing into a small bag to use on public transport, or giving it to a kid as their first tablet.<br/>
<br/>
If you do not see the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;'s smaller display, easy one-handed grip, lightweight design, and portable form factor as an advantage for your use case and are focused on a more versatile display size, you will likely prefer the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;, especially as it is now available with a 13-inch size option. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; is more of an all-around device that works as a potential laptop replacement with support for &zwnj;Stage Manager&zwnj;, with the added bonuses that come with a bigger screen for productivity and entertainment.<br/>
<br/>
It is also worth noting that the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; is almost three years old, while the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has just been refreshed, so the latter is almost certainly a better purchase in terms of longevity. A new &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; model is expected to launch later this year with a faster chip, so if you have your heart set on the smallest &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; it may be worth holding off until the refreshed version comes out.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a>, <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad_Mini">iPad Mini (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air/">iPad Mini vs. iPad Air Buyer&#039;s Guide</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ipad-mini-vs-ipad-air-buyers-guide.2337402/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Nintendo 3DS Emulator for iPhone Released in App Store With Caveats</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/nintendo-3ds-emulator-for-iphone-on-app-store/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nintendo-3ds-emulator-for-iphone-released-in-app-store-with-caveats.2428124/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:08:04 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/nintendo-3ds-emulator-for-iphone-on-app-store/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>App Store</category>
		<category>Nintendo</category>
		<category>Emulator</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Folium has become the first Nintendo 3DS emulator for the iPhone <a href="https://apps.apple.com/us/app/folium/id6498623389">available in the App Store</a>, although there are some caveats to be aware of.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/Folium-Alpha-Sapphire-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953425" /><br/>
Foremost, this is the first Nintendo emulator on the App Store that costs money. Folium developer Jarrod Norwell is charging &#36;4.99 for the app, which is a bold choice given that Nintendo recently sued the developers of Yuzu, a Nintendo Switch emulator that made a profit off a subscription-based "early access" tier. Yuzu reached a <a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/3/4/24090357/nintendo-yuzu-emulator-lawsuit-settlement">&#36;2.4 million settlement</a> with Nintendo and discontinued its emulator earlier this year. It is unclear if Nintendo will take any action against Folium, but it might risk more scrutiny as a paid app.<br/>
<br/>
Second, Apple does not allow emulators to use "just-in-time" (JIT) compilation. This limitation can result in Nintendo 3DS games having reduced performance, especially on older iPhone models, but your mileage may vary. We recommend reading user reviews <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/EmulationOniOS/comments/1d7vi7j/appstore_folium_3ds_should_you_spend_5/">on Reddit</a> and <a href="https://mobilesyrup.com/2024/06/03/3ds-emulator-iphone-ios-ipad-folium/">elsewhere</a> before deciding whether to purchase Folium.<br/>
<br/>
Third, it is possible that another all-in-one emulator on the App Store <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/retroarch-ios-emulator/">like RetroArch</a> could add Nintendo 3DS support for free in the future.<br/>
<br/>
With all of that in mind, Folium gives you the opportunity to relive classic Nintendo 3DS games on your iPhone right now, provided that you supply the ROMs. However, be aware that downloading copyrighted games is illegal in many countries.<br/>
<br/>
Folium also offers Game Boy Advance and Nintendo DS emulation, but we recommend using the free <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/17/delta-game-emulator-iphone/">Delta app</a> for those consoles. Folium is compatible with many hardware controllers, including the Nintendo Switch Joy-Con, Nintendo Switch Pro Controller, Backbone One, and the latest PlayStation and Xbox controllers.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/nintendo/">Nintendo</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/emulator/">Emulator</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/nintendo-3ds-emulator-for-iphone-on-app-store/">Nintendo 3DS Emulator for iPhone Released in App Store With Caveats</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/nintendo-3ds-emulator-for-iphone-released-in-app-store-with-caveats.2428124/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 18: These iPhones Likely Won&#039;t Support Some AI Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-these-iphones-wont-support-ai/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-these-iphones-likely-wont-support-some-ai-features.2428119/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:04:27 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-these-iphones-wont-support-ai/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning a major AI overhaul in iOS 18, but some new features are unlikely to work on older iPhones, even if they do appear on the new operating system's device compatibility list.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
Apple's initial AI roadmap for iOS 18 is said to come in two parts: Basic AI features that will be processed on-device, and more advanced capabilities that will require communication with Apple's servers.<br/>
<br/>
At the heart of these features is a redesigned Siri. To that end, Apple engineers have had to rearchitect ‌Siri‌'s underlying software using large language models (LLMs), the algorithm that underpins generative AI. <br/>
<br/>
According to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/30/ai-siri-features-ios-18-2025/"><em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a>, this will allow Siri to do things like open specific documents, organize notes in folders, delete an email, summarize an article, email a web link, and more. Apple reportedly plans to use AI to analyze what people are doing on their devices to automatically enable these‌ features.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's own LLM is expected to handle what are deemed basic AI tasks, and it will be entirely on-device. In other words, the model is powered by the iPhone's processor, rather than in the cloud. It's not clear what the criteria for a basic task will be, but the LLM is said to include code that determines if a request can be processed on device or requires Apple's servers.<br/>
<br/>
<a href="https://x.com/markgurman/status/1796414625053020649">According to Gurman</a>, the on-device AI capabilities will largely require an iPhone 15 Pro or later to work. Meanwhile, rumors suggest iOS 18 will be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/27/ios-18-compatible-iphones-rumor/">compatible with the same iPhone models as iOS 17</a>. Combining the two reports, we should therefore expect the following iPhone models to run iOS 18, but lack support for some of Apple's on-device AI features:<br/>
<div style="float: left; width: 50%;"><br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 15</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 15 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Plus</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 14 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 13 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12</li></ul></div><div style="float: right; width: 50%;"><br/>
<ul><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 mini</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 12 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro</li><br/>
<li>iPhone 11 Pro Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XS Max</li><br/>
<li>iPhone XR</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (2nd generation)</li><br/>
<li>iPhone SE (3rd generation)</li></ul></div><br/>
<div style="clear:both;"></div><br/>
Both iPadOS 18 and macOS 15 are expected to share many of the same AI features, and Gurman has said that Macs and iPads will need at least an M1 chip for the on-device AI capabilities. In other words, Apple silicon Macs are the requirement for on-device AI in macOS 15 (ruling out Intel Macs), while anything older than the fifth-generation iPad Pro will not support on-device AI features in iPadOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
While it's not entirely clear which hardware factor is the key requirement for Apple's on-device AI, it's worth noting that (non-supported) standard iPhone 15 models have 6GB of RAM, while the supported Pro models have 8GB of RAM. Likewise, all Apple Silicon iPads and Macs come with a minimum of 8GB. Even when scaled back for narrow use cases, LLMs require a lot of working memory due to the sheer number of parameters involved, so this could be where Apple is coming up against the hardware limitations of its own devices. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/ios-18-these-iphones-wont-support-ai/">iOS 18: These iPhones Likely Won&#039;t Support Some AI Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-18-these-iphones-likely-wont-support-some-ai-features.2428119/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Netflix to End Support for 2nd and 3rd Generation Apple TV</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/netflix-end-support-2nd-3rd-gen-apple-tv/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-to-end-support-for-2nd-and-3rd-generation-apple-tv.2428117/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 04:51:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/netflix-end-support-2nd-3rd-gen-apple-tv/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple TV</category>
		<category>Netflix</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Netflix will no longer support second-generation and third-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a> models from July 31, 2024, the company has announced in an email to some subscribers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/apple-tv-2nd-gen-2010.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953356" /><br/>
Netflix said that the decision made to "maintain the best possible Netflix experience" by focusing on devices that can support the latest features and updates. <br/>
<br/>
The second-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; was the first of its kind to feature a black body and an aluminum Apple Remote, an updated look compared to the silver and white &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; that was originally released in 2007. The unit was powered by an A4 chip, and offered up to 720p resolution output.<br/>
<br/>
Apple sold the second-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; from 2010 until 2012, which is when the company released the third-generation &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; with an A5 chip and support for 1080p content. <br/>
<br/>
Both models run on an early variant of iOS that precedes tvOS and lacks an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>. The devices are classed as obsolete by Apple and no longer receive updates.<br/>
<br/>
Netflix will remain available to access on the &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; HD (originally the fourth-generation model) and all &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; 4K models.<br/>
<br/>
After the July 31 date, Netflix recommends that to continue viewing content, affected users either upgrade to a newer &zwnj;Apple TV&zwnj; model, or use other compatible devices such as smart TVs or Roku devices.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-tv/">Apple TV</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/netflix/">Netflix</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_TV">Apple TV (Caution)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-tv-and-home-theater.100">Apple TV and Home Theater</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/netflix-end-support-2nd-3rd-gen-apple-tv/">Netflix to End Support for 2nd and 3rd Generation Apple TV</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/netflix-to-end-support-for-2nd-and-3rd-generation-apple-tv.2428117/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Aptoide Launching Alternative iOS Game Marketplace in EU</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/aptoide-marketplace-games-ios/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aptoide-launching-alternative-ios-game-marketplace-in-eu.2428114/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:56:52 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/aptoide-marketplace-games-ios/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>European Union</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<a href="https://press.ios.aptoide.com/en">Aptoide</a>, a popular Google Play alternative for Android devices, will be launching an iOS game marketplace on Thursday, June 6, in the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/aptoide.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953350" /><br/>
The Aptoide iOS store will launch with a limited selection of titles, but the company says that new games will arrive every day, and that 30 titles are currently being processed for inclusion. Examples of current games include Word Jungle, Condor — Leap of Faith, Solitaire, Mahjong, and Charades.<br/>
<br/>
Initially, access to the store will be restricted to users with invitation-only access codes, but Aptoide says it has a waiting list of 20,000 signups and plans to issue between 500 to 1,000 codes per day.<br/>
<br/>
As noted by <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/6/4/24171037/aptoide-ios-game-store-eu-third-party-app-dma">The Verge</a></em>, Aptoide is the first third-party iOS marketplace to launch with an Apple-approved in-app purchases (IAP) solution, which it will provide to developers via an IAP software development kit.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's 50 euro cents Core Technology Fee (CFT) will be covered by a fee charged to developers for in-app purchases, which means IAP-driven apps will be "preferred" in Aptoide iOS, according to the marketplace's CEO, Paulo Trezentos.<br/>
<br/>
Apps distributed through alternative app marketplaces are required to submit to a notarization process to ensure they are free from malware, but Apple does not have restrictions on content so apps that might not have been eligible for the ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>‌ can be distributed through alternative means. Alternative app marketplaces are not available outside of the European Union.<br/>
<br/>
Aptoide has operated for an Android &zwnj;App Store&zwnj; since 2009, and last year reached nearly half a billion downloads.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/european-union/">European Union</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/aptoide-marketplace-games-ios/">Aptoide Launching Alternative iOS Game Marketplace in EU</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/aptoide-launching-alternative-ios-game-marketplace-in-eu.2428114/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OpenAI Says ChatGPT Suffering Major Outage [Updated]</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-says-chatgpt-suffering-major-outage/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-says-chatgpt-suffering-major-outage-updated.2428112/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:22:49 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-says-chatgpt-suffering-major-outage/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>ChatGPT</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[<strong>Update:</strong> OpenAI's <a href="https://status.openai.com">status page</a> indicates the first issue was resolved at 4:45 a.m. Pacific Time, but the service is continuing to have problems.<br/>
<br/>
<hr /><br/>
<br/>
OpenAI's ChatGPT chatbot is currently suffering a major outage that is making the generative AI service unavailable for "some users," according to the company's <a href="https://status.openai.com">system status page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/05/chatgpt-for-iphone-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-896306" /><br/>
ChatGPT has been down for several hours, with the chatbot unable to respond to queries via the web and mobile apps due to an internal server error. The company says it first started working on the issue at 12:21 a.m. Pacific Time on June 4. <br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT has more than 100 million weekly users, according to OpenAI. Apple has reportedly <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/13/apple-finalizing-deal-openai-chatgpt-ios-18/">closed in on a deal</a> with OpenAI that should see ChatGPT being used to power new features in iOS 18, Apple's next major iPhone operating system update, so outages like this one could potentially affect millions more users.<br/>
<br/>
ChatGPT also suffered a partial outage last month when Microsoft's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/bing-copilot-duckduckgo-chatgpt-search-down/">Bing API stopped functioning</a>, leaving the chatbot and many other services unable to search the web. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/chatgpt/">ChatGPT</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/openai-says-chatgpt-suffering-major-outage/">OpenAI Says ChatGPT Suffering Major Outage [Updated]</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/openai-says-chatgpt-suffering-major-outage-updated.2428112/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple iPhone Trade-In Promotion Ends as Credit Values Lowered</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-iphone-trade-in-promotion-ends/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-iphone-trade-in-promotion-ends-as-credit-values-lowered.2428110/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 03:00:30 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-iphone-trade-in-promotion-ends/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Trade-In</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As expected, Apple has ended its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-boosts-iphone-trade-in-values-promotion/">limited-time promotion</a> that increased the trade-in values for select iPhone models in the United States when customers buy a new iPhone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-trade-in-2024.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951609" /><br/>
The two-week promotion officially came to a close on June 3, which means anyone trading in their existing iPhone 11 or newer today will get slightly less money knocked off the price of a new iPhone than they would have done the previous day. Some of the new values have been reproduced below, with the previous promotional values in brackets:<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro Max: Up to &#36;630 (vs. &#36;650)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Pro: Up to &#36;520 (vs. &#36;530)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14 Plus: Up to &#36;420 (vs. &#36;430)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 14: Up to &#36;370 (vs. &#36;380)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro Max: Up to &#36;450 (vs. &#36;460)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 Pro: Up to &#36;370 (vs. &#36;380)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13: Up to &#36;300 (vs. &#36;320)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone 13 mini: Up to &#36;270 (vs. &#36;300)</li><br/>
  <li>iPhone SE (3rd generation): Up to &#36;160 (vs. &#36;170)</li><br/>
</ul>Trade-ins can be completed on Apple's website or at an Apple Store, and the credit can be applied towards the purchase of a new Apple product, or placed on an Apple gift card for later use. Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/trade-in">trade-in page</a> offers a complete list of values for devices.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-trade-in/">Apple Trade-In</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/04/apple-iphone-trade-in-promotion-ends/">Apple iPhone Trade-In Promotion Ends as Credit Values Lowered</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-iphone-trade-in-promotion-ends-as-credit-values-lowered.2428110/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Security Researcher Calls Windows 11 AI &#039;Recall&#039; Screenshotting Feature a Disaster</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/windows-11-recall-feature-disaster/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/security-researcher-calls-windows-11-ai-recall-screenshotting-feature-a-disaster.2428084/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 17:58:42 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/windows-11-recall-feature-disaster/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Microsoft</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Last month, Microsoft <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/microsoft-ai-windows-pcs/">announced the upcoming launch</a> of Copilot+ Windows PCs with integrated AI hardware and software. One feature that Microsoft touted was Recall, a tool that's designed to take regular snapshots of PC content to help users find anything they've seen or done on their machine.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/maC9iZMaAlM" title="Recall instantly with Recall on Copilot+ PC" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
As it turns out, Recall might be a security nightmare for Windows users. Security expert Kevin Beaumont <a href="https://doublepulsar.com/recall-stealing-everything-youve-ever-typed-or-viewed-on-your-own-windows-pc-is-now-possible-da3e12e9465e">recently said</a> (via <em><a href="https://www.theverge.com/2024/6/3/24170305/microsoft-windows-recall-ai-screenshots-security-privacy-issues">The Verge</a></em>) that he was able to automate a program that provides plain text data of everything a user has viewed, despite Microsoft's claims that Recall information cannot be exfiltrated remotely.<br/>
<br/>
Beaumont claims that Recall is "essentially an infostealer" that's included in Windows by default, and that it will "set cybersecurity back a decade by empowering cybercriminals." With Recall, hackers are able to scrape "everything you've ever looked at within seconds," and users should prepare for "AI powered super breaches."<br/>
<br/>
Microsoft describes Recall as a feature that lets you "search across time to find the content you need." Powered by AI, Recall takes snapshots every five seconds when content on the screen is different from the prior snapshot and stores the snapshots in a timeline, with AI software using OCR to make the text in the snapshots searchable. Microsoft says that snapshots are locally stored and are analyzed on-device, which should make them secure, but the OCR data is stored in an SQLite database that could be accessed by hackers who infiltrate a PC using malware.<br/>
<br/>
According to Beaumont, infostealer trojans are able to be "easily modified to support Recall" and data from the feature can be accessed remotely. Microsoft "tried to do a bunch of things" to improve security, but ultimately, "none of it actually works properly in the real world." The database that is theoretically accessible by malicious actors contains everything a user has seen such as text messages and passwords, every user interaction, and all websites visited (with the exception of Microsoft Edge in Private Mode).<br/>
<br/>
Beaumont has not shared full technical details on how he automated exfiltration of the Recall database, and is holding until Recall is shipped because he wants to give Microsoft "time to do something." Beaumont recommends that Microsoft pull the feature for the time being.<br/>
<br/>
Copilot+ PCs with Recall are set to launch on June 18. As of now, Recall is turned on by default, though users can optionally disable it.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/microsoft/">Microsoft</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/windows-11-recall-feature-disaster/">Security Researcher Calls Windows 11 AI &#039;Recall&#039; Screenshotting Feature a Disaster</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/security-researcher-calls-windows-11-ai-recall-screenshotting-feature-a-disaster.2428084/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Spotify Raises Prices for Second Time in 12 Months, Now More Expensive Than Apple Music</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/spotify-price-increase/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-raises-prices-for-second-time-in-12-months-now-more-expensive-than-apple-music.2428081/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:02:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/spotify-price-increase/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Spotify</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Spotify <a href="https://newsroom.spotify.com/2024-06-03/adjusting-spotify-premium-prices-in-the-us/">today announced</a> that it is increasing Premium plan pricing in the United States in order to "bring users the best experience."<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/08/General-Spotify-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1407" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-810756" /><br/>
The Individual Premium plan is now priced at &#36;11.99, up from &#36;10.99. Duo is priced at &#36;16.99 (up &#36;2), Family is priced at &#36;19.99 (up &#36;3), and Student is priced at &#36;5.99 (no change).<br/>
<br/>
This is actually the second time <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/24/spotify-increases-premium-plan-price/">Spotify has raised prices</a> in the last 12 months. In July 2023, the Premium plan price went from &#36;9.99 to &#36;10.99, so there has been a 20 percent increase in the last year. Prior to the July 2023 increase, Duo was priced at &#36;12.99 and the Family plan was priced at &#36;15.99, marking a 31 percent total increase for Duo and a 25 percent increase for Family after the 2024 price hikes.<br/>
<br/>
Spotify subscribers will soon be seeing emails notifying them of the upcoming price increase. Emails will include instructions on how to cancel a Premium subscription.<br/>
<blockquote>On Spotify, users discover and enjoy music, podcasts, and audiobooks. So that we can continue to invest in and innovate on our product features and bring users the best experience, we occasionally update our prices. Over the next month, subscribers in the U.S. will receive an email explaining what this update means for their subscription.</blockquote><br/>
At &#36;11.99 and &#36;19.99, respectively, the Spotify Premium and Family plans are now more expensive than the equivalent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-music/">Apple Music</a> plans. Apple's Individual plan is priced at &#36;10.99 per month, while the Family plan is priced at &#36;16.99 per month.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/spotify/">Spotify</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/spotify-price-increase/">Spotify Raises Prices for Second Time in 12 Months, Now More Expensive Than Apple Music</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/spotify-raises-prices-for-second-time-in-12-months-now-more-expensive-than-apple-music.2428081/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says iPad Air Performance Details Are Accurate Despite 9-Core GPU Mistake</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/ipad-air-performance-accurate-gpu-error/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ipad-air-performance-details-are-accurate-despite-9-core-gpu-mistake.2428070/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:40:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/ipad-air-performance-accurate-gpu-error/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Though Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/apple-says-m2-ipad-air-9-gpu-cores-not-10/">mistakenly listed</a> the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> chip in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> as having a 10-core GPU instead of a 9-core GPU, the performance claims that it shared during the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; launch and in marketing materials are accurate.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m2-iPad-Air-Horizontal-Feature-Orange.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-950736" /><br/>
In a statement provided to <em><a href="https://9to5mac.com/2024/06/03/apple-says-m2-ipad-air-performance-claims-are-accurate-despite-gpu-mix-up/">9to5Mac</a></em>, Apple said that the details it shared on the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;'s performance were always based on a 9-core GPU.<br/>
<blockquote>We are updating Apple.com to correct the core count for the M2 iPad Air. All performance claims for the M2 iPad Air are accurate and based on a 9-core GPU.</blockquote><br/>
Apple's website says that the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip is "nearly 50 percent faster than the previous generation," and that it specifically has "25 percent faster graphics."<br/>
<br/>
Apple recently updated its technical specifications website for the &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; to state that the device has a 9-core GPU. Prior to the update, it listed a 10-core GPU. The prior-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> had a 10-core GPU, so it is a surprise that the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; version is limited to a 9-core GPU.<br/>
<br/>
Other &zwnj;M2&zwnj; chip specifications have not changed. The &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; has an 8-core CPU with four performance cores and four efficiency cores, along with 8GB RAM and a 16-core Neural Engine.<br/>
<br/>
Because it took Apple several days to correct the chip error on its website, some users may have purchased the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; believing it had a 10-core GPU. The two week return period has expired for those who bought on launch day, but customers would have a good argument for a return exception.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/ipad-air-performance-accurate-gpu-error/">Apple Says iPad Air Performance Details Are Accurate Despite 9-Core GPU Mistake</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-ipad-air-performance-details-are-accurate-despite-9-core-gpu-mistake.2428070/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Verizon Launches Rare Discounts on Apple TV 4K (&#36;89.99) and 2nd Gen HomePod (&#36;174.99)</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/verizon-apple-tv-homepod/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/verizon-launches-rare-discounts-on-apple-tv-4k-89-99-and-2nd-gen-homepod-174-99.2428065/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:04:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/verizon-apple-tv-homepod/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Verizon today has a few rare Apple deals, including record low prices on the <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-tv-4k-wifi-with-64-gb-storage%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5710030">64GB Apple TV 4K</a> and <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-homepod%2F">second generation HomePod</a>. These deals are available to all shoppers and you don't need to be a Verizon customer to get the discounts.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Apple-TV-Deals-22-Feature-Multi0011.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-850916" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Verizon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
You can get the 64GB Apple TV 4K for <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-tv-4k-wifi-with-64-gb-storage%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5710030"><strong>&#36;89.99</strong></a> in this sale, down from &#36;129.99, which is a new all-time low price. We haven't tracked any notable deals on the 2022 A15 Apple TV 4K in nearly a year, much less one as low as Verizon's sale.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-tv-4k-wifi-with-64-gb-storage%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku5710030"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>Apple TV 4K (64GB) for &#36;89.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Secondly, Verizon has the second generation HomePod for <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-homepod%2F"><strong>&#36;174.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;299.99. This is a massive &#36;125 discount on the 2023 smart speaker, beating the traditional discounted price by nearly &#36;100. This one is only available in Midnight.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/06/new-homepod-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-953293" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-homepod%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;125 OFF</div>HomePod (2nd Gen) for &#36;174.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Lastly, the carrier has a few buy one, get one half off deals going on right now on both <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fonesearch%2Fsearch%3Fq%3Dairpods%26ES%3Dshop%26src%3Dwireless">AirPods</a> and <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fapple-homepod-mini%2F%3Fsku%3Dsku4240002">HomePod mini</a>. AirPods under this deal include AirPods Pro 2, AirPods 3, and AirPods 2. All colors of the HomePod mini are available for the BOGO deal, and would effectively make each speaker about &#36;75.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/06/03/verizon-apple-tv-homepod/">Verizon Launches Rare Discounts on Apple TV 4K (&#36;89.99) and 2nd Gen HomePod (&#36;174.99)</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/verizon-launches-rare-discounts-on-apple-tv-4k-89-99-and-2nd-gen-homepod-174-99.2428065/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
