<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 13:03:03 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Blood Glucose Team Gains New Lead</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-gains-new-lead.2401766/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 12:29:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple has done some internal shuffling and appointed Tim Millet, vice president of platform architecture, to lead the team that is working on blood glucose monitoring functionality for the Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Apple-Watch-Blood-Glucose-Monitoring-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888310" /><br/>
According to <em><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2023-09-14/apple-taps-new-chief-for-team-developing-watch-s-glucose-tracker">Bloomberg</a></em>, Millet is now in charge of the Exploratory Design Group or XDG that has been developing noninvasive blood glucose testing for years. The team was previously led by longtime Apple employee Bill Athas, but he unexpectedly died in late 2022.<br/>
<br/>
Millet has been at Apple for almost 20 years, and he reports to Apple chip chief Johny Srouji. <em>Bloomberg</em> says that Millet has played a key role in the transition to Apple silicon, leading several teams that work on the processors.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's work on blood glucose monitoring is being overseen by the semiconductor team rather than a health team because it requires advanced sensors and chips. Apple is exploring a noninvasive monitoring technique that involves shooting a laser underneath the skin to determine the concentration of glucose in the blood.<br/>
<br/>
Noninvasive blood glucose monitoring would allow diabetics to test their blood glucose levels without needing to prick the skin, plus it would likely be able to detect pre-diabetes and other blood glucose issues.<br/>
<br/>
Earlier this year, Apple reached a milestone "proof-of-concept" stage with hardware that is about the size of an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, but Apple needs to condense the components into a size that can fit into an Apple Watch.<br/>
<br/>
A blood glucose monitoring function for the Apple Watch remains several years away.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch/">Apple Watch Series 9</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch">Apple Watch (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-update/">Apple Watch Blood Glucose Team Gains New Lead</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-blood-glucose-team-gains-new-lead.2401766/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Available to Order Tomorrow With These 12 New Features</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-available-to-order-tomorrow-with-these-12-new-features.2401761/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 11:45:07 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple will begin accepting pre-orders for the new iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max this Friday, September 15 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time. As usual, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">Pro models</a> have a long list of new features, including a USB-C port, lightweight titanium frame, customizable Action button, and much more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-lineup.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910338" /><br/>
Below, we have highlighted 12 new features on the iPhone 15 Pro models:<br/>
<ul><li>Lightning has been replaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-pro/">with a <strong>USB-C port</strong></a> for a more universal charging standard and faster data transfer speeds up to 10 Gbps.</li><br/>
<li>All four iPhone 15 models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/"><strong>support DisplayPort</strong></a> for up to 4K HDR video mirroring and video output to an external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable, according to Apple's tech specs for the devices.</li><br/>
<li>A new <strong>titanium frame</strong> results in the iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/titanium-iphone-15-pro-weight/">weighing up to 10% less</a> than the iPhone 14 Pro models with a stainless steel frame.</li><br/>
<li>A customizable <strong>Action button</strong> replaces the traditional mute switch on previous iPhones. By default, the button is set to toggle between Ring and Silent modes, but it can also be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-action-button-everything-it-can-do/">assigned to a different action</a> for quick access to the camera, flashlight, Voice Memos, Shortcuts, Focus modes, and more.</li><br/>
<li>The new <strong>A17 Pro chip</strong> enables <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores/">up to 10% faster CPU performance</a> and up to 20% faster GPU performance compared to the A16 Bionic chip.</li><br/>
<li>The devices are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/02/iphone-15-pro-features-specs-rumors/">equipped with <strong>8GB of RAM</strong></a>, up from 6GB in the iPhone 14 Pro models. Along with the new A17 Pro chip, extra RAM benefits overall system performance, particularly for multitasking.</li><br/>
<li>There are <strong>thinner bezels</strong> around the screen compared to the iPhone 14 Pro models.</li><br/>
<li>Like the latest Macs and iPad Pro, the iPhone 15 Pro models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-models-wi-fi-6e/">support <strong>Wi-Fi 6E</strong></a> (6GHz) for faster wireless speeds and less signal interference. Remember, you'll need a Wi-Fi 6E router in order to take advantage of this functionality.</li><br/>
<li>The iPhone 15 Pro Max exclusively features <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-max-25x-digital-zoom/"><strong>up to 5x optical zoom</strong></a>.</li><br/>
<li>The devices are equipped with a <strong>second-generation Ultra Wideband chip</strong>. Apple says two iPhones with this chip can connect from 3x farther away.</li><br/>
<li>The devices feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-models-more-repairable/"><strong>more repairable internal design</strong></a>, with a redesigned frame that allows for the back glass panel to be easily removed from the devices. This change was first made to the iPhone 14 and iPhone 14 Plus last year.</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/new-iphone-15-pro-color-options-no-gold/"><strong>New colors</strong></a>: Natural Titanium, Blue Titanium, White Titanium, and Black Titanium.</li></ul>For more details about the devices, read our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-pre-orders-tomorrow/">iPhone 15 Pro Available to Order Tomorrow With These 12 New Features</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-available-to-order-tomorrow-with-these-12-new-features.2401761/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Sells EarPods With USB-C, Lightning, or Headphone Plug</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-sells-earpods-with-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug.2401757/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 10:51:33 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>EarPods</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In addition to updating the AirPods Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">with a USB-C charging case</a>, Apple has made its wired EarPods headphones available with a USB-C connector for use with the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">iPhone 15 models</a>. The earbuds are &#36;19 on Apple's online store.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/EarPods-USB-C-Feature-Yellow.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-893683" /><br/>
Apple now sells three versions of EarPods, including ones with a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MTJY3AM/A/earpods-usb-c">USB-C connector</a>, <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MMTN2AM/A/earpods-lightning-connector">Lightning connector</a>, and a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MNHF2AM/A/earpods-35mm-headphone-plug">3.5mm headphone plug</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Released in 2012, the EarPods have become far less popular since Apple launched wireless AirPods in 2016. Starting with the iPhone 12 series in 2020, Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2020/10/13/iphone-12-ships-without-earpods-or-charger/">stopped including EarPods</a> and a charger in the box with new iPhones in order to be more environmentally friendly, a decision that was controversial at the time.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/EarPods-Trio.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911208" /><br/>
Apple released its original iconic white earbuds in 2001 alongside the launch of the first iPod, and they received a major redesign and the EarPods name in 2012.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/earpods/">EarPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/earpods-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug/">Apple Now Sells EarPods With USB-C, Lightning, or Headphone Plug</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-sells-earpods-with-usb-c-lightning-or-headphone-plug.2401757/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Surveys Devs With Vision Pro About Digital &#039;Persona&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-vision-pro-developer-survey/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-surveys-devs-with-vision-pro-about-digital-persona.2401745/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 09:53:17 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-vision-pro-developer-survey/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Vision Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[While the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a> headset is not launching until early 2024, some developers have access to the device in order to develop <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/visionos/">visionOS</a> apps. Though Feedback Assistant, Apple is collecting opinions on the Vision Pro "Persona" that is created for each person for use with <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/facetime/">FaceTime</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/apple-vision-pro-facetime.jpg" alt="" width="2432" height="1368" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900260" /><br/>
The Persona is a digital representation of the user, with Apple using the headset's cameras to recreate the face and hands. While the &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; call is ongoing, the Persona is able to make the same facial expressions and hand movements as the user, so that &zwnj;FaceTime&zwnj; calls feel more like a person-to-person interaction.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/vision-pro-headset-survey.jpg" alt="" width="1074" height="1388" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911183" /><br/>
There is likely some degree of uncanny valley with this experience, so it is no surprise that it is a feature that Apple is working to refine. Apple is asking developers a number of questions about the Persona experience.<br/>
<ul><br/>
 	<li>How do you feel about your Persona?</li><br/>
 	<li>To what extent do you feel this Persona represents your appearance?</li><br/>
 	<li>To what extent do you feel your Persona responds to your facial expressions?</li><br/>
 	<li>What do you like most about your Persona?</li><br/>
 	<li>What do you like least about your Persona?</li><br/>
 	<li>What do you like/not like about this Persona?</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
Respondents are given multiple choice answers for most of the questions, with the last one being an open feedback form. For the "How do you feel about your Persona?" question, for example, responses include "Very Happy - I'm excited to use it," "Happy - I would be okay using it," "Unhappy - I would be hesitant to use it," and "Very Unhappy - I would never use it."<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Exclusive: Apple is asking developers with the Vision Pro to fill out a feedback survey about FaceTime Personas.<br><br>Some questions include: <br><br>How do you feel about your Persona?<br><br>To what extent do you feel this Persona represents your appearance? <a href="https://t.co/wKgQlKrODL">pic.twitter.com/wKgQlKrODL</a></p>&mdash; Aaron (@aaronp613) <a href="https://twitter.com/aaronp613/status/1702364571053248573?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 14, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script></div><br/>
Apple does not plan to release the Vision Pro headset until early 2024, so it still has several months of software refining and hardware tweaking to do before the device needs to be mass produced in order to sell.<br/>
<br/>
The headset will be priced at &#36;3,500 when it launches, and it will first be available in the United States before expanding to other countries.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-vision-pro/">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-vision-pro.209">Apple Vision Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-vision-pro-developer-survey/">Apple Surveys Devs With Vision Pro About Digital &#039;Persona&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-surveys-devs-with-vision-pro-about-digital-persona.2401745/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17: How to Send Files and Photos With AirDrop Proximity Sharing</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-share-files-media-airdrop-proximity/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-send-files-and-photos-with-airdrop-proximity-sharing.2401729/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:56:25 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-share-files-media-airdrop-proximity&#038;post_date=1694714185/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>AirDrop</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, Apple has made sharing files and media easier than ever, thanks to a cool new AirDrop proximity feature that does most of the work for you. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/airdrop-videos-ios-17.jpg" alt="" width="2484" height="1391" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-900711" /><br/>
In prior versions of iOS, transferring a file or photo between Apple devices involves opening the file in question, tapping the Share button, selecting AirDrop, then choosing the nearby device you want to send the file to.<br/>
<br/>
With &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, this procedure still exists for sharing between Apple devices, but if you're transferring between iPhones or iPads then you can cut out some of the typical sharing steps by using AirDrop's new proximity feature.<br/>
<br/>
To initiate a transfer, select the photo or file that you want to share with someone. From there, simply bring your unlocked ‌<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>‌ (or <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>) next to the other person's unlocked ‌&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;, and your device will pop up a share interface without you having to tap on the Share Sheet.<br/>
<br/>
Tap the Share button that pops up to send the photo or file to the person next to you, and it will be received on the other device automatically, with permission granted through their proximity.<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/08/airdrop-proximity-sharing.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1327" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-905665" /><br/>
<br/>
Note that sharing files this way works even if AirDrop receiving is turned off or limited to contacts, so it offers a way to share a file with someone without having to change your overall AirDrop settings. <br/>
<br/>
<h3>Enable or Disable AirDrop Proximity Sharing</h3><br/>
 We're used to AirDrop working with someone in the same room and involving a few manual steps, but the proximity sharing feature makes transfers between two devices virtually effortless. Of course, if you don't like the idea of proximity sharing, you can turn it off. Here's how it's done in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPadOS 17&zwnj;.<br/>
<ol><li>Open the <strong>Settings</strong> app.</li><br/>
<li>Tap through to <strong>General -> AirDrop</strong>.</li><br/>
<li>Toggle the switch next to <strong>Bringing Devices Together </strong>on or off.</li></ol><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/enable-disable-airdrop-proximity-sharing.jpg" alt="settings" width="4137" height="2716" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911172" /><br/>
<br/>
That's all there is to it. Note that disabling this setting will also prevent the sharing of contacts via NameDrop. To learn about how contact sharing has also become easier than ever in &zwnj;iOS 17&zwnj;, check out our <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-share-contact-details-with-namedrop/">dedicated NameDrop how-to</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/airdrop/">AirDrop</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/how-to/ios-share-files-media-airdrop-proximity/">iOS 17: How to Send Files and Photos With AirDrop Proximity Sharing</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-how-to-send-files-and-photos-with-airdrop-proximity-sharing.2401729/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra vs. Ultra 2 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 12 Differences Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2-buyers-guide-12-differences-compared.2401719/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:41:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2&#038;post_date=1694713292/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> replaces the first-generation model that was introduced last year in Apple's smartwatch lineup, but how different are the two successive smartwatch generations?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-vs-Ultra-2-Buyers-Guide.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1265" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-911116" /><br/>
In 2023, Apple unveiled the Apple Watch Ultra, introducing a more durable design and titanium casing, a larger and brighter display, additional speakers and microphones, considerably longer battery life, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-series-8-vs-apple-watch-ultra/">more</a>. The first-generation Apple Watch Ultra has now been discontinued by Apple, and as a year-old model, prices at third-party resellers are falling. As such, some customers may be weighing up whether to upgrade to a first- or second-generation Ultra‌.<br/>
<br/>
The two Apple Watch Ultra models share the overwhelming majority of their features, so should you consider buying or sticking with the first-generation to save money? This breakdown also serves as a way to see all the differences that the Ultra 2 brings to the table.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>Apple Watch Ultra (first-generation)</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Retina display with up to 2,000 nits of brightness</td><br/>
 <td>Retina display with up to 3,000 nits of brightness, Apple's brightest display ever</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Flashlight</td><br/>
 <td>Flashlight boost via Digital Crown</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Double Tap gesture to stop timers, play and pause music, snooze alarms, answer and end phone calls, take photos with the Camera Remote, open the Smart Stack, and scroll through widgets, all without touching the display</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>S8 chip (based on A13 Bionic chip)</td><br/>
 <td>S9 chip (based on A15 Bionic chip: 60% more transistors, 30% faster)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Neural Engine</td><br/>
 <td>4-core Neural Engine (up to twice as fast)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a> processed in the cloud via internet connection</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; processed on-device for requests that do not need information from the internet, resulting in quicker and more reliable responses</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Siri&zwnj; can access health and fitness data</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Dictation</td><br/>
 <td>25% more accurate dictation</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models, providing distance and direction, as well as visual, haptic, and audio guidance to a misplaced <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a></td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/homepod/">HomePod</a> integration: When a user gets within four meters of a playing &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, the Apple Watch launches Now Playing to control playback. If nothing is playing, media suggestions appear at the top of the Smart Stack.</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>32GB storage</td><br/>
 <td>64GB storage</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 </table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
Overall, the &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; is a very minor upgrade over the first-generation model, with the S9 chip, Double Tap, and Precision Finding for &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; models being the most significant changes. As a result, it is very difficult to recommend upgrading.<br/>
<br/>
Most users of the existing Apple Watch Ultra will not be able to justify upgrading to the Ultra 2, but some customers coming from an older Apple Watch or those who do not have one at all could still have good reason to prefer the latest model, namely those who heavily use a &zwnj;HomePod&zwnj;, plan to buy an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; model and can take advantage of Precision Finding, need additional storage for downloaded media, or think one-handed use with the Double Tap gesture would be useful.<br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;Apple Watch Ultra 2&zwnj; is very similar to the first-generation model, so most customers who are interested in buying an Ultra model may prefer to look for a discounted first-generation model. If the original device can be found for a substantially lower price, it remains a solid buy. The Ultra 2 is priced at &#36;799, so if you are not interested in its new features and can find the original model for less than ~&#36;650, it may be worth getting that instead.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2/">Apple Watch Ultra vs. Ultra 2 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 12 Differences Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-vs-ultra-2-buyers-guide-12-differences-compared.2401719/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Get Ready for iPhone 15 Pre-Orders With This List of the Best Carrier Deals</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pre-orders-carrier-deals/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-ready-for-iphone-15-pre-orders-with-this-list-of-the-best-carrier-deals.2401715/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 07:24:55 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pre-orders-carrier-deals/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">announcement</a> of the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro at this week's "Wonderlust" event, carrier discounts and offers have quickly emerged for the latest generation of iPhone. In this article we're highlighting all of the best carrier deals you can expect ahead of pre-order day on Friday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-2.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911150" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
Remember that for all of the links and deals below, you won't be able to add the iPhone 15 to your cart and get the discounts until pre-orders go live at 5 a.m. Pacific Time on September 15. The smartphones will then launch on September 22.<br/>
<br/>
Like years past, most of the carriers are all offering similar discounts. Apple even mentioned these sales during its keynote, stating it was working with multiple carriers to offer customers as much as &#36;1,000 off the new iPhone 15 Pro Max.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>AT&T</h2><br/>
AT&T has the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15.html">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.dpbolvw.net/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro.html">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models at no cost when you trade in an eligible smartphone and put the new device on an unlimited data plan. All of AT&T's new deals are available for both new and existing customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-3.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911152" /><br/>
You can get the <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-plus.html">iPhone 15 Plus</a> for up to &#36;830 off and the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-max.html">iPhone 15 Pro Max</a> for up to &#36;1,000 off, both with an eligible smartphone trade in on a qualifying installment agreement. There's also a &#36;35 activation/upgrade fee that comes with the new smartphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at AT&T</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
For every AT&T offer, you'll receive the discounts in the form of bill credits. You'll get up to &#36;1,000 in bill credits on iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max with a smartphone trade in value of &#36;230 or more.<br/>
<br/>
You'll get up to &#36;830 in bill credits with a smartphone trade in value of &#36;130 to &#36;229. Additionally, you'll get up to &#36;350 in bill credits with a smartphone trade in value of &#36;35 to &#36;129.<br/>
<br/>
AT&T has <a href="https://www.kqzyfj.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbrand%2Fapple%2Fwatch%2F">Apple Watch deals</a>, allowing customers to buy one and get another for &#36;300 off without any trade in required.<br/>
<br/>
Finally, AT&T is marking down the <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-13761603?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.att.com%2Fbuy%2Fphones%2Fapple-iphone-14-pro.html">iPhone 14 family of smartphones</a> to as low as &#36;15/month for 14 and 14 Pro, and &#36;20/month for 14 Pro Max. No trade in is required to get the deals on these previous generation devices, which also includes the ninth generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Verizon</h2><br/>
New and existing Verizon customers can get up to &#36;1,000 off any iPhone 15 model with any iPhone trade-in, which means you can get the <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fwireless-devices%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-announcement%2F">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fwireless-devices%2Fsmartphones%2Fapple-iphone-15-pro-announcement%2F">iPhone 15 Pro</a> at no cost. Existing customers upgrading can get up to &#36;830 off the new iPhone 15 lineup on Unlimited plans.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue-4.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911155" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2F"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at Verizon</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also get the <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-11557999?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fwireless-devices%2Fsmart-watches%2Fapple-watch-series-9-announcement%2F">Apple Watch Series 9</a> for less than &#36;6/month or an Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;14/month when purchased alongside select iPhones with a qualified watch trade-in.<br/>
<br/>
Lastly, Verizon is one of the only carriers hosting a notable accessory sale on iPhone launch day. You can get <a href="https://www.jdoqocy.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fshop%2Fonline%2Fmagsafe-accessories-sale%2F">25 percent off MagSafe chargers</a> and <a href="https://www.tkqlhce.com/click-462641-14066852?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.verizon.com%2Fproducts%2Fsale%2F">20 percent off select cases, chargers, and screen protectors</a> for iPhone 15 devices.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>T-Mobile</h2><br/>
Similar to other carriers, <a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/devices/new-apple-iphone-15-pro-release?icid=MGPO_MTW_U_23APPLNPI_FU9X6OK5VBCXRCZG35882_HP">T-Mobile</a> has up to &#36;1,000 off iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro devices. The carrier said that this means you can get the iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Pro at no cost.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-blue.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911148" /><div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.t-mobile.com/devices/new-apple-iphone-15-pro-release?icid=MGPO_MTW_U_23APPLNPI_FU9X6OK5VBCXRCZG35882_HP"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">UP TO &#36;1,000 OFF</div>iPhone 15 at T-Mobile</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You'll need to trade in an eligible smartphone on the Go5G Plus or Go5G Next cellular plans in order to get these discounts. T-Mobile also has a BOGO deal on the new iPhone 15, where you can get &#36;700 off the second model after you purchase the first and add a line on an existing plan.<br/>
<br/>
You can get up to &#36;650 off any iPhone 15 series device on the Magenta MAX plan, &#36;350 off on Go5G and Magenta, and &#36;200 off on nearly all other T-Mobile plans. <br/>
<br/>
Lastly, if you buy any new Apple Watch you can get &#36;300 off a second model when adding a new watch line on an existing cellular plan.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Visible</h2><br/>
Verizon-owned <a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909">Visible</a> has two unlimited plans on offer this season, starting at &#36;25/month. When you join Visible and purchase a select smartphone, you'll also save up to &#36;240 via monthly service credits.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://visible.pxf.io/c/153062/1007955/12909"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">SAVE &#36;240</div>iPhone 15 at Visible</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
This deal requires you to add a new line of service, purchase a new device on device payment or at full retail price, and purchase the &#36;45/month Visible+ plan. You can also get the Apple Watch Series 9 and save &#36;5/month for a year when added to a cellular plan.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pre-orders-carrier-deals/">Get Ready for iPhone 15 Pre-Orders With This List of the Best Carrier Deals</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/get-ready-for-iphone-15-pre-orders-with-this-list-of-the-best-carrier-deals.2401715/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>These Apple Products Are Still Sold With Lightning Following iPhone 15&#039;s Switch to USB-C</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-apple-products-are-still-sold-with-lightning-following-iphone-15s-switch-to-usb-c.2401711/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 06:40:28 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Lightning</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[As widely expected, all four iPhone 15 models are <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-iphone-15-and-15-plus/">equipped with a USB-C port</a> instead of a Lightning port. Apple also made the AirPods Pro <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-usb-c-iphone-airpods-earpods/">available with a USB-C charging case</a>, and released wired EarPods with a USB-C connector.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/04/lightning-connector-feature-purple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-891738" /><br/>
Nevertheless, there are a handful of Apple devices and accessories that are still sold with Lightning, which debuted on the iPhone 5 back in 2012:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li>iPhone 14 Plus, iPhone 14, iPhone 13, and iPhone SE</li><br/>
<li>Ninth-generation iPad</li><br/>
<li>Second-generation and third-generation AirPods</li><br/>
<li>AirPods Max</li><br/>
<li>First-generation Apple Pencil</li><br/>
<li>Magic Keyboard (Mac version)</li><br/>
<li>Magic Mouse</li><br/>
<li>Magic Trackpad</li><br/>
<li>Various cables and adapters</li></ul>Apple did <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-discontinues-magsafe-battery-pack-and-duo/">discontinue its MagSafe Battery Pack and MagSafe Duo Charger</a> accessories with Lightning following the iPhone 15 event.<br/>
<br/>
Some of these products will likely be updated with USB-C in the future, such as the AirPods Max and the trio of Magic accessories for the Mac, while previous-generation products in the list like the older iPhones, iPad, and Apple Pencil will eventually be discontinued. Until then, the Lightning era of Apple is not completely over.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/lightning/">Lightning</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/remaining-apple-products-with-lightning/">These Apple Products Are Still Sold With Lightning Following iPhone 15&#039;s Switch to USB-C</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/these-apple-products-are-still-sold-with-lightning-following-iphone-15s-switch-to-usb-c.2401711/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Buy a Large Product at an Apple Store? You Can Now Choose Delivery</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-store-delivery-option/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/buy-a-large-product-at-an-apple-store-you-can-now-choose-delivery.2401699/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:46:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-store-delivery-option/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Store</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Have you ever been into an Apple Store to purchase something small, like a new iPhone case or Apple Watch band, but passed by that colorful iMac or pixel-perfect Studio Display along the way and just couldn't resist buying one?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/imac-2021-box-feature-1.jpg" alt="" width="2566" height="1443" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-799803" /><br/>
For those spur-of-the-moment purchases, Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2023/09/apple-offers-more-ways-to-order-the-all-new-iphone-15-and-apple-watch-lineups/">announced</a> a new solution called Easy Pay Online Ordering that gives customers the option to have the products they purchase in store delivered to their home. Apple said its retail stores are also now able to sell out-of-stock items to customers that are delivered to their home at a later date.<br/>
<br/>
This new option means that customers will no longer have to drag heavy, large-boxed products to their vehicle in the parking lot or on public transportation. Alternatively, ordering via Apple's online store remains an option to avoid this dilemma as well.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's plans to offer Easy Pay Online Ordering were <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/07/24/apple-retail-stores-home-delivery-option/">reported by <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman</a> in July, and the company officially announced the feature today.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-store/">Apple Store</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-store-delivery-option/">Buy a Large Product at an Apple Store? You Can Now Choose Delivery</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/buy-a-large-product-at-an-apple-store-you-can-now-choose-delivery.2401699/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 15 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 20 Upgrades Compared</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-15/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-15-buyers-guide-20-upgrades-compared.2401686/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 05:08:46 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-15&#038;post_date=1694704126/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Buyer's Guide</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 14</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus are Apple's latest standard <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models, sporting some bigger upgrades than seen in recent years, but how different really are the two successive &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; generations?<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-14-vs-15-Buyers-Guide.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910683" /><br/>
In 2022, Apple unveiled the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> as the successor to the popular <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a>, offering 2GB more memory, longer battery life, the Photonic Engine, Action mode, Emergency SOS via satellite, Crash Detection, and more. As devices that are more affordable than the "Pro" models, but more full-featured than the low-cost <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a>, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus will likely be the most popular option for many customers, starting at a price of &#36;799 for the 128GB model. The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus continue to be available from Apple for &#36;699 and &#36;799, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
As the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; share the overwhelming majority of their features, should you consider buying or sticking with the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; to save money? Our guide helps to answer the question of how to decide which of these two &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models is best for you, and serves as a way to clearly see the differences that the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; brings to the table. This article focuses on the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;, Apple's standard &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models, but to understand the differences between the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a>, see our other buyer's guide:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-pro-vs-iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro vs. iPhone 15 Pro Buyer's Guide: 30+ Upgrades Compared</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; both feature the same display sizes, battery life, 12-megapixel ultra wide camera, and more. Nevertheless, the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; still offers a number of substantial upgrades, such as the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/dynamic-island/">Dynamic Island</a>, USB-C port, and 48-megapixel camera.<br/>
<br/>
<table class="comparison"><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;</th><br/>
 <th>&zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;</th><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with squared-off edges</td><br/>
 <td>Aluminum chassis with contoured edges</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Glossy glass back</td><br/>
 <td>Color-infused frosted glass back</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>"Notch" TrueDepth camera array</td><br/>
 <td>&zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>800 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 <td>1,000 nits max brightness (typical)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>1,200 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 <td>1,600 nits peak brightness (HDR)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>2,000 nits peak brightness (outdoor)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>A15 Bionic chip</td><br/>
 <td>A16 Bionic chip</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU</td><br/>
 <td>5-core GPU with 50% more memory bandwidth</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>12-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.5 aperture</td><br/>
 <td>48-megapixel main camera with ƒ/1.6 aperture</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>0.5x and 1x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 <td>0.5x, 1x, and 2x optical zoom options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>24- and 48-megapixel super-high-resolution photos</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 4</td><br/>
 <td>Smart HDR 5</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Portrait mode with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 <td>Next-generation portraits with Focus and Depth Control</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 <td>Improved Night mode and Night mode portraits</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Improved audio quality on phone calls</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>First-generation Ultra Wideband chip</td><br/>
 <td>Second-generation Ultra Wideband chip (connects from 3x further away)</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td></td><br/>
 <td>Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/find-my-network-accessory-program/">Find My</a> friends</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Lightning port</td><br/>
 <td>USB-C port</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Support for Qi wireless charging</td><br/>
 <td>Support for Qi2 wireless charging</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
 <tr><br/>
 <td>Yellow, Blue, Purple, (PRODUCT)RED, Starlight, and Midnight color options </td><br/>
 <td>Yellow, Blue, Pink, Green, and Black color options</td><br/>
 </tr><br/>
</table><br/>
<div class="clear"></div><br/>
<br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;'s upgrades over the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; are fairly substantial, offering a more refined and appealing design with contoured edges, frosted back glass, and the &zwnj;Dynamic Island&zwnj;. Features like the brighter display and USB-C port are meaningful quality-of-life enhancements that all users will be able to take advantage of. The 48-megapixel main camera, 2x optical zoom option, next-generation portraits, Smart HDR 5, and improved Night mode also make for a significant overall camera improvement for average users. Iterative changes like the A16 Bionic and support for Qi2 are also welcome refinements.<br/>
<br/>
Depending on what sort of user you are, it may not be worth upgrading from an &zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; or &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; model to the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; unless you actively want several of the new features, but the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; Plus seem to be an unusually large upgrade for Apple's non-Pro iPhones. As a result, a large number of users with one of these older devices may be able to justify upgrading to an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; model. Those with an &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 or older will definitely receive a major upgrade by purchasing an &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
For everyday users, it is worth noting that the switch to USB-C on the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; will make any Lightning cables and accessories you have redundant, meaning you'll need to purchase a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-releases-usb-c-lightning-adapter-and-more/">&#36;29 adapter</a> or use a new cable. If you're coming from a much older device, you will also likely need to buy a new power adapter. If you are unhappy about this change, then it may be worth sticking with what you have for another year, but it is worth highlighting that the switch to USB-C is beneficial in the long term since it is a standard port used across a wide range of devices.<br/>
<br/>
Since the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; is a mostly noteworthy upgrade, it is generally not worth buying an &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; model instead, unless it can be found for a significantly lower price. The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus are only a year old and still very good devices, but the &zwnj;iPhone 15&zwnj; has a range of improvements that are likely to make it age better and be slightly more useful over time, which warrants its higher price.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPhone-14">iPhone 14 (Don't Buy)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone-14-vs-iphone-15/">iPhone 14 vs. iPhone 15 Buyer&#039;s Guide: 20 Upgrades Compared</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-14-vs-iphone-15-buyers-guide-20-upgrades-compared.2401686/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Watch Ultra 2 Already Facing 6-7 Week Shipping Delay for Some Configurations</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-ultra-2-shipping-delays/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-already-facing-6-7-week-shipping-delay-for-some-configurations.2401682/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 04:18:40 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-ultra-2-shipping-delays/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple Watch Ultra</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-announces-apple-watch-ultra-2/">all-new Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> is available to order in the U.S. and more than 40 other countries, with pricing set at &#36;799. The high-end Apple Watch will launch in stores and begin arriving to customers on September 22, but some configurations are already facing lengthy shipping delays as of late Wednesday.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-Watch-Ultra-2-hero-230912.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910333" /><br/>
A quick spot check of Apple's online store in the U.S. reveals that models with an Alpine band in Blue in Medium/Large sizes face 2-3 week shipping estimates for orders placed on late Wednesday, while models with the Trail Loop in Orange and Beige   for both S/M and M/L sizes face an even lengthier 6-7 week delay at this time. That said, there are still at least a half-dozen band options available with September 22 launch day delivery overall.<br/>
<br/>
The second-generation Apple Watch Ultra offers all of the features of the original Ultra, plus a faster new S9 SiP chip, a new double tap gesture, Apple's brightest display ever, expanded altitude range, quicker on-device <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/siri/">Siri</a>, Precision Finding for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, and new capabilities for water adventures.<br/>
<br/>
Apple Watch Ultra is advertised as having up to 36 hours of battery life per charge during normal usage, and up to 72 hours of normal usage with Low Power Mode enabled – up 12 hours from the previous generation.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/apple-watch-ultra/">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#Apple_Watch_Ultra">Apple Watch Ultra (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/apple-watch.172">Apple Watch</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-watch-ultra-2-shipping-delays/">Apple Watch Ultra 2 Already Facing 6-7 Week Shipping Delay for Some Configurations</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-watch-ultra-2-already-facing-6-7-week-shipping-delay-for-some-configurations.2401682/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Selling New 60W and 240W USB-C Woven Charge Cables</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-selling-60w-and-60w-240w-usb-c-charge-cables/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-selling-new-60w-and-240w-usb-c-woven-charge-cables.2401676/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 03:03:50 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-selling-60w-and-60w-240w-usb-c-charge-cables/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>USB-C</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Following its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">iPhone 15 event on Tuesday</a>, Apple released a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-releases-usb-c-lightning-adapter-and-more/">few related accessories</a>, including a USB-C to Lightning adapter and a one-meter Thunderbolt 4 Pro cable. It turns out the company has also made available a new <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MU2G3AM/A/240w-usb-c-charge-cable-2-m?">60W 1-meter USB-C Charge Cable (&#36;19)</a> and a <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MU2G3AM/A/240w-usb-c-charge-cable-2-m?">240W 2-meter USB-C Charge Cable (&#36;29)</a>, designed for charging iPhone 15 models, iPads, and Macs.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/USB-C-60w-240w-charge-cable.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911066" /><br/>
Apple advertises the new woven charge cable with USB-C connectors on both ends as "ideal for charging, syncing, and transferring data between USB-C devices." It supports charging of up to 240 watts and transfers data at USB 2 rates. <br/>
<br/>
Compatible with all iPhone 15 models and Apple's latest iPad and Mac models, the cable can be paired with a compatible USB-C power adapter to charge the devices from a wall outlet and take advantage of fast-charging capabilities.<br/>
<br/>
While the new standard iPhone 15 and iPhone 15 Plus are equipped with a USB-C port, data transfer over a cable remains limited to USB 2.0 speeds of up to 480 Mbps, which is equal to the Lightning port on previous iPhones. <br/>
<br/>
The higher-end iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are also equipped with a USB-C port, but those devices support USB 3 data transfer speeds of up to 10 Gbps over a cable. For this reason, Apple made its previously-existing Thunderbolt 4 Pro cable available in a shorter one-meter size for &#36;69. <br/>
<br/>
<em>(Thanks MacRumors forum member BeatCrazy!)</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/usb-c/">USB-C</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-selling-60w-and-60w-240w-usb-c-charge-cables/">Apple Selling New 60W and 240W USB-C Woven Charge Cables</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-selling-new-60w-and-240w-usb-c-woven-charge-cables.2401676/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Makes iPhone Battery Replacements Cheaper in the UK</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-iphone-battery-servicing-uk-cheaper/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-makes-iphone-battery-replacements-cheaper-in-the-uk.2401671/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 02:16:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-iphone-battery-servicing-uk-cheaper/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>United Kingdom</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> price drops in the United Kingdom compared to last year's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a> models, Apple has also reduced the cost of its <a href="https://support.apple.com/en-gb/iphone/repair/battery-replacement">iPhone Battery Servicing</a> program for several earlier models.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/uk-iphone-battery-servicing.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911057" /><br/>
The biggest savings can be found for &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models. Prior to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/everything-apple-announced-fall-2023-event/">Tuesday's iPhone 15 announcement</a>, Apple charged £105 for &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; battery replacements, whereas now it lists £95, or a £10 reduction. <br/>
<br/>
New batteries for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> XR through <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-13/">iPhone 13</a> models are now £85 compared to £89 previously, and new batteries for <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-se/">iPhone SE</a> through &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X models are now £65 instead of £69.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's new battery replacement charges for all models offered through its &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; Battery Servicing program are as follows: <ul><li>&zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models - £95</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone 13&zwnj; models - £85</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-12/">iPhone 12</a> models - £85</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 11 models - £85</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XS models - £85</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; XR models - £85</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; X - £85</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 8 - £65</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 7 - £65</li><br/>
<li>&zwnj;iPhone SE&zwnj; - £65</li></ul>With the exception of the starting price of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> Max, Apple on Tuesday made UK prices of the newly announced &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max models <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-100-pound-cheaper-uk/">at least £100 cheaper</a> across all configuration options than the equivalent <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a> models when they were launched last year. Similar reductions were also reported across other European countries.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, Apple cut the price of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, from £549 down to £499, as well as updated second-generation <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a>, from £249 down to £229. <br/>
<br/>
In the US, the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max was the only device to see a price increase, rising &#36;100 to &#36;1,199 because of Apple's decision to drop its 128GB storage option and make 256GB the new minimum storage configuration. Apple increased prices more aggressively for the phones in some other markets, including Canada and India.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/united-kingdom/">United Kingdom</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/apple-iphone-battery-servicing-uk-cheaper/">Apple Makes iPhone Battery Replacements Cheaper in the UK</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-makes-iphone-battery-replacements-cheaper-in-the-uk.2401671/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro Geekbench Scores Confirm Apple&#039;s Faster A17 Pro Chip Performance Claims, 8GB of RAM</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores-confirm-apples-faster-a17-pro-chip-performance-claims-8gb-of-ram.2401665/</comments>
		<pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 01:17:19 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Tim Hardwick</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Geekbench</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The first Geekbench scores for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> have confirmed Apple's performance improvement claims for its new A17 Pro chip over last year's A16 Bionic chipset found in the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14-pro/">iPhone 14 Pro</a>. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-pro-gray.jpg" alt="" width="1876" height="1055" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910519" /><br/>
As spotted by <em><a href="https://www.mysmartprice.com/gear/apple-iphone-15-pro-iphone-15-pro-max-geekbench-scores-spotted/">MySmartPrice</a></em>, the benchmarking platform has recorded an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; tested in the wild with the model number <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/v6/cpu/2592695">iPhone 16,1</a> and a six-core CPU with a base frequency of 3.78GHz. <br/>
<br/>
In the test result, the device scored 2,908 and 7,238 points in the single-core and multi-core tests, while last year's &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj; scored 2,642 and 6,739, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, an &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; Max with the model number <a href="https://browser.geekbench.com/v6/cpu/2592698">iPhone 16,2</a> scored 2,846 and 7,024 points in the single-core and multi-core tests respectively. That also compares favorably to last years &zwnj;iPhone 14 Pro&zwnj; Max, which scored 2,546 and 6,631 points in the same respective tests.<br/>
<br/>
The Geekbench results also recorded 8GB of RAM for both &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; models, compared to 6GB of RAM in last year's Pro models, corroborating <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-models-have-8gb-ram/">previous reporting</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's A17 Pro chip is made with a first-of-its-kind 3-nanometer process. The A17 Pro has a six-core CPU, for 10% faster CPU performance and 20% faster GPU performance. It also has a two-times faster 16-core neural engine to accelerate machine learning such as more accurate autocorrect or pulling a subject from an image. It can process up to 35 trillion operations per second.<br/>
<br/>
In addition, the A17 Pro contains a brand new GPU with an Apple-designed shader architecture. Apple says it is the biggest redesign in the history of Apple GPUs, with a focus on performance and efficiency, running complex applications, and new rendering features.<br/>
<br/>
The ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;‌ starts at &#36;999 for 128GB of storage, while the ‌&zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj;‌ Max starts at &#36;1,199 for 256GB of storage. All of the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> models are available to pre-order starting Friday, September 15, and will launch on Friday, September 22 in more than 40 countries and regions around the world.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/geekbench/">Geekbench</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/14/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores/">iPhone 15 Pro Geekbench Scores Confirm Apple&#039;s Faster A17 Pro Chip Performance Claims, 8GB of RAM</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pro-geekbench-scores-confirm-apples-faster-a17-pro-chip-performance-claims-8gb-of-ram.2401665/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>All iPhone 15 Models Support DisplayPort for Up to 4K HDR Video Output to External Display</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport-for-up-to-4k-hdr-video-output-to-external-display.2401630/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 19:00:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iPhone 15</category>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>DisplayPort</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new iPhone 15, iPhone 15 Plus, iPhone 15 Pro, and iPhone 15 Pro Max all support DisplayPort for up to 4K HDR video mirroring and video output to an external display or TV, according to Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/iphone-15-pro/specs/">tech specs</a> for the devices.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-USB-C-Port-Keynote.jpeg" alt="" width="1600" height="898" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911041" /><br/>
DisplayPort support is built into the USB-C port on all iPhone 15 models, meaning that the devices can output video at up to 4K/60Hz natively to a DisplayPort-equipped external display or TV with a supported USB-C to DisplayPort cable. Alternatively, you can use Apple's &#36;69 <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/product/MUF82AM/A/usb-c-digital-av-multiport-adapter">USB-C Digital AV Multiport Adapter</a> to mirror video from any iPhone 15 to an HDMI-equipped TV or display at up to 4K/60Hz, but HDR is not supported this way.<br/>
<br/>
On previous iPhones with a Lightning port, video mirroring is limited to 1080p with Apple's Lightning-to-HDMI or Lightning-to-VGA adapters.<br/>
<br/>
Unfortunately for fans of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/17/stage-manager-ipados-16-hands-on/">Stage Manager</a> feature on select iPad models, the iPhone does not yet offer an extended display mode.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/displayport/">DisplayPort</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport/">All iPhone 15 Models Support DisplayPort for Up to 4K HDR Video Output to External Display</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/all-iphone-15-models-support-displayport-for-up-to-4k-hdr-video-output-to-external-display.2401630/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Action Button to Support Translate App Later This Year</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-action-button-translate-later/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pros-action-button-to-support-translate-app-later-this-year.2401628/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 18:05:01 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-action-button-translate-later/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 15 Pro</category>
		<category>Apple Translate</category>
		<category>Action Button</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The new iPhone 15 Pro and iPhone 15 Pro Max are equipped with a customizable Action button that replaces the traditional mute switch on previous iPhones. By default, the button is set to toggle between Ring and Silent modes, but it can also be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/iphone-15-pro-action-button-everything-it-can-do/">assigned to a different action</a> for quick access to the camera, flashlight, Voice Memos, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iPhone-15-Pro-Action-Button-Translate.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-911022" /><br/>
One of the options for the Action button will be the Translate app, allowing you to quickly start translating between two languages without having to open the app. However, fine print on Apple's website says the Translate option will not be available for the Action button until later this year, suggesting that it will be enabled in a future iOS 17 update.<br/>
<br/>
A recap of the other options that will be available for the Action button immediately:<ul><li>Ring/Silent</li><br/>
<li>Focus</li><br/>
<li>Camera</li><br/>
<li>Flashlight</li><br/>
<li>Voice Memos</li><br/>
<li>Magnifier</li><br/>
<li>Shortcuts</li><br/>
<li>Accessibility</li></ul>You must press and hold the Action button to launch the assigned action.<br/>
<br/>
iPhone 15 models can be pre-ordered starting Friday, September 15 at 5 a.m. Pacific Time, and will launch on Friday, September 22.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-translate/">Apple Translate</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/action-button/">Action Button</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/iphone-15-pro-action-button-translate-later/">iPhone 15 Pro&#039;s Action Button to Support Translate App Later This Year</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-15-pros-action-button-to-support-translate-app-later-this-year.2401628/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17 Adds 20+ New Ringtones and Text Tones for Calls, Messages and Alarms</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-ringtones-text-tones/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-adds-20-new-ringtones-and-text-tones-for-calls-messages-and-alarms.2401609/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 15:49:47 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-ringtones-text-tones/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[In <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, Apple is overhauling its entire offering of ringtones and text tones, debuting more than 20 new sounds that can be used for phone calls, texts, alarms, and more. Almost all of the Ringtones listed in the Sounds & Haptics menu are new, so there are plenty of options to choose from.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ios-17-ringtones.jpg" alt="" width="1200" height="630" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910968" /><br/>
The new ringtones include Arpeggio, Breaking, Canopy, Chalet, Chirp, Daybreak, Departure, Dollop, Journey, Kettle, Mercury, Milky Way, Quad, Radial, Scavenger, Seedling, Shelter, Sprinkles, Steps, Storytime, Tease, Tilt, Unfold, and Valley. Reflection continues to be the default ringtone option.<br/>
<br/>
Compared to the old ringtones, many of the new ringtones are longer in length and sound more modern. Apple has moved all of the prior ringtones to the "Classic" section so they are still accessible for those who prefer options like Illuminate, Night Owl, Constellation, and Twinkle.<br/>
<br/>
Ringtones activate when the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> rings and the mute function is disabled, plus they can be set as alarm sounds. You can have different ringtones for each person in your Contact app, and you can use separate ringtones if you have multiple lines on one &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Apple has also introduced more than 10 new Text Tones that can be used for incoming text messages. The Text Tones also replace the prior options, with those older sounds moved to the Classic interface. The updated Text Tones can be used for New Voicemail, New Mail, Sent Mail, Calendar Alerts, and Reminder Alerts in addition to texts.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-ringtones-text-tones/">iOS 17 Adds 20+ New Ringtones and Text Tones for Calls, Messages and Alarms</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-adds-20-new-ringtones-and-text-tones-for-calls-messages-and-alarms.2401609/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iOS 17 Includes &#039;Grid Forecast&#039; Feature to Let You Know When &#039;Cleaner&#039; Energy is Available</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-grid-forecast/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-includes-grid-forecast-feature-to-let-you-know-when-cleaner-energy-is-available.2401593/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 14:28:38 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-grid-forecast/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[With the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/apple-releases-ios-17-rc/">iOS 17 release candidate</a> that came out yesterday, Apple added a new "Grid Forecast" section to the Home app. The feature is designed to use your location to tell you when "clean" energy is available to use, so you can be mindful of when you're using energy.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/ios-17-grid-forecast.jpg" alt="" width="3189" height="1794" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-910962" /><br/>
According to Apple, the energy sources that are used to power a home can change throughout the day. When the forecast reads "Cleaner," it means that the available energy sources may have lower carbon emissions. When it reads "Less Clean," available energy sources that are powering the grid may emit more carbon into the atmosphere.<br/>
<br/>
Apple suggests that users can take advantage of this forecast to decide when to use electricity in situations where energy usage can be timed. Choosing to run the washing machine, the dryer, or the dishwasher during the "Cleaner" time will cut down on carbon emissions.<br/>
<br/>
The Grid Forecast is based on each person's location, and Apple says that it is relative to the energy sources available on the grid in a particular place. According to Apple, even in areas with limited renewable generation, relatively cleaner energy may still be available. Apple does not provide information on where its energy information is sourced.<br/>
<br/>
You can get to the Grid Forecast in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a> by opening up the Home app and tapping on the "Energy" option at the end of the top navigation bar. You will see the current energy status and a time when it will shift. A Grid Forecast icon is also available at the top right of the Home app.<br/>
<br/>
Grid Forecast is not a metric that is available in Automations, so it cannot be used to activate smart home devices at select times. The Grid Forecast is available on all Apple devices in the Home app, including <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a>, Apple Watch, and Mac.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-grid-forecast/">iOS 17 Includes &#039;Grid Forecast&#039; Feature to Let You Know When &#039;Cleaner&#039; Energy is Available</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ios-17-includes-grid-forecast-feature-to-let-you-know-when-cleaner-energy-is-available.2401593/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Lossless Audio With Apple Vision Pro Will Be Limited to USB-C AirPods Pro 2</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-vision-pro-lossless-new-airpods-pro-2-only/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lossless-audio-with-apple-vision-pro-will-be-limited-to-usb-c-airpods-pro-2.2401578/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:10:05 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-vision-pro-lossless-new-airpods-pro-2-only/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>AirPods Pro</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Alongside the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15/">iPhone 15</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models, Apple yesterday debuted a new version of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> 2 with a USB-C charging case. The swap to USB-C instead of Lightning is the primary new feature, but Apple also updated audio quality in a way that may upset some of its customers.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/AirPods-Pro-Case-With-USB-C.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-909509" /><br/>
As <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/12/new-airpods-pro-features/">we highlighted yesterday</a>, the new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; feature additional dust resistance and support for 20-bit 48kHz lossless audio when connected to the Vision Pro headset. At the time, it seemed unusual that Apple would limit a key audio feature to the new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 when the original version is just a year old, but that's exactly what Apple has done.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><blockquote class="twitter-tweet"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Apple confirms to Power On: The new Vision Pro lossless audio feature for AirPods requires the second-generation USB-C AirPods Pro announced yesterday and does not work with the second-generation AirPods Pro from last year. <a href="https://t.co/P1UtQa7dqB">https://t.co/P1UtQa7dqB</a> <a href="https://t.co/7aNV0yrLBY">https://t.co/7aNV0yrLBY</a></p>&mdash; Mark Gurman (@markgurman) <a href="https://twitter.com/markgurman/status/1702051324248854913?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 13, 2023</a></blockquote> <script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script> </div><br/>
According to the <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/account/newsletters/power-on">latest PowerOn newsletter</a> from <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a>, Apple confirmed that Lossless Audio will not be available on the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 with Lightning charging case, and it is indeed a feature limited to the new USB-C &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2.<br/>
<br/>
Apple in a press release announcing the &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2 with USB-C charging case touted the new audio feature, calling it the "perfect true wireless solution" for Vision Pro.<blockquote>AirPods Pro (2nd generation) with MagSafe Charging Case (USB‑C) will enable Lossless Audio with ultra-low latency to deliver the perfect true wireless solution with Apple Vision Pro. The H2 chip in the latest AirPods Pro and Apple Vision Pro, combined with a groundbreaking wireless audio protocol, unlocks powerful 20-bit, 48 kHz Lossless Audio with a massive reduction in audio latency.<br/>
<br/>
When Apple Vision Pro is available early next year in the U.S., customers will be able to enjoy the most advanced wireless audio experience in the industry with the new AirPods Pro for exceptional entertainment, gaming, FaceTime calls, and so much more.</blockquote><br/>
Customers who want to be able to use Lossless Audio with Vision Pro for this audio experience will need to purchase the new &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; 2, which are available for &#36;249. The Vision Pro headset itself is set to be priced at &#36;3,500.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#AirPods-Pro">AirPods Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/airpods.216">AirPods</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/apple-vision-pro-lossless-new-airpods-pro-2-only/">Lossless Audio With Apple Vision Pro Will Be Limited to USB-C AirPods Pro 2</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/lossless-audio-with-apple-vision-pro-will-be-limited-to-usb-c-airpods-pro-2.2401578/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Apple ID Sign-In Options: Phone Number on File or Trusted Device</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/new-apple-id-sign-in-options-ios-17/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-id-sign-in-options-phone-number-on-file-or-trusted-device.2401566/</comments>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 11:58:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/new-apple-id-sign-in-options-ios-17/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 17</category>
		<category>macOS Sonoma</category>
		<category>Apple ID</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The upcoming iOS 17, iPadOS 17, and macOS Sonoma updates for the iPhone, iPad, and Mac include a couple of new sign-in methods for an Apple ID account.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/06/iOS-17-Passkey-With-Apple-ID-Feature-3.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-901156" /><br/>
First, it is now possible to sign into an Apple ID with any phone number or secondary email address on file with the account. We were able to sign into an Apple ID with a phone number on the Apple ID website using a Mac running macOS Ventura, so it's unclear if this feature specifically requires the new software updates or is simply a backend change.<br/>
<br/>
Second, starting with an iOS 17 update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/ios-17-features-coming-later-this-year/">coming later this year</a>, there will be a new Apple ID proximity sign-in feature. This will allow you to bring an existing signed-in and trusted iPhone or iPad into proximity with a new device being set up, pair the devices by scanning an on-screen "particle cloud," and complete sign-in automatically.<br/>
<br/>
iOS 17, iPadOS 17, and macOS Sonoma also <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/20/ios-17-macos-sonoma-apple-id-passkey/">added passkey support to Apple IDs</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Apple announced that iOS 17 and iPadOS 17 will be released on Monday, September 18, while macOS Sonoma launches Tuesday, September 26.<div class="linkback">Related Roundups: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-17/">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipados-17/">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macos-sonoma/">macOS Sonoma</a></div><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-id/">Apple ID</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forums: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ios-17.241">iOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipados-17.242">iPadOS 17</a>, <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macos-sonoma.243">macOS Sonoma</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/13/new-apple-id-sign-in-options-ios-17/">New Apple ID Sign-In Options: Phone Number on File or Trusted Device</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-apple-id-sign-in-options-phone-number-on-file-or-trusted-device.2401566/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
