<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MacRumors: Mac News and Rumors - All Stories</title>
	<atom:link href="https://feeds.macrumors.com/MacRumors-All" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://www.macrumors.com</link>
	
	<description>Apple, iPhone, iPad, Mac News and Rumors</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 09:03:12 PDT</lastBuildDate>

	<language>en</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://www.macrumors.com</generator>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Hits New Low Price of &#36;299.99 on Amazon</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-10th-gen-ipad-hits-new-low-price-of-299-99-on-amazon.2427572/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:36:10 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's 10th generation 64GB Wi-Fi iPad has hit a new all-time low price today on Amazon, available for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;299.99</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;349.00. You can also find another record low price on the 256GB Wi-Fi model, and both of these deals <strong>require you to clip an on-page coupon</strong> in order to see the deal price at checkout.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/10th-gen-ipad-new.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951776" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with Amazon. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
For the 256GB Wi-Fi iPad, you can get this tablet for <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"><strong>&#36;449.99</strong></a> in two colors, down from &#36;499.00. Both tablets are available to be delivered as soon as this week, if you are a Prime member (or pay for the fastest delivery option), and early next week otherwise.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><em><strong>Note: You won't see the deal price until checkout.</strong></em></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLCWFNM%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (64GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;299.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLBNNRT%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>10th Gen iPad (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;449.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Apple cut the prices of this iPad lineup earlier in the month, and each model is now &#36;100 cheaper. After this, we quickly saw discounts measuring about &#36;20-&#36;30 on Wi-Fi models, and today marks the first time we've tracked steeper &#36;49 markdowns on the new prices of the 10th generation iPad.<br/>
<br/>
Head to our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to get caught up with all of the latest deals and discounts that we've been tracking over the past week.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/10th-gen-ipad-new-low-price/">Apple&#039;s 10th Gen iPad Hits New Low Price of &#36;299.99 on Amazon</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-10th-gen-ipad-hits-new-low-price-of-299-99-on-amazon.2427572/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Hearing Study Reveals New Insights on Tinnitus</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hearing-study-reveals-new-insights-on-tinnitus.2427570/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 06:02:35 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Apple</category>
		<category>Rumors</category>
		<category>Mac</category>
		<category>iOS</category>
		<category>iPhone</category>
		<category>iPad</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-hearing-study-shares-preliminary-insights-on-tinnitus/">shared an update</a> on the Apple Hearing Study that reveals new insights into the hearing condition tinnitus.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-hearing-study.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-952448" /><br/>
In one of the largest surveys on tinnitus to date, researchers from the University of Michigan examined data from over 160,000 participants using Apple devices. Tinnitus, defined as the perception of sound without an external source, can manifest as ringing, buzzing, or other sounds and can impact quality of life by disrupting sleep, concentration, and clear hearing.<br/>
<br/>
The study found that 77.6% of participants had experienced tinnitus at some point in their lives. The prevalence of daily tinnitus increased with age, with those aged 55 and older being three times more likely to experience it daily compared to younger participants aged 18-34. Male participants reported a slightly higher incidence of daily tinnitus, at 2.7% more than females, but a higher percentage of males stated they had never experienced tinnitus.<br/>
<br/>
Participants reported employing various methods to manage their tinnitus. The most common strategies included using noise machines, listening to nature sounds, and practicing meditation. Regarding the causes of tinnitus, the study highlighted that noise trauma or exposure to excessively high noise levels was the primary reported cause, cited by 20.3% of participants. Apple highlighted several ways in which its devices can help support hearing health:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
  <li><b>Noise app</b>: The Noise app on the Apple Watch can notify users when environmental noise levels may impact their hearing health. The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s Health app tracks a user's history of sound level exposure and indicates if headphone audio or environmental noise levels exceed World Health Organization standards.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Environmental sound levels</b>: Users can view environmental sound levels over the course of a week on the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; and check noise levels in decibels on the Apple Watch, ensuring their exposure remains within safe limits.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Active Noise Cancellation and Loud Sound Reduction mode</b>: Active Noise Cancellation on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-pro/">AirPods Pro</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a> uses built-in microphones to detect and counter external sounds with anti-noise, effectively canceling them before they reach the user's ears. For those who still wish to hear surrounding sounds, the Loud Sound Reduction mode on &zwnj;AirPods Pro&zwnj; (2nd generation) reduces loud noises while maintaining sound quality.</li><br/>
  <li><b>Reduce loud audio</b>: To set a headphone volume limit, users can navigate to Settings, tap "Sounds & Haptics" (on &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 7 and later) or "Sounds" (for earlier models), then tap "Headphone Safety" to enable "Reduce Loud Audio" and adjust the slider to the desired decibel level.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
The Apple Hearing Study, conducted in collaboration with the University of Michigan, seeks to advance understanding of sound exposure and its impact on hearing health. The study has already accumulated approximately 400 million hours of calculated environmental sound levels, supplemented by lifestyle surveys, to analyze how sound exposure affects hearing, stress, and related health aspects. The data collected is also being shared with the World Health Organization as part of its Make Listening Safe initiative. See Apple's <a href="https://www.apple.com/newsroom/2024/05/apple-hearing-study-shares-preliminary-insights-on-tinnitus/">full press release</a> for more information.<br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-hearing-study-reveals-tinnitus-insights/">Apple Hearing Study Reveals New Insights on Tinnitus</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-hearing-study-reveals-new-insights-on-tinnitus.2427570/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Beats Pill Speaker Listed on Apple&#039;s Regulatory Website as Launch Approaches</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-listed-on-apples-regulatory-website-as-launch-approaches.2427568/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:58:09 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[After appearing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">alongside athletes</a> and celebrities, in <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-beats-pill-ios-17-5/">iOS 17.5 code</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/">in the FCC database</a> over the past month or so, a next-generation Beats Pill speaker has now been <a href="https://regulatoryinfo.apple.com/cwt/api/ext/file?fileId=eurocompliance%2FA3211_V1_V0.zip">listed on Apple's regulatory compliance website</a> for Europe.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/New-Beats-Pill-iOS-17.5-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949655" /><em>The new Beats Pill speaker</em></div><br/>
The original Beats Pill was a wireless Bluetooth speaker introduced in 2012, prior to Apple's acquisition of Beats. The speaker received a few updates in its first several years on the market, with the final revision being a redesigned Beats Pill+ with a Lightning charging port, introduced under Apple's ownership in 2015. Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/01/10/beats-pill-discontinued/">discontinued the Beats Pill+ in early 2022</a>, but a new version now appears to be on the horizon.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/beats-pill-f1-daniel-ricciardo.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-949043" /><em>The new Beats Pill speaker</em></div><br/>
The new Beats Pill is likely to feature a USB-C charging port, upgraded Bluetooth, and more. Leaked images revealed a built-in lanyard, which was not available on previous models, along with red, black, and gold color options.<br/>
<br/>
Beats is releasing <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/beats-solo-buds-announced/">new Solo Buds earbuds</a> in June, so perhaps the new Beats Pill will launch next month too, but Apple has yet to formally announce the speaker. The previous Beats Pill+ was originally priced at &#36;229.95 in the U.S. when it launched in 2015, but it had been available for &#36;179.95 prior to being discontinued.<br/>
<br/>
<em>The listing on Apple's regulatory website was spotted by MacRumors contributor <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/author/aaron-perris/">Aaron Perris</a>.</em><div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/new-beats-pill-speaker-on-apple-regulatory-website/">New Beats Pill Speaker Listed on Apple&#039;s Regulatory Website as Launch Approaches</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-listed-on-apples-regulatory-website-as-launch-approaches.2427568/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Green-Lights iPhone 16 Pro Display Production</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-green-lights-iphone-16-pro-display-production.2427561/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:13:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 16 Pro</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>The Elec</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Samsung Display and LG Display have been granted approval for mass production of OLED screens for Apple's upcoming <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a> models, Korea's <a href="https://www.thelec.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=28125"><em>The Elec</em></a> reports. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/Apple-iPhone-15-Pro-lineup-Action-button-230912.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-910375" /><br/>
Both suppliers apparently received approval earlier this month, paving the way for the commencement of mass production of screens for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; models. While Samsung Display will supply OLED screens for all four <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> models, LG Display will supply screens exclusively for the Pro models. Additionally, BOE is expected to help supply OLED displays for the &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; Plus.<br/>
<br/>
The development is particularly noteworthy for LG, which has historically struggled to meet Apple's production deadlines. Last year, LG Display received approval for the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> OLED screens several months after Samsung Display, allowing Samsung to increase its market share and secure higher prices. <br/>
<br/>
Samsung Display is expected to undergo the approval process for the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; Max's OLED screens by the end of this month, with LG Display scheduled to follow in the middle of June. Currently, Samsung Display has received approval for the standard &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; and the &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj;, with the Plus and Pro Max models soon to follow. <br/>
<br/>
<em>The Elec</em> claims that differences between the OLED displays for the &zwnj;iPhone 15 Pro&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 16 Pro&zwnj; are minimal, but the bezels <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/04/iphone-16-even-thinner-bezels/">may be slightly thinner</a> thanks to Border Reduction Structure (BRS) technology. The entire &zwnj;iPhone 16&zwnj; lineup is expected to launch in the fall. <div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16-pro/">iPhone 16 Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-elec/">The Elec</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-16-pro-display-production-greenlit/">Apple Green-Lights iPhone 16 Pro Display Production</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-green-lights-iphone-16-pro-display-production.2427561/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s Next-Gen Chip Technology on Track for 2025 Debut</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025-debut.2427559/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 05:06:34 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>TSMC</category>
		<category>Apple Silicon</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple chip supplier TSMC is on track to deliver 2nm chip technology next year, <a href="https://www.businesskorea.co.kr/news/articleView.html?idxno=217935"><em>BusinessKorea</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/apple-silicon-feature-joeblue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945652" /><br/>
Apple is expected to move its custom silicon to the 2nm process next year to leverage TSMC's advancements. TSMC is said to be confidently progressing with the 2nm node. The chipmaker's Vice President of Process Development, Zhang Xiaogang, announced that "the development of the 2nm process is progressing smoothly" and mass production is on track for 2025.<br/>
<br/>
Some rumors suggested that TSMC may be forced to delay full-scale mass production of its 2nm process until 2026 due to technical challenges associated with the first-time application of Gate-All-Around (GAA) technology. These rumors were dispelled by Zhang, who confirmed that "the yield when applying GAA has reached 90 percent of the target," indicating substantial progress. Jeff Williams, Apple's Chief Operating Officer, recently made a discreet <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-coo-jeff-williams-secures-2nm-chips/">visit to Taiwan</a> to meet with TSMC President Wei Zhejia and secure supply of 2nm chips.<br/>
<br/>
The <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> is powered by the A17 Pro chip, which is manufactured with TSMC's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/3nm/">3nm</a> process. This process allows for more transistors to be packed into a smaller space, delivering improvements in performance and efficiency. Apple's M4 chip, which just debuted in the new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a>, uses an enhanced version of this ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ technology. The transition to 2nm chips should bring further improvements, with projected performance gains of 10 to 15 percent and power consumption reductions of up to 30 percent compared to the ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ process.<br/>
<br/>
TSMC remains the only company capable of manufacturing 2nm and &zwnj;3nm&zwnj; chips at the scale and quality Apple requires. For its ‌&zwnj;3nm&zwnj;‌ chips, Apple booked all of TSMC's available chipmaking capacity, and the chipmaker plans to triple its production capacity for the node by the end of the year to meet soaring demand. 2nm chips could first appear in 2025's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 lineup.<div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/tsmc/">TSMC</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-silicon/">Apple Silicon</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/apple-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025/">Apple&#039;s Next-Gen Chip Technology on Track for 2025 Debut</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-next-gen-chip-technology-on-track-for-2025-debut.2427559/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>OLED MacBook Pro Could Launch as Soon as 2026</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026.2427558/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 04:20:44 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>MacBook Pro 14&quot; &amp;amp; 16&quot;</category>
		<category>OLED</category>
		<category>Omdia</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is "highly likely" to introduce new MacBook Pros featuring OLED displays in 2026, market research firm <a href="https://omdia.tech.informa.com/pr/2024/may/omdia-forecasts-oleds-for-mobile-pc-market-to-grow-37-cagr-by-2031">Omdia</a> claims.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/11/New-MacBook-Pros-Launching-Tomorrow-With-These-4-New-Features-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-921192" /><br/>
According to Omdia's Display long-term demand forecast tracker, demand for OLED displays in mobile devices is projected to grow by 37 percent from 2023 to 2031. This substantial growth reflects a significant shift as many tech companies, including Apple, are increasingly incorporating OLED panels into their high-end notebooks and tablets. Ricky Park, Senior Principal Analyst in Omdia's Display research practice, said:<blockquote>Apple is highly likely to incorporate OLED into its MacBook Pro models as early as 2026. This move could spark a significant surge in OLED demand within the notebook market, potentially reaching over 60 million units by 2031.</blockquote><br/>
<br/>
OLED panels can individually control each pixel, resulting in more precise color reproduction and deeper blacks compared to other common display technologies. They also provide superior contrast, faster response times, better viewing angles, and greater design flexibility. <br/>
<br/>
Apple's move to offer OLED displays on the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> for the first time is projected to triple demand for OLED tablets in 2024 compared to the previous year. The company is expected to bring OLED display technology to most of its tablet lineup, including the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-mini/">iPad mini</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a>. This decision is expected to influence competitors' OLED adoption strategies and drive tablet OLED demand to exceed 30 million units by 2029.<br/>
<br/>
A <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-developing-oled-ipad-mini-for-2026/">report from last week</a> claimed that Samsung has started developing a new 8-inch OLED display panel for the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj;. The same report predicted that Apple would update the &zwnj;iPad mini&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; with OLED technology in 2026. Last year, Samsung was <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/04/macbook-pro-not-getting-oled-until-2026/">rumored</a> to be investing &#36;3.14 billion into its facility in Asan, South Korea to produce OLED panels for upcoming 14-inch and 16-inch MacBook Pro models with OLED displays.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-pro/">MacBook Pro 14 & 16" </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/oled/">OLED</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/omdia/">Omdia</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#MacBook_Pro_16">14" & 16" MacBook Pro (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/macbook-pro.90">MacBook Pro</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026/">OLED MacBook Pro Could Launch as Soon as 2026</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/oled-macbook-pro-could-launch-as-soon-as-2026.2427558/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iPhone Sales Recover in China Amid Surge in Smartphone Demand</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-recover-in-china-amid-surge-in-smartphone-demand.2427556/</comments>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 03:45:37 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>China</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> sales in China surged by 52% in April, reflecting a significant rebound driven by aggressive price cuts and renewed consumer demand, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2024-05-28/apple-s-china-iphone-shipments-jump-52-as-rebound-gains-steam"><em>Bloomberg</em></a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/09/iphone-15-series-store.jpg" alt="" width="2880" height="1620" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-913490" /><br/>
The surge in shipments from 2.3 million units in April 2023 to 3.5 million units in April 2024, revealed in data from the China Academy of Information and Communications Technology (CAICT), follows a series of strategic price reductions from Apple aimed at boosting sales in the region. The &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj;'s recovery in China is part of a broader resurgence in the smartphone market, which saw overall sales rise by 25.5% to 22.7 million units in April. The CAICT data revealed that &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; sales contributed significantly to this growth.<br/>
<br/>
This change comes after a challenging start to the year for Apple in China, where the company experienced a 37% slump in sales during the first two months of 2024. The recovery began in March with a 12% increase in shipments, continuing into April.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's comeback strategy in China involved substantial discounts on iPhones, with price cuts reaching up to 2,300 yuan (approximately &#36;318) on its official Tmall site. These discounts, which are double those initially offered in February, were part of an aggressive campaign to compete with local companies like Huawei. <br/>
<br/>
<em>Bloomberg</em> noted that Apple's market share in China may soon stabilize, as consumer interest in upgrading to new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; is increasing. A recent survey indicated that more than half of Chinese consumers are willing to spend over 4,000 yuan (approximately &#36;550) on their next phone, a significant rise from the 33% who currently use premium handsets. This trend toward "premiumization" is expected to benefit Apple just four months away from the debut of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-16/">iPhone 16</a> lineup.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/china/">China</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/28/iphone-sales-recover-in-china/">iPhone Sales Recover in China Amid Surge in Smartphone Demand</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/iphone-sales-recover-in-china-amid-surge-in-smartphone-demand.2427556/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Says Future iPads Could Feature Landscape Apple Logo</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-future-ipads-could-feature-landscape-apple-logo.2427494/</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 06:31:32 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Pro</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[French website <em>Numerama</em> <a href="https://www.numerama.com/tech/1747904-rencontre-avec-lequipe-design-dapple-lipad-est-une-feuille-de-verre-magique.html">interviewed three senior Apple employees</a> about the new iPad Pro models that launched earlier this month. While the discussion did not reveal many new details, it did mention one potential change for future iPads.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPad-Pro-2024-Space-Black.jpg" alt="" width="1250" height="703" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952407" /><br/>
While the Apple logo on the back of iPads is positioned so that it appears upright in vertical orientation, the devices are often used in landscape orientation with a keyboard attached, which results in the Apple logo appearing on its side. Apple even moved the front camera to the longer right-side edge on the new iPad Pro and iPad Air models, so that it appears at the top-center when the devices are in landscape orientation.<br/>
<br/>
With landscape usage becoming increasingly popular, Apple product designer Molly Anderson said a landscape Apple logo is a possibility on future iPads.<br/>
<br/>
"I think it could change," said Anderson, per a computer translation of the French-language interview. "We are thinking about it. The iPad has long been a product that is used in portrait mode, but we are using it more and more in landscape mode."<br/>
<br/>
On the software side, Apple already began showing the Apple logo that appears when an iPad is booting up in a landscape position starting with iPadOS 14.5, when the device is in landscape orientation. With Apple seemingly open to making the change on the hardware side too, it will be something to look for on future iPads.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Pro">iPad Pro (Buy Now)</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/27/landscape-apple-logo-possible-on-future-ipads/">Apple Says Future iPads Could Feature Landscape Apple Logo</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-says-future-ipads-could-feature-landscape-apple-logo.2427494/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Report: These 10 New AI Features Are Coming in iOS 18</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-these-10-new-ai-features-are-coming-in-ios-18.2427453/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:57:51 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Artificial Intelligence</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[iOS 18 and macOS 15 will offer an array of new AI features such as auto-generated emojis, suggested replies to emails and messages, and more, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">Mark Gurman</a> reports.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/iOS-18-Siri-Integrated-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-945741" /><br/>
A significant portion of Apple's Worldwide Developers Conference (WWDC) is expected to focus on AI features. Writing his latest <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman explained that Apple's AI strategy emphasizes providing practical tools for ordinary users, with new features for core apps like Safari, Photos, and Notes. Apple will apparently use AI to deliver the following new features:<br/>
<br/>
<ul><br/>
	<li>Photo retouching.</li><br/>
	<li>Voice memo transcription.</li><br/>
	<li>Suggested replies to emails and messages.</li><br/>
	<li>Auto-generated emojis based on the content of a user's messages, providing all-new emoji for any occasion beyond the existing catalog.</li><br/>
	<li>Improved Safari web search.</li><br/>
	<li>Faster and more reliable searches in Spotlight.</li><br/>
	<li>More natural interactions with Siri.</li><br/>
	<li>More advanced version of Siri designed for the Apple Watch, optimized for "on-the-go tasks."</li><br/>
	<li>Smart recaps of missed notifications and individual messages, web-pages, news articles, documents, notes, and more.</li><br/>
	<li>Developer tools for Xcode.</li><br/>
</ul><br/>
<br/>
AI features that require less processing power will run entirely on-device, but more demanding tools will operate via the cloud. Apple will apparently tout the privacy advantages of this plan.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is purportedly considering marketing many of its new AI tools as a "preview," at least in beta versions of iOS 18 before its official launch in September, to make it clear that the technology is unfinished.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/artificial-intelligence/">Artificial Intelligence</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/10-ai-features-coming-in-ios-18/">Report: These 10 New AI Features Are Coming in iOS 18</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/report-these-10-new-ai-features-are-coming-in-ios-18.2427453/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Gurman: iOS 18 Will Allow Users to Recolor App Icons and Place Them Anywhere</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/ios-18-to-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-ios-18-will-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons-and-place-them-anywhere.2427450/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 12:22:26 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/ios-18-to-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iOS 18</category>
		<category>Bloomberg</category>
		<category>Mark Gurman</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a> update will introduce new features for further customizing the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a>'s home screen, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">Mark Gurman</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/03/iOS-18-WWDC-24-Feature-2.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-944197" /><br/>
In the latest edition of his <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/newsletters/2024-05-26/apple-ios-18-macos-15-ai-features-project-greymatter-privacy-openai-deal-lwni63s3?srnd=undefined">"Power On" newsletter</a>, Gurman claimed that Apple will allow users to change the color of app icons in &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj;. For example, "you can make all your social icons blue or finance-related ones green." This kind of home screen customization is currently only possible by creating single-action shortcuts with a custom icon that serve to launch an app.<br/>
<br/>
Gurman also corroborated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/24/ios-18-home-screen-app-icon-customization/">previous reports</a> that &zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; will allow users to place apps anywhere on the home screen's grid. This will enable users to arrange icons more freely, similar to how widgets can currently be placed.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;iOS 18&zwnj; is expected to be previewed alongside Apple's other major software updates at WWDC in June, before officially releasing to the public in the fall.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">iOS 18</a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/bloomberg-com/">Bloomberg</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/26/ios-18-to-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons/">Gurman: iOS 18 Will Allow Users to Recolor App Icons and Place Them Anywhere</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/gurman-ios-18-will-allow-users-to-recolor-app-icons-and-place-them-anywhere.2427450/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The Best Memorial Day Apple Deals From Amazon, Anker, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/memorial-day-deals-2024/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-memorial-day-apple-deals-from-amazon-anker-and-more.2427358/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 07:36:23 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/memorial-day-deals-2024/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's Memorial Day weekend, and retailers across the Internet are hosting a wide variety of discount events to honor the holiday and celebrate the unofficial start of summer. In this article, we're tracking discounts on Apple products and related accessories from Amazon, Anker, Eufy, Samsung, Target, and more.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2021/05/Memorial-Day-Deals-2021-Apple.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-801508" /><em><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
If you're looking for discounts on iPads and MacBooks, be sure to check out our post from yesterday that focused on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/best-buys-memorial-day-sale/"><strong>Memorial Day deals from Best Buy</strong></a>. There you'll find record low prices on the 5th generation iPad Air, iPad mini 6, M2 MacBook Air, and M3 MacBook Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Amazon</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/airpods-pro-final-memorial-day-not-again.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952287" /><br/>
Like most other retailers, Amazon's Memorial Day discounts are sitewide discounts across a number of different product categories. In terms of Apple devices, we're tracking steep discounts on Apple Pencil 2, AirPods, Apple Watch, iPad, and MacBook Air, all of which we've collected in the list below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07K1WWBJK%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Pencil 2</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0932QJ2JZ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirTag 4-Pack</a> - &#36;79.00, down from &#36;99.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB07PXGQC1Q%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods 2</a> - &#36;89.00, down from &#36;129.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB08PZJN7BD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">AirPods Max</a> - &#36;449.99, down from &#36;549.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHXCXKPD%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch SE</a> - &#36;189.00, down from &#36;249.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Apple Watch Ultra 2</a> - &#36;714.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">10th gen iPad</a> - &#36;329.00, down from &#36;349.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J9XDMQ%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">11-inch M4 iPad Pro</a> - &#36;949.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CX235DJ6%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">15-inch M3 MacBook Air</a> - &#36;1,199.00, down from &#36;1,299.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Anker</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/anker-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952286" /><br/>
Anker has quite a few discounts this Memorial Day weekend, highlighted by the best price we've ever seen on the popular <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a>, available for &#36;94.99 with an on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99. You'll also find sales on MagSafe-compatible accessories, Bluetooth speakers, Eufy's Bluetooth trackers, and Jackery's best portable power stations.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>Audio</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CDJWTWMB%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3NUAPVI1RMDMY_1710770269976">Soundcore Motion 300 Wireless Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;64.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;79.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BXW5JQ21%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1632VO3MVFX5T_1716561578039">Soundcore Motion X600 Portable Bluetooth Speaker</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;199.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Portable Batteries</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C9D7R1B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.3IQ1Y7SBOA6VQ_1704725913103">Nano Power Bank with Built-In USB-C Cable</a> - &#36;34.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;49.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFDSMNT7%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1QN268QXZWAAI_1716560863385">MagGo Power Bank</a> - &#36;69.99, down from &#36;89.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C812422R%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.RULOQRFTA7IW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.RULOQRFTA7IW_1716560980966">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with Smart Digital Display</a> - &#36;89.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;129.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fgp%2Fproduct%2FB0BYP45YVF%2Fref%3Dox_sc_act_title_1%3Fsmid%3DA294P4X9EWVXLJ%26psc%3D1">Prime Power Bank 20,000 mAh with 100W Charging Base</a> - &#36;149.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;184.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Power Stations</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BV23LTXZ%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10G3BZB00CFWS_1713191978237">Portable Power Station with Smart Display + Retractable Light</a> - &#36;94.99 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB09TT8GZK9%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.HZBHG58DP8H0_1709134987908">3-in-1 MagSafe Charging Cube</a> - &#36;129.99, down from &#36;149.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-A1780-Power-Storage%2Fdp%2FB09XM7WDZ2%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">SOLIX F2000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;1,299.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Wall Chargers</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Durable-Compact-Included%2Fdp%2FB099F558S1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">20W USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;13.99, down from &#36;16.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-Pixelbook-ThinkPad%2Fdp%2FB09Q52CXX1%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">100W 3-Port USB-C Charger</a> - &#36;54.99, down from &#36;74.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charging-Station-Undetachable-Extension%2Fdp%2FB0C7B4W2BV%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">6-in-1 Nano Charging Station</a> - &#36;49.49, down from &#36;65.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Charger-Compact-MacBook-Pixelbook%2Fdp%2FB0C4YTB56H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">Prime 67W 3-Port Charger</a> - &#36;49.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;65.99</li></ul><br/>
<h3>Hubs</h3><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-Transfer-Extended-Charging-Supported%2Fdp%2FB0CCDZWH5H%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp%26th%3D1">4-Port USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;15.99, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2FAnker-MacBook-Docking-Station-Thinkpad%2Fdp%2FB0BNZ5TCG8%3Fref_%3Dast_sto_dp">10-in-1 USB-C Hub</a> - &#36;48.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;149.99</li></ul> <br/>
<br/>
<h2>Eufy</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/eufy-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952285" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8GDXPBL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659902126">SmartTrack Link 1-Pack</a> - &#36;15.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;19.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BNVFJMZR%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659917907">SmartTrack Link 2-Pack</a> - &#36;29.88, down from &#36;35.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BN86R2HC%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.F587O4DYC8XW_1714659964727">SmartTrack Link 4-Pack</a> - &#36;48.99 for Prime members, down from &#36;69.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Jackery</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/jackery-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952284" /><br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CGZW67B6%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.10O5COWGT763L%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.10O5COWGT763L_1716561314983">Solar Generator 300 Plus</a> - &#36;499.00, down from &#36;579.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CFVCRJVL%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.38CAJRZQHR09X%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.38CAJRZQHR09X_1716561100304">Expansion Battery Pack 1000 Plus</a> - &#36;509.00, down from &#36;799.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB083KBKJ8Q%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.1SRZF4G375BAG%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.1SRZF4G375BAG_1716561130143">Explorer 1000 Portable Power Station</a> - &#36;619.00, down from &#36;999.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0B8ZLZ53M%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_title">Explorer 2000 PRO</a> - &#36;1,199.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;1,899.00</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0C6DP7VXX%3Fref%3Dt_ac_view_request_product_image%26campaignId%3Damzn1.campaign.38AJN54G12SMN%26linkCode%3Dtr1%26tag%3Dweeno%26linkId%3Damzn1.campaign.38AJN54G12SMN_1716561156077">Solar Generator 4000 Kit</a> - &#36;3,999.00 with on-page coupon, down from &#36;4,999.00</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Target</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/target-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952336" /><br/>
Target is joining in on the Memorial Day deals with its <a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ4heCNkA">"Hello Summer" sale</a>, set to last through Monday, May 27. This event has sitewide savings on everything from food and drinks to TVs and soundbars, which we've highlighted in a list below.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ0eYlyQ4">TCL 40-inch LED Smart TV</a> - &#36;149.99, down from &#36;199.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmkcEPEsJlc">Westinghouse 43-inch 4K Ultra HD Smart Roku TV</a> - &#36;199.99, down from &#36;259.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmkcDWZHtP3">Westinghouse 50-inch 4K Ultra HD Smart Roku TV</a> - &#36;229.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmkcF8T4Hqw">Roku 50-inch 4K LED Smart TV</a> - &#36;249.99, down from &#36;279.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ0ZEtIS5">Westinghouse 55-inch 4K Ultra HD Smart Roku TV</a> - &#36;259.99, down from &#36;309.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQZFUtseX">Samsung 65-inch UHD 4K Smart TV</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;529.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ32h8x98">LG 50-inch 4K UHD TV</a> - &#36;399.99, down from &#36;599.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ3o41ngg">Vizio 50-inch 4K HDR Smart TV</a> - &#36;499.99, down from &#36;549.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ2AKqqCi">LG 75-inch 4K UHD Smart TV</a> - &#36;899.99, down from &#36;949.99</li><br/>
<li><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ1VliHKh">LG 77-inch 4K OLED UHD TV</a> - &#36;2,199.99, down from &#36;2,999.99</li></ul><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/samsung-memorial-day.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952283" /><br/>
Samsung is hosting a new <a href="https://howl.me/cmh331qhSPn">"Discover Samsung" sale</a> this week, which includes discounts on multiple product lines sitewide. The popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor and Smart Monitor M8 are both discounted during this sale, but you'll also find sales on storage, audio, TVs, smartphones, and home appliances.<br/>
<br/>
As with previous sales, the highlight of the new event is the 27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for <a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"><strong>&#36;899.99</strong></a>, down from &#36;1,599.99. At &#36;700 off this is an all-time low price on the 2023 display, which has a matte display, modular 4K SlimFit camera, and support for Thunderbolt 4.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung's 27-inch Smart Monitor M8 is also being discounted during this sale, available for <a href="https://howl.me/cmcXSeRCgzw"><strong>&#36;349.99</strong></a> in Warm White, down from &#36;699.99. This is a 4K smart monitor with a design that looks similar to the iMac line, and this is another record low price.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXSeRCgzw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;350 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
The Discover Samsung Summer Sale is set to run through this Sunday, May 26, so be sure to browse all of the deals this week before anything expires. Remember that this sale is sitewide and you can save on many more devices, including TVs, Galaxy devices, <a href="https://howl.me/cmh4mcpiYhQ">household appliances, and more</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Be sure to visit our full <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Deals Roundup</a> to shop for even more Apple-related products and accessories.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/memorial-day-deals-2024/">The Best Memorial Day Apple Deals From Amazon, Anker, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-best-memorial-day-apple-deals-from-amazon-anker-and-more.2427358/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Top Stories: iOS 17.5.1 Fixes Concerning Photos Bug, All-New iPhone 17 Model Rumored, and More</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/top-stories-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug-fix/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-5-1-fixes-concerning-photos-bug-all-new-iphone-17-model-rumored-and-more.2427355/</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 06:00:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/top-stories-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug-fix/</guid>
		<dc:creator>MacRumors Staff</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Top Stories</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[It's been quite a week of Apple news and rumors, ranging from a concerning bug with deleted photos reappearing on users' devices to hot rumors about a new high-end iPhone model for 2025 and a MacBook with a foldable screen coming as soon as 2026.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/top-stories-25may2024.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="900" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952329" /><br/>
Other news and rumors this week included fresh expectations for iOS 18 features and new headphones from Sonos to compete head-to-head with AirPods Max, so read on below for all the details on these stories and more!<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Releases iOS 17.5.1 With Fix for Concerning Photos Bug</h2><br/>
Apple <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">released iOS 17.5.1 for the iPhone</a> this week, and the software update <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/apple-releases-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug/">includes a fix for a concerning bug</a> that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/ios-17-5-bug-deleted-photos-reappear/">caused deleted photos to reappear in the Photos app</a> for some users. iPadOS 17.5.1 and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/apple-releases-tvos-17-5-1/">tvOS 17.5.1</a> were also released with the same fix for those devices. <br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iOS-17.5.1-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951676" /><br/>
"This update provides important bug fixes and addresses a rare issue where photos that experienced database corruption could reappear in the Photos library even if they were deleted," explained Apple, in the release notes for the iOS 17.5.1 update. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-explains-resurfaced-deleted-photos-bug/">Apple has since explained</a> that the issue was a result of corrupted local database entries. The issue did not involve iCloud syncing and Apple never had access to the deleted photos.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPhone 17 Lineup Rumored to Feature All-New Slim Model Above Pro Max With 'Major Redesign'</h2><br/>
<em>The Information</em> last week reported that <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/slimmer-iphone-17-major-redesign-rumor/">Apple plans to release an all-new, high-end iPhone 17 model</a> next year that sits above the Pro Max model.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/iPhone-17-Plus-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952009" /><br/>
The device will allegedly feature a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/slim-iphone-17-top-center-cameras-rumor/">"major redesign" akin to the iPhone X</a>, and this is said to include a "significantly thinner" chassis and a narrower Dynamic Island. In addition, the rear cameras might be relocated from the top-left corner of the device to the "top center," the report said. Dan and Hartley discussed the developments and other topics on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim/">this week's episode of The MacRumors Show</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>18.8-Inch MacBook With Nearly 'Crease-Free' Foldable Screen Rumored</h2><br/>
Apple is <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">developing a MacBook with a foldable screen that is "as crease-free as possible,"</a> according to supply chain analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. The device is rumored to be released as early as 2026.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/10/space-black-mbp.jpg" alt="" width="1600" height="902" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-919458" /><br/>
This new MacBook model would be <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/23/18-8-inch-foldable-macbook-rumor/">equipped with around an 18.8-inch screen</a>, according to display industry expert Ross Young. Kuo expects the device to be powered by an M5 chip, which Apple has yet to announce.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iOS 18 to Use AI to Summarize Notifications, Add to Calendar, and More</h2><br/>
iPhones running iOS 18 will be able to <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/19/ios-18-to-use-ai-to-summarize-notifications/">auto-summarize notifications and auto-populate calendar entries</a>, according to <em>Bloomberg</em>'s Mark Gurman. These features will be two of the many widely-rumored AI capabilities <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ios-18/">coming with iOS 18</a>, which will be unveiled during Apple's WWDC keynote <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/03/26/apple-announces-wwdc-2024/">on June 10</a>.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/Apple-Silicon-AI-Optimized-Feature-Siri-1.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-947754" /><br/>
We recently shared a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/30/ios-18-rumor-recap-for-apps/">list of more than 15 Apple apps</a> that are rumored to gain new AI features on iOS 18.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Hands-On With the New Sonos 'Ace' Headphones</h2><br/>
Move aside <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>, you've got competition.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/sonos-ace-headphones.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1125" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-951709" /><br/>
The popular speaker brand <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">Sonos this week unveiled its first-ever headphones</a>. The over-ear Sonos Ace feature active noise cancellation, support for lossless audio and spatial audio, up to 30 hours of battery life per charge, a USB-C charging port, and more. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">Watch our hands-on video</a> to learn more about the headphones, which launch in the U.S. on June 5 for &#36;449.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>iPad 10 vs. iPad Air Buyer's Guide: Is the &#36;250 Difference Worth It?</h2><br/>
One of our latest buyer's guides <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air/">compares the new sixth-generation iPad Air to the tenth-generation entry-level iPad</a>, which now starts at &#36;349.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/10/iPad-10-vs-Air-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1126" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-870500" /><br/>
Is it worth spending an extra &#36;250 to buy the new iPad Air instead of the iPad 10? <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air/">Find out</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Also, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-air-vs-ipad-pro/">check out our guide</a> comparing the new iPad Pro models with the M4 chip to the new iPad Air models.<br/>
<br/>
<h3>MacRumors Newsletter</h3><br/>
Each week, we publish an email newsletter like this highlighting the top Apple stories, making it a great way to get a bite-sized recap of the week hitting all of the major topics we've covered and tying together related stories for a big-picture view.<br/>
<br/>
So if you want to have <a href="https://mailchi.mp/macrumors/may-23-2024">top stories</a> like the above recap delivered to your email inbox each week, <b><a href="http://eepurl.com/OHdUX">subscribe to our newsletter</a></b>!<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/top-stories/">Top Stories</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/25/top-stories-ios-17-5-1-photos-bug-fix/">Top Stories: iOS 17.5.1 Fixes Concerning Photos Bug, All-New iPhone 17 Model Rumored, and More</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/top-stories-ios-17-5-1-fixes-concerning-photos-bug-all-new-iphone-17-model-rumored-and-more.2427355/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple&#039;s M4 iMac: What to Expect</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-imac/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-imac-what-to-expect.2427321/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:21:21 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-imac&#038;post_date=1716596481/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>iMac</category>
		<category>M4 iMac</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple is planning to refresh the 24-inch <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a> as soon as 2024, so we could see a new model with an M4 chip before the end of the year. Apple is working to overhaul the entire Mac line with AI-focused M4 chips, &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; included.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/M4-iMac-Feature-Teal.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946085" /><br/>
This guide includes everything we know about Apple's plans for an M4 &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="m4_chip">M4 Chip</h2><br/>
The next-generation 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is expected to get the M4 chip, which is the same chip that Apple used for the latest <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models. iMacs right now have the M3 chip, so the M4 will be a direct update.<br/>
<br/>
The M4 is built on the same 3-nanometer technology as the M3, but it is a second-generation chip with some speed and efficiency improvements. In a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/10/m4-ipad-pro-cpu-benchmark/">Geekbench benchmark test</a>, the M4 proved to be up to 25 percent faster than the M3 chip, which is a notable jump in performance.<br/>
<br/>
The M3 had a single-core score of 3,087 and a multi-core score of 11,702, while the M4 had a single-core score of 3,695 and a multi-core score of 14,550.<br/>
<br/>
Apple's M4 chip has a 10-core CPU and a 10-core GPU, featuring six efficiency cores and four performance cores. There is a variant of the M4 with a 9-core CPU that Apple has used in the &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;, but it is unlikely that this chip would be offered in the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
Other Macs will get upgraded M4 Pro, M4 Max, and M4 Ultra chips, but the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is an entry-level product on par with devices like the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/macbook-air/">MacBook Air</a>, so it will only be offered with the M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="design">Design</h2><br/>
Apple last redesigned the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; in 2021, and there are no signs that a new look is on the horizon. It's likely that the 2024 refresh of the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; will focus on the internals rather than any outward-facing design changes.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/04/imac-pink.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-946010" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; is an all-in-one machine that combines a computer and a display. It measures in at just 11.5mm thick, and has a slim profile that fits easily on a desktop. It comes in a range of bright colors, with a matching chin in a pastel color.<br/>
<br/>
So far, we don't know of any updates coming to the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; except for the M4 chip.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="larger_imac">Larger iMac?</h2><br/>
There have been persistent rumors of a <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/06/26/imac-with-over-30-inch-display/">larger-screened iMac</a> that has a display that's around 30 inches in size, but that device was still in the early stages of development in mid-2023, and there is no word on when a larger &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; might come out.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/12/iMac-Pro-Mock-Graphic-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2250" height="1266" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-877852" /><br/>
There is a possibility that we could <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/17/32-inch-imac-coming-in-2025/">see it sometime in 2025</a>, but it won't be coming in 2024. Apple this year will stick to the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj;, as it has done since discontinuing the 27-inch model in 2022.<br/>
<br/>
<h2 id="release_date">Release Date</h2><br/>
Back in April, <em>Bloomberg</em>'s <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/mark-gurman/">Mark Gurman</a> said that the 24-inch &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; would likely see an M4 chip update "around the end of the year." Apple sometimes holds events in October or November when new Macs are expected, so we could see the &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; around that timeframe.<br/>
<br/>
Apple is also expected to update the MacBook Pro models and the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/mac-mini/">Mac mini</a> before the end of the year. The &zwnj;iMac&zwnj; was last updated in October 2023, so an October 2024 launch would come right at the year mark.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/imac/">iMac</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iMac">iMac (Neutral)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/imac.91">iMac</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m4-imac/">Apple&#039;s M4 iMac: What to Expect</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apples-m4-imac-what-to-expect.2427321/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Apple Now Selling Refurbished iPhone 14 Models</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-now-selling-refurbished-iphone-14-models/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-iphone-14-models.2427309/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:15:56 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-now-selling-refurbished-iphone-14-models/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>iPhone 14</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple today added refurbished <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a>, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro, and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max devices to its <a href="https://www.apple.com/shop/refurbished/iphone/iphone-14-iphone-14-pro-iphone-14-pro-max">online store for refurbished products</a>, offering the prior-generation iPhones at a discount for the first time since their 2022 launch.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2023/03/Apple-iPhone-14-color-lineup-feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-888160" /><br/>
The &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; is available starting at &#36;619, the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro is available starting at &#36;759, and the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max is available starting at &#36;849. Apple does not have any available &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus devices at the current time.<br/>
<br/>
Apple first released the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models in September 2022, and has since discontinued the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max. These devices have been replaced with the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-15-pro/">iPhone 15 Pro</a> models. Apple still sells the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Plus starting at &#36;699 and &#36;799, respectively.<br/>
<br/>
There are several configurations and colors of the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj;, &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro, and &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro Max available for purchase. &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; models are available with up to 256GB of storage, while the &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; Pro models are available with up to 1TB of storage, with more of a discount available for the higher-capacity models.<br/>
<br/>
Stock will fluctuate over time as Apple refreshes the devices that are available, so you may need to check back if you're looking for a refurbished &zwnj;iPhone 14&zwnj; in a specific color or capacity.<br/>
<br/>
All refurbished iPhones from Apple are unlocked and can be used with any carrier. Apple outfits refurbished <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> models with new batteries, outer shells, and a fresh USB-C to Lightning cable, so they are basically identical to new in the box iPhones.<br/>
<br/>
Apple also offers the same one-year warranty on refurbished &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; models that it provides for new devices, and there is option to purchase extended <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/applecare/">AppleCare</a>+ coverage.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/iphone-14/">iPhone 14</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/iphone.99">iPhone</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/apple-now-selling-refurbished-iphone-14-models/">Apple Now Selling Refurbished iPhone 14 Models</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/apple-now-selling-refurbished-iphone-14-models.2427309/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Best Apple Deals of the Week: iPads and Apple Watches See Record Low Prices Alongside Samsung Monitors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-24-24/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-ipads-and-apple-watches-see-record-low-prices-alongside-samsung-monitors.2427304/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 10:23:13 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-24-24/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Mitchel Broussard</dc:creator>
		<category>Deals</category>
		<category>Featured</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[This week began with a sitewide sale on Samsung that will end this Sunday, and continued with great discounts on the M4 iPad Pro, 10th generation iPad, Apple Watch SE, and Apple Watch Ultra 2.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2022/06/Hero0013.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-848004" /><small>Note: MacRumors is an affiliate partner with some of these vendors. When you click a link and make a purchase, we may receive a small payment, which helps us keep the site running.</small></em><br/>
<br/>
<h2>Samsung</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/samsung-viewfinity-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952118" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Save on Samsung's best monitors and TVs</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT">Samsung</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/20/samsung-new-summer-sale/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXUnrrsdT"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;700 OFF</div>27-inch ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor for &#36;899.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmcXSeRCgzw"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;350 OFF</div>27-inch Smart Monitor M8 for &#36;349.99</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ6E1Fzxk"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;1,300 OFF</div>The Frame 85-inch QLED 4K TV for &#36;2,999.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Samsung marked down a collection of monitors and TVs earlier in the week, with notable deals on the popular ViewFinity S9 5K Smart Monitor (&#36;700 off) and Smart Monitor M8 (&#36;350 off). The best TV deal can be <a href="https://howl.me/cmjQ6E1Fzxk">found on The Frame TV</a>, which has up to &#36;1,300 off select models this weekend.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>M4 iPad Pro</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/m4-ipad-pro-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952117" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;50 off the 11-inch M4 iPad Pro</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/record-low-prices-m4-ipad-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0D3J6L2ZC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;49 OFF</div>M4 11-inch iPad Pro (256GB Wi-Fi) for &#36;949.99</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon returned this week with a match of the record low price on the brand new 11-inch iPad Pro. You can get the 256GB Wi-Fi model for &#36;949.99, down from &#36;999.00 with this discount.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>10th Gen iPad</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/10th-gen-ipad-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952116" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get up to &#36;40 off the 10th generation iPad</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/record-low-prices-m4-ipad-pro/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLXMVMV%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;20 OFF</div>64GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;329.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDDCGS%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;25 OFF</div>256GB Wi-Fi iPad for &#36;474.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJLDWX34%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;30 OFF</div>64GB Cellular iPad for &#36;469.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0BJM15LXC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1%26psc%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;40 OFF</div>256GB Cellular iPad for &#36;609.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
In another iPad sale, Amazon has a few 10th generation iPads at record low prices this week. Apple cut the prices of this lineup earlier in May, and each model is now &#36;100 cheaper.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch SE</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-se-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952115" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;60 off the Apple Watch SE</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX8RVB8%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (40mm GPS) for &#36;189.00</div></a></div><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX3GRK2%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26th%3D1%26geniuslink%3Dtrue"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;60 OFF</div>Apple Watch SE (44mm GPS) for &#36;219.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Amazon discounted the Apple Watch SE by &#36;60 this week in multiple configurations, starting at &#36;189.00 for the 40mm GPS model and increasing to &#36;219.00 for the 44mm GPS model.<br/>
<br/>
<h2>Apple Watch Ultra 2</h2><br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/apple-watch-ultra-blue.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952114" /><br/>
<ul><li><strong>What's the deal?</strong> Get &#36;85 off the Apple Watch Ultra 2</li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I get it?</strong> <a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1">Amazon</a></li><br/>
<li><strong>Where can I find the original deal?</strong> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/22/apple-watch-se-for-just-189/">Right here</a></li></ul><br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?TSID=3088&GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.com%2Fdp%2FB0CHX76WNC%3Ftag%3Dmacrumors-20%26linkCode%3Dogi%26th%3D1"target="_blank"><div class="fancybutton"><div class="fancybadge">&#36;85 OFF</div>Apple Watch Ultra 2 for &#36;714.00</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
Finally, you can also get the Apple Watch Ultra 2 at an all-time low price this week on Amazon. The model with the Green/Grey Trail Loop in S/M is on sale for &#36;714.00, down from &#36;799.00.<br/>
<br/>
Keep up with all of this week's best discounts on Apple products and related accessories in our dedicated <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals roundup</a>.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/best-apple-deals/">Apple Deals</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-5-24-24/">Best Apple Deals of the Week: iPads and Apple Watches See Record Low Prices Alongside Samsung Monitors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/best-apple-deals-of-the-week-ipads-and-apple-watches-see-record-low-prices-alongside-samsung-monitors.2427304/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>MacRumors Giveaway: Win a New M2 iPad Air, Apple Pencil Pro and Rock Paper Pencil Kit From Astropad</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-new-m2-ipad-air-apple-pencil-pro-and-rock-paper-pencil-kit-from-astropad.2427296/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:02:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>Giveaway</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[For this week's giveaway, we've teamed up with <a href="https://astropad.com/">Astropad</a> to offer <em>MacRumors</em> readers a chance to win one of Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/m2/">M2</a> <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> models, an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/apple-pencil/">Apple Pencil</a> Pro, and an <a href="https://astropad.com/product/rock-paper-pencil/">Astropad Rock Paper Pencil kit</a> to go with it.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-1.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952167" /><br/>
<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/21/astropad-rock-paper-pencil-2/">We've highlighted</a> the Rock Paper Pencil before, because it's the best way to mimic the feel of writing on paper with an <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> and an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj;. The Rock Paper Pencil is a screen protector and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; tip combo with a distinctly paper-like feel that you can't get from the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s display alone.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-2.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952168" /><br/>
When Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> and &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; models came out, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/15/astropad-rock-paper-pencil-ipad-pro/">Astropad confirmed</a> that the Rock Paper Pencil works perfectly with the new tablets and the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro. The kit includes a removable screen protector in a variety of sizes to fit the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; you have, plus an &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; tip that can be swapped out with the tip that comes with the &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; 2 or &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-3.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952169" /><br/>
The NanoCling Screen Protector is designed to attach to the &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;'s display using static cling, so you can put it on and take it right off when it's not needed, with no adhesive residue to worry about. The Pencil tip has a wear-resistant copper alloy core and a palladium coating that is able to hold up to heavy daily use. It's designed to be equivalent to a standard 0.7mm ballpoint pen, which makes it ideal for note taking and sketching.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-4.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952170" /><br/>
Writing or drawing on an &zwnj;iPad&zwnj; feels distinctly different from writing or drawing with a paper and a pen, and Rock Paper Pencil does a great job at making you forget you're using a tablet. It feels like writing on paper, and as a recent customer video montage demonstrates, it also <em>sounds</em> like writing on paper.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe title="Feels like paper, SOUNDS like paper! &#x1f4dd; Rock Paper Pencil for iPad" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kc_JE1vIybI" width="486" height="864" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></div><br/>
Astropad ships the Rock Paper Pencil with two pencil tips and a protective storage sleeve so you can store the screen protector whenever it's not being used.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-5.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952171" /><br/>
Rock Paper Pencil is &#36;40 and you can <a href="https://shop.astropad.com/collections/shop-astropad/products/rock-paper-pencil">get it from the Astropad website</a>. The 13-inch version is compatible with the 13-inch ‌&zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;‌ and ‌&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;‌, while there are separate versions for the 11-inch ‌&zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;‌ and the 11-inch ‌&zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj;‌.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/rock-paper-pencil-7.jpg" alt="" width="1920" height="1080" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952172" /><br/>
We have one Rock Paper Pencil set to give away to a lucky <em>MacRumors</em> reader, and it will come with a new &zwnj;M2&zwnj; &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;Apple Pencil&zwnj; Pro. To enter to win, use the widget below and enter an email address. Email addresses will be used solely for contact purposes to reach the winner(s) and send the prize(s). You can earn additional entries by subscribing to our <a href="https://my.leadpages.net/leadbox/145ef7173f72a2%3A104a9fa76b46dc/5754903989321728/">weekly newsletter</a>, subscribing to our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/user/macrumors">YouTube channel</a>, following us on <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumors">Twitter</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/macrumors/">Instagram</a>, following us on <a href="https://www.threads.net/@macrumors">Threads</a>, or visiting the <em>MacRumors</em> <a href="https://www.facebook.com/MacRumors">Facebook page</a>.<br/>
<br/>
Due to the complexities of international laws regarding giveaways, only <strong>U.S. residents who are 18 years or older, UK residents who are 18 years or older, and Canadian residents (excluding Quebec) who have reached the age of majority in their province or territory are eligible to enter</strong>. All federal, state, provincial, and/or local taxes, fees, and surcharges are the sole responsibility of the prize winner. To offer feedback or get more information on the giveaway restrictions, please refer to <a href="http://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaways-why-are-they-only-open-to-u-s-residents.1918337/">our Site Feedback section</a>, as that is where discussion of the rules will be redirected.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a class="e-widget no-button" href="https://gleam.io/uuP5O/astropad-giveaway" rel="nofollow">Astropad Giveaway</a><br/>
<script type="text/javascript" src="https://widget.gleamjs.io/e.js" async="true"></script></div>The contest will run from today (May 24) at 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time through 9:00 a.m. Pacific Time on May 31. The winner will be chosen randomly on or shortly after May 31 and will be contacted by email. The winner will have 48 hours to respond and provide a shipping address before a new winner is chosen.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/giveaway/">Giveaway</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/macrumors-giveaway-astropad-ipad-air/">MacRumors Giveaway: Win a New M2 iPad Air, Apple Pencil Pro and Rock Paper Pencil Kit From Astropad</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/macrumors-giveaway-win-a-new-m2-ipad-air-apple-pencil-pro-and-rock-paper-pencil-kit-from-astropad.2427296/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>iFixit Provides Look Inside All-New 13-Inch iPad Air in Teardown Video</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ifixit-13-inch-ipad-air-teardown-video/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-provides-look-inside-all-new-13-inch-ipad-air-in-teardown-video.2427295/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:55:14 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ifixit-13-inch-ipad-air-teardown-video/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Joe Rossignol</dc:creator>
		<category>iPad Air</category>
		<category>iFixit</category>
		<category>Teardown</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[The popular repair website iFixit today shared a <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rJojWO2mE8Q">video teardown</a> of the first-ever 13-inch iPad Air, providing a look inside the device.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rJojWO2mE8Q?si=n2y3UayOdU0r1_LL" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The new iPad Air does not have too many internal changes compared to the previous-generation model. Like the fifth-generation iPad Air, the battery cells continue to have <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/04/02/ipad-air-5-battery-pull-tabs/">adhesive pull tabs</a>, making them easier to remove.<br/>
<br/>
iFixit gave the 13-inch iPad Air a low repairability score of 3/10 due to the display and some other components being difficult to remove.<br/>
<br/>
Apple released <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-announces-ipad-air-models-in-new-11-13-inch/">new 11-inch and 13-inch iPad Air models</a> earlier this month, with key new features including the M2 chip, Wi-Fi 6E support, a landscape front camera, Apple Pencil Pro compatibility, and a few new color options.<div class="linkback">Related Roundup: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air </a></div><div class="linkback">Tags: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ifixit/">iFixit</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/teardown/">Teardown</a></div><div class="linkback">Buyer's Guide: <a href="https://buyersguide.macrumors.com/#iPad-Air">iPad Air (Buy Now)</a></div><div class="linkback">Related Forum: <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/forums/ipad.137">iPad</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ifixit-13-inch-ipad-air-teardown-video/">iFixit Provides Look Inside All-New 13-Inch iPad Air in Teardown Video</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/ifixit-provides-look-inside-all-new-13-inch-ipad-air-in-teardown-video.2427295/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>Prototype iPod Features Apple-Designed Tetris Clone Called &#039;Stacker&#039;</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ipod-prototype-tetris-clone/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prototype-ipod-features-apple-designed-tetris-clone-called-stacker.2427287/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 08:05:00 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ipod-prototype-tetris-clone/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Juli Clover</dc:creator>
		<category>Prototypes</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Apple once designed a Tetris clone called "Stacker," with the game featured on a prototype version of the third-generation iPod. <a href="https://twitter.com/AppleDemoYT">AppleDemoYT</a>, known for sourcing rare prototype devices, shared images and a video of the unreleased iPod.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/q0c6SOP4CCo?si=X19AhLdndRHKfeyN" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe></div><br/>
The iPod in question is a "DVT" device, which means it was a mid-stage prototype that was still in "Design Validation Testing." It has a model number of A1023, which is not a known model number of any version of an iPod Classic, and had custom serial interfacing designed by an Apple engineer.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipod-game-stacker.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952161" /><br/>
The third-generation iPod was manufactured in week 14 of 2003 (over a month before the release of the third-generation iPod), and it was purchased from an electronics recycler in China that sold it as is for parts. The device was non-functional when it was purchased, but was able to boot when the hard drive flex cable was replaced.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipod-3g-dvt.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1500" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952162" /><br/>
The iPod runs a prototype version of iPodOS 2.0, and one of the games is "Stacker." Stacker works a lot like Tetris, where the Tetris pieces are moved from left to right using the scroll wheel. Pieces fall when the middle button is pressed, and the idea is to clear more lines at once to rack up points.<br/>
<br/>
There are other games on the iPod, and all of them have placeholder non-release names, including Block0, Chopper, and Klondike. There's also a battery testing playlist on the device that has classical songs that play in a loop, suggesting Apple used this iPod to test the battery life of the third-generation iPod before it was released.<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/ipod-battery-testing-prototype.jpg" alt="" width="2000" height="1497" class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-952163" /><br/>
AppleDemoYT says that he asked "iPod godfather" Tony Fadell why the Stacker game was not released, and Fadell said that it was because games were added "with a later software release."<br/>
<br/>
Apple did add several games to the iPod 3G over time, including Brick, Solitaire, Parachute, and Music Quiz. In 2006, Apple released games through the iTunes Store that people could purchase for later versions of the iPod, including an official version of Tetris.<br/>
<br/>
Other games available through the iTunes Store included Bejeweled, Mini Golf, Mahjong, Zuma, Cubis 2, and Pac-Man, all of which pre-dated the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/app-store/">App Store</a>.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/prototypes/">Prototypes</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/ipod-prototype-tetris-clone/">Prototype iPod Features Apple-Designed Tetris Clone Called &#039;Stacker&#039;</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/prototype-ipod-features-apple-designed-tetris-clone-called-stacker.2427287/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>The MacRumors Show: iPhone 17 &#039;Slim&#039; Rumors</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim-rumors.2427286/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:50:57 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Featured</category>
		<category>The MacRumors Show</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[On this week's episode of <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/apples-new-flagship-iphone-17-slim/id1602394741?i=1000656646565">The MacRumors Show</a>, we discuss Apple's new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-air/">iPad Air</a> and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad-pro/">iPad Pro</a> models, the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-rumor/">latest rumors</a> about an all new <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/iphone/">iPhone</a> 17 "Slim" model, and the newly announced Sonos Ace over-ear headphones.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lpH7tDAlfLs?si=ngfe-8mBdrzuanw8" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><em><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1">Subscribe to The MacRumors Show YouTube channel</a> for more videos</em></div><br/>
We talk through first impressions of the new &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj; and &zwnj;iPad Pro&zwnj; models, including their pricing and the state of the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/ipad/">iPad</a> lineup as a whole, giving attention to the reduced price of the tenth-generation &zwnj;iPad&zwnj;, which now costs just &#36;349, which is &#36;250 less than the starting price of the &zwnj;iPad Air&zwnj;.<br/>
<br/>
<ul><li><a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/ipad-10-vs-ipad-air/">iPad 10 vs. iPad Air Buyer's Guide: Is the &#36;250 Difference Worth It?</a></li></ul><br/>
<br/>
We also examine the recent wave of <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/06/iphone-17-slim-to-feature-6-55-inch-display/">rumors</a> about the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 "Slim," an all-new &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; model expected to sit above the &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 Pro and &zwnj;iPhone&zwnj; 17 Pro Max in Apple's 2025 smartphone lineup with a higher price tag. The device will <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/slimmer-iphone-17-major-redesign-rumor/">reportedly</a> feature a 6.55-inch display, a significantly thinner design with an aluminum chassis, an "A19" chip, 8GB of RAM, a rear camera array relocated to the center, a 24-megapixel front camera, and a 48-megapixel telephoto camera. Simultaneously, Apple is expected to discontinue its "Plus" model to make way for the "Slim," although it may not actually be called this when it debuts in the fall of next year.<br/>
<br/>
Meanwhile, Sonos just announced its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/hands-on-sonos-ace-headphones/">"Ace" over-ear headphones</a> with active noise cancelation, soundbar integration, a more lightweight design, and longer battery life, so we look at how they compare to the <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/roundup/airpods-max/">AirPods Max</a>. <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a> has <a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow">its own YouTube channel</a>, so make sure you're subscribed to keep up with new episodes and clips:<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><a href="https://www.youtube.com/@themacrumorsshow?sub_confirmation=1"><div class="fancybutton">Subscribe to <em>The MacRumors Show</em> YouTube channel!</div></a></div><br/>
<br/>
You can also listen to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; on <a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/podcast/id1602394741">Apple Podcasts</a>, <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/41XOHIA6w8IxAKJZvrnx90">Spotify</a>, <a href="https://overcast.fm/itunes1602394741">Overcast</a>, or your preferred podcasts app. You can also <a href="https://audioboom.com/channels/5096144.rss">copy our RSS feed</a> directly into your podcast player.<br/>
<br/>
<div class="center-wrap"><iframe id="embedPlayer" src="https://embed.podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/the-macrumors-show/id1602394741?itsct=podcast_box_player&amp;itscg=30200&amp;ls=1&amp;theme=auto" height="450px" frameborder="0" sandbox="allow-forms allow-popups allow-same-origin allow-scripts allow-top-navigation-by-user-activation" allow="autoplay *; encrypted-media *; clipboard-write" style="width: 100%; max-width: 660px; overflow: hidden; border-radius: 10px; transform: translateZ(0px); animation: 2s 6 loading-indicator; background-color: rgb(228, 228, 228);"></iframe></div><br/>
If you haven't already listened to the <a href="hhttps://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/17/the-macrumors-show-qa-special/">previous episode of The MacRumors Show</a>, catch up for our 101st episode special where we answer your questions.<br/>
<br/>
Subscribe to &zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; for new episodes every week, where we discuss some of the topical news breaking here on <em>MacRumors</em>, often joined by interesting guests such as <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/12/the-macrumors-show-matthew-cassinelli/">Matthew Cassinelli</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/23/the-macrumors-show-brian-tong-vision-pro/">Brian Tong</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/02/09/the-macrumors-show-one-week-with-vision-pro/">Quinn Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/24/the-macrumors-show-kevin-nether-talks-iphone-16/">Kevin Nether</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Jared Nelson</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/11/10/the-macrumors-show-apple-gaming-ft-toucharcade/">Eli Hodapp</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/20/the-macrumors-show-luke-miani-talks-future-of-ipad/">Luke Miani</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/13/the-macrumors-show-former-apple-executive-mike-bell/">Mike Bell</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/10/06/the-macrumors-show-sara-dietschy-apple-accessories/">Sara Dietschy</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/09/15/the-macrumors-show-ijustine-talks-iphone-15/">iJustine</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/08/25/the-macrumors-show-iphone-15-jon-rettinger/">Jon Rettinger</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/10/the-macrumors-show-andru-edwards-iphone-ultra/">Andru Edwards</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/26/the-macrumors-show-arnold-kim/">Arnold Kim</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/05/19/the-macrumors-show-ben-sullins-apple-car/">Ben Sullins</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/04/07/the-macrumors-show-marcus-kane-headset-design/">Marcus Kane</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/24/the-macrumors-show-christopher-lawley-talks-ipados/">Christopher Lawley</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/03/10/the-macrumors-show-frank-mcshan-yellow-iphone-14/">Frank McShan</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/02/24/the-macrumors-show-david-lewis-talks-apple-audio/">David Lewis</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2023/01/27/the-macrumors-show-tyler-stalman-new-macs/">Tyler Stalman</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/12/23/the-macrumors-show-apple-2022-jon-prosser-sam-kohl/">Jon Prosser</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/09/02/the-macrumors-show-apple-event-expectations/">Sam Kohl</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/11/09/the-macrumors-show-john-gruber-talks-macos-ventura/">John Gruber</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/10/28/the-macrumors-show-ipados-16-ft-federico-viticci/">Federico Viticci</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/08/26/the-macrumors-show-thomas-frank-talks-productivity/">Thomas Frank</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/21/the-macrumors-show-jonathan-morrison/">Jonathan Morrison</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/07/12/the-macrumors-show-ross-young/">Ross Young</a>, <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/06/21/the-macrumors-show-ian-zelbo/">Ian Zelbo</a>, and <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2022/03/25/the-macrumors-show-rene-ritchie-talks-mac-studio/">Rene Ritchie</a>.<br/>
<br/>
&zwnj;The MacRumors Show&zwnj; is on X <a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow">@MacRumorsShow</a><a href="https://twitter.com/macrumorsshow"></a>, so be sure to give us a follow to keep up with the podcast. You can also head over to <a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-discussion-thread.2383023/">The MacRumors Show</a> forum thread to engage with us directly. Remember to rate and review the podcast, and let us know what subjects and guests you would like to see in the future.<div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/the-macrumors-show/">The MacRumors Show</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim/">The MacRumors Show: iPhone 17 &#039;Slim&#039; Rumors</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/the-macrumors-show-iphone-17-slim-rumors.2427286/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
		<title>New Beats Pill Speaker Spotted in Another Database as Launch Nears</title>
		<link>https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/new-beats-pill-speaker-spotted-database/</link>
		<comments>https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-spotted-in-another-database-as-launch-nears.2427283/</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 07:33:03 PDT</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/new-beats-pill-speaker-spotted-database/</guid>
		<dc:creator>Hartley Charlton</dc:creator>
		<category>Beats</category>
		

		<description><![CDATA[Another regulatory agency has approved Apple's new version of the Beats Pill speaker ahead of its official announcement (via <a href="https://www.91mobiles.com/hub/apple-beats-pill-speaker-comeback-taiwan-ncc/"><em>91mobiles</em></a>).<br/>
<br/>
<img src="https://images.macrumors.com/article-new/2024/05/New-Beats-Pill-iOS-17.5-Feature.jpg" alt="" width="2500" height="1406" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-949655" /><br/>
Following its <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/21/beats-pill-fcc-database/">recent appearance</a> in the United States FCC database, the upcoming Beats Pill speaker has now been spotted on Taiwan's National Communications Commission (NCC) website. The device, carrying the model number A3211, matches the specifications seen in the FCC listing. Certification listings such as these are necessary steps before a product can be brought to market, and their appearance typically signals a launch within weeks.<br/>
<br/>
Images included in the NCC listing provide additional views of the new Beats Pill's design, which retains the familiar pill-shaped aesthetic of its predecessors. The front of the device is entirely covered by the speaker grille with prominent "Beats" branding. There are four physical buttons on the top and a USB-C port is located on the rear. The new model also includes a lanyard hole on the side. The device is expected to be available in three colors: Black, Gold, and Red.<br/>
<br/>
Basketball star <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/04/20/lebron-james-unreleased-beats-pill/">LeBron James</a> and Formula 1 driver <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/02/unreleased-beats-pill-daniel-ricciardo/">Daniel Ricciardo</a> were among the first to be spotted with the new Beats Pill over the past month. These sightings were followed by the speaker's <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/07/apple-beats-pill-ios-17-5/">appearance in the iOS 17.5 Release Candidate</a>. While Apple has not officially announced the new Beats Pill, the multiple certifications and celebrity sightings indicate that its launch is almost certainly very soon. <div class="linkback">Tag: <a href="https://www.macrumors.com/guide/beats/">Beats</a></div><br/>This article, &quot;<a href="https://www.macrumors.com/2024/05/24/new-beats-pill-speaker-spotted-database/">New Beats Pill Speaker Spotted in Another Database as Launch Nears</a>&quot; first appeared on <a href="https://www.macrumors.com">MacRumors.com</a><br/><br/><a href="https://forums.macrumors.com/threads/new-beats-pill-speaker-spotted-in-another-database-as-launch-nears.2427283/">Discuss this article</a> in our forums<br/><br/>]]></description>
		</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
