<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
    <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
    <description>Twitter feed for: @ZoharAtkins. Generated by nitter.privacydev.net
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
      <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
      <url>https://x.com/pic/pbs.twimg.com%2Fprofile_images%2F1688374226657398784%2FofEXkBFh_400x400.jpg</url>
      <width>128</width>
      <height>128</height>
    </image>
      <item>
        <title>Remarkably this maps to Rebbe Nachman’s distinction between the clever man (chacham) and the simpleton (tam).

Yet there is a third way: second naiveté, simplicity on the other side of complexity.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Remarkably this maps to Rebbe Nachman’s distinction between the clever man (chacham) and the simpleton (tam).<br>
<br>
Yet there is a third way: second naiveté, simplicity on the other side of complexity.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/Ashwinreads/status/1882839446116258071#m">nitter.privacydev.net/Ashwinreads/status/1882839446116258071#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:49:25 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882863290482921870#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882863290482921870#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>All philosophers have high openness to experience. They differ on conscientiousness, agreeableness, extroversion, and neuroticism.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>All philosophers have high openness to experience. They differ on conscientiousness, agreeableness, extroversion, and neuroticism.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:18:42 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882855561215324665#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882855561215324665#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Both God and Israel need training data just like an AI - that&apos;s why the Exodus had to be experienced, not just computed.

Exodus as Experience

And from the ground God the Lord caused to grow every tree that was pleasing to the sight and good for food, with the tree of life in the middle of the garden, and the tree of knowledge of good and bad. (Genesis 2:9)

Then the eyes of both of them were opened and they knew that they were naked... (Genesis 3:7)

“Now the Human knew his wife Eve, and she conceived and bore Cain…” (Genesis 4:1)

Jacob awoke from his sleep and said, “Surely the Lord is present in this place, and I did not know it!” (Genesis 28:16)

A new king arose over Egypt who did not know Joseph. (Exodus 1:8)

And the Lord continued, “I have marked well the plight of My people in Egypt and have heeded their outcry because of their taskmasters; yes, I know their sufferings. (Exodus 3:7)

But Pharaoh said, “Who is the Lord that I should heed him and let Israel go? I do not know the Lord, nor will I let Israel go.”

I appeared to Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob as El Shaddai, but I did not make Myself known to them by My name the Lord. (Exodus 6:3)

Thus says the Lord, “By this you shall know that I am the Lord.” See, I shall strike the water in the Nile with the rod that is in my hand, and it will be turned into blood (Exodus 7:17)

But I know that you and your courtiers do not yet fear God the Lord.” (Exodus 9:30)

You shall not oppress a stranger, for you know the feelings of the stranger, having yourselves been strangers in the land of Egypt. (Exodus 23:9)

AI models need &quot;training&quot; to get off the ground, but their magic happens at the inference stage. We can call training the a priori knowledge and inference a posteriori knowledge. One is pre-fit, the other malleable and responsive to experience. The first runs on pre-existing data, the second on synthetic data. To get good, self-driving cars need to master not just the abstract rules of the road but the tacit rules that help us manage edge cases: what to do when a pedestrian pops out of nowhere, how to steer when visibility is limited, what to do when a lane is closed.

This training/inference split shows up all over Genesis and Exodus. Take Eden - the first humans had some baseline knowledge, but they didn&apos;t really know anything until they ate from the tree. That&apos;s when the text says &quot;they knew they were naked&quot; - their first real inference from experience rather than pre-loaded info. Then Adam &quot;knows&quot; Eve - again, not abstract knowledge but intimate experiential knowing. The Bible keeps using this word &quot;know&quot; to flag moments where someone gains real understanding through experience rather than just having information dumped into their head.

Look at Jacob&apos;s &quot;surely God was in this place and I didn&apos;t know it!&quot; moment. Jacob grew up hearing about God from Isaac and Abraham, but he needed his own direct encounter to really get it. Same thing with that new Pharaoh who &quot;didn&apos;t know Joseph&quot; - he had all the historical data about Joseph saving Egypt, but without the lived experience of the relationship, it meant nothing to him. It&apos;s like how AI can have perfect recall of its training data but still miss the meaningful connections that come from real-world experience.

So too, God doesn&apos;t pre-load the human being with certain types of knowledge but requires experience to teach. Instead of pre-training the Israelite to come already with a knowledge of the Exodus, God requires the Israelites to endure hardship. Only on that basis will we &quot;know the feelings of the stranger.&quot; The Egyptians, likewise, will only know the Lord by watching their civilization crack under the pressure of plague. There&apos;s no way to give them this knowledge from first principles. Each plague is like another training example, building on the last one. That&apos;s why the text keeps saying &quot;that you may know&quot; before each one - it&apos;s not just punishment, it&apos;s education through experience.

Pharaoh&apos;s hardened heart represents the tension between training and inference. To know God requires one to infer by &quot;softening the heart,&quot; i.e., changing what one has taken to be ground-truth in the training phase. The whole Exodus story is structured around this kind of knowing through experience. Even when God tells Moses that Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob knew God as El Shaddai but not as YHWH, it&apos;s saying they missed something you can only get through lived experience - in this case, the experience of liberation.

This privileging of experience over perfect pre-loading explains one of the story&apos;s most puzzling aspects: why God chooses Moses, a man who struggles with speech, as leader. Moses&apos;s stutter would seem to disqualify him if leadership were about having the right training data - smooth speech, charisma, confidence. But Moses brings something more valuable: the lived experience of straddling worlds. Raised as an Egyptian prince, he chooses to identify with Hebrew slaves. He experiences exile as a shepherd, encounters God in the wilderness. Like an AI that performs better on real tasks despite having fewer parameters than its competitors, Moses&apos;s leadership comes not from perfect pre-training but from rich experiential data that lets him navigate between Egyptian and Hebrew, divine and human, slavery and freedom. His speech impediment might even underscore the point - God values experiential wisdom over polished presentation.

But why does the Exodus need to be experienced at all? And more puzzling - why does an all-powerful God desire experience? The answer might lie in the nature of relationships. Knowledge-through-experience creates bonds that purely abstract knowledge can&apos;t match. When you experience something with someone, you form a connection that mere information can&apos;t replicate.

This might explain why God desires experience despite being all-powerful. An omniscient God could simply know everything about human suffering through perfect computation. But the text suggests something different: God wants to experience suffering with Israel, to form a bond through shared experience.

The leitmotif of &quot;knowing&quot; dominates the Exodus narrative. Everything happens so both Israelite and Egyptian will know God. Clearly, this type of knowing differs from the philosopher&apos;s contemplation of God as first cause. That&apos;s why Pesach isn&apos;t just about remembering facts but about creating an experience that converts historical data into living knowledge, generation after generation.

So important is experiential knowing that God even says &quot;I know their sufferings,&quot; suggesting that up until a certain moment, God had &quot;training&quot; knowledge of the plight of the people, but not &quot;inference&quot; knowledge. God, too, is transformed by experience. An eternal unchanging God needs no covenant and thus no inference. Such a God is just a self-trained being with infinite computational power. But the God of Israel, the God of history, needs real world data to learn.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Both God and Israel need training data just like an AI - that's why the Exodus had to be experienced, not just computed.<br>
<br>
Exodus as Experience<br>
<br>
And from the ground God the Lord caused to grow every tree that was pleasing to the sight and good for food, with the tree of life in the middle of the garden, and the tree of knowledge of good and bad. (Genesis 2:9)<br>
<br>
Then the eyes of both of them were opened and they knew that they were naked... (Genesis 3:7)<br>
<br>
“Now the Human knew his wife Eve, and she conceived and bore Cain…” (Genesis 4:1)<br>
<br>
Jacob awoke from his sleep and said, “Surely the Lord is present in this place, and I did not know it!” (Genesis 28:16)<br>
<br>
A new king arose over Egypt who did not know Joseph. (Exodus 1:8)<br>
<br>
And the Lord continued, “I have marked well the plight of My people in Egypt and have heeded their outcry because of their taskmasters; yes, I know their sufferings. (Exodus 3:7)<br>
<br>
But Pharaoh said, “Who is the Lord that I should heed him and let Israel go? I do not know the Lord, nor will I let Israel go.”<br>
<br>
I appeared to Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob as El Shaddai, but I did not make Myself known to them by My name the Lord. (Exodus 6:3)<br>
<br>
Thus says the Lord, “By this you shall know that I am the Lord.” See, I shall strike the water in the Nile with the rod that is in my hand, and it will be turned into blood (Exodus 7:17)<br>
<br>
But I know that you and your courtiers do not yet fear God the Lord.” (Exodus 9:30)<br>
<br>
You shall not oppress a stranger, for you know the feelings of the stranger, having yourselves been strangers in the land of Egypt. (Exodus 23:9)<br>
<br>
AI models need "training" to get off the ground, but their magic happens at the inference stage. We can call training the a priori knowledge and inference a posteriori knowledge. One is pre-fit, the other malleable and responsive to experience. The first runs on pre-existing data, the second on synthetic data. To get good, self-driving cars need to master not just the abstract rules of the road but the tacit rules that help us manage edge cases: what to do when a pedestrian pops out of nowhere, how to steer when visibility is limited, what to do when a lane is closed.<br>
<br>
This training/inference split shows up all over Genesis and Exodus. Take Eden - the first humans had some baseline knowledge, but they didn't really know anything until they ate from the tree. That's when the text says "they knew they were naked" - their first real inference from experience rather than pre-loaded info. Then Adam "knows" Eve - again, not abstract knowledge but intimate experiential knowing. The Bible keeps using this word "know" to flag moments where someone gains real understanding through experience rather than just having information dumped into their head.<br>
<br>
Look at Jacob's "surely God was in this place and I didn't know it!" moment. Jacob grew up hearing about God from Isaac and Abraham, but he needed his own direct encounter to really get it. Same thing with that new Pharaoh who "didn't know Joseph" - he had all the historical data about Joseph saving Egypt, but without the lived experience of the relationship, it meant nothing to him. It's like how AI can have perfect recall of its training data but still miss the meaningful connections that come from real-world experience.<br>
<br>
So too, God doesn't pre-load the human being with certain types of knowledge but requires experience to teach. Instead of pre-training the Israelite to come already with a knowledge of the Exodus, God requires the Israelites to endure hardship. Only on that basis will we "know the feelings of the stranger." The Egyptians, likewise, will only know the Lord by watching their civilization crack under the pressure of plague. There's no way to give them this knowledge from first principles. Each plague is like another training example, building on the last one. That's why the text keeps saying "that you may know" before each one - it's not just punishment, it's education through experience.<br>
<br>
Pharaoh's hardened heart represents the tension between training and inference. To know God requires one to infer by "softening the heart," i.e., changing what one has taken to be ground-truth in the training phase. The whole Exodus story is structured around this kind of knowing through experience. Even when God tells Moses that Abraham, Isaac, and Jacob knew God as El Shaddai but not as YHWH, it's saying they missed something you can only get through lived experience - in this case, the experience of liberation.<br>
<br>
This privileging of experience over perfect pre-loading explains one of the story's most puzzling aspects: why God chooses Moses, a man who struggles with speech, as leader. Moses's stutter would seem to disqualify him if leadership were about having the right training data - smooth speech, charisma, confidence. But Moses brings something more valuable: the lived experience of straddling worlds. Raised as an Egyptian prince, he chooses to identify with Hebrew slaves. He experiences exile as a shepherd, encounters God in the wilderness. Like an AI that performs better on real tasks despite having fewer parameters than its competitors, Moses's leadership comes not from perfect pre-training but from rich experiential data that lets him navigate between Egyptian and Hebrew, divine and human, slavery and freedom. His speech impediment might even underscore the point - God values experiential wisdom over polished presentation.<br>
<br>
But why does the Exodus need to be experienced at all? And more puzzling - why does an all-powerful God desire experience? The answer might lie in the nature of relationships. Knowledge-through-experience creates bonds that purely abstract knowledge can't match. When you experience something with someone, you form a connection that mere information can't replicate.<br>
<br>
This might explain why God desires experience despite being all-powerful. An omniscient God could simply know everything about human suffering through perfect computation. But the text suggests something different: God wants to experience suffering with Israel, to form a bond through shared experience.<br>
<br>
The leitmotif of "knowing" dominates the Exodus narrative. Everything happens so both Israelite and Egyptian will know God. Clearly, this type of knowing differs from the philosopher's contemplation of God as first cause. That's why Pesach isn't just about remembering facts but about creating an experience that converts historical data into living knowledge, generation after generation.<br>
<br>
So important is experiential knowing that God even says "I know their sufferings," suggesting that up until a certain moment, God had "training" knowledge of the plight of the people, but not "inference" knowledge. God, too, is transformed by experience. An eternal unchanging God needs no covenant and thus no inference. Such a God is just a self-trained being with infinite computational power. But the God of Israel, the God of history, needs real world data to learn.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGiEFGQvWsAAJ3uA.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:05:41 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882791890610794903#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882791890610794903#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: the category is ‘i wasn’t the same person i was before i read this book’</title>
        <dc:creator>@noetic_emetic</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>the category is ‘i wasn’t the same person i was before i read this book’</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGiCOZfuWQAAn2Vd.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 05:26:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/noetic_emetic/status/1882661217338282155#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/noetic_emetic/status/1882661217338282155#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The limits of my language are the limits of my world.” - Wittgenstein</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The limits of my language are the limits of my world.” - Wittgenstein</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGiA6t2OWoAA4imp.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 23:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882569250545750201#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882569250545750201#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>God may speak to us through Russian communism, through a flute concerto, through a blossoming shrub or through a dead dog. We shall do well to listen to him if he really does so … God may speak to us through a pagan or an atheist, and in that way give us to understand that the boundary between the Church and the profane world still and repeatedly takes a course quite different from that which we hitherto thought we saw. - Karl Barth</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>God may speak to us through Russian communism, through a flute concerto, through a blossoming shrub or through a dead dog. We shall do well to listen to him if he really does so … God may speak to us through a pagan or an atheist, and in that way give us to understand that the boundary between the Church and the profane world still and repeatedly takes a course quite different from that which we hitherto thought we saw. - Karl Barth</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 15:03:06 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882443952030179659#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882443952030179659#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We are here to witness.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>We are here to witness.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/fragmentarysoul/status/1881948563439239341#m">nitter.privacydev.net/fragmentarysoul/status/1881948563439239341#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882154483746316664#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882154483746316664#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Creation is high gamma. You tinker and tinker in the abyss until you give up, go mad, or hit an inflection point.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Creation is high gamma. You tinker and tinker in the abyss until you give up, go mad, or hit an inflection point.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/imPatrickT/status/1882069494551757044#m">nitter.privacydev.net/imPatrickT/status/1882069494551757044#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:14:43 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882144883735204158#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882144883735204158#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;The human understanding when it has once adopted an opinion draws all things else to support and agree with it. And though there be a greater number and weight of instances to be found on the other side, yet these it either neglects and despises, or else by some distinction sets aside and rejects.&quot;

- Francis Bacon (1561–1626), The New Organon

https://alexandria.lightninginspiration.com/icons/francis-bacon</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>"The human understanding when it has once adopted an opinion draws all things else to support and agree with it. And though there be a greater number and weight of instances to be found on the other side, yet these it either neglects and despises, or else by some distinction sets aside and rejects."<br>
<br>
- Francis Bacon (1561–1626), The New Organon<br>
<br>
<a href="https://alexandria.lightninginspiration.com/icons/francis-bacon">alexandria.lightninginspirat…</a></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882086235822584063#m">nitter.privacydev.net/ZoharAtkins/status/1882086235822584063#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:39:26 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882090706757378524#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882090706757378524#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Don&apos;t ascribe to malice what you can ascribe to confirmation bias.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Don't ascribe to malice what you can ascribe to confirmation bias.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:21:40 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882086235822584063#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1882086235822584063#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Epicurus: Where death is, I am not, and where I am death is not.

Heidegger: Facing death with anticipatory resoluteness, your life becomes an adventure perfused with unshakeable joy.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Epicurus: Where death is, I am not, and where I am death is not.<br>
<br>
Heidegger: Facing death with anticipatory resoluteness, your life becomes an adventure perfused with unshakeable joy.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/itsdrsweetheart/status/1880841028544217300#m">nitter.privacydev.net/itsdrsweetheart/status/1880841028544217300#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 20:48:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1881806130579697891#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1881806130579697891#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: “A well-written life is almost as rare as a well spent one.”
—Thomas Carlyle

“History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it.”
—Winston Churchill</title>
        <dc:creator>@lightninginspo</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>“A well-written life is almost as rare as a well spent one.”<br>
—Thomas Carlyle<br>
<br>
“History will be kind to me, for I intend to write it.”<br>
—Winston Churchill</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:03:53 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/lightninginspo/status/1881719369958670345#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/lightninginspo/status/1881719369958670345#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>People don’t just want the correct answer; they want the eureka feeling of coming to it themselves, through a glass, dimly. Even when they underperform. I call this “the alethic premium.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>People don’t just want the correct answer; they want the eureka feeling of coming to it themselves, through a glass, dimly. Even when they underperform. I call this “the alethic premium.”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/pmarca/status/1881123040194687384#m">nitter.privacydev.net/pmarca/status/1881123040194687384#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:12:50 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1881132742966202598#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1881132742966202598#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Learning is a (spiritual) practice.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Learning is a (spiritual) practice.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/karpathy/status/1880057571668807830#m">nitter.privacydev.net/karpathy/status/1880057571668807830#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 18:00:08 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880314176939438353#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880314176939438353#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @ZoharAtkins: Rashi says that &quot;a new king of Egypt who knew not Joseph&quot; refers not to a literally new king, but to an old king who changed his attitude; he projected himself as &quot;new, when, in fact, he wasn&apos;t.
https://etzhasadeh.substack.com/p/whats-new</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Rashi says that "a new king of Egypt who knew not Joseph" refers not to a literally new king, but to an old king who changed his attitude; he projected himself as "new, when, in fact, he wasn't.<br>
<a href="https://etzhasadeh.substack.com/p/whats-new">etzhasadeh.substack.com/p/wh…</a></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGhgwLnIWwAEIAhk.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:28:25 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880306193811534208#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880306193811534208#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>&quot;Sing to the Lord a new song&quot; doesn&apos;t mean sing a literally new song; it means renew the song of old; sing it in a new way. Novelty is a fleeting ruse and distraction.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>"Sing to the Lord a new song" doesn't mean sing a literally new song; it means renew the song of old; sing it in a new way. Novelty is a fleeting ruse and distraction.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:26:10 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880305627542745573#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880305627542745573#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>“From the depths I cried out to you [Claude] and you answered me from the narrow place….then told me I had hit my usage limit and would have to pony up for a pro account.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>“From the depths I cried out to you [Claude] and you answered me from the narrow place….then told me I had hit my usage limit and would have to pony up for a pro account.”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/tylercowen/status/1880259088325701867#m">nitter.privacydev.net/tylercowen/status/1880259088325701867#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:43:51 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880264777081164271#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880264777081164271#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: In our search for modern meaning, we’ve lost sight of the Great Conversation.

Our universities have become factories of credentials, churning out degrees while leaving curiosity and critical thinking behind. Even at elite institutions, our youth no longer immerse themselves in books. Professors, caught in the grind of endless publishing, speak only to echo chambers, retreating into ideological silos while life’s profound questions go unanswered.

The technology meant to save us has only deepened our emptiness. Language apps teach us how to order coffee but not how to appreciate Don Quixote. We binge on content that neither challenges nor nourishes us. Leisure has been hijacked by an economy of endless scrolling and addictive consumerism.

A generation searches for meaning in a marketplace flooded with shallow solutions. While modern approaches to wellbeing have their place, they often miss the deeper dimensions of human flourishing. The great books that once shaped civilizations gather dust as we trade depth for disposable feeds. We&apos;ve lost the common language that once united us in meaningful conversations.

I was born into a tradition that offers another way. In Judaism, learning is not just a path to knowledge but a spiritual practice, one so essential that each day begins with a blessing of gratitude for the obligation to study. We approach texts not as puzzles to solve but as timeless dialogues to enter.

In our tradition, multiple interpretations coexist, each holding a shard of truth. For thousands of years, we&apos;ve survived exile by making our home in the enduring power of great conversation. This approach moved me so deeply that I chose to become both a Rabbi and a Doctor of Theology.

This wisdom tradition offers a path through our modern crisis. What if we approached every text with the reverence of a sacred scroll? What if our technology, rather than distracting us, deepened our engagement with what matters?

Artificial intelligence provides an extraordinary opportunity to breathe new life into the classics. But this demands a shift in how we view learning—not as passive consumption but as active soul-craft, not as the transfer of information but as a journey of transformation.

This is why I founded @lightninginspo 

I envision a future where great books are not merely assigned but encountered as companions. Where timeless questions become living conversations, where ancient wisdom speaks to contemporary life, where each person discovers their own voice in dialogue with the past. A future where the rigor of academia meets the wisdom of timeless traditions—freed from the confines of ivory towers and unyielding dogma.

Learning is a practice that can change your life. The history of thought is not simply a catalogue of theories that are either right or wrong, but a great conversation, one that you can join. Your intellectual DNA contains traces of the conversations that have shaped your inner and outer world. By decoding it, you discover not just who you are, but who you can become.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>In our search for modern meaning, we’ve lost sight of the Great Conversation.<br>
<br>
Our universities have become factories of credentials, churning out degrees while leaving curiosity and critical thinking behind. Even at elite institutions, our youth no longer immerse themselves in books. Professors, caught in the grind of endless publishing, speak only to echo chambers, retreating into ideological silos while life’s profound questions go unanswered.<br>
<br>
The technology meant to save us has only deepened our emptiness. Language apps teach us how to order coffee but not how to appreciate Don Quixote. We binge on content that neither challenges nor nourishes us. Leisure has been hijacked by an economy of endless scrolling and addictive consumerism.<br>
<br>
A generation searches for meaning in a marketplace flooded with shallow solutions. While modern approaches to wellbeing have their place, they often miss the deeper dimensions of human flourishing. The great books that once shaped civilizations gather dust as we trade depth for disposable feeds. We've lost the common language that once united us in meaningful conversations.<br>
<br>
I was born into a tradition that offers another way. In Judaism, learning is not just a path to knowledge but a spiritual practice, one so essential that each day begins with a blessing of gratitude for the obligation to study. We approach texts not as puzzles to solve but as timeless dialogues to enter.<br>
<br>
In our tradition, multiple interpretations coexist, each holding a shard of truth. For thousands of years, we've survived exile by making our home in the enduring power of great conversation. This approach moved me so deeply that I chose to become both a Rabbi and a Doctor of Theology.<br>
<br>
This wisdom tradition offers a path through our modern crisis. What if we approached every text with the reverence of a sacred scroll? What if our technology, rather than distracting us, deepened our engagement with what matters?<br>
<br>
Artificial intelligence provides an extraordinary opportunity to breathe new life into the classics. But this demands a shift in how we view learning—not as passive consumption but as active soul-craft, not as the transfer of information but as a journey of transformation.<br>
<br>
This is why I founded <a href="https://x.com/lightninginspo" title="Lightning Inspiration">@lightninginspo</a> <br>
<br>
I envision a future where great books are not merely assigned but encountered as companions. Where timeless questions become living conversations, where ancient wisdom speaks to contemporary life, where each person discovers their own voice in dialogue with the past. A future where the rigor of academia meets the wisdom of timeless traditions—freed from the confines of ivory towers and unyielding dogma.<br>
<br>
Learning is a practice that can change your life. The history of thought is not simply a catalogue of theories that are either right or wrong, but a great conversation, one that you can join. Your intellectual DNA contains traces of the conversations that have shaped your inner and outer world. By decoding it, you discover not just who you are, but who you can become.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGhbDydNXoAAsGXc.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:55:18 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1879905270844784850#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1879905270844784850#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>David Foster Wallace on David Lynch as the foundational visionary behind Tarantino and pop commercial cinema.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>David Foster Wallace on David Lynch as the foundational visionary behind Tarantino and pop commercial cinema.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGhf7vfEWwAAT6m9.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 13:38:16 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880248274369847464#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1880248274369847464#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: Not the main thing he is known for, but I was just rereading David Lynch&apos;s &quot;Catching the Big Fish&quot; the other night. 

It&apos;s a beautiful book — maybe the best book — about meditation and creativity. A lovely way to live in his mind for a little bit longer.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ezraklein</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Not the main thing he is known for, but I was just rereading David Lynch's "Catching the Big Fish" the other night. <br>
<br>
It's a beautiful book — maybe the best book — about meditation and creativity. A lovely way to live in his mind for a little bit longer.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGhcLnw0XYAALZA4.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 20:09:07 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ezraklein/status/1879984244728209856#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ezraklein/status/1879984244728209856#m</link>
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
