<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
    <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
    <description>Twitter feed for: @ZoharAtkins. Generated by nitter.privacydev.net
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
      <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
      <url>https://x.com/pic/pbs.twimg.com%2Fprofile_images%2F1688374226657398784%2FofEXkBFh_400x400.jpg</url>
      <width>128</width>
      <height>128</height>
    </image>
      <item>
        <title>In the ancient world, literacy was scarce, so wordcels dominated.

Today, literacy is abundant, so imagecels dominate.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>In the ancient world, literacy was scarce, so wordcels dominated.<br>
<br>
Today, literacy is abundant, so imagecels dominate.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 22:26:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894151934182822093#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894151934182822093#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @ZoharAtkins: The revised prompt should be what books are considered great in your field but are actually mid? It’s sort of the inverse of the hidden gem. The overpolished rock.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The revised prompt should be what books are considered great in your field but are actually mid? It’s sort of the inverse of the hidden gem. The overpolished rock.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:59:43 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894145206930338214#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894145206930338214#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>All great books err, but err greatly.
The important distinction is not between right and wrong, helpful and harmful, but great and mid.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>All great books err, but err greatly.<br>
The important distinction is not between right and wrong, helpful and harmful, but great and mid.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/AlecStapp/status/1892977663330988235#m">nitter.privacydev.net/AlecStapp/status/1892977663330988235#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:57:32 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894144656989909475#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894144656989909475#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: Without having clicked thru to read the results, let me immediately offer an annoying anti-anti take

understanding harmful ideas is important! ppl should definitely read the anti-reading list</title>
        <dc:creator>@DKThomp</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Without having clicked thru to read the results, let me immediately offer an annoying anti-anti take<br>
<br>
understanding harmful ideas is important! ppl should definitely read the anti-reading list</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:54:32 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/DKThomp/status/1892981242804502850#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/DKThomp/status/1892981242804502850#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Prompt: Gamify “I would prefer not to”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Prompt: Gamify “I would prefer not to”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/emollick/status/1894096525602574824#m">nitter.privacydev.net/emollick/status/1894096525602574824#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:17:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894119428180078731#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1894119428180078731#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>“AI will boost economic growth rates by half a percentage point a year.  That is very much a guess.  It does mean that, with compounding, the world is very different a few decades out.  It also means that year to year non-infovores will not necessarily notice huge changes in their environments.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>“AI will boost economic growth rates by half a percentage point a year.  That is very much a guess.  It does mean that, with compounding, the world is very different a few decades out.  It also means that year to year non-infovores will not necessarily notice huge changes in their environments.”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/tylercowen/status/1893741949586116648#m">nitter.privacydev.net/tylercowen/status/1893741949586116648#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:18:34 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893817762927067511#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893817762927067511#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @ZoharAtkins: From Alex Karp’s Technological Republic:</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>From Alex Karp’s Technological Republic:</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkfgXEuXQAAptpC.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 18:25:21 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893728872853577772#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893728872853577772#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: This is a fabulous read by @ZoharAtkins on those who retreat from confronting moral ambiguity and psychology of evil-doers. So relevant to campuses, institutional rot, and rampant pernicious or lurking evil.

Small correction: @GadSaad coined &quot;Suicidal Empathy&quot;. Not Rabbi YY Jacobson.</title>
        <dc:creator>@mikeeisenberg</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>This is a fabulous read by <a href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins" title="Zohar Atkins">@ZoharAtkins</a> on those who retreat from confronting moral ambiguity and psychology of evil-doers. So relevant to campuses, institutional rot, and rampant pernicious or lurking evil.<br>
<br>
Small correction: <a href="https://x.com/GadSaad" title="Gad Saad">@GadSaad</a> coined "Suicidal Empathy". Not Rabbi YY Jacobson.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892980432339345870#m">nitter.privacydev.net/ZoharAtkins/status/1892980432339345870#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:39:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/mikeeisenberg/status/1893671908312559738#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/mikeeisenberg/status/1893671908312559738#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: Ingmar Bergman on the creative process</title>
        <dc:creator>@DylanoA4</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ingmar Bergman on the creative process</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkVAnmHWIAEEjkz.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:31:15 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/DylanoA4/status/1892990480071213425#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/DylanoA4/status/1892990480071213425#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Every word.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Every word.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkVNHo5WgAAkIJY.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:25:31 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893004140122423567#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893004140122423567#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Technological Republic is a great read.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The Technological Republic is a great read.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkVLjL0WMAAht8B.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:18:19 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893002328229224629#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1893002328229224629#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Law of the Tunnel
How Torah Confronts Those Who Weaponize Ambiguity

If the thief is seized while tunneling [bamachteret] and beaten to death, there is no bloodguilt in that case. If the sun had already risen, there is bloodguilt in that case [The thief] must make restitution, and if lacking the means, shall be sold for the theft. (Exodus 22:1-2)

In the dark they tunnel into [chatar] houses;
By day they shut themselves in;
They do not know the light. (Job 24:16)

If they tunnel [yacht’ru] down to Sheol,
From there My hand shall take them (Amos 9:2)

“I and the burrow belong together in such a way that I could calmly, in spite of all my fears, settle down here without at all having to try to open the entrance-way despite all my reservations.” (Kafka, “The Burrow”)

The 10 commandments, which we read last week in Yitro, speak in absolutes: “Thou Shalt X,” “Thou Shalt Not Y.” This week’s Torah reading, Mishpatim, speaks in terms of tangible cases and situations: “If this happens, do this,” “When this happens don’t do this.” “Although you will want to do this, don’t.” Read Mishpatim carefully and you’ll find nearly every verse beginning with a ki (“when”) or im (“if”). The 10 commandments provide a priori, unconditional principles, or general rules for a good life. The Mishpatim that follow speak to the conditional rules, triggered by non-ideal events, that help us live in a world of transgression, error, and ambiguity. We hope that we won’t have to know, first-hand, what to do in many of these situations, but the laws are waiting for us in the event that we need them. It’s hard to reason in a crisis. Mishpatim offer structure to those in a state of moral chaos. They also help society work. If every individual kept the 10 commandments, we wouldn’t need them. But given the “Tragedy of the Commons,” Mishpatim describe a social covenant that will be needed to manage individual and interpersonal failure.

One such law is that of the night burglar. Tractate Sanhedrin turns him into an archetype of the rodef, the criminal whom one is permitted to kill in self defense. One is not allowed to kill a daytime thief as we cannot presume the thief’s intent to kill. Still, in the night, we do not see the thief and we do not see his intention outright, yet we can infer that he has chosen a time and place specifically to maximize the chance of a violent confrontation. In such conditions, it would be folly to offer the would-be-killer what Rabbi Y.Y. Jacobson calls “Suicidal empathy.”

Mishpatim asks us to judge (sharing the same root as shofet) the situation. And while the courts will settle the hard cases, one cannot observe Mishpatim without being a judge oneself. Developing discernment is a religious obligation. One might think Torah law is only about submission, but Mishpatim break that spell, because agency and interpretive creativity are needed to bridge the general, abstract rule with the specific circumstances in which I must apply it. Ex-ante, “Thou Shalt Not Steal,” “Thou Shalt not Kill.” Ex-post, I hear an unidentified sound and I need to figure out how to respond. It isn’t just the burglar burrowing beneath my home, it’s every event that disturbs my pre-fit, preconception of how things are. The thief robs me of my ability to assume there are no thieves. The tunneler has not just violated my physical space, but my mental space. He has created a situation of maximum ambiguity, and chosen time specifically to create moral confusion. The thief turns the home, a site of shelter, into a battlefield.

The Torah permits, even obligates me, to self-defend. The covenant is aspirational, but it must also be practical. Paul is wrong when he writes, I would not have known sin, but through the law; for I would not have known lust, except that the law had said, “Thou shalt not covet.”” (Romans 7:7) Quite the opposite: the Mishpatim are needed—im v’ ki—if, when, and because most people are not saints. Paul’s critique, in any case, refers to the Law as an abstraction. But what Paul needs to address is not the absolute law of “Thou shalt not” but the relative, worldly laws regarding what to do when we share the earth with those who violate basic norms of decency.

The tunneling thief thus emerges as more than just a legal case - he becomes a paradigm for how Torah law confronts those who make ambiguity itself their weapon. Just as the tunnel transforms domestic space into a zone of uncertainty, modern forms of warfare and violation often operate by creating spaces where moral clarity becomes impossible. The Torah&apos;s insight is not just that we must defend against such violations, but that we must understand the psychology of those who choose to operate underground - whether literally or metaphorically. They win their war against the light not through direct confrontation but by forcing its defenders to meet them in twilight. This is why the law appears in Mishpatim: it teaches us how to judge and act in precisely those moments when judgment seems most impossible. The tunneling thief may be an extreme figure, but he reveals a profound truth about moral life - that some of our most difficult challenges come not from those who break rules directly, but from those who deliberately create spaces where rules become unclear.

The underground is not only the home of evildoers. It is also the home, ironically, of those who judge our good-enough-world too harshly. The underground is a hideout from the complex architecture of Mishpatim, back into the primal place where one need not change one’s mind. Dostoevsky and Kafka describe the paranoid and pressured consciousness of underground life. The modern misanthrope is not the plotting, hostile thief or terrorist, but his inverse: one who retreats from the world above ground because the terrorist-thief has robbed him of his faith in ordinary life. Like the hidden, primordial light that must go underground until it is “sewn by the righteous” these beings are too sensitive for this world. They cannot accept the moral ambiguity above ground so they hold on to their moral absolutism, even if it means they have to become refugees from daylight. They denounce all who disagree with them as evil until they are left only with themselves. Amos writes about those who dig into Sheol so as to avoid divine judgment—as though God’s gaze might not penetrate to certain recesses. But one might invert his point, as well: they dig into Sheol so as not to have to judge their fellow earthlings, so as not to have to develop discernment.

The Torah enjoins us to both moral clarity and moral complexity. We must strike down our pursuers and identify them as such, even and precisely as they deliberately obfuscate. We must not let their underground logic—their preference for digging into Sheol rather than building in the light—cause us to burrow in self-righteousness. Discernment is the middle way between a quietistic retreat from moral judgment, on the one hand, and a facile moralizing on the other. Having now experienced Revelation, and accepted a moral ideal, the challenging, ongoing work begins of realizing it in the world.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The Law of the Tunnel<br>
How Torah Confronts Those Who Weaponize Ambiguity<br>
<br>
If the thief is seized while tunneling [bamachteret] and beaten to death, there is no bloodguilt in that case. If the sun had already risen, there is bloodguilt in that case [The thief] must make restitution, and if lacking the means, shall be sold for the theft. (Exodus 22:1-2)<br>
<br>
In the dark they tunnel into [chatar] houses;<br>
By day they shut themselves in;<br>
They do not know the light. (Job 24:16)<br>
<br>
If they tunnel [yacht’ru] down to Sheol,<br>
From there My hand shall take them (Amos 9:2)<br>
<br>
“I and the burrow belong together in such a way that I could calmly, in spite of all my fears, settle down here without at all having to try to open the entrance-way despite all my reservations.” (Kafka, “The Burrow”)<br>
<br>
The 10 commandments, which we read last week in Yitro, speak in absolutes: “Thou Shalt X,” “Thou Shalt Not Y.” This week’s Torah reading, Mishpatim, speaks in terms of tangible cases and situations: “If this happens, do this,” “When this happens don’t do this.” “Although you will want to do this, don’t.” Read Mishpatim carefully and you’ll find nearly every verse beginning with a ki (“when”) or im (“if”). The 10 commandments provide a priori, unconditional principles, or general rules for a good life. The Mishpatim that follow speak to the conditional rules, triggered by non-ideal events, that help us live in a world of transgression, error, and ambiguity. We hope that we won’t have to know, first-hand, what to do in many of these situations, but the laws are waiting for us in the event that we need them. It’s hard to reason in a crisis. Mishpatim offer structure to those in a state of moral chaos. They also help society work. If every individual kept the 10 commandments, we wouldn’t need them. But given the “Tragedy of the Commons,” Mishpatim describe a social covenant that will be needed to manage individual and interpersonal failure.<br>
<br>
One such law is that of the night burglar. Tractate Sanhedrin turns him into an archetype of the rodef, the criminal whom one is permitted to kill in self defense. One is not allowed to kill a daytime thief as we cannot presume the thief’s intent to kill. Still, in the night, we do not see the thief and we do not see his intention outright, yet we can infer that he has chosen a time and place specifically to maximize the chance of a violent confrontation. In such conditions, it would be folly to offer the would-be-killer what Rabbi Y.Y. Jacobson calls “Suicidal empathy.”<br>
<br>
Mishpatim asks us to judge (sharing the same root as shofet) the situation. And while the courts will settle the hard cases, one cannot observe Mishpatim without being a judge oneself. Developing discernment is a religious obligation. One might think Torah law is only about submission, but Mishpatim break that spell, because agency and interpretive creativity are needed to bridge the general, abstract rule with the specific circumstances in which I must apply it. Ex-ante, “Thou Shalt Not Steal,” “Thou Shalt not Kill.” Ex-post, I hear an unidentified sound and I need to figure out how to respond. It isn’t just the burglar burrowing beneath my home, it’s every event that disturbs my pre-fit, preconception of how things are. The thief robs me of my ability to assume there are no thieves. The tunneler has not just violated my physical space, but my mental space. He has created a situation of maximum ambiguity, and chosen time specifically to create moral confusion. The thief turns the home, a site of shelter, into a battlefield.<br>
<br>
The Torah permits, even obligates me, to self-defend. The covenant is aspirational, but it must also be practical. Paul is wrong when he writes, I would not have known sin, but through the law; for I would not have known lust, except that the law had said, “Thou shalt not covet.”” (Romans 7:7) Quite the opposite: the Mishpatim are needed—im v’ ki—if, when, and because most people are not saints. Paul’s critique, in any case, refers to the Law as an abstraction. But what Paul needs to address is not the absolute law of “Thou shalt not” but the relative, worldly laws regarding what to do when we share the earth with those who violate basic norms of decency.<br>
<br>
The tunneling thief thus emerges as more than just a legal case - he becomes a paradigm for how Torah law confronts those who make ambiguity itself their weapon. Just as the tunnel transforms domestic space into a zone of uncertainty, modern forms of warfare and violation often operate by creating spaces where moral clarity becomes impossible. The Torah's insight is not just that we must defend against such violations, but that we must understand the psychology of those who choose to operate underground - whether literally or metaphorically. They win their war against the light not through direct confrontation but by forcing its defenders to meet them in twilight. This is why the law appears in Mishpatim: it teaches us how to judge and act in precisely those moments when judgment seems most impossible. The tunneling thief may be an extreme figure, but he reveals a profound truth about moral life - that some of our most difficult challenges come not from those who break rules directly, but from those who deliberately create spaces where rules become unclear.<br>
<br>
The underground is not only the home of evildoers. It is also the home, ironically, of those who judge our good-enough-world too harshly. The underground is a hideout from the complex architecture of Mishpatim, back into the primal place where one need not change one’s mind. Dostoevsky and Kafka describe the paranoid and pressured consciousness of underground life. The modern misanthrope is not the plotting, hostile thief or terrorist, but his inverse: one who retreats from the world above ground because the terrorist-thief has robbed him of his faith in ordinary life. Like the hidden, primordial light that must go underground until it is “sewn by the righteous” these beings are too sensitive for this world. They cannot accept the moral ambiguity above ground so they hold on to their moral absolutism, even if it means they have to become refugees from daylight. They denounce all who disagree with them as evil until they are left only with themselves. Amos writes about those who dig into Sheol so as to avoid divine judgment—as though God’s gaze might not penetrate to certain recesses. But one might invert his point, as well: they dig into Sheol so as not to have to judge their fellow earthlings, so as not to have to develop discernment.<br>
<br>
The Torah enjoins us to both moral clarity and moral complexity. We must strike down our pursuers and identify them as such, even and precisely as they deliberately obfuscate. We must not let their underground logic—their preference for digging into Sheol rather than building in the light—cause us to burrow in self-righteousness. Discernment is the middle way between a quietistic retreat from moral judgment, on the one hand, and a facile moralizing on the other. Having now experienced Revelation, and accepted a moral ideal, the challenging, ongoing work begins of realizing it in the world.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkU3mFwWcAEWppR.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 16:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892980432339345870#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892980432339345870#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thinking is a calling. 
Arguing is a profession.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thinking is a calling. <br>
Arguing is a profession.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 13:58:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892936886257102987#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892936886257102987#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>There should be a German word for this:</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>There should be a German word for this:</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/JYuter/status/1892785082412216529#m">nitter.privacydev.net/JYuter/status/1892785082412216529#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:52:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892920275596972274#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892920275596972274#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Amazing that Hasidus transforms teach laws before judges to address the souls of your students.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Amazing that Hasidus transforms teach laws before judges to address the souls of your students.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkT3Pj9XMAE8I4b.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 12:10:41 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892909809629872156#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892909809629872156#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Image</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGkRNeGoWUAAykpr.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:48:15 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892722968779706599#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892722968779706599#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>A premise is your starting point, an assumption is your turning point.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>A premise is your starting point, an assumption is your turning point.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:56:19 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892664601021485263#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892664601021485263#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>We need to make Conversation Great Again. @lightninginspo</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>We need to make Conversation Great Again. <a href="https://x.com/lightninginspo" title="Lightning Inspiration">@lightninginspo</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:19:33 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892640249307640189#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892640249307640189#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Nietzsche reflecting on being a first time founder:

I come too early… my time has not come yet. This tremendous event is still on its way, still wandering–it has not yet reached the ears of man.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Nietzsche reflecting on being a first time founder:<br>
<br>
I come too early… my time has not come yet. This tremendous event is still on its way, still wandering–it has not yet reached the ears of man.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892635393914273873#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892635393914273873#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: “As our tools for measuring the world grow stronger, we must get better at preserving what can’t be measured.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@DBashIdeas</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>“As our tools for measuring the world grow stronger, we must get better at preserving what can’t be measured.”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1892618292939919512#m">nitter.privacydev.net/ZoharAtkins/status/1892618292939919512#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:52:50 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/DBashIdeas/status/1892633526127689811#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/DBashIdeas/status/1892633526127689811#m</link>
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
