<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://x.com/geoffreylitt/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Geoffrey Litt / @geoffreylitt</title>
    <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt</link>
    <description>Twitter feed for: @geoffreylitt. Generated by nitter.privacydev.net
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>Geoffrey Litt / @geoffreylitt</title>
      <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt</link>
      <url>https://x.com/pic/pbs.twimg.com%2Fprofile_images%2F722626068293763072%2F4erM-SPN_400x400.jpg</url>
      <width>128</width>
      <height>128</height>
    </image>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: And here&apos;s the general background on what Jacquard is all about and why we&apos;re working in this space!</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>And here's the general background on what Jacquard is all about and why we're working in this space!</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1820939140432543866#m">nitter.privacydev.net/geoffreylitt/status/1820939140432543866#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:26:33 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836517189161226616#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836517189161226616#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: We&apos;ve also been thinking about what it might mean to have this kind of provenance as a universal primitive in a collaborative OS. For more notes on that, check out our latest lab notebook post:

https://www.inkandswitch.com/jacquard/notebook/03/</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>We've also been thinking about what it might mean to have this kind of provenance as a universal primitive in a collaborative OS. For more notes on that, check out our latest lab notebook post:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.inkandswitch.com/jacquard/notebook/03/">inkandswitch.com/jacquard/no…</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:25:31 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836516929164529998#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836516929164529998#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: Fine-grained provenance is our latest area of exploration on the Jacquard project at &gt;@inkandswitch -- where we&apos;re imagining editing tools for science papers with better version control and provenance tracking.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fine-grained provenance is our latest area of exploration on the Jacquard project at <a href="https://x.com/inkandswitch" title="Ink & Switch">@inkandswitch</a> -- where we're imagining editing tools for science papers with better version control and provenance tracking.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:24:58 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836516789527675338#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836516789527675338#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: All of these are examples of interactions for fine-grained provenance: linking parts of a source and build document to more fluidly work across the two.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>All of these are examples of interactions for fine-grained provenance: linking parts of a source and build document to more fluidly work across the two.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGXydKBTX0AAI-x1.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:20:28 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515657225244755#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515657225244755#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: What if, instead of a list of files, you could visualize the layout of a project by seeing which scripts feed into each part of the final paper?</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>What if, instead of a list of files, you could visualize the layout of a project by seeing which scripts feed into each part of the final paper?</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGXyc4txXYAAWkZ3.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:19:51 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515504925876484#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515504925876484#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: What if, when you leave a comment on the PDF, it gets mirrored to the underlying source LaTeX as well?

So that reviewers get to comment on the nice PDF, but authors get to see the comments as they edit the text:</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>What if, when you leave a comment on the PDF, it gets mirrored to the underlying source LaTeX as well?<br>
<br>
So that reviewers get to comment on the nice PDF, but authors get to see the comments as they edit the text:</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/ext_tw_video_thumb%2F1836515028922449920%2Fpu%2Fimg%2F7wdXkD-3Xn98iZmv.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:18:38 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515196413891033#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836515196413891033#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>So you&apos;re reviewing a draft PDF generated from LaTeX, and you notice a typo...

What if you could just fix it right away, using a little popup to edit the underlying LaTeX?</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>So you're reviewing a draft PDF generated from LaTeX, and you notice a typo...<br>
<br>
What if you could just fix it right away, using a little popup to edit the underlying LaTeX?</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/ext_tw_video_thumb%2F1836513645393506304%2Fpu%2Fimg%2F7GxJF-uA6om-h1A2.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:16:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836514607395148186#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1836514607395148186#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: Even weirder how most people have no idea that self-driving has truly (within specific operating parameters) been solved. 

Strong “future is here, just not evenly distributed” vibes</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Even weirder how most people have no idea that self-driving has truly (within specific operating parameters) been solved. <br>
<br>
Strong “future is here, just not evenly distributed” vibes</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 23:11:49 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833644579557412888#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833644579557412888#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: It&apos;s one thing to think in theory about the threshold of &quot;how much safer would self driving have to be bla bla bla&quot;

It&apos;s another thing to start viscerally feeling the danger of random human drivers, because you&apos;ve experienced the alternative</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>It's one thing to think in theory about the threshold of "how much safer would self driving have to be bla bla bla"<br>
<br>
It's another thing to start viscerally feeling the danger of random human drivers, because you've experienced the alternative</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 22:50:32 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833639221233369509#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833639221233369509#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I&apos;ve reached the point where I trust Waymo a lot more than most Uber drivers, which is wild. Suddenly more aware of how unsafe human drivers are...

If you&apos;re skeptical, taking some Waymo rides is prob the only way to really feel the feeling</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I've reached the point where I trust Waymo a lot more than most Uber drivers, which is wild. Suddenly more aware of how unsafe human drivers are...<br>
<br>
If you're skeptical, taking some Waymo rides is prob the only way to really feel the feeling</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/can/status/1833537529943146855#m">nitter.privacydev.net/can/status/1833537529943146855#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 22:48:48 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833638785449447432#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833638785449447432#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: If you&apos;re interested in attending, more details on the site:

https://liveprog.org/

(For those unfamiliar w/ academic CS confs, basically you can register for a 1-day workshop to attend LIVE, and/or you can register for other parts of SPLASH, like Onward and OOPSLA)</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If you're interested in attending, more details on the site:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://liveprog.org/">liveprog.org/</a><br>
<br>
(For those unfamiliar w/ academic CS confs, basically you can register for a 1-day workshop to attend LIVE, and/or you can register for other parts of SPLASH, like Onward and OOPSLA)</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/card_img%2F1834682898181738496%2FHpt_cCQY%3Fformat%3Dpng%26name%3D144x144_2" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:53:44 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833609828259787218#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833609828259787218#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>✨ We&apos;ve finalized the program for LIVE 2024! 

It&apos;ll be a packed workshop day of 16 talks + discussion, exploring all aspects of live programming environments.

Oct 21 in Pasadena, colocated w/ SPLASH.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>✨ We've finalized the program for LIVE 2024! <br>
<br>
It'll be a packed workshop day of 16 talks + discussion, exploring all aspects of live programming environments.<br>
<br>
Oct 21 in Pasadena, colocated w/ SPLASH.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGXJJFEYWcAI0R-z.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 20:53:43 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833609823193030727#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1833609823193030727#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>👀</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>👀</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 17:22:40 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1829208056112251066#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1829208056112251066#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: If you&apos;re doing it right, it should feel like your prompts are absurdly long. Like, I&apos;ll sometimes ramble for minutes.

You should rarely stop to re-record -- if you make a mistake just keep going and correct yourself. Feel free to think aloud on thef ly</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If you're doing it right, it should feel like your prompts are absurdly long. Like, I'll sometimes ramble for minutes.<br>
<br>
You should rarely stop to re-record -- if you make a mistake just keep going and correct yourself. Feel free to think aloud on thef ly</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 01:58:06 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827888219179901310#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827888219179901310#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: The key is that you can get very detailed with your prompt since voice makes it so fast. Just say everything you’d say to a junior, be verbose. 

Feels less like “computer magically doing coding for me” and more like “saving myself some typing”, still a huge accelerator.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The key is that you can get very detailed with your prompt since voice makes it so fast. Just say everything you’d say to a junior, be verbose. <br>
<br>
Feels less like “computer magically doing coding for me” and more like “saving myself some typing”, still a huge accelerator.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 01:25:15 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827879949862088900#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827879949862088900#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>For those discovering Cursor recently: try out cmd-k with voice input from a transcription app!

Started doing this a while back and it’s stuck, today I was hacking on some UI and did majority of my coding by voice.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>For those discovering Cursor recently: try out cmd-k with voice input from a transcription app!<br>
<br>
Started doing this a while back and it’s stuck, today I was hacking on some UI and did majority of my coding by voice.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1745953276338536830#m">nitter.privacydev.net/geoffreylitt/status/1745953276338536830#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 01:23:24 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827879486228148280#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827879486228148280#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: And from @dubroy, on playing like a kid again:

https://dubroy.com/blog/playing-like-a-kid-again/</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>And from <a href="https://x.com/dubroy" title="Patrick Dubroy">@dubroy</a>, on playing like a kid again:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://dubroy.com/blog/playing-like-a-kid-again/">dubroy.com/blog/playing-like…</a></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV18CC8WIAABfEo.png" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 17:02:27 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827753418145816817#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827753418145816817#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: Related wisdom from Richard Feynman, on rediscovering the joy of physics:

https://www.asc.ohio-state.edu/kilcup.1/262/feynman.html</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Related wisdom from Richard Feynman, on rediscovering the joy of physics:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.asc.ohio-state.edu/kilcup.1/262/feynman.html">asc.ohio-state.edu/kilcup.1/…</a></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV17J0BXQAAJL07.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 17:02:01 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827753310855500200#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827753310855500200#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @geoffreylitt: geoffreylitt.com/2024/08/25/…</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.geoffreylitt.com/2024/08/25/your-pie-doesnt-need-be-original">geoffreylitt.com/2024/08/25/…</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:16:22 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827741818915607032#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827741818915607032#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Your pie doesn&apos;t need to be original (unless you claim it so)

Imagine you bake a delicious peach pie over the weekend, and you offer a slice to your friend. They respond:

&quot;Wait, how is this different from every other peach pie that&apos;s ever been baked? It seems really similar to another pie I had recently.&quot;

This is obviously an absurd reaction!

But this exact dynamic happens all the time in creative software projects. Someone shares a project they made, and the first reaction is: how&apos;s it different?

The problem here is a mismatch in values.

The friend has assumed that your goal is to &quot;efficiently&quot; reach the goal of a delicious pie, or perhaps even to create a new kind of pie. But that&apos;s not the goal at all!

Baking a pie is a creative act. It&apos;s personal, it&apos;s inherently delightful, it&apos;s an act of caring for others. It&apos;s also a craft that one can improve at over time. Just buying the &quot;best&quot; pie would defeat the point.

---

The next day, you find out there&apos;s a scientific conference in town: CRISP, the Conference for Research on Innovative Sweet Pastries. This is where the world&apos;s foremost experts push forward the frontier of pie-baking technique.

You show up with your delicious peach pie, and the first question from the judging panel is:

&quot;Wait, how is this different from every other peach pie that&apos;s ever been baked? It seems really similar to another pie I had recently.&quot;

You respond: &quot;I have no idea, I just enjoyed baking it and thought it was delicious! I don&apos;t even know what recipe I used. Why does it matter to you, huh?&quot;

The expert says: &quot;Well then, you&apos;re welcome to bake pies all you want at home, but your pie is not welcome at CRISP. The community cannot understand your contribution or build on your work.&quot;

You might be upset about this outcome, but you&apos;d be wrong. In this context, the judge&apos;s criticism is totally fair.

The goal of CRISP isn&apos;t just to enjoy pies, it&apos;s to build up a community of practice. Part of being a good citizen of that community is being able to explain how your pie is different—which in turn requires learning about all the other ways of making pie. This isn&apos;t merely a higher bar than amateur weekend baking, it&apos;s a totally different frame of mind.

---

I think mixing up these two situations is the source of a lot of unfortunate confusion.

I work on prototyping new kinds of software interfaces and programming tools, and I spend time in various communities that span across the cultures of playful exploration (sharing demos on Twitter) and academic research (writing formal papers).

Often I see creative people share personal projects and get their spirits weakened by &quot;how&apos;s it different?&quot; The question can be well-meaning; it isn&apos;t necessarily cynical! It&apos;s just misunderstanding the goal.

On the other hand, I see people submit cool work to academic research venues and get confused by, or even chafe at, the stringent requirement of situating the work in context. I used to be pretty dismissive of Related Work sections myself, until I went through grad school and realized how valuable they are to the world.

---

So, as creators and feedback-givers, how can we avoid this confusion?

There&apos;s an answer that seems obvious: clearly set the goal up front. Are you trying to do a personal project for fun, or are you trying to make a novel research contribution? Just proactively broadcast your intent, and most people will be better at asking questions that are aligned with your goals.

Unfortunately, in my experience, things don&apos;t work out this cleanly. Many of the best new ideas start out as playful explorations, and over time snowball into a larger project that are worthy of a serious research contribution.

A strategy I&apos;ve found helpful is to _start_ from a place of personal creativity. If the initial goal is playful exploration for its own sake, that creates free space to explore and quells early doubts (from both myself and others). It doesn&apos;t matter if it&apos;s new or good (yet), I&apos;m just having fun.

Occasionally a project grows into something more. At that point it can be appropriate to apply a critical academic lens.

Starting from the other side seems a lot tougher. If you start off saying &quot;we&apos;re going to make a big serious contribution no one&apos;s ever done before,&quot; that sets up high stakes and invites harsh critique from the start. Maybe this approach works for some projects with narrower success criteria, but it doesn&apos;t seem to work well for most of what I do.

A final thing to keep in mind: when I&apos;m on the side of giving feedback, I always try to first understand the creator&apos;s goals. This can be a subtle art when they don&apos;t even know their own goals yet. The weekend baker may just need encouragement, not critique.</title>
        <dc:creator>@geoffreylitt</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Your pie doesn't need to be original (unless you claim it so)<br>
<br>
Imagine you bake a delicious peach pie over the weekend, and you offer a slice to your friend. They respond:<br>
<br>
"Wait, how is this different from every other peach pie that's ever been baked? It seems really similar to another pie I had recently."<br>
<br>
This is obviously an absurd reaction!<br>
<br>
But this exact dynamic happens all the time in creative software projects. Someone shares a project they made, and the first reaction is: how's it different?<br>
<br>
The problem here is a mismatch in values.<br>
<br>
The friend has assumed that your goal is to "efficiently" reach the goal of a delicious pie, or perhaps even to create a new kind of pie. But that's not the goal at all!<br>
<br>
Baking a pie is a creative act. It's personal, it's inherently delightful, it's an act of caring for others. It's also a craft that one can improve at over time. Just buying the "best" pie would defeat the point.<br>
<br>
---<br>
<br>
The next day, you find out there's a scientific conference in town: CRISP, the Conference for Research on Innovative Sweet Pastries. This is where the world's foremost experts push forward the frontier of pie-baking technique.<br>
<br>
You show up with your delicious peach pie, and the first question from the judging panel is:<br>
<br>
"Wait, how is this different from every other peach pie that's ever been baked? It seems really similar to another pie I had recently."<br>
<br>
You respond: "I have no idea, I just enjoyed baking it and thought it was delicious! I don't even know what recipe I used. Why does it matter to you, huh?"<br>
<br>
The expert says: "Well then, you're welcome to bake pies all you want at home, but your pie is not welcome at CRISP. The community cannot understand your contribution or build on your work."<br>
<br>
You might be upset about this outcome, but you'd be wrong. In this context, the judge's criticism is totally fair.<br>
<br>
The goal of CRISP isn't just to enjoy pies, it's to build up a community of practice. Part of being a good citizen of that community is being able to explain how your pie is different—which in turn requires learning about all the other ways of making pie. This isn't merely a higher bar than amateur weekend baking, it's a totally different frame of mind.<br>
<br>
---<br>
<br>
I think mixing up these two situations is the source of a lot of unfortunate confusion.<br>
<br>
I work on prototyping new kinds of software interfaces and programming tools, and I spend time in various communities that span across the cultures of playful exploration (sharing demos on Twitter) and academic research (writing formal papers).<br>
<br>
Often I see creative people share personal projects and get their spirits weakened by "how's it different?" The question can be well-meaning; it isn't necessarily cynical! It's just misunderstanding the goal.<br>
<br>
On the other hand, I see people submit cool work to academic research venues and get confused by, or even chafe at, the stringent requirement of situating the work in context. I used to be pretty dismissive of Related Work sections myself, until I went through grad school and realized how valuable they are to the world.<br>
<br>
---<br>
<br>
So, as creators and feedback-givers, how can we avoid this confusion?<br>
<br>
There's an answer that seems obvious: clearly set the goal up front. Are you trying to do a personal project for fun, or are you trying to make a novel research contribution? Just proactively broadcast your intent, and most people will be better at asking questions that are aligned with your goals.<br>
<br>
Unfortunately, in my experience, things don't work out this cleanly. Many of the best new ideas start out as playful explorations, and over time snowball into a larger project that are worthy of a serious research contribution.<br>
<br>
A strategy I've found helpful is to _start_ from a place of personal creativity. If the initial goal is playful exploration for its own sake, that creates free space to explore and quells early doubts (from both myself and others). It doesn't matter if it's new or good (yet), I'm just having fun.<br>
<br>
Occasionally a project grows into something more. At that point it can be appropriate to apply a critical academic lens.<br>
<br>
Starting from the other side seems a lot tougher. If you start off saying "we're going to make a big serious contribution no one's ever done before," that sets up high stakes and invites harsh critique from the start. Maybe this approach works for some projects with narrower success criteria, but it doesn't seem to work well for most of what I do.<br>
<br>
A final thing to keep in mind: when I'm on the side of giving feedback, I always try to first understand the creator's goals. This can be a subtle art when they don't even know their own goals yet. The weekend baker may just need encouragement, not critique.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV1sDXhWcAAVVlt.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV1sF9OXEAAu7kJ.png" style="max-width:250px;" />
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV1sGUZXEAA9w0r.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGV1sGnRWYAAOMBq.png" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 15:59:03 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827737464297214323#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/geoffreylitt/status/1827737464297214323#m</link>
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
