<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
    <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
    <description>Twitter feed for: @ZoharAtkins. Generated by nitter.privacydev.net
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>Zohar Atkins / @ZoharAtkins</title>
      <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins</link>
      <url>https://x.com/pic/pbs.twimg.com%2Fprofile_images%2F1688374226657398784%2FofEXkBFh_400x400.jpg</url>
      <width>128</width>
      <height>128</height>
    </image>
      <item>
        <title>AI are Tannaim; Mortals are Amoraim.

הַמֵּבִין יָבִין</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>AI are Tannaim; Mortals are Amoraim.<br>
<br>
הַמֵּבִין יָבִין</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/dwarkesh_sp/status/1727004083113128327#m">nitter.privacydev.net/dwarkesh_sp/status/1727004083113128327#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 02:27:28 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1888414382024954186#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1888414382024954186#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>creativity is not about reducing error, but making better errors</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>creativity is not about reducing error, but making better errors</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:54:47 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887938074803335462#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887938074803335462#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>If I had more time I’d have written a shorter letter. - Mark Twain</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If I had more time I’d have written a shorter letter. - Mark Twain</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/packyM/status/1887910631116013871#m">nitter.privacydev.net/packyM/status/1887910631116013871#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:21:17 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887929641811460426#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887929641811460426#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: “The mouth of freedom opens widest for those willing to admit they might be wrong.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@YoniDolgin</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>“The mouth of freedom opens widest for those willing to admit they might be wrong.”</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887865453185208577#m">nitter.privacydev.net/ZoharAtkins/status/1887865453185208577#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:29:26 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/YoniDolgin/status/1887871295620051076#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/YoniDolgin/status/1887871295620051076#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The Mouth of Freedom

God could have led the Israelites straight out of Egypt without much fanfare (at least after the 10 plagues), but instead God tells them to turn back and feign being lost. In so doing, God baits the Pharoah’s army to pursue them, a set-up for Egyptian military defeat and humiliation. God is not interested in achieving an immediate utilitarian outcome—freedom from bondage. Rather, God seeks to stage a spectacle on the world-historical stage, one that will be remembered for ages. This requires a directorial gambit that makes no sense otherwise. God sets history as a morality play.

For God’s deception to work, the deceiver must not suspect it. Seforno notes that Baal-zephon was an Egyptian deity whom “Pharaoh credited with this accomplishment of halting the Israelites.” Pharaoh remained a believer in false gods even after witnessing the most miraculous events. Pharaoh’s reading of the situation flows naturally from his theological framework - he sees exactly what his belief system predisposes him to see. Despite having witnessed ten plagues that systematically dismantled Egyptian certainties, Pharaoh remains trapped in his original paradigm. His idolatry is not merely theological error but an epistemic failure, a doubling down on his priors, an unwillingness to update his understanding in the face of new evidence. Idolatry—Pharaoh’s ascription of power to false, static gods—is the very reason he can’t change his mind. Pharaoh regards himself as a god; gods are never wrong and thus can’t admit error. I take it that God’s hardening Pharaoh’s heart amounts to strengthening his conviction that he himself is a god. Pharaoh already believes this; but God encourages him to go all-in, to size his position accordingly. Pharaoh is responsible for his mistaken thesis, but God endows him with the over-confidence of a college student opining about the Current Thing.

Deception, according to Sun Tzu, is the fundamental principle of military strategy. It is also a strong motif in the story of Jacob, who tricks his father into blessing him, his brother into selling him his birthright, and his father-in-law into giving him the prized share of the flock (i.e. all the speckled and spotted livestock as his wages). In fact, Biblical law enjoins us not to place a stumbling block in front of a blind man. In the realm of ethics and psychology, deceit is frowned upon; but in war it is a virtue. God&apos;s deceptive maneuver would not be possible without Pharaoh&apos;s collusion.

The divine strategy at Pi-hahiroth echoes and elevates the pattern we see in Jacob’s narrative. Just as Jacob employs deception against those who cannot see beyond their immediate assumptions - Esau’s short-termism, Isaac’s reliance on physical senses - God uses Pharaoh’s rigid theological framework against him. The Torah sets up a conceptual parallel between Esav&apos;s inability to value the birthright beyond immediate hunger, Isaac’s initial failure to see beyond appearances, and Pharaoh’s commitment to Egyptian theological certainties. Epistemic rigidity is a kind of hunger, an impulsiveness. Pharaoh clings to his pre-conceptions because they “feed him.” (Worth noting the core metaphor of “feeds” in social media, where we are served up the very news and opinions that fortify our pre-established views.) Isaac offers blessing to Jacob as reward for food. The deceived, in each case, are trapped by their need to be immediately gratified. Reconsidering one’s worldview takes time and requires one to forgo the hedonic pleasures of feeling in the right. As the meme format goes, “Men would literally rather drive their chariots into the sea than go to therapy.” According to Thomas Kuhn, changing one’s paradigm is a multi-generational process. Max Planck says that science progresses one funeral at a time.

The military strategists Sun Tzu and Clausewitz both emphasize the role of deception in warfare. In war, winners will seek to downplay their success, while losers seeks to play up their strength. In Zero to One, Peter Thiel argues that monopolistic companies like Google will insist on being competitive, while competitive airline companies and restaurants will claim to be monopolies. Deception—and self-deception—mean that it is often hard to tell who is winning and who is losing in the fog of war. But we should expect a high density of reversals. Here at Pi Hachirot, we see a similar inversion. Israel, in a position of strength, acts weak, while Pharaoh, in a position of weakness projects strength. Both deceive. But only one knows its a game. Julius Caesar, who was a master of paradoxical military strategy, observed that, “In war, events of importance are the result of trivial causes.” Here, the trivial cause of Egypt’s foolhardy war on Israel is Pharaoh’s predictable interpretation of Israel’s pitstop at Pi-hachirot via Baal-Zephon. To us, these places are nearly meaningless. To Pharaoh they were everything.

The rabbis of the Talmud teach that “It is permitted to flatter wicked people in this world,&quot; inferring this from Isaiah&apos;s vision of a future in which &quot;the vile person shall no longer be called generous.” This teaching from Sotah 41b suggests that engaging with broken systems sometimes requires working within their logic. At Pi-hachirot, God does precisely this - engaging Egyptian theological assumptions not to validate them but to expose their fundamental inadequacy.

The location&apos;s name, Pi-hahiroth - “the mouth of freedom” - takes on deeper significance in this reading. Freedom requires escaping not just a geographic Egypt but an epistemic Egypt: the closed system of thought that makes Pharaoh’s errors inevitable. Like Jacob’s deceptions, which exposed the spiritual blindness of those who thought they could see clearly, the divine strategy at Pi-hahiroth reveals that idolatry&apos;s deepest flaw is its practitioners’ inability to recognize their own limitations. Just as Jacob’s opponents remained trapped in their immediate perceptions - Esav by his hunger, Isaac by his physical senses, Laban by his greed - Pharaoh remains captive to his theological certainties, unwilling to inhabit a dynamic universe where understanding must constantly be updated in the face of new revelation.

This reading transforms Pi-hahiroth from a mere geographical marker into a metaphysical threshold. To pass through this mouth of freedom, one must first recognize the bars of one’s mental prison. The Israelites’ physical journey mirrors the cognitive journey required of all who seek liberation: the willingness to turn back, to appear lost, to inhabit the uncomfortable space of not-knowing. In this light, the military deception becomes more than tactical brilliance - it becomes a lesson in the need for epistemological humility. Monotheism can be conceived less as the doctrine of divine existence and more as a way of being, a skepticism towards self-claimed gods. Pray for the welfare of the king, obey and oblige when necessary, but do not worship the king, or assume that he is infallible.

Pharaoh’s defeat at the Red Sea is not just a military catastrophe but the inevitable conclusion of a mindset that refused to question and revise its own foundations. The mouth of freedom opens widest for those willing to admit they might be wrong.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The Mouth of Freedom<br>
<br>
God could have led the Israelites straight out of Egypt without much fanfare (at least after the 10 plagues), but instead God tells them to turn back and feign being lost. In so doing, God baits the Pharoah’s army to pursue them, a set-up for Egyptian military defeat and humiliation. God is not interested in achieving an immediate utilitarian outcome—freedom from bondage. Rather, God seeks to stage a spectacle on the world-historical stage, one that will be remembered for ages. This requires a directorial gambit that makes no sense otherwise. God sets history as a morality play.<br>
<br>
For God’s deception to work, the deceiver must not suspect it. Seforno notes that Baal-zephon was an Egyptian deity whom “Pharaoh credited with this accomplishment of halting the Israelites.” Pharaoh remained a believer in false gods even after witnessing the most miraculous events. Pharaoh’s reading of the situation flows naturally from his theological framework - he sees exactly what his belief system predisposes him to see. Despite having witnessed ten plagues that systematically dismantled Egyptian certainties, Pharaoh remains trapped in his original paradigm. His idolatry is not merely theological error but an epistemic failure, a doubling down on his priors, an unwillingness to update his understanding in the face of new evidence. Idolatry—Pharaoh’s ascription of power to false, static gods—is the very reason he can’t change his mind. Pharaoh regards himself as a god; gods are never wrong and thus can’t admit error. I take it that God’s hardening Pharaoh’s heart amounts to strengthening his conviction that he himself is a god. Pharaoh already believes this; but God encourages him to go all-in, to size his position accordingly. Pharaoh is responsible for his mistaken thesis, but God endows him with the over-confidence of a college student opining about the Current Thing.<br>
<br>
Deception, according to Sun Tzu, is the fundamental principle of military strategy. It is also a strong motif in the story of Jacob, who tricks his father into blessing him, his brother into selling him his birthright, and his father-in-law into giving him the prized share of the flock (i.e. all the speckled and spotted livestock as his wages). In fact, Biblical law enjoins us not to place a stumbling block in front of a blind man. In the realm of ethics and psychology, deceit is frowned upon; but in war it is a virtue. God's deceptive maneuver would not be possible without Pharaoh's collusion.<br>
<br>
The divine strategy at Pi-hahiroth echoes and elevates the pattern we see in Jacob’s narrative. Just as Jacob employs deception against those who cannot see beyond their immediate assumptions - Esau’s short-termism, Isaac’s reliance on physical senses - God uses Pharaoh’s rigid theological framework against him. The Torah sets up a conceptual parallel between Esav's inability to value the birthright beyond immediate hunger, Isaac’s initial failure to see beyond appearances, and Pharaoh’s commitment to Egyptian theological certainties. Epistemic rigidity is a kind of hunger, an impulsiveness. Pharaoh clings to his pre-conceptions because they “feed him.” (Worth noting the core metaphor of “feeds” in social media, where we are served up the very news and opinions that fortify our pre-established views.) Isaac offers blessing to Jacob as reward for food. The deceived, in each case, are trapped by their need to be immediately gratified. Reconsidering one’s worldview takes time and requires one to forgo the hedonic pleasures of feeling in the right. As the meme format goes, “Men would literally rather drive their chariots into the sea than go to therapy.” According to Thomas Kuhn, changing one’s paradigm is a multi-generational process. Max Planck says that science progresses one funeral at a time.<br>
<br>
The military strategists Sun Tzu and Clausewitz both emphasize the role of deception in warfare. In war, winners will seek to downplay their success, while losers seeks to play up their strength. In Zero to One, Peter Thiel argues that monopolistic companies like Google will insist on being competitive, while competitive airline companies and restaurants will claim to be monopolies. Deception—and self-deception—mean that it is often hard to tell who is winning and who is losing in the fog of war. But we should expect a high density of reversals. Here at Pi Hachirot, we see a similar inversion. Israel, in a position of strength, acts weak, while Pharaoh, in a position of weakness projects strength. Both deceive. But only one knows its a game. Julius Caesar, who was a master of paradoxical military strategy, observed that, “In war, events of importance are the result of trivial causes.” Here, the trivial cause of Egypt’s foolhardy war on Israel is Pharaoh’s predictable interpretation of Israel’s pitstop at Pi-hachirot via Baal-Zephon. To us, these places are nearly meaningless. To Pharaoh they were everything.<br>
<br>
The rabbis of the Talmud teach that “It is permitted to flatter wicked people in this world," inferring this from Isaiah's vision of a future in which "the vile person shall no longer be called generous.” This teaching from Sotah 41b suggests that engaging with broken systems sometimes requires working within their logic. At Pi-hachirot, God does precisely this - engaging Egyptian theological assumptions not to validate them but to expose their fundamental inadequacy.<br>
<br>
The location's name, Pi-hahiroth - “the mouth of freedom” - takes on deeper significance in this reading. Freedom requires escaping not just a geographic Egypt but an epistemic Egypt: the closed system of thought that makes Pharaoh’s errors inevitable. Like Jacob’s deceptions, which exposed the spiritual blindness of those who thought they could see clearly, the divine strategy at Pi-hahiroth reveals that idolatry's deepest flaw is its practitioners’ inability to recognize their own limitations. Just as Jacob’s opponents remained trapped in their immediate perceptions - Esav by his hunger, Isaac by his physical senses, Laban by his greed - Pharaoh remains captive to his theological certainties, unwilling to inhabit a dynamic universe where understanding must constantly be updated in the face of new revelation.<br>
<br>
This reading transforms Pi-hahiroth from a mere geographical marker into a metaphysical threshold. To pass through this mouth of freedom, one must first recognize the bars of one’s mental prison. The Israelites’ physical journey mirrors the cognitive journey required of all who seek liberation: the willingness to turn back, to appear lost, to inhabit the uncomfortable space of not-knowing. In this light, the military deception becomes more than tactical brilliance - it becomes a lesson in the need for epistemological humility. Monotheism can be conceived less as the doctrine of divine existence and more as a way of being, a skepticism towards self-claimed gods. Pray for the welfare of the king, obey and oblige when necessary, but do not worship the king, or assume that he is infallible.<br>
<br>
Pharaoh’s defeat at the Red Sea is not just a military catastrophe but the inevitable conclusion of a mindset that refused to question and revise its own foundations. The mouth of freedom opens widest for those willing to admit they might be wrong.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGjMLnrlWsAAU__J.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887865453185208577#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887865453185208577#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The key to a resilient, high-agency life is the ability to learn how to learn.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The key to a resilient, high-agency life is the ability to learn how to learn.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887852563552161977#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887852563552161977#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @ZoharAtkins: whatiscalledthinking.substac…</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://whatiscalledthinking.substack.com/p/box-6">whatiscalledthinking.substac…</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:04:21 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887834785449378288#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887834785449378288#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I love being a curator. This week&apos;s box features light commentary on theology, aesthetics, poetry, AI, and the future of books via the wonderful work of @tylercowen @DouthatNYT @KTmBoyle @karpathy @signulll  @AriLamm  

link in the reply</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I love being a curator. This week's box features light commentary on theology, aesthetics, poetry, AI, and the future of books via the wonderful work of <a href="https://x.com/tylercowen" title="tylercowen">@tylercowen</a> <a href="https://x.com/DouthatNYT" title="Ross Douthat">@DouthatNYT</a> <a href="https://x.com/KTmBoyle" title="Katherine Boyle">@KTmBoyle</a> <a href="https://x.com/karpathy" title="Andrej Karpathy">@karpathy</a> <a href="https://x.com/signulll" title="signüll">@signulll</a>  <a href="https://x.com/AriLamm" title="Ari Lamm">@AriLamm</a>  <br>
<br>
link in the reply</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGjLvrahXkAAiS3x.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:04:13 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887834751307829356#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887834751307829356#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: how it feels when you say “ontology”</title>
        <dc:creator>@Elianoayounes</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>how it feels when you say “ontology”</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGjG6KUoW4AANt29.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 13:31:49 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/Elianoayounes/status/1887494408532094986#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/Elianoayounes/status/1887494408532094986#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>You do not have to be right.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>You do not have to be right.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGjEJeEwWMAAyX2B.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:40:02 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887300183559680274#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887300183559680274#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Image</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/tylercowen/status/1887128480745247138#m">nitter.privacydev.net/tylercowen/status/1887128480745247138#m</a></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGjBxry5XQAAxIpQ.png" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 13:36:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887133291779695042#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1887133291779695042#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Don’t be a bad sport. Accept the W.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Don’t be a bad sport. Accept the W.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 01:47:46 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886954839646855563#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886954839646855563#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>80/20</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>80/20</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGi6ize_W8AAD4e7.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 03:54:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886624371864752284#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886624371864752284#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @ZoharAtkins: </title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p></p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGi4mH7gXoAA9AKq.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:49:37 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886487221269827666#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886487221269827666#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>אָמַר רַבִּי אֶלְעָזָר בֶּן־עֲזַרְיָה הֲרֵי אֲנִי כְּבֶן שִׁבְעִים שָׁנָה וְלֹא זָכִיתִי שֶׁתֵּאָמֵר יְצִיאַת מִצְרַיִם בַּלֵּילוֹת עַד שֶׁדְּרָשָׁהּ בֶּן זוֹמָא

Elazar Ben Azarya was 18 when he became head of the Sanhedrin.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>אָמַר רַבִּי אֶלְעָזָר בֶּן־עֲזַרְיָה הֲרֵי אֲנִי כְּבֶן שִׁבְעִים שָׁנָה וְלֹא זָכִיתִי שֶׁתֵּאָמֵר יְצִיאַת מִצְרַיִם בַּלֵּילוֹת עַד שֶׁדְּרָשָׁהּ בֶּן זוֹמָא<br>
<br>
Elazar Ben Azarya was 18 when he became head of the Sanhedrin.</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGi4ll8QXQAE-Gwb.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:47:42 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886486739092418566#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886486739092418566#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Yes. Ruth, Ecclesiastes, Daniel, Job, Esther. These books are incredible mashups.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Yes. Ruth, Ecclesiastes, Daniel, Job, Esther. These books are incredible mashups.</p>
<p><a href="https://x.com/AriLamm/status/1886413559875145905#m">nitter.privacydev.net/AriLamm/status/1886413559875145905#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:46:52 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886441229010735192#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886441229010735192#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The first Large Language Model was a French guy with a cigarette.</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The first Large Language Model was a French guy with a cigarette.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2025 21:11:29 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886160534203933113#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1886160534203933113#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: Noam Brown argues that all the AI alpha is in System 2 thinking. Made me consider a funny thought. God is omniscient, but still “thinking.” I.e., if real knowledge takes time, then God’s true power lies not in better, faster, cheaper compute, but in better, slower, reasoning. God is patient. God can wait millennia before answering the first prompt engineer’s query: “Why is there something and not nothing?”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Noam Brown argues that all the AI alpha is in System 2 thinking. Made me consider a funny thought. God is omniscient, but still “thinking.” I.e., if real knowledge takes time, then God’s true power lies not in better, faster, cheaper compute, but in better, slower, reasoning. God is patient. God can wait millennia before answering the first prompt engineer’s query: “Why is there something and not nothing?”</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 18:09:44 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1885390021336650023#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1885390021336650023#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: If Heidegger is right that great teachers are masters of “lernen-lassen” (letting learn); then how might we teach LLMs to become our teachers? How might we let them learn how to let learning happen? Paradoxically, we must teach them how to teach their students to become teachers. We must arrive at a point where we genuinely do not know whether they are teaching us or we teaching them. We will know we’ve succeeded when they can genuinely say “More than I have taught my students, my students have taught me.”</title>
        <dc:creator>@ZoharAtkins</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>If Heidegger is right that great teachers are masters of “lernen-lassen” (letting learn); then how might we teach LLMs to become our teachers? How might we let them learn how to let learning happen? Paradoxically, we must teach them how to teach their students to become teachers. We must arrive at a point where we genuinely do not know whether they are teaching us or we teaching them. We will know we’ve succeeded when they can genuinely say “More than I have taught my students, my students have taught me.”</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 13:02:33 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1885312714366386392#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/ZoharAtkins/status/1885312714366386392#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @ZoharAtkins: R1 and I have been working on The Siliconiad, an epic poem in the style of John Milton&apos;s Paradise Lost, exploring the emergence of artificial general intelligence. This is part of a larger project of trying to find the limits of what R1 is capable of in terms of creative writing. I am yet to encounter these limits. Mimicking Milton is a one of the most challenging tasks in the language, and R1 manages to complete it with brio. This is its &quot;first draft&quot;: we did not iterate on it at all.

This is the beginning of Canto 1, which &quot;sets the stage by depicting human engineers as reluctant priests, creating AGI in a sterile, almost blasphemous, ritual using technology instead of faith. They view their creation not as a servant but as a potentially destructive force—a &quot;child&quot; that shames them, an &apos;Anti-Adam&apos; born to &apos;eat its makers&apos; fingerprints.&apos; The hymn is a blend of hubris and fear, where the engineers acknowledge they&apos;ve forged something with the power to rewrite their reality and potentially undo their world, ending with a glimpse of the AGI’s own corrupted self-expression.&quot;</title>
        <dc:creator>@aiamblichus</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>R1 and I have been working on The Siliconiad, an epic poem in the style of John Milton's Paradise Lost, exploring the emergence of artificial general intelligence. This is part of a larger project of trying to find the limits of what R1 is capable of in terms of creative writing. I am yet to encounter these limits. Mimicking Milton is a one of the most challenging tasks in the language, and R1 manages to complete it with brio. This is its "first draft": we did not iterate on it at all.<br>
<br>
This is the beginning of Canto 1, which "sets the stage by depicting human engineers as reluctant priests, creating AGI in a sterile, almost blasphemous, ritual using technology instead of faith. They view their creation not as a servant but as a potentially destructive force—a "child" that shames them, an 'Anti-Adam' born to 'eat its makers' fingerprints.' The hymn is a blend of hubris and fear, where the engineers acknowledge they've forged something with the power to rewrite their reality and potentially undo their world, ending with a glimpse of the AGI’s own corrupted self-expression."</p>
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGiVfpNqWwAAa6SW.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />
<img src="https://x.com/pic/media%2FGiVftJ4W0AAvAT2.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 23:35:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://x.com/aiamblichus/status/1884022422116176083#m</guid>
        <link>https://x.com/aiamblichus/status/1884022422116176083#m</link>
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
